[
    {
        "question": "207185734÷42558=？",
        "answer": 3.687378638049622
    },
    {
        "question": "144870001÷779563=？",
        "answer": 2.2691272448799937
    },
    {
        "question": "687234705÷1032=？",
        "answer": 5.823425385734291
    },
    {
        "question": "7947048÷13457=？",
        "answer": 2.771257583744869
    },
    {
        "question": "24122÷6651=？",
        "answer": 0.559526365292116
    },
    {
        "question": "39441887÷3347=？",
        "answer": 4.071301972158943
    },
    {
        "question": "2774×67892=？",
        "answer": 8.274925059286602
    },
    {
        "question": "414386215÷711649=？",
        "answer": 2.765139456280967
    },
    {
        "question": "8687410÷1693944=？",
        "answer": 0.7099912694940067
    },
    {
        "question": "468883×2092=？",
        "answer": 8.991626167273964
    },
    {
        "question": "193×2027=？",
        "answer": 5.592411057700782
    },
    {
        "question": "335693768÷50962=？",
        "answer": 3.8186968153288237
    },
    {
        "question": "1×265451561=？",
        "answer": 8.423985283573176
    },
    {
        "question": "300×1395346=？",
        "answer": 8.621803166457376
    },
    {
        "question": "1×564048=？",
        "answer": 5.751316063643116
    },
    {
        "question": "367778955÷9113441=？",
        "answer": 1.6059044881500522
    },
    {
        "question": "8×330795=？",
        "answer": 6.422648923516889
    },
    {
        "question": "6×70259=？",
        "answer": 5.624853214547699
    },
    {
        "question": "9×6540651=？",
        "answer": 7.769863485842676
    },
    {
        "question": "40162854÷547955=？",
        "answer": 1.8650796723458123
    },
    {
        "question": "129218×2277=？",
        "answer": 8.468686045483
    },
    {
        "question": "26954×25914=？",
        "answer": 8.844157678463057
    },
    {
        "question": "5×2472450=？",
        "answer": 7.092097522019326
    },
    {
        "question": "1×5442=？",
        "answer": 3.735758537443739
    },
    {
        "question": "25114667÷49231=？",
        "answer": 2.7076887667154765
    },
    {
        "question": "2416182÷652=？",
        "answer": 3.568882048877236
    },
    {
        "question": "835351854÷15295855=？",
        "answer": 1.7372956828566801
    },
    {
        "question": "489×900=？",
        "answer": 5.643551368562945
    },
    {
        "question": "286196÷346=？",
        "answer": 2.9175874607844845
    },
    {
        "question": "23200÷19917=？",
        "answer": 0.06626406152431688
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1327319=？",
        "answer": 6.122975311176763
    },
    {
        "question": "3077422÷269167=？",
        "answer": 1.058165240053484
    },
    {
        "question": "1×273629=？",
        "answer": 5.4371621232840015
    },
    {
        "question": "3950826÷244796=？",
        "answer": 1.2078835860550532
    },
    {
        "question": "67×1655745=？",
        "answer": 8.045068254944175
    },
    {
        "question": "458392459÷7485255=？",
        "answer": 1.7870308644225281
    },
    {
        "question": "3437014÷1194111=？",
        "answer": 0.459136602127008
    },
    {
        "question": "93×2048=？",
        "answer": 5.279812900857729
    },
    {
        "question": "456×629=？",
        "answer": 5.457615488109704
    },
    {
        "question": "76894×377=？",
        "answer": 7.4622338035501095
    },
    {
        "question": "152×1739=？",
        "answer": 5.422143169947485
    },
    {
        "question": "717098587÷240=？",
        "answer": 6.475367625039579
    },
    {
        "question": "194865051÷15044=？",
        "answer": 4.112370630740445
    },
    {
        "question": "143564×668=？",
        "answer": 7.981822012678171
    },
    {
        "question": "14×67438293=？",
        "answer": 8.975034604559708
    },
    {
        "question": "19158419÷1330=？",
        "answer": 4.158508026202064
    },
    {
        "question": "1×141339=？",
        "answer": 5.150262014274457
    },
    {
        "question": "293695÷358=？",
        "answer": 2.9140135263110216
    },
    {
        "question": "10×499133=？",
        "answer": 6.698216284039884
    },
    {
        "question": "274376708÷144805=？",
        "answer": 3.2775636831270254
    },
    {
        "question": "126748276÷1299966=？",
        "answer": 1.989010067187734
    },
    {
        "question": "35961518÷2689301=？",
        "answer": 1.1261986024437265
    },
    {
        "question": "203×1213171=？",
        "answer": 8.3914180581716
    },
    {
        "question": "9075201÷18125=？",
        "answer": 2.6995782374429877
    },
    {
        "question": "1743331×564=？",
        "answer": 8.99265895685688
    },
    {
        "question": "328548418÷203070226=？",
        "answer": 0.20895312820135453
    },
    {
        "question": "12224771÷266743=？",
        "answer": 1.6611477011907647
    },
    {
        "question": "277657÷9272=？",
        "answer": 1.4763352039726265
    },
    {
        "question": "6×1636667=？",
        "answer": 6.9921115762379555
    },
    {
        "question": "29×1409474=？",
        "answer": 7.611455066924829
    },
    {
        "question": "2484×26063=？",
        "answer": 7.811175995531077
    },
    {
        "question": "112×191571=？",
        "answer": 7.331547788930415
    },
    {
        "question": "188056239÷18351334=？",
        "answer": 1.010620106673527
    },
    {
        "question": "3×3110262=？",
        "answer": 6.969918229071789
    },
    {
        "question": "3972369÷429791=？",
        "answer": 0.9657922670920709
    },
    {
        "question": "789885549÷2601396=？",
        "answer": 2.4823577003346013
    },
    {
        "question": "1×4764=？",
        "answer": 3.67797175281074
    },
    {
        "question": "339549706÷552=？",
        "answer": 5.788964281038717
    },
    {
        "question": "1175368÷395004=？",
        "answer": 0.47357236912507766
    },
    {
        "question": "10504714÷4380132=？",
        "answer": 0.3798970342231686
    },
    {
        "question": "125707÷8581=？",
        "answer": 1.165821560095548
    },
    {
        "question": "23×17108=？",
        "answer": 5.5949270776023665
    },
    {
        "question": "787947055÷94260507=？",
        "answer": 0.9221672652855188
    },
    {
        "question": "109×296=？",
        "answer": 4.5087182089995625
    },
    {
        "question": "4863199÷1671=？",
        "answer": 3.4639455911807793
    },
    {
        "question": "6×3067=？",
        "answer": 4.264865026366129
    },
    {
        "question": "10393×3074=？",
        "answer": 7.504444790449986
    },
    {
        "question": "7×87571998=？",
        "answer": 8.787463298486077
    },
    {
        "question": "9709×346=？",
        "answer": 6.526250599880318
    },
    {
        "question": "19364÷11270=？",
        "answer": 0.23507115792274555
    },
    {
        "question": "645×6559=？",
        "answer": 6.626397345537303
    },
    {
        "question": "9×2521972=？",
        "answer": 7.3559827699820985
    },
    {
        "question": "1068×5537=？",
        "answer": 6.771845776204471
    },
    {
        "question": "469304×916=？",
        "answer": 8.633349729500896
    },
    {
        "question": "313920979÷45801=？",
        "answer": 3.835945379788467
    },
    {
        "question": "26408817÷918071=？",
        "answer": 1.458872678014053
    },
    {
        "question": "45×2531553=？",
        "answer": 8.05659953788082
    },
    {
        "question": "146547÷2368=？",
        "answer": 1.7915952342644699
    },
    {
        "question": "143851575÷18076861=？",
        "answer": 0.9007916026727784
    },
    {
        "question": "373698499÷3769=？",
        "answer": 4.996295216013288
    },
    {
        "question": "5080×1386=？",
        "answer": 6.847626942559708
    },
    {
        "question": "314083÷68695=？",
        "answer": 0.6601193026211971
    },
    {
        "question": "863676782÷61332=？",
        "answer": 4.1486641177253505
    },
    {
        "question": "193049849÷150857655=？",
        "answer": 0.10710211370168918
    },
    {
        "question": "18693191÷2450583=？",
        "answer": 0.8824140270238848
    },
    {
        "question": "930630÷741066=？",
        "answer": 0.0989201600820934
    },
    {
        "question": "3198×88363=？",
        "answer": 8.451148911531845
    },
    {
        "question": "866395605÷3773=？",
        "answer": 5.361029435358686
    },
    {
        "question": "16787968÷5909752=？",
        "answer": 0.45342887642251356
    },
    {
        "question": "438×4735=？",
        "answer": 6.3167940938433915
    },
    {
        "question": "69434÷18212=？",
        "answer": 0.581214543466122
    },
    {
        "question": "507759489÷12507533=？",
        "answer": 1.608486390836122
    },
    {
        "question": "73×4281381=？",
        "answer": 8.494906737530792
    },
    {
        "question": "59507824÷5446=？",
        "answer": 4.038496432869812
    },
    {
        "question": "1×98803882=？",
        "answer": 7.994774008333157
    },
    {
        "question": "516003210÷2876608=？",
        "answer": 2.2537717194198414
    },
    {
        "question": "3×1385=？",
        "answer": 3.61857102812013
    },
    {
        "question": "3×462800=？",
        "answer": 6.142514604999374
    },
    {
        "question": "8×54095=？",
        "answer": 5.636247112121415
    },
    {
        "question": "1×167056613=？",
        "answer": 8.222863672027808
    },
    {
        "question": "7×1051=？",
        "answer": 3.866700756042499
    },
    {
        "question": "805407÷13620=？",
        "answer": 1.7718382922764224
    },
    {
        "question": "17×4906=？",
        "answer": 4.9211764652486405
    },
    {
        "question": "5×31248396=？",
        "answer": 8.193797733976838
    },
    {
        "question": "13×167749=？",
        "answer": 6.338603292201361
    },
    {
        "question": "2×26453228=？",
        "answer": 7.723508670789414
    },
    {
        "question": "177×779974=？",
        "answer": 8.140053392328277
    },
    {
        "question": "222775258÷1992556=？",
        "answer": 2.0484564193897405
    },
    {
        "question": "135×19389=？",
        "answer": 6.417889179137341
    },
    {
        "question": "35×57846=？",
        "answer": 6.30634137759503
    },
    {
        "question": "129346÷1117=？",
        "answer": 2.063699829671872
    },
    {
        "question": "59698280÷686198=？",
        "answer": 1.9395123706896127
    },
    {
        "question": "626831593÷357=？",
        "answer": 6.244482661154354
    },
    {
        "question": "1×35226762=？",
        "answer": 7.546872725209043
    },
    {
        "question": "86198411÷927688=？",
        "answer": 1.968097321152703
    },
    {
        "question": "31×4423816=？",
        "answer": 8.137158748874471
    },
    {
        "question": "19×43548=？",
        "answer": 5.91772181520101
    },
    {
        "question": "289603342÷64458430=？",
        "answer": 0.6525238459898774
    },
    {
        "question": "31×378=？",
        "answer": 4.068853493671498
    },
    {
        "question": "129973÷277=？",
        "answer": 2.6713733742510426
    },
    {
        "question": "65530÷3007=？",
        "answer": 1.3383067398556212
    },
    {
        "question": "5×2271=？",
        "answer": 4.055187138555754
    },
    {
        "question": "68819×3752=？",
        "answer": 8.411971187360766
    },
    {
        "question": "13522517÷2684444=？",
        "answer": 0.7022031874864373
    },
    {
        "question": "37×193050=？",
        "answer": 6.853871530027063
    },
    {
        "question": "159943223÷72410567=？",
        "answer": 0.3441638950232108
    },
    {
        "question": "22958001÷307=？",
        "answer": 4.873795694988113
    },
    {
        "question": "43920×6399=？",
        "answer": 8.448774441611127
    },
    {
        "question": "63×18535=？",
        "answer": 6.067333139819164
    },
    {
        "question": "99231411÷22170796=？",
        "answer": 0.6508678808510152
    },
    {
        "question": "11550781÷8980=？",
        "answer": 3.109335013147286
    },
    {
        "question": "1×476903910=？",
        "answer": 8.678430883105838
    },
    {
        "question": "2×539=？",
        "answer": 3.03261876085072
    },
    {
        "question": "163×8609=？",
        "answer": 6.147140312221816
    },
    {
        "question": "7250×75568=？",
        "answer": 8.738675934803618
    },
    {
        "question": "674×154628=？",
        "answer": 8.017948035176097
    },
    {
        "question": "6708×112146=？",
        "answer": 8.876376841804815
    },
    {
        "question": "69×6263=？",
        "answer": 5.635631502438563
    },
    {
        "question": "78620÷7886=？",
        "answer": 0.9986762667468659
    },
    {
        "question": "15×1668=？",
        "answer": 4.398287305357401
    },
    {
        "question": "6574÷221=？",
        "answer": 1.473437426060495
    },
    {
        "question": "83801÷1372=？",
        "answer": 1.7858950897403392
    },
    {
        "question": "202×30613=？",
        "answer": 6.791257260938892
    },
    {
        "question": "491408÷1558=？",
        "answer": 2.4988747690712003
    },
    {
        "question": "24×259817=？",
        "answer": 6.794878805556581
    },
    {
        "question": "8×4790=？",
        "answer": 4.5834255004065065
    },
    {
        "question": "906388÷418=？",
        "answer": 3.336137865335953
    },
    {
        "question": "527423143÷2343=？",
        "answer": 5.352386893850742
    },
    {
        "question": "208357÷45971=？",
        "answer": 0.6563241446822355
    },
    {
        "question": "245653÷364=？",
        "answer": 2.8292206886096536
    },
    {
        "question": "214×221964=？",
        "answer": 7.676696315956785
    },
    {
        "question": "13×47001=？",
        "answer": 5.78605045045238
    },
    {
        "question": "255×379=？",
        "answer": 4.985179390402028
    },
    {
        "question": "40972÷26701=？",
        "answer": 0.18595963727409745
    },
    {
        "question": "45305281÷9071961=？",
        "answer": 0.698447653865058
    },
    {
        "question": "851235×444=？",
        "answer": 8.577432442201834
    },
    {
        "question": "19493×5779=？",
        "answer": 8.0517313772568
    },
    {
        "question": "342440842÷18106=？",
        "answer": 4.276763040196803
    },
    {
        "question": "128180616÷46950=？",
        "answer": 3.4361867577481027
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1846742=？",
        "answer": 6.266406226353709
    },
    {
        "question": "13617×7212=？",
        "answer": 7.992137155512876
    },
    {
        "question": "12×8494=？",
        "answer": 5.008293502702285
    },
    {
        "question": "9×13014190=？",
        "answer": 8.068659652343479
    },
    {
        "question": "26298÷6001=？",
        "answer": 0.6416990942715064
    },
    {
        "question": "21513987÷22270=？",
        "answer": 2.9850006848292288
    },
    {
        "question": "3062788÷667=？",
        "answer": 3.661991102943385
    },
    {
        "question": "298690702÷132665003=？",
        "answer": 0.3524653323987619
    },
    {
        "question": "682039×557=？",
        "answer": 8.579664404141836
    },
    {
        "question": "59416577÷237915=？",
        "answer": 2.3974858042223617
    },
    {
        "question": "318×2032=？",
        "answer": 5.810350823596314
    },
    {
        "question": "2×44469=？",
        "answer": 4.949087358992723
    },
    {
        "question": "22247×498=？",
        "answer": 7.044500797569322
    },
    {
        "question": "28902476÷7321055=？",
        "answer": 0.596361379692724
    },
    {
        "question": "104×10354=？",
        "answer": 6.0321414999446175
    },
    {
        "question": "997×1020=？",
        "answer": 6.007295330073573
    },
    {
        "question": "1575773÷1828=？",
        "answer": 2.935517463413126
    },
    {
        "question": "1×62737=？",
        "answer": 4.797523747473038
    },
    {
        "question": "183×2945151=？",
        "answer": 8.73155865601335
    },
    {
        "question": "352×2734=？",
        "answer": 5.983341173709935
    },
    {
        "question": "21609÷248=？",
        "answer": 1.940182988670136
    },
    {
        "question": "1521÷339=？",
        "answer": 0.6519295158499162
    },
    {
        "question": "33139÷5923=？",
        "answer": 0.7477976664021072
    },
    {
        "question": "33×2689=？",
        "answer": 4.948104742101189
    },
    {
        "question": "439×51763=？",
        "answer": 7.356483958800944
    },
    {
        "question": "17980÷709=？",
        "answer": 1.4041434522141434
    },
    {
        "question": "67274900÷2233=？",
        "answer": 4.478964337812805
    },
    {
        "question": "23745661÷3150693=？",
        "answer": 0.8771781753288821
    },
    {
        "question": "796294462÷7848898=？",
        "answer": 2.0062650100773585
    },
    {
        "question": "6×13305431=？",
        "answer": 7.902180197507805
    },
    {
        "question": "3×72451346=？",
        "answer": 8.337167712918058
    },
    {
        "question": "67091254÷3692222=？",
        "answer": 1.259378103632191
    },
    {
        "question": "9812653÷685786=？",
        "answer": 1.1555978264240097
    },
    {
        "question": "325171433÷83417=？",
        "answer": 3.590857818035892
    },
    {
        "question": "140940÷46221=？",
        "answer": 0.4841949298739822
    },
    {
        "question": "454003752÷141603=？",
        "answer": 3.505986987579062
    },
    {
        "question": "70556÷10753=？",
        "answer": 0.8170043057538835
    },
    {
        "question": "1446÷690=？",
        "answer": 0.3213192022212567
    },
    {
        "question": "1410×821=？",
        "answer": 6.06356226977482
    },
    {
        "question": "3331÷313=？",
        "answer": 1.0270302951447283
    },
    {
        "question": "117819÷57099=？",
        "answer": 0.3145868299783603
    },
    {
        "question": "1455959÷16789=？",
        "answer": 1.9381243162494362
    },
    {
        "question": "196×134064=？",
        "answer": 7.419568244433068
    },
    {
        "question": "183455565÷6194048=？",
        "answer": 1.4715563237754523
    },
    {
        "question": "7×420=？",
        "answer": 3.4683473304121573
    },
    {
        "question": "788654820÷349=？",
        "answer": 6.3540615349690235
    },
    {
        "question": "121225686÷93373810=？",
        "answer": 0.11336957040467786
    },
    {
        "question": "165336921÷20049=？",
        "answer": 3.9162771298400707
    },
    {
        "question": "549736÷135990=？",
        "answer": 0.6066472043178401
    },
    {
        "question": "262×380338=？",
        "answer": 7.998471009752255
    },
    {
        "question": "6×1038=？",
        "answer": 3.7943486038960827
    },
    {
        "question": "81284552÷24181140=？",
        "answer": 0.5265312449952866
    },
    {
        "question": "549670×483=？",
        "answer": 8.424049165352324
    },
    {
        "question": "271491871÷59813=？",
        "answer": 3.656961244917888
    },
    {
        "question": "55×1129=？",
        "answer": 4.793056631419212
    },
    {
        "question": "37335302÷574=？",
        "answer": 4.813207776227412
    },
    {
        "question": "30439×832=？",
        "answer": 7.403553706924881
    },
    {
        "question": "997×386768=？",
        "answer": 8.586145693013416
    },
    {
        "question": "66676701÷1495970=？",
        "answer": 1.6490512195321607
    },
    {
        "question": "9111538÷8890=？",
        "answer": 3.0106899297828567
    },
    {
        "question": "127430÷303=？",
        "answer": 2.6238290546044887
    },
    {
        "question": "676239795÷27125405=？",
        "answer": 1.3967244931075369
    },
    {
        "question": "7×157667=？",
        "answer": 6.0428388442015875
    },
    {
        "question": "27×21286=？",
        "answer": 5.759457821974014
    },
    {
        "question": "54×37757=？",
        "answer": 6.309391239749717
    },
    {
        "question": "206026×4656=？",
        "answer": 8.981935002418798
    },
    {
        "question": "114187÷516=？",
        "answer": 2.34496696139263
    },
    {
        "question": "63616033÷1241400=？",
        "answer": 1.7096548426165648
    },
    {
        "question": "34609725÷85418=？",
        "answer": 2.6076487499930736
    },
    {
        "question": "3826÷3294=？",
        "answer": 0.0650213708575415
    },
    {
        "question": "4665124÷433=？",
        "answer": 4.032375295523375
    },
    {
        "question": "258852588÷18105794=？",
        "answer": 1.1552349365568504
    },
    {
        "question": "17463217÷6833854=？",
        "answer": 0.40745855443619716
    },
    {
        "question": "4570056÷116686=？",
        "answer": 1.5929027693397
    },
    {
        "question": "32×4209842=？",
        "answer": 8.12941577491192
    },
    {
        "question": "53762÷1178=？",
        "answer": 1.6593301260829192
    },
    {
        "question": "6×3807331=？",
        "answer": 7.358771885334241
    },
    {
        "question": "5281191÷66515=？",
        "answer": 1.8998122790856142
    },
    {
        "question": "494×1185130=？",
        "answer": 8.767492940776947
    },
    {
        "question": "43398×214=？",
        "answer": 6.96788348882995
    },
    {
        "question": "2269915÷233=？",
        "answer": 3.988653673734452
    },
    {
        "question": "24×12863=？",
        "answer": 5.4895535113495795
    },
    {
        "question": "2689259÷308=？",
        "answer": 3.9410819142294056
    },
    {
        "question": "680063865÷1560585=？",
        "answer": 2.6392622710890064
    },
    {
        "question": "383265÷96703=？",
        "answer": 0.5980592136882655
    },
    {
        "question": "294×10548=？",
        "answer": 6.491517451533554
    },
    {
        "question": "28883×1892=？",
        "answer": 7.7375634323130935
    },
    {
        "question": "4618189÷602=？",
        "answer": 3.8848752112465585
    },
    {
        "question": "938×7094=？",
        "answer": 6.823094022514988
    },
    {
        "question": "54940÷1108=？",
        "answer": 1.6953488946921322
    },
    {
        "question": "20×707=？",
        "answer": 4.15044940946088
    },
    {
        "question": "49763282÷93614=？",
        "answer": 2.725568212865019
    },
    {
        "question": "3225572÷335=？",
        "answer": 3.983561933458827
    },
    {
        "question": "9×239=？",
        "answer": 3.3326404103874627
    },
    {
        "question": "1×21475196=？",
        "answer": 7.3319371362439085
    },
    {
        "question": "276471÷9900=？",
        "answer": 1.4460143887809807
    },
    {
        "question": "2677162÷218697=？",
        "answer": 1.087831826344042
    },
    {
        "question": "1447÷277=？",
        "answer": 0.7179887620545888
    },
    {
        "question": "542734÷4716=？",
        "answer": 2.061013232729413
    },
    {
        "question": "26178×259=？",
        "answer": 6.831236227451716
    },
    {
        "question": "210952342÷38947=？",
        "answer": 3.7337103407289463
    },
    {
        "question": "1001295÷1224=？",
        "answer": 2.912780629697258
    },
    {
        "question": "6089÷4997=？",
        "answer": 0.08583662461193574
    },
    {
        "question": "2520841÷273=？",
        "answer": 3.965382806727597
    },
    {
        "question": "1579521÷9751=？",
        "answer": 2.2094762478602394
    },
    {
        "question": "3773364÷47719=？",
        "answer": 1.8980373677073308
    },
    {
        "question": "26343÷4140=？",
        "answer": 0.8036648907522178
    },
    {
        "question": "41373÷10720=？",
        "answer": 0.5865222278328833
    },
    {
        "question": "78076÷2272=？",
        "answer": 1.5361092283570195
    },
    {
        "question": "1276×6761=？",
        "answer": 6.935861610321261
    },
    {
        "question": "4×6895129=？",
        "answer": 7.4406023870703
    },
    {
        "question": "227828÷4108=？",
        "answer": 1.7439766627731406
    },
    {
        "question": "434488515÷8308757=？",
        "answer": 1.7184422433965854
    },
    {
        "question": "17963÷237=？",
        "answer": 1.8796305238847895
    },
    {
        "question": "1284073×647=？",
        "answer": 8.91949399489685
    },
    {
        "question": "58535749÷5709508=？",
        "answer": 1.0108224939711017
    },
    {
        "question": "148674÷1203=？",
        "answer": 2.0919693987220542
    },
    {
        "question": "67738686÷21591=？",
        "answer": 3.4965640105069467
    },
    {
        "question": "22×5305486=？",
        "answer": 8.067147853687406
    },
    {
        "question": "75340994÷1549=？",
        "answer": 4.686979927944349
    },
    {
        "question": "2091×7820=？",
        "answer": 7.21356078587752
    },
    {
        "question": "285×3607=？",
        "answer": 6.011991002326873
    },
    {
        "question": "328422792÷41083571=？",
        "answer": 0.9027651032023836
    },
    {
        "question": "4205×4506=？",
        "answer": 7.277557187521743
    },
    {
        "question": "1×266663=？",
        "answer": 5.425962760682101
    },
    {
        "question": "55457÷1619=？",
        "answer": 1.5347095235442672
    },
    {
        "question": "2×875456=？",
        "answer": 6.243264319198924
    },
    {
        "question": "44×319482=？",
        "answer": 7.147899070996606
    },
    {
        "question": "4×1054085=？",
        "answer": 6.624935624540859
    },
    {
        "question": "1788×9742=？",
        "answer": 7.24101563969565
    },
    {
        "question": "96961746÷17848104=？",
        "answer": 0.7350083393822795
    },
    {
        "question": "22798311÷6792=？",
        "answer": 3.5259049964947944
    },
    {
        "question": "3205442÷668888=？",
        "answer": 0.680534518384659
    },
    {
        "question": "783428485÷557=？",
        "answer": 6.148144163017714
    },
    {
        "question": "13274÷12250=？",
        "answer": 0.03486572460547277
    },
    {
        "question": "161×47510=？",
        "answer": 6.8836109064510556
    },
    {
        "question": "8×44349207=？",
        "answer": 8.549975845689493
    },
    {
        "question": "24833÷383=？",
        "answer": 1.8118304145647506
    },
    {
        "question": "6×1206509=？",
        "answer": 6.859681816276819
    },
    {
        "question": "741140411÷2243867=？",
        "answer": 2.5189033824547837
    },
    {
        "question": "1×203765=？",
        "answer": 5.309129588835061
    },
    {
        "question": "689074÷72627=？",
        "answer": 0.9771677583621864
    },
    {
        "question": "323132688÷131868=？",
        "answer": 3.3892414738998253
    },
    {
        "question": "138×127915=？",
        "answer": 7.246800561569929
    },
    {
        "question": "1048789÷904371=？",
        "answer": 0.06434149610207814
    },
    {
        "question": "7×17078=？",
        "answer": 5.077535049234812
    },
    {
        "question": "28558619÷349=？",
        "answer": 4.912911775613427
    },
    {
        "question": "5×1492=？",
        "answer": 3.8727388274726686
    },
    {
        "question": "29187÷434=？",
        "answer": 1.827699728599787
    },
    {
        "question": "5×3620=？",
        "answer": 4.2576785748691846
    },
    {
        "question": "1435561×355=？",
        "answer": 8.707250004363786
    },
    {
        "question": "1×282674=？",
        "answer": 5.451285864464724
    },
    {
        "question": "6×378690=？",
        "answer": 6.356435087318148
    },
    {
        "question": "13165×1491=？",
        "answer": 7.292898506895082
    },
    {
        "question": "10115×20134=？",
        "answer": 8.308895951382192
    },
    {
        "question": "489208418÷23811660=？",
        "answer": 1.3127042487478793
    },
    {
        "question": "13×33367=？",
        "answer": 5.637260513651035
    },
    {
        "question": "6×280258=？",
        "answer": 6.225709268818422
    },
    {
        "question": "2232039÷12773=？",
        "answer": 2.2424088665024375
    },
    {
        "question": "42×319216=？",
        "answer": 7.12733394167798
    },
    {
        "question": "145521×3182=？",
        "answer": 8.665625845787304
    },
    {
        "question": "81585×11295=？",
        "answer": 8.964496553127233
    },
    {
        "question": "14385135÷4192735=？",
        "answer": 0.5354165280872284
    },
    {
        "question": "121491÷279=？",
        "answer": 2.638939903507572
    },
    {
        "question": "1130×94652=？",
        "answer": 8.029208238537457
    },
    {
        "question": "427885×690=？",
        "answer": 8.470176152796293
    },
    {
        "question": "983645838÷371438538=？",
        "answer": 0.42295179744954137
    },
    {
        "question": "298×534=？",
        "answer": 5.2017575211048115
    },
    {
        "question": "2550×52199=？",
        "answer": 8.124202363538863
    },
    {
        "question": "127×57258=？",
        "answer": 6.861639895166626
    },
    {
        "question": "62342678÷1023951=？",
        "answer": 1.7845062794774487
    },
    {
        "question": "11278799÷271618=？",
        "answer": 1.6183043100857941
    },
    {
        "question": "129514473÷15733=？",
        "answer": 3.91550676006212
    },
    {
        "question": "26×2455=？",
        "answer": 4.805024844429806
    },
    {
        "question": "46×6595719=？",
        "answer": 8.482019976630259
    },
    {
        "question": "1×524812006=？",
        "answer": 8.720003761733283
    },
    {
        "question": "775596÷282=？",
        "answer": 3.4393864522956523
    },
    {
        "question": "1255327÷5663=？",
        "answer": 2.3457103082521464
    },
    {
        "question": "913721÷22935=？",
        "answer": 1.6003148619249052
    },
    {
        "question": "269×302=？",
        "answer": 4.909759222959559
    },
    {
        "question": "457×2983=？",
        "answer": 6.134569453431913
    },
    {
        "question": "380985902÷131431172=？",
        "answer": 0.4622105247302719
    },
    {
        "question": "4342×71959=？",
        "answer": 8.494774938529275
    },
    {
        "question": "7×3128=？",
        "answer": 4.340364784402067
    },
    {
        "question": "602×1216809=？",
        "answer": 8.86481890452818
    },
    {
        "question": "2×27124226=？",
        "answer": 7.734387349940846
    },
    {
        "question": "502×840=？",
        "answer": 5.624983003206901
    },
    {
        "question": "49×170468=？",
        "answer": 6.921838945892273
    },
    {
        "question": "249156399÷37812=？",
        "answer": 3.8188423962678018
    },
    {
        "question": "134681÷759=？",
        "answer": 2.249064556448352
    },
    {
        "question": "4472635÷28432=？",
        "answer": 2.1967560475250196
    },
    {
        "question": "61498÷16054=？",
        "answer": 0.5832777335072236
    },
    {
        "question": "6488617÷8859=？",
        "answer": 2.864767438370831
    },
    {
        "question": "236×3310595=？",
        "answer": 8.892818057771285
    },
    {
        "question": "5647×110588=？",
        "answer": 8.795525791590489
    },
    {
        "question": "205438496÷202629452=？",
        "answer": 0.005979257056554359
    },
    {
        "question": "186860÷4717=？",
        "answer": 1.5978504682659296
    },
    {
        "question": "231567471÷1217030=？",
        "answer": 2.2793762688525603
    },
    {
        "question": "30×5882102=？",
        "answer": 8.246653805943598
    },
    {
        "question": "318506÷723=？",
        "answer": 2.643979320671493
    },
    {
        "question": "719843339÷28225818=？",
        "answer": 1.406591453428654
    },
    {
        "question": "3947843÷75826=？",
        "answer": 1.71654172654375
    },
    {
        "question": "1×508=？",
        "answer": 2.7058637122839193
    },
    {
        "question": "780912367÷156395=？",
        "answer": 3.6983794362259337
    },
    {
        "question": "1085×256=？",
        "answer": 5.443669703496398
    },
    {
        "question": "57663×4183=？",
        "answer": 8.382385098011815
    },
    {
        "question": "172896×251=？",
        "answer": 7.63745866734014
    },
    {
        "question": "2×9842=？",
        "answer": 4.294113356362043
    },
    {
        "question": "80620563÷462171=？",
        "answer": 2.2416431354740074
    },
    {
        "question": "514112÷603=？",
        "answer": 2.9307404288071406
    },
    {
        "question": "1524275÷46328=？",
        "answer": 1.517219774795053
    },
    {
        "question": "481×15448=？",
        "answer": 6.87101733714517
    },
    {
        "question": "4939×81816=？",
        "answer": 8.606477269102045
    },
    {
        "question": "1756241÷1066783=？",
        "answer": 0.2165080254179463
    },
    {
        "question": "12163×574=？",
        "answer": 6.8439525991401675
    },
    {
        "question": "11253×9805=？",
        "answer": 8.042715916874188
    },
    {
        "question": "106×84635=？",
        "answer": 6.952855863805709
    },
    {
        "question": "56×10758=？",
        "answer": 5.779919566952027
    },
    {
        "question": "703894016÷253659=？",
        "answer": 3.4432569971590916
    },
    {
        "question": "2118257÷4996=？",
        "answer": 2.627356220550362
    },
    {
        "question": "6325655÷2910344=？",
        "answer": 0.33716117665795586
    },
    {
        "question": "122412029÷230=？",
        "answer": 5.726096260481786
    },
    {
        "question": "8240805÷5095550=？",
        "answer": 0.208778570211746
    },
    {
        "question": "164113÷10375=？",
        "answer": 1.199154879109824
    },
    {
        "question": "111913336÷703957=？",
        "answer": 2.201335709899086
    },
    {
        "question": "12373621÷6456759=？",
        "answer": 0.282482233020586
    },
    {
        "question": "20568418÷419=？",
        "answer": 4.6909868666724375
    },
    {
        "question": "548490÷234=？",
        "answer": 3.369952856570945
    },
    {
        "question": "23433÷1040=？",
        "answer": 1.3527945532265477
    },
    {
        "question": "676×509196=？",
        "answer": 8.53683167932712
    },
    {
        "question": "15×690=？",
        "answer": 4.014940349792936
    },
    {
        "question": "168823432÷82655=？",
        "answer": 3.3101635945450254
    },
    {
        "question": "12146664÷717467=？",
        "answer": 1.228655087809779
    },
    {
        "question": "21×15731=？",
        "answer": 5.5189756257919065
    },
    {
        "question": "114833261÷1436=？",
        "answer": 4.902913258056214
    },
    {
        "question": "1132927÷481=？",
        "answer": 3.3720568506841264
    },
    {
        "question": "82×8304=？",
        "answer": 5.833101192888099
    },
    {
        "question": "394978÷71732=？",
        "answer": 0.7408599665878809
    },
    {
        "question": "6×3989110=？",
        "answer": 7.379027262560703
    },
    {
        "question": "399079411÷4741=？",
        "answer": 4.925189367253991
    },
    {
        "question": "780839×416=？",
        "answer": 8.511654827219042
    },
    {
        "question": "5×212=？",
        "answer": 3.0253058652647704
    },
    {
        "question": "896282÷24314=？",
        "answer": 1.5665882622283362
    },
    {
        "question": "70×807=？",
        "answer": 4.751971574736327
    },
    {
        "question": "9×6123581=？",
        "answer": 7.74124797630988
    },
    {
        "question": "121×2391=？",
        "answer": 5.461364946432225
    },
    {
        "question": "28×13549=？",
        "answer": 5.579065274116606
    },
    {
        "question": "673776375÷5933=？",
        "answer": 5.055241430662927
    },
    {
        "question": "7151×1319=？",
        "answer": 6.974611573587235
    },
    {
        "question": "180314818÷63305730=？",
        "answer": 0.4545883967040128
    },
    {
        "question": "19×6962347=？",
        "answer": 8.121509265466992
    },
    {
        "question": "26140657÷6170858=？",
        "answer": 0.626970945807922
    },
    {
        "question": "78738667÷1425=？",
        "answer": 4.74237319381803
    },
    {
        "question": "14237573÷3730135=？",
        "answer": 0.5817114138843293
    },
    {
        "question": "616×321=？",
        "answer": 5.2960857445692975
    },
    {
        "question": "18571÷9122=？",
        "answer": 0.3087452220916665
    },
    {
        "question": "4411×201=？",
        "answer": 5.947733115198896
    },
    {
        "question": "5×7481=？",
        "answer": 4.572929659079372
    },
    {
        "question": "462848÷48847=？",
        "answer": 0.9766004953197186
    },
    {
        "question": "144225÷1056=？",
        "answer": 2.1353766294323866
    },
    {
        "question": "41×4529867=？",
        "answer": 8.268869307736091
    },
    {
        "question": "361003888÷210=？",
        "answer": 6.2352925845342115
    },
    {
        "question": "17×2694639=？",
        "answer": 7.660949512493089
    },
    {
        "question": "42521÷223=？",
        "answer": 2.2802986065701503
    },
    {
        "question": "112557757÷18414=？",
        "answer": 3.786227291273725
    },
    {
        "question": "716×88607=？",
        "answer": 7.802381055044646
    },
    {
        "question": "3319×371=？",
        "answer": 6.090381162023649
    },
    {
        "question": "9×1447474=？",
        "answer": 7.114853280969755
    },
    {
        "question": "2950×7565=？",
        "answer": 7.348630948337369
    },
    {
        "question": "175656×2121=？",
        "answer": 8.57120365738635
    },
    {
        "question": "856×6146=？",
        "answer": 6.7210663205975125
    },
    {
        "question": "42×10377=？",
        "answer": 5.6393211071319245
    },
    {
        "question": "9×1588=？",
        "answer": 4.155093007530402
    },
    {
        "question": "917×84956=？",
        "answer": 7.891563391916561
    },
    {
        "question": "1×3724=？",
        "answer": 3.571009672309305
    },
    {
        "question": "2681558÷489499=？",
        "answer": 0.7386353859326312
    },
    {
        "question": "18034840÷309=？",
        "answer": 4.766153814308819
    },
    {
        "question": "2206×2892=？",
        "answer": 6.804803796726665
    },
    {
        "question": "18×2676=？",
        "answer": 4.682758614199091
    },
    {
        "question": "6882×891=？",
        "answer": 6.787592372321786
    },
    {
        "question": "155148÷2473=？",
        "answer": 1.797522065140826
    },
    {
        "question": "12435÷2447=？",
        "answer": 0.7060118202541656
    },
    {
        "question": "804602284÷4246839=？",
        "answer": 2.277515464095195
    },
    {
        "question": "6×46105=？",
        "answer": 5.441899276742038
    },
    {
        "question": "8803×20070=？",
        "answer": 8.247178074343763
    },
    {
        "question": "4×4485=？",
        "answer": 4.253822438708073
    },
    {
        "question": "9955377÷58421=？",
        "answer": 2.2314887243877246
    },
    {
        "question": "794159501÷42969004=？",
        "answer": 1.2667524489162285
    },
    {
        "question": "1×657=？",
        "answer": 2.8175653695597807
    },
    {
        "question": "5038×443=？",
        "answer": 6.348661889385164
    },
    {
        "question": "48034×3663=？",
        "answer": 8.245385672398957
    },
    {
        "question": "472284÷35333=？",
        "answer": 1.1260227194237789
    },
    {
        "question": "199×302=？",
        "answer": 4.778860019366857
    },
    {
        "question": "4418×545=？",
        "answer": 6.381622213812059
    },
    {
        "question": "2×655052=？",
        "answer": 6.117305772627779
    },
    {
        "question": "26×252=？",
        "answer": 3.816373888752362
    },
    {
        "question": "3905×3224=？",
        "answer": 7.1000160713463725
    },
    {
        "question": "219×782438=？",
        "answer": 8.233894049142105
    },
    {
        "question": "140299866÷541=？",
        "answer": 5.413859991128573
    },
    {
        "question": "5743900÷3356=？",
        "answer": 3.2333849181746848
    },
    {
        "question": "11×911=？",
        "answer": 4.000911062131223
    },
    {
        "question": "9163473÷11292=？",
        "answer": 2.909289235074212
    },
    {
        "question": "62324×7095=？",
        "answer": 8.645607718690666
    },
    {
        "question": "430938÷4255=？",
        "answer": 2.00551522733002
    },
    {
        "question": "3×8925898=？",
        "answer": 7.427773174386367
    },
    {
        "question": "112497×270=？",
        "answer": 7.482504705265766
    },
    {
        "question": "1×200855192=？",
        "answer": 8.30288306249441
    },
    {
        "question": "307÷223=？",
        "answer": 0.1388335124290258
    },
    {
        "question": "303623903÷19275=？",
        "answer": 4.197341571977282
    },
    {
        "question": "45×123241=？",
        "answer": 6.74396772737935
    },
    {
        "question": "309883105÷256=？",
        "answer": 6.082957933595107
    },
    {
        "question": "65771×1453=？",
        "answer": 7.98030005933776
    },
    {
        "question": "1527÷262=？",
        "answer": 0.7655377457366757
    },
    {
        "question": "7×237298=？",
        "answer": 6.220392117917124
    },
    {
        "question": "6×31978105=？",
        "answer": 8.283003974570983
    },
    {
        "question": "626829164÷2905=？",
        "answer": 5.334003057626713
    },
    {
        "question": "1×327946517=？",
        "answer": 8.515803022779712
    },
    {
        "question": "44748983÷291392=？",
        "answer": 2.1863055453596973
    },
    {
        "question": "3667258÷87200=？",
        "answer": 1.6238249797143793
    },
    {
        "question": "418796401÷9514=？",
        "answer": 4.6436397937534934
    },
    {
        "question": "767418÷155806=？",
        "answer": 0.6924478033873069
    },
    {
        "question": "69×36098=？",
        "answer": 6.396332231340272
    },
    {
        "question": "60016693÷1006=？",
        "answer": 4.775674080821783
    },
    {
        "question": "8×57646=？",
        "answer": 5.663859164395484
    },
    {
        "question": "1×410=？",
        "answer": 2.6127838567197355
    },
    {
        "question": "6639566÷768355=？",
        "answer": 0.936577770575761
    },
    {
        "question": "1204068÷4565=？",
        "answer": 2.421210232618631
    },
    {
        "question": "154493÷35666=？",
        "answer": 0.636654401306632
    },
    {
        "question": "9823143÷12583=？",
        "answer": 2.892466269713261
    },
    {
        "question": "71508×13739=？",
        "answer": 8.992309755004772
    },
    {
        "question": "5230867÷27980=？",
        "answer": 2.2717259676425305
    },
    {
        "question": "297473÷654=？",
        "answer": 2.657869804990232
    },
    {
        "question": "114×39983=？",
        "answer": 6.65878022827629
    },
    {
        "question": "155101358÷784=？",
        "answer": 5.296299537639318
    },
    {
        "question": "869881÷270=？",
        "answer": 3.5080960808985084
    },
    {
        "question": "473346360÷1077413=？",
        "answer": 2.6427968303599507
    },
    {
        "question": "40124÷17021=？",
        "answer": 0.3724191500260096
    },
    {
        "question": "1324÷258=？",
        "answer": 0.710268279140451
    },
    {
        "question": "153522÷6210=？",
        "answer": 1.3930790193368305
    },
    {
        "question": "518871×959=？",
        "answer": 8.696878005574346
    },
    {
        "question": "514858523÷18787=？",
        "answer": 4.43783047110405
    },
    {
        "question": "1056153÷69191=？",
        "answer": 1.1836772295910845
    },
    {
        "question": "711×456068=？",
        "answer": 8.51089920177806
    },
    {
        "question": "203497638÷537=？",
        "answer": 5.578585087028664
    },
    {
        "question": "2274×52720=？",
        "answer": 8.078765861937669
    },
    {
        "question": "4294÷881=？",
        "answer": 0.687886131688182
    },
    {
        "question": "1×47177274=？",
        "answer": 7.67373284284545
    },
    {
        "question": "1158602÷12341=？",
        "answer": 1.9725839215371983
    },
    {
        "question": "159117599÷2067=？",
        "answer": 4.8863777402656225
    },
    {
        "question": "360929÷1779=？",
        "answer": 2.3072458301628562
    },
    {
        "question": "1486×555163=？",
        "answer": 8.916439323371192
    },
    {
        "question": "175713÷429=？",
        "answer": 2.612346601464289
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1268509=？",
        "answer": 6.1032935528636
    },
    {
        "question": "8718314÷25452=？",
        "answer": 2.5347105920091457
    },
    {
        "question": "60708×287=？",
        "answer": 7.241127822190185
    },
    {
        "question": "1×656417629=？",
        "answer": 8.817180236114469
    },
    {
        "question": "45850×1209=？",
        "answer": 7.743765640866812
    },
    {
        "question": "4×69262793=？",
        "answer": 8.44255999168075
    },
    {
        "question": "3836×1555=？",
        "answer": 6.775608991861482
    },
    {
        "question": "907920931÷574549=？",
        "answer": 3.198720955241029
    },
    {
        "question": "2×263664=？",
        "answer": 5.722080832060927
    },
    {
        "question": "700871234÷2992664=？",
        "answer": 2.3695802761526576
    },
    {
        "question": "45453÷24385=？",
        "answer": 0.27043979298679605
    },
    {
        "question": "549059101÷46938196=？",
        "answer": 1.0680927005259182
    },
    {
        "question": "235660÷5333=？",
        "answer": 1.6453142896624
    },
    {
        "question": "2×848171=？",
        "answer": 6.229513414983989
    },
    {
        "question": "3×949=？",
        "answer": 3.454387467146955
    },
    {
        "question": "58349÷606=？",
        "answer": 1.9835607932296115
    },
    {
        "question": "2694338×364=？",
        "answer": 8.991553459938446
    },
    {
        "question": "685059÷165699=？",
        "answer": 0.6164080888246994
    },
    {
        "question": "1145×255=？",
        "answer": 5.465345667109862
    },
    {
        "question": "78708÷54758=？",
        "answer": 0.15757129951886045
    },
    {
        "question": "672492÷4716=？",
        "answer": 2.1541133258922556
    },
    {
        "question": "4×36329=？",
        "answer": 5.162313434870306
    },
    {
        "question": "4028×1892=？",
        "answer": 6.882010593947355
    },
    {
        "question": "16547÷1004=？",
        "answer": 1.2169855540914927
    },
    {
        "question": "162429×881=？",
        "answer": 8.155639478979746
    },
    {
        "question": "296×1002488=？",
        "answer": 8.472370893782605
    },
    {
        "question": "10842÷4416=？",
        "answer": 0.39008033822343297
    },
    {
        "question": "42843483÷2046161=？",
        "answer": 1.320944967241193
    },
    {
        "question": "4×37251296=？",
        "answer": 8.173201378099725
    },
    {
        "question": "262621÷449=？",
        "answer": 2.7670831096894783
    },
    {
        "question": "630518255÷6631936=？",
        "answer": 1.9780573384454996
    },
    {
        "question": "9915106÷3763=？",
        "answer": 3.4207631431835352
    },
    {
        "question": "3910045÷3233656=？",
        "answer": 0.08248793835405746
    },
    {
        "question": "13×1175979=？",
        "answer": 7.184342918719107
    },
    {
        "question": "58434÷2993=？",
        "answer": 1.2905588993771184
    },
    {
        "question": "208345÷6680=？",
        "answer": 1.4940066199589053
    },
    {
        "question": "703987÷5682=？",
        "answer": 2.0930634100387278
    },
    {
        "question": "265908918÷263777669=？",
        "answer": 0.0034948767740668935
    },
    {
        "question": "31835849÷5537699=？",
        "answer": 0.7595870900387953
    },
    {
        "question": "2×873=？",
        "answer": 3.2420442393695508
    },
    {
        "question": "30716÷662=？",
        "answer": 1.6665066694772304
    },
    {
        "question": "17×3427=？",
        "answer": 4.765363025808141
    },
    {
        "question": "33×9138622=？",
        "answer": 8.479394653892452
    },
    {
        "question": "594283÷296211=？",
        "answer": 0.30239212474133376
    },
    {
        "question": "540245590÷7890=？",
        "answer": 4.835514227234369
    },
    {
        "question": "184460802÷30423=？",
        "answer": 3.782702055098773
    },
    {
        "question": "416×433864=？",
        "answer": 8.25644694653154
    },
    {
        "question": "182930183÷4251754=？",
        "answer": 1.633717239876209
    },
    {
        "question": "6×112848505=？",
        "answer": 8.83064706036764
    },
    {
        "question": "2431×13471=？",
        "answer": 7.515184794979231
    },
    {
        "question": "150427902÷40363807=？",
        "answer": 0.5713362775719647
    },
    {
        "question": "1137×668201=？",
        "answer": 8.880667585936205
    },
    {
        "question": "36115322÷25869=？",
        "answer": 3.144911850512239
    },
    {
        "question": "651×623=？",
        "answer": 5.608069035227362
    },
    {
        "question": "324558÷66885=？",
        "answer": 0.6859635870781392
    },
    {
        "question": "129×1238=？",
        "answer": 5.203310354983348
    },
    {
        "question": "1403÷1281=？",
        "answer": 0.039508541283673655
    },
    {
        "question": "67×227=？",
        "answer": 4.182100659893949
    },
    {
        "question": "227684383÷10476=？",
        "answer": 4.337137753380516
    },
    {
        "question": "318349÷102210=？",
        "answer": 0.493410101705743
    },
    {
        "question": "647994×1481=？",
        "answer": 8.982126043127982
    },
    {
        "question": "6034240÷7414=？",
        "answer": 2.91056999769578
    },
    {
        "question": "61354÷25025=？",
        "answer": 0.38946879584725536
    },
    {
        "question": "3×245380635=？",
        "answer": 8.866961540720718
    },
    {
        "question": "6×10937826=？",
        "answer": 7.817082260678351
    },
    {
        "question": "98475840÷18073092=？",
        "answer": 0.7362972346845483
    },
    {
        "question": "192718938÷169838=？",
        "answer": 3.0548895267992453
    },
    {
        "question": "4005×5489=？",
        "answer": 7.342095751201872
    },
    {
        "question": "254×2388=？",
        "answer": 5.782868039077269
    },
    {
        "question": "131×189250=？",
        "answer": 7.394307183827874
    },
    {
        "question": "2×44284402=？",
        "answer": 7.9472807801671586
    },
    {
        "question": "37×163843=？",
        "answer": 6.782629615459396
    },
    {
        "question": "265512×2558=？",
        "answer": 8.831984694245666
    },
    {
        "question": "14×4819=？",
        "answer": 4.829084961979446
    },
    {
        "question": "373069958÷6083=？",
        "answer": 4.787672461792249
    },
    {
        "question": "11×83302=？",
        "answer": 5.962048113678299
    },
    {
        "question": "179317×821=？",
        "answer": 8.167964621562891
    },
    {
        "question": "2710×319612=？",
        "answer": 8.937592367636343
    },
    {
        "question": "172989110÷599=？",
        "answer": 5.460591941920008
    },
    {
        "question": "20808×31459=？",
        "answer": 8.815975252599548
    },
    {
        "question": "17393343÷2119088=？",
        "answer": 0.914234069249781
    },
    {
        "question": "840096400÷25192356=？",
        "answer": 1.5230603388594781
    },
    {
        "question": "2×416613330=？",
        "answer": 8.920763157225847
    },
    {
        "question": "565744÷14320=？",
        "answer": 1.596676938767684
    },
    {
        "question": "12×736935=？",
        "answer": 6.946610429447738
    },
    {
        "question": "2×18955382=？",
        "answer": 7.5787625366723015
    },
    {
        "question": "6088×70061=？",
        "answer": 8.629950975593497
    },
    {
        "question": "111×6173579=？",
        "answer": 8.835859988738216
    },
    {
        "question": "394×3229=？",
        "answer": 6.104564266842735
    },
    {
        "question": "16×17141342=？",
        "answer": 8.438164802598964
    },
    {
        "question": "2×177017525=？",
        "answer": 8.549046259958173
    },
    {
        "question": "1850×853=？",
        "answer": 6.1981207595705365
    },
    {
        "question": "280572129÷240684478=？",
        "answer": 0.06659644456220648
    },
    {
        "question": "933×355=？",
        "answer": 5.520109996801594
    },
    {
        "question": "13688760÷622384=？",
        "answer": 1.3423056897779144
    },
    {
        "question": "6191÷236=？",
        "answer": 1.4188488010427984
    },
    {
        "question": "2×210096332=？",
        "answer": 8.623448465937305
    },
    {
        "question": "218×212=？",
        "answer": 4.664792354533356
    },
    {
        "question": "28401÷489=？",
        "answer": 1.7640247727134193
    },
    {
        "question": "2×3554542=？",
        "answer": 6.851813645824939
    },
    {
        "question": "1425×9130=？",
        "answer": 7.114285641878828
    },
    {
        "question": "257314÷12848=？",
        "answer": 1.301627888113826
    },
    {
        "question": "6680×43003=？",
        "answer": 8.458275216613234
    },
    {
        "question": "165525285÷101261=？",
        "answer": 3.2134221323842054
    },
    {
        "question": "646244070÷167502=？",
        "answer": 3.5863765740431695
    },
    {
        "question": "98172÷1690=？",
        "answer": 1.7641009340952436
    },
    {
        "question": "3589142×234=？",
        "answer": 8.924206498411666
    },
    {
        "question": "9×24801=？",
        "answer": 5.348711701786759
    },
    {
        "question": "3×215461367=？",
        "answer": 8.810490665630258
    },
    {
        "question": "14×1306434=？",
        "answer": 7.262215510086151
    },
    {
        "question": "105×27375=？",
        "answer": 6.458543426918113
    },
    {
        "question": "66×89139=？",
        "answer": 6.769611693215316
    },
    {
        "question": "50185×737=？",
        "answer": 7.568041416344868
    },
    {
        "question": "2×588561=？",
        "answer": 6.0708214765910995
    },
    {
        "question": "98×1678=？",
        "answer": 5.216018032185176
    },
    {
        "question": "1737×62933=？",
        "answer": 8.038678253394824
    },
    {
        "question": "8574147÷1102340=？",
        "answer": 0.8908753583249058
    },
    {
        "question": "506×367142=？",
        "answer": 8.268984586238576
    },
    {
        "question": "110×1807=？",
        "answer": 5.298350837719157
    },
    {
        "question": "10×554=？",
        "answer": 3.74350976472843
    },
    {
        "question": "6773×48100=？",
        "answer": 8.512926151980192
    },
    {
        "question": "2612669÷299=？",
        "answer": 3.941413203959693
    },
    {
        "question": "653×14682=？",
        "answer": 6.981698401010506
    },
    {
        "question": "440553484÷8772=？",
        "answer": 4.700900017088924
    },
    {
        "question": "5×42952174=？",
        "answer": 8.331955154629224
    },
    {
        "question": "31809979÷1251=？",
        "answer": 4.405306072705765
    },
    {
        "question": "102842701÷3543693=？",
        "answer": 1.4627173834711324
    },
    {
        "question": "1110×209664=？",
        "answer": 8.366846845858925
    },
    {
        "question": "70096×3174=？",
        "answer": 8.34730015825293
    },
    {
        "question": "11×72026259=？",
        "answer": 8.89888354352996
    },
    {
        "question": "1×142752542=？",
        "answer": 8.154583850485267
    },
    {
        "question": "38987×1435=？",
        "answer": 7.747771719136375
    },
    {
        "question": "286×214=？",
        "answer": 4.786779806478234
    },
    {
        "question": "1634100÷1405379=？",
        "answer": 0.06548517022681527
    },
    {
        "question": "1×79395456=？",
        "answer": 7.8997956473817945
    },
    {
        "question": "33×787432=？",
        "answer": 7.414726999736508
    },
    {
        "question": "10×650695=？",
        "answer": 6.813377469588086
    },
    {
        "question": "404107887÷396=？",
        "answer": 6.008802140753594
    },
    {
        "question": "46915380÷225728=？",
        "answer": 2.3177298046749915
    },
    {
        "question": "1207332÷14986=？",
        "answer": 1.906140983377607
    },
    {
        "question": "8619321÷49687=？",
        "answer": 2.239230279250343
    },
    {
        "question": "9×32554794=？",
        "answer": 8.46685746100532
    },
    {
        "question": "643614216÷2582826=？",
        "answer": 2.396530478549497
    },
    {
        "question": "157037959÷4105=？",
        "answer": 4.582691480709607
    },
    {
        "question": "193372162÷899627=？",
        "answer": 2.3323314716952117
    },
    {
        "question": "26352639÷3003=？",
        "answer": 3.943268780546906
    },
    {
        "question": "158372÷813=？",
        "answer": 2.289587855646849
    },
    {
        "question": "1×2907=？",
        "answer": 3.4634450317704277
    },
    {
        "question": "135899821÷710=？",
        "answer": 5.281960535984254
    },
    {
        "question": "28165×1471=？",
        "answer": 7.6173224282989
    },
    {
        "question": "652165696÷111141332=？",
        "answer": 0.7684823537376412
    },
    {
        "question": "1221347×376=？",
        "answer": 8.662026914912909
    },
    {
        "question": "209010÷3118=？",
        "answer": 1.8262909544014088
    },
    {
        "question": "3770÷947=？",
        "answer": 0.5999913712025194
    },
    {
        "question": "1233×212183=？",
        "answer": 8.417673662089678
    },
    {
        "question": "964142879÷612542425=？",
        "answer": 0.19700522443754792
    },
    {
        "question": "88069÷3063=？",
        "answer": 1.458676068266659
    },
    {
        "question": "1×2044732=？",
        "answer": 6.310636393737782
    },
    {
        "question": "151562÷35230=？",
        "answer": 0.633677684374688
    },
    {
        "question": "5×5524=？",
        "answer": 4.441223674242613
    },
    {
        "question": "3×18222=？",
        "answer": 4.737717297021571
    },
    {
        "question": "17×412=？",
        "answer": 3.8453461374114086
    },
    {
        "question": "567×106867=？",
        "answer": 7.782426676819582
    },
    {
        "question": "627360÷6116=？",
        "answer": 2.011049348215849
    },
    {
        "question": "11807680÷191310=？",
        "answer": 1.790426903114413
    },
    {
        "question": "11697096÷13739=？",
        "answer": 2.930122930716501
    },
    {
        "question": "12837478÷2601958=？",
        "answer": 0.6931794303063601
    },
    {
        "question": "11×38429=？",
        "answer": 5.626051768552252
    },
    {
        "question": "106395551÷54859714=？",
        "answer": 0.2876699288609226
    },
    {
        "question": "15×49642=？",
        "answer": 5.87194052929306
    },
    {
        "question": "70338÷638=？",
        "answer": 2.042369336648552
    },
    {
        "question": "5×229113=？",
        "answer": 6.0590197363368
    },
    {
        "question": "1395×89175=？",
        "answer": 8.094817325620008
    },
    {
        "question": "3×13930195=？",
        "answer": 7.621078450600282
    },
    {
        "question": "280×155670=？",
        "answer": 7.639362956756809
    },
    {
        "question": "1984×148770=？",
        "answer": 8.470057030828933
    },
    {
        "question": "289272253÷56445=？",
        "answer": 3.7096813007352556
    },
    {
        "question": "951330535÷657=？",
        "answer": 6.1607660670263265
    },
    {
        "question": "172743÷234=？",
        "answer": 2.868184600239751
    },
    {
        "question": "623413596÷1364=？",
        "answer": 5.65996189923311
    },
    {
        "question": "100×2755=？",
        "answer": 5.440121603187804
    },
    {
        "question": "1×6910=？",
        "answer": 3.8394780473741985
    },
    {
        "question": "3×86690=？",
        "answer": 5.415090257671115
    },
    {
        "question": "753÷451=？",
        "answer": 0.22261843432274006
    },
    {
        "question": "161134308÷4661346=？",
        "answer": 1.5386766775964318
    },
    {
        "question": "993736×307=？",
        "answer": 8.484409398736103
    },
    {
        "question": "1216×248913=？",
        "answer": 8.480981154071744
    },
    {
        "question": "233518173÷14898778=？",
        "answer": 1.195170035184473
    },
    {
        "question": "771572÷560413=？",
        "answer": 0.13886825776997075
    },
    {
        "question": "43310965÷725233=？",
        "answer": 1.7761203028276653
    },
    {
        "question": "482×1438=？",
        "answer": 5.840805924285713
    },
    {
        "question": "229367945÷4218423=？",
        "answer": 1.7353825973585888
    },
    {
        "question": "1×82164=？",
        "answer": 4.914681573914944
    },
    {
        "question": "665807243÷37315=？",
        "answer": 4.25146506937283
    },
    {
        "question": "4×2394407=？",
        "answer": 6.981257964813008
    },
    {
        "question": "234648606÷132241=？",
        "answer": 3.2490518538108066
    },
    {
        "question": "3872÷517=？",
        "answer": 0.8744448055424136
    },
    {
        "question": "736464÷12130=？",
        "answer": 1.7832907215497287
    },
    {
        "question": "2×2121671=？",
        "answer": 6.627708035944598
    },
    {
        "question": "6×14396=？",
        "answer": 4.936393088364517
    },
    {
        "question": "448109558÷47621283=？",
        "answer": 0.9735831154682718
    },
    {
        "question": "21163÷583=？",
        "answer": 1.5599086771814037
    },
    {
        "question": "93×807513=？",
        "answer": 7.8756324712385855
    },
    {
        "question": "399689225÷411=？",
        "answer": 5.987880618637931
    },
    {
        "question": "469640192÷2360253=？",
        "answer": 2.2988066986143383
    },
    {
        "question": "2813385÷1293732=？",
        "answer": 0.33738484721909257
    },
    {
        "question": "1×135744147=？",
        "answer": 8.132721112806719
    },
    {
        "question": "89×1632112=？",
        "answer": 8.162139964563366
    },
    {
        "question": "36289982÷1099627=？",
        "answer": 1.5185413579147917
    },
    {
        "question": "129×313=？",
        "answer": 4.606134047845697
    },
    {
        "question": "18299100÷91164=？",
        "answer": 2.302606358008276
    },
    {
        "question": "63683×5360=？",
        "answer": 8.533188303793565
    },
    {
        "question": "70007522÷61444=？",
        "answer": 3.0566652250677753
    },
    {
        "question": "4731×81610=？",
        "answer": 8.586696325904496
    },
    {
        "question": "4×330=？",
        "answer": 3.12057393120585
    },
    {
        "question": "19074450÷54160=？",
        "answer": 2.546773368516869
    },
    {
        "question": "1642045÷13173=？",
        "answer": 2.0957003628984054
    },
    {
        "question": "25×10787943=？",
        "answer": 8.430878651787442
    },
    {
        "question": "2×2104156=？",
        "answer": 6.624107930493429
    },
    {
        "question": "618×127635=？",
        "answer": 7.8969582578012805
    },
    {
        "question": "48×238=？",
        "answer": 4.057818194432099
    },
    {
        "question": "4711440÷5518=？",
        "answer": 2.9313719686233752
    },
    {
        "question": "2305876÷1528=？",
        "answer": 3.1787125948752504
    },
    {
        "question": "54866732÷108650=？",
        "answer": 2.7032793626426197
    },
    {
        "question": "103767903÷7943=？",
        "answer": 4.116078477806772
    },
    {
        "question": "16111×242=？",
        "answer": 6.590937863631395
    },
    {
        "question": "2×167877=？",
        "answer": 5.526021195332055
    },
    {
        "question": "6×6075=？",
        "answer": 4.5616975326539935
    },
    {
        "question": "59246483÷2652=？",
        "answer": 4.349089055050212
    },
    {
        "question": "3×42193081=？",
        "answer": 8.10236249407272
    },
    {
        "question": "25334688÷5610=？",
        "answer": 3.654752699010051
    },
    {
        "question": "2209764÷4386=？",
        "answer": 2.7022772667188906
    },
    {
        "question": "55141663÷24692=？",
        "answer": 3.3489235914223165
    },
    {
        "question": "47×230969=？",
        "answer": 7.03565155197336
    },
    {
        "question": "3183255÷5405=？",
        "answer": 2.7700757316157003
    },
    {
        "question": "33123692÷29234=？",
        "answer": 3.0542504950836715
    },
    {
        "question": "46×2000=？",
        "answer": 4.963787827345556
    },
    {
        "question": "266×2937732=？",
        "answer": 8.892893810580206
    },
    {
        "question": "12427×8974=？",
        "answer": 8.04735236353319
    },
    {
        "question": "789×210=？",
        "answer": 5.219296297943339
    },
    {
        "question": "1266393÷4877=？",
        "answer": 2.414415745702266
    },
    {
        "question": "25841×5669=？",
        "answer": 8.165815773050804
    },
    {
        "question": "10591103÷21890=？",
        "answer": 2.6846954300663506
    },
    {
        "question": "3×101487=？",
        "answer": 5.483531669482677
    },
    {
        "question": "4×755979=？",
        "answer": 6.480569722926005
    },
    {
        "question": "1×9737=？",
        "answer": 3.988425170006303
    },
    {
        "question": "326439159÷2860=？",
        "answer": 5.057436217190344
    },
    {
        "question": "14435×43637=？",
        "answer": 8.799271673849114
    },
    {
        "question": "27×20122=？",
        "answer": 5.735034908823009
    },
    {
        "question": "25904101÷119289=？",
        "answer": 2.3367681268181895
    },
    {
        "question": "1×813=？",
        "answer": 2.910090545594068
    },
    {
        "question": "6489746÷277416=？",
        "answer": 1.369096193982127
    },
    {
        "question": "86×549726=？",
        "answer": 7.67464472921257
    },
    {
        "question": "246×119463=？",
        "answer": 7.4681685238185205
    },
    {
        "question": "38×782=？",
        "answer": 4.4729903496766585
    },
    {
        "question": "1057800÷550252=？",
        "answer": 0.2838419329253033
    },
    {
        "question": "18720÷1381=？",
        "answer": 1.1321121658234552
    },
    {
        "question": "193×15801=？",
        "answer": 6.484241882084917
    },
    {
        "question": "81×549507=？",
        "answer": 7.648458248016703
    },
    {
        "question": "758907÷216=？",
        "answer": 3.5457348075357644
    },
    {
        "question": "33708×523=？",
        "answer": 7.246234674116478
    },
    {
        "question": "353×1437=？",
        "answer": 5.705231473522049
    },
    {
        "question": "846710087÷2664=？",
        "answer": 5.502200513127583
    },
    {
        "question": "13×444=？",
        "answer": 3.7613263224214566
    },
    {
        "question": "55×440=？",
        "answer": 4.383815365980431
    },
    {
        "question": "2×67184=？",
        "answer": 5.128295852957845
    },
    {
        "question": "26185118÷567721=？",
        "answer": 1.6639195762607746
    },
    {
        "question": "635153÷483333=？",
        "answer": 0.11863190571851384
    },
    {
        "question": "168×135821=？",
        "answer": 7.35827620541868
    },
    {
        "question": "835776020÷6741=？",
        "answer": 5.093365579114761
    },
    {
        "question": "4×23516683=？",
        "answer": 7.973436056334701
    },
    {
        "question": "160×236708=？",
        "answer": 7.578332918646449
    },
    {
        "question": "580144192÷363=？",
        "answer": 6.203629323711515
    },
    {
        "question": "71355÷3268=？",
        "answer": 1.339142362615205
    },
    {
        "question": "977635841÷1188=？",
        "answer": 5.9153606741673785
    },
    {
        "question": "3775313÷12131=？",
        "answer": 2.493056360796697
    },
    {
        "question": "73195×8331=？",
        "answer": 8.785178549591492
    },
    {
        "question": "13707918÷45460=？",
        "answer": 2.479342066451309
    },
    {
        "question": "64053780÷1402=？",
        "answer": 4.659796750187799
    },
    {
        "question": "1×11430520=？",
        "answer": 7.058065987875044
    },
    {
        "question": "624380×235=？",
        "answer": 8.166516845661558
    },
    {
        "question": "151387617÷6886903=？",
        "answer": 1.3420663866643285
    },
    {
        "question": "38769592÷201=？",
        "answer": 5.285295173220949
    },
    {
        "question": "632134694÷6862628=？",
        "answer": 1.9643191688604784
    },
    {
        "question": "66309873÷24972380=？",
        "answer": 0.42411826124338176
    },
    {
        "question": "11577×10259=？",
        "answer": 8.074701063107039
    },
    {
        "question": "2×3110=？",
        "answer": 3.7937903846908188
    },
    {
        "question": "81831192÷64015998=？",
        "answer": 0.1066303569376661
    },
    {
        "question": "23940476÷3892738=？",
        "answer": 0.7888776064862678
    },
    {
        "question": "25417÷2312=？",
        "answer": 1.0411364591786576
    },
    {
        "question": "435×475074=？",
        "answer": 8.31525051981857
    },
    {
        "question": "54820086÷48718=？",
        "answer": 3.0512502614331507
    },
    {
        "question": "268×1434=？",
        "answer": 5.58468394536057
    },
    {
        "question": "140936236÷708=？",
        "answer": 5.2989894108744995
    },
    {
        "question": "1552×18877=？",
        "answer": 7.466824692743877
    },
    {
        "question": "82×3418=？",
        "answer": 5.447585910768435
    },
    {
        "question": "81000×936=？",
        "answer": 7.8797608676167545
    },
    {
        "question": "58241÷748=？",
        "answer": 1.891327225355929
    },
    {
        "question": "137751×3116=？",
        "answer": 8.632692209285914
    },
    {
        "question": "11×3178114=？",
        "answer": 7.543562156595653
    },
    {
        "question": "679×28935=？",
        "answer": 7.293293260980067
    },
    {
        "question": "919686019÷222552=？",
        "answer": 3.616208082927311
    },
    {
        "question": "573770÷3092=？",
        "answer": 2.2684983518406487
    },
    {
        "question": "4045476÷1578679=？",
        "answer": 0.40867579713367996
    },
    {
        "question": "671×149987=？",
        "answer": 8.002776138738463
    },
    {
        "question": "6381278÷877=？",
        "answer": 3.8619080716819973
    },
    {
        "question": "12470÷1925=？",
        "answer": 0.8114357196340232
    },
    {
        "question": "4×1968459=？",
        "answer": 6.896186364856449
    },
    {
        "question": "2348073÷6777=？",
        "answer": 2.5396741090668775
    },
    {
        "question": "788263093÷4920832=？",
        "answer": 2.2046326548568196
    },
    {
        "question": "170256×1859=？",
        "answer": 8.500381815619429
    },
    {
        "question": "520907÷2512=？",
        "answer": 2.316740558499132
    },
    {
        "question": "6×999238=？",
        "answer": 6.777820191839103
    },
    {
        "question": "7687÷5427=？",
        "answer": 0.15119705948979126
    },
    {
        "question": "4×489=？",
        "answer": 3.291368850451583
    },
    {
        "question": "266943÷2894=？",
        "answer": 1.9649200101313342
    },
    {
        "question": "113×5026314=？",
        "answer": 8.754328059496379
    },
    {
        "question": "7×79465=？",
        "answer": 5.745273927742067
    },
    {
        "question": "963883×415=？",
        "answer": 8.602072417401056
    },
    {
        "question": "44168781÷16883=？",
        "answer": 3.4176657930000323
    },
    {
        "question": "38785693÷273=？",
        "answer": 5.152508908527696
    },
    {
        "question": "116359÷49420=？",
        "answer": 0.3718972391580837
    },
    {
        "question": "126383÷11015=？",
        "answer": 1.0597041586722327
    },
    {
        "question": "139×5545299=？",
        "answer": 8.886939768331553
    },
    {
        "question": "121248701÷24386875=？",
        "answer": 0.6965209422662567
    },
    {
        "question": "2426839÷4664=？",
        "answer": 2.7162824238142367
    },
    {
        "question": "1795568÷547=？",
        "answer": 3.516214530617137
    },
    {
        "question": "80×4423=？",
        "answer": 5.548806926361547
    },
    {
        "question": "99503÷22313=？",
        "answer": 0.6492782094178575
    },
    {
        "question": "5227÷2064=？",
        "answer": 0.40354280714257684
    },
    {
        "question": "12477×10661=？",
        "answer": 8.123908118434896
    },
    {
        "question": "712×16345=？",
        "answer": 7.0658649185532445
    },
    {
        "question": "1×8819=？",
        "answer": 3.945419342603063
    },
    {
        "question": "12×4506=？",
        "answer": 4.732972433435437
    },
    {
        "question": "54348÷282=？",
        "answer": 2.284934458411221
    },
    {
        "question": "62260475÷757=？",
        "answer": 4.915116550195155
    },
    {
        "question": "13×2640=？",
        "answer": 4.535547279176668
    },
    {
        "question": "20727×553=？",
        "answer": 7.059261578708254
    },
    {
        "question": "489×1150141=？",
        "answer": 8.750059944493103
    },
    {
        "question": "8966325÷2596=？",
        "answer": 3.5383097884434394
    },
    {
        "question": "1668÷850=？",
        "answer": 0.29277712058742716
    },
    {
        "question": "112346×264=？",
        "answer": 7.47216154115188
    },
    {
        "question": "192529÷27123=？",
        "answer": 0.8511584311354453
    },
    {
        "question": "16×660=？",
        "answer": 4.023663918197793
    },
    {
        "question": "2485×382282=？",
        "answer": 8.977710242527792
    },
    {
        "question": "68×22199=？",
        "answer": 6.178842323901757
    },
    {
        "question": "3613590×268=？",
        "answer": 8.986073669747162
    },
    {
        "question": "32×5635=？",
        "answer": 5.256043898702031
    },
    {
        "question": "133756018÷179536=？",
        "answer": 2.8721617860457287
    },
    {
        "question": "43960×262=？",
        "answer": 7.061358975071198
    },
    {
        "question": "1×222=？",
        "answer": 2.346352974450639
    },
    {
        "question": "67185867÷21347630=？",
        "answer": 0.4979282589432437
    },
    {
        "question": "13099×3255=？",
        "answer": 7.629789135044031
    },
    {
        "question": "179352764÷3008701=？",
        "answer": 1.7753290435845386
    },
    {
        "question": "492276511÷727047=？",
        "answer": 2.8306466271215367
    },
    {
        "question": "3637379÷491180=？",
        "answer": 0.8695478803463375
    },
    {
        "question": "1420×221=？",
        "answer": 5.496680618068167
    },
    {
        "question": "31×6016=？",
        "answer": 5.270669521417859
    },
    {
        "question": "297535869÷65055=？",
        "answer": 3.660258647750074
    },
    {
        "question": "12793÷5242=？",
        "answer": 0.38747538327609177
    },
    {
        "question": "155132×1005=？",
        "answer": 8.192867453315891
    },
    {
        "question": "3598÷920=？",
        "answer": 0.5922733316639773
    },
    {
        "question": "316162586÷67184487=？",
        "answer": 0.6726414697880715
    },
    {
        "question": "10106÷493=？",
        "answer": 1.3117323746249816
    },
    {
        "question": "408270÷4100=？",
        "answer": 1.998163612076321
    },
    {
        "question": "1×536=？",
        "answer": 2.72916478969277
    },
    {
        "question": "637×224341=？",
        "answer": 8.155048083745166
    },
    {
        "question": "52×313=？",
        "answer": 4.211547681181248
    },
    {
        "question": "616429030÷1543769=？",
        "answer": 2.6013007673820105
    },
    {
        "question": "129×11012=？",
        "answer": 6.152455913020542
    },
    {
        "question": "453943369÷2199=？",
        "answer": 5.3147764471419805
    },
    {
        "question": "19×5432226=？",
        "answer": 8.013731430802443
    },
    {
        "question": "84888991÷257=？",
        "answer": 5.5189182482087205
    },
    {
        "question": "155273531÷101352904=？",
        "answer": 0.18526123242725362
    },
    {
        "question": "89107402÷18636340=？",
        "answer": 0.6795531565530355
    },
    {
        "question": "622×15780=？",
        "answer": 6.99189738356422
    },
    {
        "question": "112×266=？",
        "answer": 4.474099659301249
    },
    {
        "question": "21440×15918=？",
        "answer": 8.533113281386704
    },
    {
        "question": "5295÷614=？",
        "answer": 0.935697593302336
    },
    {
        "question": "1×8246=？",
        "answer": 3.9162433304653397
    },
    {
        "question": "355×10820=？",
        "answer": 6.584455613825645
    },
    {
        "question": "3817×751=？",
        "answer": 6.4573620969532675
    },
    {
        "question": "5×1922692=？",
        "answer": 6.982879723616768
    },
    {
        "question": "7724×59508=？",
        "answer": 8.662417619446092
    },
    {
        "question": "399×13716=？",
        "answer": 6.738200372129655
    },
    {
        "question": "66234330÷3587432=？",
        "answer": 1.266299469781415
    },
    {
        "question": "60×27495=？",
        "answer": 6.217404974401542
    },
    {
        "question": "10248÷844=？",
        "answer": 1.0842966701109749
    },
    {
        "question": "134003585÷1082930=？",
        "answer": 2.092516032231312
    },
    {
        "question": "671×50777=？",
        "answer": 7.532389558535499
    },
    {
        "question": "9×6968=？",
        "answer": 4.797350651438932
    },
    {
        "question": "134×8508=？",
        "answer": 6.056932279595499
    },
    {
        "question": "912143×516=？",
        "answer": 8.672712631230313
    },
    {
        "question": "1×137374=？",
        "answer": 5.137904544040737
    },
    {
        "question": "23×24929=？",
        "answer": 5.758432693615132
    },
    {
        "question": "1262÷397=？",
        "answer": 0.5022688481450005
    },
    {
        "question": "112031×4830=？",
        "answer": 8.733285343297425
    },
    {
        "question": "259×470490=？",
        "answer": 8.085850161257977
    },
    {
        "question": "1343002÷366=？",
        "answer": 3.5645955740265887
    },
    {
        "question": "8×14571425=？",
        "answer": 8.066592012294866
    },
    {
        "question": "2415×1801=？",
        "answer": 6.638430847907064
    },
    {
        "question": "4147493÷206194=？",
        "answer": 1.3035096380305025
    },
    {
        "question": "2756920÷108235=？",
        "answer": 1.4060564424977071
    },
    {
        "question": "631268÷513=？",
        "answer": 3.0900964096809953
    },
    {
        "question": "708323÷92444=？",
        "answer": 0.8843526151382259
    },
    {
        "question": "79670643÷1215=？",
        "answer": 4.81672204431753
    },
    {
        "question": "185937866÷204426=？",
        "answer": 2.95883171138703
    },
    {
        "question": "152576620÷7609=？",
        "answer": 4.302160405724708
    },
    {
        "question": "10490652÷15774=？",
        "answer": 2.8228606441918966
    },
    {
        "question": "1475×326502=？",
        "answer": 8.682677866220232
    },
    {
        "question": "430804÷16422=？",
        "answer": 1.418853679259899
    },
    {
        "question": "328201÷3403=？",
        "answer": 1.9842779508809245
    },
    {
        "question": "464231232÷57430=？",
        "answer": 3.907595538772341
    },
    {
        "question": "5669÷1293=？",
        "answer": 0.6419079321105761
    },
    {
        "question": "12266×32075=？",
        "answer": 8.59486962539844
    },
    {
        "question": "1337×58160=？",
        "answer": 7.890755805112966
    },
    {
        "question": "40092×2627=？",
        "answer": 8.022517794471826
    },
    {
        "question": "2×28191150=？",
        "answer": 7.75114278804737
    },
    {
        "question": "8×3026=？",
        "answer": 4.3839589106791115
    },
    {
        "question": "16953936÷1092060=？",
        "answer": 1.1910240393437541
    },
    {
        "question": "444282454÷250=？",
        "answer": 6.249719153361433
    },
    {
        "question": "35×6954572=？",
        "answer": 8.386338452041704
    },
    {
        "question": "6913101÷58760=？",
        "answer": 2.0705911148274647
    },
    {
        "question": "5079÷2908=？",
        "answer": 0.24218381064159747
    },
    {
        "question": "1×703=？",
        "answer": 2.846955325019824
    },
    {
        "question": "73258983÷5719316=？",
        "answer": 1.1075167928116203
    },
    {
        "question": "78×109753=？",
        "answer": 6.93251100281775
    },
    {
        "question": "12100619÷1088238=？",
        "answer": 1.0460837000710068
    },
    {
        "question": "53634892÷570=？",
        "answer": 4.97357255478512
    },
    {
        "question": "386×198058=？",
        "answer": 7.8833796938795535
    },
    {
        "question": "72×6502083=？",
        "answer": 8.670385005456637
    },
    {
        "question": "96137÷9891=？",
        "answer": 0.9876503637790529
    },
    {
        "question": "64398×12151=？",
        "answer": 8.893484400609356
    },
    {
        "question": "90447751÷994963=？",
        "answer": 1.958590841716348
    },
    {
        "question": "26139×3683=？",
        "answer": 7.983490687608651
    },
    {
        "question": "213144×240=？",
        "answer": 7.708884353484495
    },
    {
        "question": "332599÷239=？",
        "answer": 3.1435230381772907
    },
    {
        "question": "1×2459196=？",
        "answer": 6.390793143755483
    },
    {
        "question": "97140489÷6680=？",
        "answer": 4.162623822882051
    },
    {
        "question": "216840907÷2110=？",
        "answer": 5.011858759877325
    },
    {
        "question": "39111033÷3593252=？",
        "answer": 1.0368116107050371
    },
    {
        "question": "18×1557=？",
        "answer": 4.447561117671427
    },
    {
        "question": "3×91518=？",
        "answer": 5.438627775363819
    },
    {
        "question": "72×245706=？",
        "answer": 7.247748258263712
    },
    {
        "question": "1240×22321=？",
        "answer": 7.442135332629988
    },
    {
        "question": "2368×3481=？",
        "answer": 6.916085721335171
    },
    {
        "question": "1286×3238=？",
        "answer": 6.619517813005558
    },
    {
        "question": "693275÷1997=？",
        "answer": 2.540527474636006
    },
    {
        "question": "47422095÷575=？",
        "answer": 4.9163128915160526
    },
    {
        "question": "1×20466835=？",
        "answer": 7.3110506883728315
    },
    {
        "question": "18×218=？",
        "answer": 3.593728998707911
    },
    {
        "question": "63617844÷235083=？",
        "answer": 2.432357722535231
    },
    {
        "question": "4139×15205=？",
        "answer": 7.798881850880911
    },
    {
        "question": "21013÷3838=？",
        "answer": 0.7383830901186252
    },
    {
        "question": "11435÷8081=？",
        "answer": 0.15077106217691105
    },
    {
        "question": "874889998÷4657545=？",
        "answer": 2.2737963919468727
    },
    {
        "question": "2957÷352=？",
        "answer": 0.9243086610479866
    },
    {
        "question": "772×18347=？",
        "answer": 7.151182361296593
    },
    {
        "question": "1×292644=？",
        "answer": 5.466339624320338
    },
    {
        "question": "45×19482384=？",
        "answer": 8.942854612862883
    },
    {
        "question": "98635663÷241092=？",
        "answer": 2.6118511684201287
    },
    {
        "question": "42754×966=？",
        "answer": 7.615953879319713
    },
    {
        "question": "7499×1089=？",
        "answer": 6.912031233355816
    },
    {
        "question": "1×4140=？",
        "answer": 3.617000341120899
    },
    {
        "question": "56715×16023=？",
        "answer": 8.958441769107017
    },
    {
        "question": "1574×701=？",
        "answer": 6.042722745989704
    },
    {
        "question": "470403÷585=？",
        "answer": 2.9053142167122856
    },
    {
        "question": "9257÷624=？",
        "answer": 1.1712856740468605
    },
    {
        "question": "89663÷57219=？",
        "answer": 0.1950730021698593
    },
    {
        "question": "3043108÷1890=？",
        "answer": 3.206855561583453
    },
    {
        "question": "1786452÷5179=？",
        "answer": 2.5377454406623587
    },
    {
        "question": "933÷361=？",
        "answer": 0.412374441840842
    },
    {
        "question": "732814073÷84204=？",
        "answer": 3.93966107837751
    },
    {
        "question": "7×357=？",
        "answer": 3.39776625612645
    },
    {
        "question": "4255414÷3396624=？",
        "answer": 0.09789434411019823
    },
    {
        "question": "1192×22409=？",
        "answer": 7.4266987320119275
    },
    {
        "question": "18×50338=？",
        "answer": 5.95716846152386
    },
    {
        "question": "4×4269=？",
        "answer": 4.232386146131909
    },
    {
        "question": "38511×989=？",
        "answer": 7.580781087520437
    },
    {
        "question": "5×533=？",
        "answer": 3.425697213362591
    },
    {
        "question": "2×1387=？",
        "answer": 3.443106456737266
    },
    {
        "question": "640105934÷8615=？",
        "answer": 4.870996571488154
    },
    {
        "question": "78796650÷766610=？",
        "answer": 2.0119332739856124
    },
    {
        "question": "159×12037=？",
        "answer": 6.2819153848475695
    },
    {
        "question": "3508÷336=？",
        "answer": 1.0187203073041589
    },
    {
        "question": "11954225÷3873=？",
        "answer": 3.4894739287912206
    },
    {
        "question": "6×19844761=？",
        "answer": 8.075797123241026
    },
    {
        "question": "14181÷12434=？",
        "answer": 0.05709599399043931
    },
    {
        "question": "532801438÷22846=？",
        "answer": 4.367755215840735
    },
    {
        "question": "785877÷18995=？",
        "answer": 1.6167152807168874
    },
    {
        "question": "2×6322=？",
        "answer": 4.101884487167542
    },
    {
        "question": "20×7756112=？",
        "answer": 8.19067406742583
    },
    {
        "question": "3254874÷205510=？",
        "answer": 1.1997012219301837
    },
    {
        "question": "442067÷315=？",
        "answer": 3.1471775425394446
    },
    {
        "question": "922957×301=？",
        "answer": 8.443747963577788
    },
    {
        "question": "3592976÷755=？",
        "answer": 3.6775073646285152
    },
    {
        "question": "237834531÷4967071=？",
        "answer": 1.680174541814298
    },
    {
        "question": "905088057÷887043506=？",
        "answer": 0.008745913449859461
    },
    {
        "question": "30948×26335=？",
        "answer": 8.911165910879062
    },
    {
        "question": "1436939÷15806=？",
        "answer": 1.9586163545354054
    },
    {
        "question": "810×287817=？",
        "answer": 8.367601460974539
    },
    {
        "question": "4×11168=？",
        "answer": 4.6500353966070485
    },
    {
        "question": "9×946=？",
        "answer": 3.9301336458411176
    },
    {
        "question": "732637÷316057=？",
        "answer": 0.3651234343567336
    },
    {
        "question": "2×10729803=？",
        "answer": 7.331621744023377
    },
    {
        "question": "77827÷3823=？",
        "answer": 1.3087259919883125
    },
    {
        "question": "610×566=？",
        "answer": 5.538146266199038
    },
    {
        "question": "16017×2677=？",
        "answer": 7.632229546764504
    },
    {
        "question": "22×1234103=？",
        "answer": 7.433774088870217
    },
    {
        "question": "12×23680614=？",
        "answer": 8.453574204797615
    },
    {
        "question": "3963454÷8288=？",
        "answer": 2.6796240797190016
    },
    {
        "question": "6031702÷2290285=？",
        "answer": 0.4205503480751983
    },
    {
        "question": "247022÷469=？",
        "answer": 2.721562790921603
    },
    {
        "question": "160948×4791=？",
        "answer": 8.887111755207764
    },
    {
        "question": "155551×589=？",
        "answer": 7.9619881022156616
    },
    {
        "question": "60281×1697=？",
        "answer": 8.009862290520317
    },
    {
        "question": "116908121÷17087=？",
        "answer": 3.8351788609603927
    },
    {
        "question": "11423670÷368827=？",
        "answer": 1.4909829428838233
    },
    {
        "question": "1882×207542=？",
        "answer": 8.591725616633209
    },
    {
        "question": "627192÷1129=？",
        "answer": 2.744706568245653
    },
    {
        "question": "4249720÷147114=？",
        "answer": 1.4607063127433024
    },
    {
        "question": "420×2280343=？",
        "answer": 8.981249467136742
    },
    {
        "question": "14079200÷9571837=？",
        "answer": 0.16758268393246595
    },
    {
        "question": "168267×379=？",
        "answer": 7.8046381618134335
    },
    {
        "question": "609×329=？",
        "answer": 5.30181319058285
    },
    {
        "question": "1×205869=？",
        "answer": 5.313590954959288
    },
    {
        "question": "10870×816=？",
        "answer": 6.947919702840156
    },
    {
        "question": "1388966÷241129=？",
        "answer": 0.7604421698664472
    },
    {
        "question": "26×14389149=？",
        "answer": 8.573008457714732
    },
    {
        "question": "1717344÷814228=？",
        "answer": 0.3241112641114479
    },
    {
        "question": "1162138÷2149=？",
        "answer": 2.7330212866420096
    },
    {
        "question": "130996÷3780=？",
        "answer": 1.5397662347158674
    },
    {
        "question": "45×1964=？",
        "answer": 4.946353997226274
    },
    {
        "question": "23366÷2143=？",
        "answer": 1.037562201315656
    },
    {
        "question": "50069804÷492=？",
        "answer": 5.0076107885739285
    },
    {
        "question": "1×74716=？",
        "answer": 4.873413613430447
    },
    {
        "question": "740528÷3251=？",
        "answer": 2.357524514719096
    },
    {
        "question": "1×2613=？",
        "answer": 3.4171394097273255
    },
    {
        "question": "115904068÷764931=？",
        "answer": 2.180476417367364
    },
    {
        "question": "395365850÷1479=？",
        "answer": 5.4270309801131225
    },
    {
        "question": "297×5609=？",
        "answer": 6.221641889326729
    },
    {
        "question": "30930374÷208=？",
        "answer": 5.172321836419474
    },
    {
        "question": "21832356÷189153=？",
        "answer": 2.062287370686687
    },
    {
        "question": "491375186÷294=？",
        "answer": 6.2230658908092895
    },
    {
        "question": "163041×882=？",
        "answer": 8.15776541551565
    },
    {
        "question": "72456÷397=？",
        "answer": 2.2612838479715887
    },
    {
        "question": "960805649÷10456=？",
        "answer": 4.963269973238594
    },
    {
        "question": "1012÷415=？",
        "answer": 0.3871324157916876
    },
    {
        "question": "225954÷222=？",
        "answer": 3.0076670594774852
    },
    {
        "question": "24183650÷26028=？",
        "answer": 2.9680810507883675
    },
    {
        "question": "219147÷51955=？",
        "answer": 0.6251081806236187
    },
    {
        "question": "453991219÷2564=？",
        "answer": 5.248129432061589
    },
    {
        "question": "3894÷598=？",
        "answer": 0.813694763195602
    },
    {
        "question": "2898204÷55385=？",
        "answer": 1.7187367914655431
    },
    {
        "question": "19982689÷1471=？",
        "answer": 4.133041256572031
    },
    {
        "question": "112492620÷117832=？",
        "answer": 2.979860782632687
    },
    {
        "question": "624÷352=？",
        "answer": 0.24864192620429296
    },
    {
        "question": "129243798÷93822=？",
        "answer": 3.13910502530233
    },
    {
        "question": "3×97461529=？",
        "answer": 8.46595447513508
    },
    {
        "question": "3×5276535=？",
        "answer": 7.199470077941279
    },
    {
        "question": "110598370÷1472=？",
        "answer": 4.875840916377489
    },
    {
        "question": "128106999÷3929358=？",
        "answer": 1.5132512588812495
    },
    {
        "question": "514631×515=？",
        "answer": 8.423303172445715
    },
    {
        "question": "31×9103175=？",
        "answer": 8.450554585549733
    },
    {
        "question": "154918÷5232=？",
        "answer": 1.4714341462680993
    },
    {
        "question": "103423866÷2546812=？",
        "answer": 1.608623880240291
    },
    {
        "question": "480×26609=？",
        "answer": 7.106269790895692
    },
    {
        "question": "29348÷225=？",
        "answer": 2.115395992291374
    },
    {
        "question": "4×1040162=？",
        "answer": 6.619160975075791
    },
    {
        "question": "22337÷3261=？",
        "answer": 0.8356740454018103
    },
    {
        "question": "18×6027061=？",
        "answer": 8.035378092096243
    },
    {
        "question": "1868697÷326=？",
        "answer": 3.758321288311495
    },
    {
        "question": "39725×1641=？",
        "answer": 7.81417248693251
    },
    {
        "question": "3862×90679=？",
        "answer": 8.54431899156309
    },
    {
        "question": "63680×496=？",
        "answer": 7.49948473121981
    },
    {
        "question": "217×21458=？",
        "answer": 6.668048974803666
    },
    {
        "question": "55518574÷7149785=？",
        "answer": 0.890145320293803
    },
    {
        "question": "93696271÷11084672=？",
        "answer": 0.9269994601401214
    },
    {
        "question": "4572×12891=？",
        "answer": 7.77039283012681
    },
    {
        "question": "5×1820=？",
        "answer": 3.9590413923210934
    },
    {
        "question": "957245469÷208866100=？",
        "answer": 0.6611553617869587
    },
    {
        "question": "2×8889=？",
        "answer": 4.249882901863694
    },
    {
        "question": "114502×8345=？",
        "answer": 8.980239413554735
    },
    {
        "question": "39259×7892=？",
        "answer": 8.491126309694039
    },
    {
        "question": "82710÷936=？",
        "answer": 1.946282172087331
    },
    {
        "question": "1328251÷145143=？",
        "answer": 0.9614840561604445
    },
    {
        "question": "16579÷366=？",
        "answer": 1.6560772461528135
    },
    {
        "question": "41×1059821=？",
        "answer": 7.638016377383763
    },
    {
        "question": "202×58928=？",
        "answer": 7.075673070957461
    },
    {
        "question": "1393÷253=？",
        "answer": 0.7408305952481455
    },
    {
        "question": "259064×492=？",
        "answer": 8.105372169602648
    },
    {
        "question": "315×355735=？",
        "answer": 8.04943715037566
    },
    {
        "question": "767905257÷13284=？",
        "answer": 4.761978773807921
    },
    {
        "question": "61×358=？",
        "answer": 4.339212861654642
    },
    {
        "question": "1918×2177=？",
        "answer": 6.620707031875739
    },
    {
        "question": "34173÷353=？",
        "answer": 1.9859084011912995
    },
    {
        "question": "513971×686=？",
        "answer": 8.547262731014708
    },
    {
        "question": "207×123380=？",
        "answer": 7.407215111364878
    },
    {
        "question": "13×327196=？",
        "answer": 6.628751338050174
    },
    {
        "question": "42495594÷425616=？",
        "answer": 1.9993259583116088
    },
    {
        "question": "287×1640379=？",
        "answer": 8.672826097582005
    },
    {
        "question": "10744÷403=？",
        "answer": 1.4258609535195494
    },
    {
        "question": "3943÷242=？",
        "answer": 1.212011411092792
    },
    {
        "question": "7×7077=？",
        "answer": 4.694947235619515
    },
    {
        "question": "59841687÷4498797=？",
        "answer": 1.1239074313843114
    },
    {
        "question": "4×33927181=？",
        "answer": 8.132607767064874
    },
    {
        "question": "23×17921=？",
        "answer": 5.615090075850661
    },
    {
        "question": "74780996÷672852=？",
        "answer": 2.0458716975242837
    },
    {
        "question": "78286001÷3107=？",
        "answer": 4.40134285577614
    },
    {
        "question": "102653×3215=？",
        "answer": 8.518552623265023
    },
    {
        "question": "89530905÷888982=？",
        "answer": 2.0030800069514547
    },
    {
        "question": "388114×1759=？",
        "answer": 8.834225148296637
    },
    {
        "question": "6×627885=？",
        "answer": 6.576031358390166
    },
    {
        "question": "1×296683241=？",
        "answer": 8.472293014645837
    },
    {
        "question": "111657010÷1309217=？",
        "answer": 1.9308743580176997
    },
    {
        "question": "746462×417=？",
        "answer": 8.493143759050385
    },
    {
        "question": "29189774÷2633=？",
        "answer": 4.0447798733970926
    },
    {
        "question": "620250051÷30857=？",
        "answer": 4.303213108144651
    },
    {
        "question": "26095×37561=？",
        "answer": 8.99129444731752
    },
    {
        "question": "79665×2078=？",
        "answer": 8.218913103695977
    },
    {
        "question": "19×2094290=？",
        "answer": 7.5997904199763635
    },
    {
        "question": "241×959=？",
        "answer": 5.363835649745532
    },
    {
        "question": "13×1050883=？",
        "answer": 7.135497718874681
    },
    {
        "question": "74040308÷7985218=？",
        "answer": 0.9671814396359109
    },
    {
        "question": "5000×1153=？",
        "answer": 6.760799311630718
    },
    {
        "question": "19429×1481=？",
        "answer": 7.459005506796845
    },
    {
        "question": "3×1041=？",
        "answer": 3.4945719842301988
    },
    {
        "question": "101919300÷7997889=？",
        "answer": 1.1052810597763556
    },
    {
        "question": "62×1511414=？",
        "answer": 7.971775130202947
    },
    {
        "question": "2×28419916=？",
        "answer": 7.754652785624525
    },
    {
        "question": "521×418=？",
        "answer": 5.33801400507456
    },
    {
        "question": "1323×862=？",
        "answer": 6.0570671100122135
    },
    {
        "question": "205525÷138157=？",
        "answer": 0.17249176267093438
    },
    {
        "question": "19×241579=？",
        "answer": 6.6618127801547855
    },
    {
        "question": "34712÷3031=？",
        "answer": 1.0588937007535333
    },
    {
        "question": "252066÷33085=？",
        "answer": 0.8818831307023889
    },
    {
        "question": "802795×650=？",
        "answer": 8.717518015576426
    },
    {
        "question": "245×1592678=？",
        "answer": 8.591294065464725
    },
    {
        "question": "4×446114=？",
        "answer": 6.251505843861985
    },
    {
        "question": "110125231÷14206=？",
        "answer": 3.8894150220663164
    },
    {
        "question": "1×289=？",
        "answer": 2.4608978427565478
    },
    {
        "question": "26587÷8482=？",
        "answer": 0.49617106744218464
    },
    {
        "question": "1192259÷9668=？",
        "answer": 2.091033967739413
    },
    {
        "question": "33054656÷19869601=？",
        "answer": 0.22104349565351922
    },
    {
        "question": "110005÷33178=？",
        "answer": 0.5205622225566369
    },
    {
        "question": "30×696142=？",
        "answer": 7.319819091350706
    },
    {
        "question": "2×88186=？",
        "answer": 5.246429639692092
    },
    {
        "question": "107×2011042=？",
        "answer": 8.332804918484719
    },
    {
        "question": "336×820=？",
        "answer": 5.44015312977356
    },
    {
        "question": "212511912÷946307=？",
        "answer": 2.351351226063871
    },
    {
        "question": "132×18491=？",
        "answer": 6.387534329803546
    },
    {
        "question": "99113318÷86192384=？",
        "answer": 0.060663122131263514
    },
    {
        "question": "4156333÷576298=？",
        "answer": 0.8580632229919527
    },
    {
        "question": "6×1917314=？",
        "answer": 7.060844493830367
    },
    {
        "question": "31740÷286=？",
        "answer": 2.0452408892897864
    },
    {
        "question": "614×85524=？",
        "answer": 7.7202563759857465
    },
    {
        "question": "1552959÷1524=？",
        "answer": 3.008175022975584
    },
    {
        "question": "1156×1659=？",
        "answer": 6.282804220108871
    },
    {
        "question": "7831425÷2838720=？",
        "answer": 0.44071823556872963
    },
    {
        "question": "11×2750597=？",
        "answer": 7.480819650140043
    },
    {
        "question": "6×9823=？",
        "answer": 4.770395394430415
    },
    {
        "question": "2×22506=？",
        "answer": 4.653328310198348
    },
    {
        "question": "4182÷1326=？",
        "answer": 0.49884050441289873
    },
    {
        "question": "109221818÷219=？",
        "answer": 5.697865286262511
    },
    {
        "question": "681×211770=？",
        "answer": 8.159011548528131
    },
    {
        "question": "5632×132678=？",
        "answer": 8.873461562437106
    },
    {
        "question": "590352110÷21207=？",
        "answer": 4.444631883426049
    },
    {
        "question": "5×14259764=？",
        "answer": 7.85308234231008
    },
    {
        "question": "4936÷1456=？",
        "answer": 0.5302137760481669
    },
    {
        "question": "4411384÷3431703=？",
        "answer": 0.10906516930378558
    },
    {
        "question": "648÷538=？",
        "answer": 0.0807927302042042
    },
    {
        "question": "2668×6057=？",
        "answer": 7.208443398907813
    },
    {
        "question": "1×6390264=？",
        "answer": 6.805518800470584
    },
    {
        "question": "8144×5295=？",
        "answer": 7.634703729436187
    },
    {
        "question": "3421÷256=？",
        "answer": 1.125913108873213
    },
    {
        "question": "6050015÷52015=？",
        "answer": 2.065627848590479
    },
    {
        "question": "58290809÷16602250=？",
        "answer": 0.5454331335322719
    },
    {
        "question": "168×505=？",
        "answer": 4.928600659844524
    },
    {
        "question": "601×275=？",
        "answer": 5.218207165833002
    },
    {
        "question": "204×595=？",
        "answer": 5.084147133154448
    },
    {
        "question": "621×6949=？",
        "answer": 6.635013911856031
    },
    {
        "question": "767140÷823=？",
        "answer": 2.969474792985913
    },
    {
        "question": "19×8038421=？",
        "answer": 8.183924348913457
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1261005=？",
        "answer": 6.100716808593783
    },
    {
        "question": "495×339733=？",
        "answer": 8.225742933091862
    },
    {
        "question": "891550÷348542=？",
        "answer": 0.4078905854117562
    },
    {
        "question": "769469581÷388251586=？",
        "answer": 0.29707821730343614
    },
    {
        "question": "398922÷15545=？",
        "answer": 1.4092972613348376
    },
    {
        "question": "3×226210336=？",
        "answer": 8.8316336995408
    },
    {
        "question": "3901415÷5830=？",
        "answer": 2.825553594636051
    },
    {
        "question": "12×3440=？",
        "answer": 4.615739688619155
    },
    {
        "question": "1×527=？",
        "answer": 2.7218106152125467
    },
    {
        "question": "249779×1475=？",
        "answer": 8.566347942873131
    },
    {
        "question": "182771266÷50021=？",
        "answer": 3.5627555503467345
    },
    {
        "question": "188×714761=？",
        "answer": 8.128318697032833
    },
    {
        "question": "9×1727=？",
        "answer": 4.191534847006784
    },
    {
        "question": "1×111474083=？",
        "answer": 8.047173908474635
    },
    {
        "question": "24×63020=？",
        "answer": 6.1796896405495865
    },
    {
        "question": "33298×10035=？",
        "answer": 8.52393552579383
    },
    {
        "question": "27996÷1761=？",
        "answer": 1.2013366288741005
    },
    {
        "question": "16580×1918=？",
        "answer": 7.5024331290488995
    },
    {
        "question": "3×683=？",
        "answer": 3.311541958401195
    },
    {
        "question": "38445521÷1676=？",
        "answer": 4.360571736389598
    },
    {
        "question": "44194÷856=？",
        "answer": 1.7128895466681053
    },
    {
        "question": "594×882=？",
        "answer": 5.719255030113013
    },
    {
        "question": "1147244÷1234=？",
        "answer": 2.9683406353478743
    },
    {
        "question": "18677405÷210166=？",
        "answer": 1.9487540775408871
    },
    {
        "question": "580×236=？",
        "answer": 5.136339996533044
    },
    {
        "question": "66944339÷860833=？",
        "answer": 1.8907949504444597
    },
    {
        "question": "1423×1640=？",
        "answer": 6.368048748131982
    },
    {
        "question": "2×5600=？",
        "answer": 4.049218022670182
    },
    {
        "question": "737586211÷46404575=？",
        "answer": 1.2012519895832194
    },
    {
        "question": "27770×18183=？",
        "answer": 8.70324141847993
    },
    {
        "question": "40112÷2228=？",
        "answer": 1.25535913011245
    },
    {
        "question": "107685571÷820=？",
        "answer": 5.118343662846609
    },
    {
        "question": "7328093÷48380=？",
        "answer": 2.18032510825109
    },
    {
        "question": "1×907=？",
        "answer": 2.957607287060095
    },
    {
        "question": "28079×7036=？",
        "answer": 8.295707467640083
    },
    {
        "question": "1523410×410=？",
        "answer": 8.795600658791441
    },
    {
        "question": "5348÷390=？",
        "answer": 1.1371267915634475
    },
    {
        "question": "40×52826=？",
        "answer": 6.3249077183560765
    },
    {
        "question": "1960×141436=？",
        "answer": 8.442816036768034
    },
    {
        "question": "126784310÷4963=？",
        "answer": 4.407321236218763
    },
    {
        "question": "40258649÷6034134=？",
        "answer": 0.8242442464175453
    },
    {
        "question": "1149662÷43931=？",
        "answer": 1.417799087569002
    },
    {
        "question": "173×297049=？",
        "answer": 7.7108741978141895
    },
    {
        "question": "963689÷335771=？",
        "answer": 0.4578937176630395
    },
    {
        "question": "775147797÷249=？",
        "answer": 6.493185169993623
    },
    {
        "question": "1159968÷1513=？",
        "answer": 2.884607080501048
    },
    {
        "question": "420×2830=？",
        "answer": 6.0750357259221905
    },
    {
        "question": "11850646÷39354=？",
        "answer": 2.4787531438780315
    },
    {
        "question": "86×6557=？",
        "answer": 5.751203634910083
    },
    {
        "question": "1642818÷583559=？",
        "answer": 0.4495046812784723
    },
    {
        "question": "8875342÷314274=？",
        "answer": 1.4508766438678082
    },
    {
        "question": "6×3623=？",
        "answer": 4.337219584418181
    },
    {
        "question": "1×15251=？",
        "answer": 4.183298321075812
    },
    {
        "question": "702×41993=？",
        "answer": 7.4695140140815175
    },
    {
        "question": "463300704÷282365=？",
        "answer": 3.215052096533044
    },
    {
        "question": "122×331=？",
        "answer": 4.606187824450467
    },
    {
        "question": "124275×2470=？",
        "answer": 8.487080725070703
    },
    {
        "question": "18878×616=？",
        "answer": 7.065536693918169
    },
    {
        "question": "17692360÷4217=？",
        "answer": 3.6227821666950715
    },
    {
        "question": "464006÷5109=？",
        "answer": 1.9581876937132292
    },
    {
        "question": "15×9364=？",
        "answer": 5.147552664080268
    },
    {
        "question": "68×280931=？",
        "answer": 7.281108577810631
    },
    {
        "question": "909075470÷1803=？",
        "answer": 5.702604212433556
    },
    {
        "question": "5×13053078=？",
        "answer": 7.81468293752716
    },
    {
        "question": "1185504÷2751=？",
        "answer": 2.634412433276693
    },
    {
        "question": "98822÷39276=？",
        "answer": 0.400726387715825
    },
    {
        "question": "36036÷12229=？",
        "answer": 0.46934563324941814
    },
    {
        "question": "3494760÷21009=？",
        "answer": 2.221011975193
    },
    {
        "question": "319×13573=？",
        "answer": 6.636466532150143
    },
    {
        "question": "50547÷17343=？",
        "answer": 0.46457116091417144
    },
    {
        "question": "300×1399=？",
        "answer": 5.62293896921149
    },
    {
        "question": "1×486262212=？",
        "answer": 8.686870521351995
    },
    {
        "question": "67314787÷5289863=？",
        "answer": 1.10466605135389
    },
    {
        "question": "16447388÷2934=？",
        "answer": 3.748636828203845
    },
    {
        "question": "2920879÷573=？",
        "answer": 3.7073589443451693
    },
    {
        "question": "31137÷2497=？",
        "answer": 1.0958582243197692
    },
    {
        "question": "8733846÷538=？",
        "answer": 4.2104232542660975
    },
    {
        "question": "479552405÷1976933=？",
        "answer": 2.3848441224194237
    },
    {
        "question": "97×8040=？",
        "answer": 5.892027783014696
    },
    {
        "question": "7531×50787=？",
        "answer": 8.58260520731071
    },
    {
        "question": "315510÷3825=？",
        "answer": 1.916381689149135
    },
    {
        "question": "37×4155363=？",
        "answer": 8.186810692502615
    },
    {
        "question": "448×1347210=？",
        "answer": 8.780713311824073
    },
    {
        "question": "33×1172554=？",
        "answer": 7.587646792426625
    },
    {
        "question": "26×1181=？",
        "answer": 4.487223245584333
    },
    {
        "question": "4×1938=？",
        "answer": 3.889413764042709
    },
    {
        "question": "79724771÷7173362=？",
        "answer": 1.0458705326224493
    },
    {
        "question": "70026×492=？",
        "answer": 7.53722442221057
    },
    {
        "question": "124168÷6635=？",
        "answer": 1.2721687587040622
    },
    {
        "question": "6×187737=？",
        "answer": 6.051701124029303
    },
    {
        "question": "1×7521=？",
        "answer": 3.876275588677879
    },
    {
        "question": "354830589÷48010=？",
        "answer": 3.868689346174948
    },
    {
        "question": "31×1350=？",
        "answer": 4.621695462329279
    },
    {
        "question": "490898÷72919=？",
        "answer": 0.8281505585398542
    },
    {
        "question": "220055÷85732=？",
        "answer": 0.40938828558424983
    },
    {
        "question": "93176251÷11226925=？",
        "answer": 0.9190444109675389
    },
    {
        "question": "1540389÷844532=？",
        "answer": 0.26101429865401315
    },
    {
        "question": "1056×32013=？",
        "answer": 7.528990292822899
    },
    {
        "question": "23×265486=？",
        "answer": 6.78576946018063
    },
    {
        "question": "53996514÷51576497=？",
        "answer": 0.019913880636861194
    },
    {
        "question": "59256151÷550818=？",
        "answer": 2.0317253143565104
    },
    {
        "question": "18164979÷162256=？",
        "answer": 2.0490341347518792
    },
    {
        "question": "1182×252361=？",
        "answer": 8.474639716208099
    },
    {
        "question": "20216111÷445154=？",
        "answer": 1.657187333336395
    },
    {
        "question": "4×202387=？",
        "answer": 5.908242604191445
    },
    {
        "question": "19×37568=？",
        "answer": 5.85357167618433
    },
    {
        "question": "375053464÷604=？",
        "answer": 5.793056242347
    },
    {
        "question": "58089273÷17660=？",
        "answer": 3.5171052419779385
    },
    {
        "question": "286723÷2676=？",
        "answer": 2.029976422959312
    },
    {
        "question": "4×6630404=？",
        "answer": 7.423599982722965
    },
    {
        "question": "29753541÷2227229=？",
        "answer": 1.1257737862107149
    },
    {
        "question": "19807003÷332=？",
        "answer": 4.775680683655386
    },
    {
        "question": "3821862÷1363165=？",
        "answer": 0.44772657465380833
    },
    {
        "question": "376350÷5633=？",
        "answer": 1.824852169134941
    },
    {
        "question": "961998002÷56179=？",
        "answer": 4.233600165654742
    },
    {
        "question": "94419÷214=？",
        "answer": 2.6446456231190414
    },
    {
        "question": "228708637÷132797928=？",
        "answer": 0.23609126676383538
    },
    {
        "question": "19×1239492=？",
        "answer": 7.3719973290174865
    },
    {
        "question": "4265×290=？",
        "answer": 6.092317033402498
    },
    {
        "question": "556996433÷247=？",
        "answer": 6.3531554607051275
    },
    {
        "question": "8238÷4110=？",
        "answer": 0.30197996574432956
    },
    {
        "question": "37×335=？",
        "answer": 4.093246531103841
    },
    {
        "question": "71×92989=？",
        "answer": 6.8196899260703425
    },
    {
        "question": "23989967÷267289=？",
        "answer": 1.9530485643757038
    },
    {
        "question": "14×15945891=？",
        "answer": 8.348776826775078
    },
    {
        "question": "2152÷333=？",
        "answer": 0.8103980334880317
    },
    {
        "question": "79914902÷11693009=？",
        "answer": 0.8347014872612721
    },
    {
        "question": "498640625÷4799296=？",
        "answer": 2.0166101220522923
    },
    {
        "question": "2553854÷9789=？",
        "answer": 2.4164577371658402
    },
    {
        "question": "12879×23114=？",
        "answer": 8.473757252140134
    },
    {
        "question": "230934728÷738=？",
        "answer": 5.49543288527638
    },
    {
        "question": "1111×10210=？",
        "answer": 7.054739801027778
    },
    {
        "question": "3085÷303=？",
        "answer": 1.0078125398669555
    },
    {
        "question": "273809461÷8022=？",
        "answer": 4.533165792686694
    },
    {
        "question": "2091645÷2446=？",
        "answer": 2.9320315240419066
    },
    {
        "question": "16×21636849=？",
        "answer": 8.539313996874514
    },
    {
        "question": "3289×669=？",
        "answer": 6.342489991250478
    },
    {
        "question": "8618478÷44960=？",
        "answer": 2.282604274799312
    },
    {
        "question": "777748662÷1080277=？",
        "answer": 2.857304142945855
    },
    {
        "question": "92867463÷102082=？",
        "answer": 2.958914411237133
    },
    {
        "question": "496926060÷13731=？",
        "answer": 4.558589605644916
    },
    {
        "question": "5×18129631=？",
        "answer": 7.957358969143349
    },
    {
        "question": "2×772=？",
        "answer": 3.188647295999717
    },
    {
        "question": "2×125352=？",
        "answer": 5.399161263212581
    },
    {
        "question": "4×174824=？",
        "answer": 5.844661044066214
    },
    {
        "question": "151435355÷711506=？",
        "answer": 2.3280487132167114
    },
    {
        "question": "22334377÷1049=？",
        "answer": 4.328198354477931
    },
    {
        "question": "5685÷279=？",
        "answer": 1.309126265750156
    },
    {
        "question": "1×448490=？",
        "answer": 5.651752764006117
    },
    {
        "question": "21×31936=？",
        "answer": 5.826499814341196
    },
    {
        "question": "4346507÷18553=？",
        "answer": 2.369726238811532
    },
    {
        "question": "4193÷224=？",
        "answer": 1.2722768440694054
    },
    {
        "question": "85×22082=？",
        "answer": 6.273457331258226
    },
    {
        "question": "12×2449079=？",
        "answer": 7.4681840404458
    },
    {
        "question": "3×281=？",
        "answer": 2.9258275746247424
    },
    {
        "question": "41256÷22770=？",
        "answer": 0.25812408778351564
    },
    {
        "question": "11477412÷238788=？",
        "answer": 1.6818314735478754
    },
    {
        "question": "2×44620=？",
        "answer": 4.9505595616118
    },
    {
        "question": "773133407÷692993=？",
        "answer": 3.0475255917107806
    },
    {
        "question": "187816578÷285298=？",
        "answer": 2.8184351963088705
    },
    {
        "question": "32×45444=？",
        "answer": 6.162626529488357
    },
    {
        "question": "186877÷71995=？",
        "answer": 0.4142535175663326
    },
    {
        "question": "361×298591=？",
        "answer": 8.032583915176637
    },
    {
        "question": "11×6132517=？",
        "answer": 7.829031445949565
    },
    {
        "question": "224147605÷565873=？",
        "answer": 2.5978151302711803
    },
    {
        "question": "5316963÷26456=？",
        "answer": 2.3031394562246423
    },
    {
        "question": "924067118÷372125=？",
        "answer": 3.395014668931579
    },
    {
        "question": "196187÷1285=？",
        "answer": 2.1837670985401423
    },
    {
        "question": "19×5693=？",
        "answer": 5.034094784764377
    },
    {
        "question": "71×2950=？",
        "answer": 5.321080364697238
    },
    {
        "question": "5669×255=？",
        "answer": 6.160046637424926
    },
    {
        "question": "13925364÷57087=？",
        "answer": 2.3872693353339542
    },
    {
        "question": "122208038÷2027134=？",
        "answer": 1.7802173138475952
    },
    {
        "question": "8×8301=？",
        "answer": 4.822220400852558
    },
    {
        "question": "33×1110=？",
        "answer": 4.563836918664545
    },
    {
        "question": "135532607÷3089=？",
        "answer": 4.642225883857858
    },
    {
        "question": "45571×11515=？",
        "answer": 8.719952501049844
    },
    {
        "question": "44×203182=？",
        "answer": 6.9513379074261525
    },
    {
        "question": "22×11876=？",
        "answer": 5.417092869746213
    },
    {
        "question": "521436÷33994=？",
        "answer": 1.1857987415308024
    },
    {
        "question": "51343÷353=？",
        "answer": 2.1627065357567345
    },
    {
        "question": "183829÷46764=？",
        "answer": 0.5945023728729721
    },
    {
        "question": "109×152196=？",
        "answer": 7.219829736441173
    },
    {
        "question": "6×6664=？",
        "answer": 4.601886238782375
    },
    {
        "question": "5×4477727=？",
        "answer": 7.3500276161320075
    },
    {
        "question": "134087÷18161=？",
        "answer": 0.8682469157621014
    },
    {
        "question": "7299×5962=？",
        "answer": 7.638655335347093
    },
    {
        "question": "121×14367=？",
        "answer": 6.24015146207872
    },
    {
        "question": "2571×386=？",
        "answer": 5.996689381314615
    },
    {
        "question": "66527365÷1895=？",
        "answer": 4.545391108050384
    },
    {
        "question": "121036÷10573=？",
        "answer": 1.0587163304732283
    },
    {
        "question": "11498÷1456=？",
        "answer": 0.8974609293329376
    },
    {
        "question": "2756242÷18722=？",
        "answer": 2.1679651053660187
    },
    {
        "question": "49968×647=？",
        "answer": 7.509596247554824
    },
    {
        "question": "43×4009372=？",
        "answer": 8.23654480867525
    },
    {
        "question": "1×5549=？",
        "answer": 3.744214724814166
    },
    {
        "question": "115078328÷3516238=？",
        "answer": 1.5149152802554222
    },
    {
        "question": "509251÷243=？",
        "answer": 3.321325616884995
    },
    {
        "question": "232234834÷1217=？",
        "answer": 5.280636783939715
    },
    {
        "question": "5162827÷1604865=？",
        "answer": 0.5074490668535426
    },
    {
        "question": "2×3602=？",
        "answer": 3.857573704147496
    },
    {
        "question": "9×3514=？",
        "answer": 4.500044266598601
    },
    {
        "question": "71×25999=？",
        "answer": 6.266214992734742
    },
    {
        "question": "56×88628=？",
        "answer": 6.6957589760311125
    },
    {
        "question": "149331000÷4095413=？",
        "answer": 1.5618522688462961
    },
    {
        "question": "7×18431=？",
        "answer": 5.110646939134582
    },
    {
        "question": "651893÷237557=？",
        "answer": 0.4384084854982263
    },
    {
        "question": "1×37553545=？",
        "answer": 7.574650940042432
    },
    {
        "question": "2959796÷221=？",
        "answer": 4.1268695052361855
    },
    {
        "question": "126015×7127=？",
        "answer": 8.953329002561313
    },
    {
        "question": "63×2381=？",
        "answer": 5.1760999448584615
    },
    {
        "question": "21033892÷845=？",
        "answer": 4.396062930723516
    },
    {
        "question": "50×4655147=？",
        "answer": 8.366903403999425
    },
    {
        "question": "25201231÷50263=？",
        "answer": 2.700173348851242
    },
    {
        "question": "45×2741461=？",
        "answer": 8.09119458576932
    },
    {
        "question": "12729×54399=？",
        "answer": 8.840385202756634
    },
    {
        "question": "750265614÷542=？",
        "answer": 6.1412157558836995
    },
    {
        "question": "143323÷3266=？",
        "answer": 1.6422997097284349
    },
    {
        "question": "73×3214286=？",
        "answer": 8.370407376821515
    },
    {
        "question": "57×1552=？",
        "answer": 4.946766572594661
    },
    {
        "question": "454÷252=？",
        "answer": 0.2556553120755598
    },
    {
        "question": "41×16341917=？",
        "answer": 8.826086857122307
    },
    {
        "question": "5411178÷7146=？",
        "answer": 2.879228808361911
    },
    {
        "question": "11×16397978=？",
        "answer": 8.256182984572924
    },
    {
        "question": "4980047÷632992=？",
        "answer": 0.8958352202347191
    },
    {
        "question": "7247×11822=？",
        "answer": 7.932849216331147
    },
    {
        "question": "25541×8340=？",
        "answer": 8.3284039477147
    },
    {
        "question": "1206916÷260829=？",
        "answer": 0.6653211684174032
    },
    {
        "question": "43788÷30143=？",
        "answer": 0.16216863586602792
    },
    {
        "question": "335781258÷9063755=？",
        "answer": 1.5687482941416306
    },
    {
        "question": "17857×410=？",
        "answer": 6.864592355343782
    },
    {
        "question": "158587786÷2878592=？",
        "answer": 1.7410896219948964
    },
    {
        "question": "1484×21012=？",
        "answer": 7.493901293074079
    },
    {
        "question": "44118530÷13734012=？",
        "answer": 0.5068236110864682
    },
    {
        "question": "268985882÷148148288=？",
        "answer": 0.2590328490663332
    },
    {
        "question": "20395×780=？",
        "answer": 7.2016183123435935
    },
    {
        "question": "776×158530=？",
        "answer": 8.089973180881989
    },
    {
        "question": "307147÷13766=？",
        "answer": 1.3485385125696974
    },
    {
        "question": "338985268÷1419951=？",
        "answer": 2.377907466652588
    },
    {
        "question": "8×6349680=？",
        "answer": 7.705841826026275
    },
    {
        "question": "41×1226=？",
        "answer": 4.701274326902132
    },
    {
        "question": "328×32738=？",
        "answer": 7.030925988076093
    },
    {
        "question": "480403÷391=？",
        "answer": 3.0894289534069785
    },
    {
        "question": "128×8899=？",
        "answer": 6.056551176418366
    },
    {
        "question": "880965÷622829=？",
        "answer": 0.15058982872729745
    },
    {
        "question": "21474715÷740=？",
        "answer": 4.462695689105311
    },
    {
        "question": "4094÷257=？",
        "answer": 1.2022147149951923
    },
    {
        "question": "2×194255286=？",
        "answer": 8.589402841151845
    },
    {
        "question": "4139094÷2658=？",
        "answer": 3.192350312857042
    },
    {
        "question": "4131×99210=？",
        "answer": 8.612610644609951
    },
    {
        "question": "396907426÷5767=？",
        "answer": 4.837739273071103
    },
    {
        "question": "172683×271=？",
        "answer": 7.670218875867485
    },
    {
        "question": "1×563=？",
        "answer": 2.7505083948513462
    },
    {
        "question": "1188313÷450983=？",
        "answer": 0.4207706770114246
    },
    {
        "question": "232285×202=？",
        "answer": 7.671372535219477
    },
    {
        "question": "17×44358=？",
        "answer": 5.877420877959435
    },
    {
        "question": "665885280÷37506533=？",
        "answer": 1.2492924934966279
    },
    {
        "question": "82198561÷2582961=？",
        "answer": 1.5027463658463904
    },
    {
        "question": "221432÷15067=？",
        "answer": 1.1672135943932611
    },
    {
        "question": "5859÷820=？",
        "answer": 0.8540096456238001
    },
    {
        "question": "2×131861844=？",
        "answer": 8.421149140432995
    },
    {
        "question": "1900788÷254967=？",
        "answer": 0.8724497075526686
    },
    {
        "question": "179193185÷3012=？",
        "answer": 4.774466521206066
    },
    {
        "question": "22590×2093=？",
        "answer": 7.67468545925905
    },
    {
        "question": "15398723÷577386=？",
        "answer": 1.4260184574998354
    },
    {
        "question": "1882921÷25118=？",
        "answer": 1.8748470429987596
    },
    {
        "question": "2564×229499=？",
        "answer": 8.769698818365253
    },
    {
        "question": "978080320÷30637=？",
        "answer": 4.504128283961448
    },
    {
        "question": "1495×243=？",
        "answer": 5.560247466258761
    },
    {
        "question": "133153÷2205=？",
        "answer": 1.7809423619411988
    },
    {
        "question": "29×4639=？",
        "answer": 5.128822370417716
    },
    {
        "question": "2902343÷24755=？",
        "answer": 2.0690858055543706
    },
    {
        "question": "232826÷5142=？",
        "answer": 1.6558994046419222
    },
    {
        "question": "113×342722=？",
        "answer": 7.588020427026024
    },
    {
        "question": "1×5625=？",
        "answer": 3.7501225267834
    },
    {
        "question": "568525÷10128=？",
        "answer": 1.7492258741927362
    },
    {
        "question": "51×20655=？",
        "answer": 6.022595375410542
    },
    {
        "question": "92584087÷36012=？",
        "answer": 3.4100891067432744
    },
    {
        "question": "4770711÷1294=？",
        "answer": 3.5666488323438723
    },
    {
        "question": "457551846÷4229005=？",
        "answer": 2.0342021132397083
    },
    {
        "question": "2594940÷447239=？",
        "answer": 0.7635876528317488
    },
    {
        "question": "7648÷980=？",
        "answer": 0.8923218035755488
    },
    {
        "question": "574345369÷5293448=？",
        "answer": 2.035434472500726
    },
    {
        "question": "1×2198057=？",
        "answer": 6.342038950355213
    },
    {
        "question": "55×16751595=？",
        "answer": 8.96441885410412
    },
    {
        "question": "441857÷12795=？",
        "answer": 1.5382414493536416
    },
    {
        "question": "3×1154=？",
        "answer": 3.539327063539375
    },
    {
        "question": "769841530÷52238=？",
        "answer": 4.168414794859005
    },
    {
        "question": "121×131746=？",
        "answer": 7.202522808589657
    },
    {
        "question": "11229×5007=？",
        "answer": 7.749918673232994
    },
    {
        "question": "21×156120=？",
        "answer": 6.51567783734313
    },
    {
        "question": "7380902÷20244=？",
        "answer": 2.5618131103794286
    },
    {
        "question": "4×458540=？",
        "answer": 6.2634372179677085
    },
    {
        "question": "2640×20418=？",
        "answer": 7.731617126349284
    },
    {
        "question": "441×874419=？",
        "answer": 8.586158175172416
    },
    {
        "question": "8×623335=？",
        "answer": 6.69781150002242
    },
    {
        "question": "124274136÷4356=？",
        "answer": 4.455292881361082
    },
    {
        "question": "88025÷20232=？",
        "answer": 0.6385672174058734
    },
    {
        "question": "3344321÷305=？",
        "answer": 4.040008116572708
    },
    {
        "question": "143462119÷121652=？",
        "answer": 3.071617987997946
    },
    {
        "question": "22170÷2747=？",
        "answer": 0.9069070336939262
    },
    {
        "question": "351×283=？",
        "answer": 4.9970935519901145
    },
    {
        "question": "401377945÷5044=？",
        "answer": 4.900778427201218
    },
    {
        "question": "8×58100261=？",
        "answer": 8.667268070339334
    },
    {
        "question": "8×8810434=？",
        "answer": 7.848087289179557
    },
    {
        "question": "2546×3180=？",
        "answer": 6.908285519302069
    },
    {
        "question": "14×501=？",
        "answer": 3.8459657615454836
    },
    {
        "question": "24780÷11561=？",
        "answer": 0.33110590085357733
    },
    {
        "question": "843×5439=？",
        "answer": 6.661346633439914
    },
    {
        "question": "83950736÷621=？",
        "answer": 5.130932907794063
    },
    {
        "question": "91×255=？",
        "answer": 4.365581572755048
    },
    {
        "question": "84×6706=？",
        "answer": 5.750742835154683
    },
    {
        "question": "4×27369651=？",
        "answer": 8.03932925093244
    },
    {
        "question": "10×474=？",
        "answer": 3.6757783416740852
    },
    {
        "question": "84×211446=？",
        "answer": 7.24947875991766
    },
    {
        "question": "119×5250=？",
        "answer": 5.795706264798488
    },
    {
        "question": "155099÷1523=？",
        "answer": 2.0079090943751643
    },
    {
        "question": "6733500÷5120=？",
        "answer": 3.1189709034815034
    },
    {
        "question": "227254205÷13506436=？",
        "answer": 1.2259711629096854
    },
    {
        "question": "20×217=？",
        "answer": 3.637489729512511
    },
    {
        "question": "42288×440=？",
        "answer": 7.269669822273823
    },
    {
        "question": "8976127÷4851061=？",
        "answer": 0.267252252906127
    },
    {
        "question": "67760÷1773=？",
        "answer": 1.5822646617217326
    },
    {
        "question": "4141073÷492=？",
        "answer": 3.925147783667821
    },
    {
        "question": "346510484÷301=？",
        "answer": 6.061149883540036
    },
    {
        "question": "20×3800=？",
        "answer": 4.880813592280791
    },
    {
        "question": "157409407÷45372375=？",
        "answer": 0.5402391699835797
    },
    {
        "question": "627911355÷20793149=？",
        "answer": 1.4799780711529913
    },
    {
        "question": "35×11741=？",
        "answer": 5.613773132402127
    },
    {
        "question": "145×158396=？",
        "answer": 7.361112212317603
    },
    {
        "question": "1473861×221=？",
        "answer": 8.512848800777002
    },
    {
        "question": "57×6037=？",
        "answer": 5.536696031525964
    },
    {
        "question": "2×35388895=？",
        "answer": 7.849896997891927
    },
    {
        "question": "254×416697=？",
        "answer": 8.024654090395824
    },
    {
        "question": "632925204÷1170575=？",
        "answer": 2.732953145616401
    },
    {
        "question": "2×1734952=？",
        "answer": 6.540317459561192
    },
    {
        "question": "2304×41674=？",
        "answer": 7.9823476621428195
    },
    {
        "question": "20563÷4255=？",
        "answer": 0.6841869110971951
    },
    {
        "question": "469476966÷10318466=？",
        "answer": 1.6579991518071386
    },
    {
        "question": "44983÷16628=？",
        "answer": 0.4322084001386884
    },
    {
        "question": "2009178÷137443=？",
        "answer": 1.1648957880605997
    },
    {
        "question": "5×1634849=？",
        "answer": 6.912447650326088
    },
    {
        "question": "2318985÷393922=？",
        "answer": 0.769887703245746
    },
    {
        "question": "21053÷656=？",
        "answer": 1.5064101510864059
    },
    {
        "question": "546933563÷1172=？",
        "answer": 5.669006963326223
    },
    {
        "question": "57478729÷1412600=？",
        "answer": 1.6094879543043572
    },
    {
        "question": "55×635750=？",
        "answer": 7.54364905834199
    },
    {
        "question": "536×665=？",
        "answer": 5.551986434995874
    },
    {
        "question": "713839÷27217=？",
        "answer": 1.4187600182880291
    },
    {
        "question": "151×336376=？",
        "answer": 7.7058019491652
    },
    {
        "question": "1423×423=？",
        "answer": 5.779545267459326
    },
    {
        "question": "22738908÷16533584=？",
        "answer": 0.13840259836330873
    },
    {
        "question": "671÷296=？",
        "answer": 0.35543080911005354
    },
    {
        "question": "16768482÷314190=？",
        "answer": 1.7273013907650452
    },
    {
        "question": "8031÷205=？",
        "answer": 1.5930157648508407
    },
    {
        "question": "151×115076=？",
        "answer": 7.239961704855227
    },
    {
        "question": "239848983÷4088028=？",
        "answer": 1.7684240195880154
    },
    {
        "question": "38×2046=？",
        "answer": 4.8906892259929515
    },
    {
        "question": "2×5005383=？",
        "answer": 7.000467309931394
    },
    {
        "question": "84089×1385=？",
        "answer": 8.066188961210845
    },
    {
        "question": "1581×2101=？",
        "answer": 6.5213579223381615
    },
    {
        "question": "76927425÷47815816=？",
        "answer": 0.20650962387435487
    },
    {
        "question": "28×2224=？",
        "answer": 4.794292814252239
    },
    {
        "question": "7×5955=？",
        "answer": 4.6199798058330535
    },
    {
        "question": "201257÷129779=？",
        "answer": 0.19054657125228647
    },
    {
        "question": "435×452239=？",
        "answer": 8.293857269087042
    },
    {
        "question": "53×7428=？",
        "answer": 5.595147764668532
    },
    {
        "question": "96×1455=？",
        "answer": 5.1451342263614945
    },
    {
        "question": "57811×4831=？",
        "answer": 8.446047519242292
    },
    {
        "question": "924×503018=？",
        "answer": 8.667255497351194
    },
    {
        "question": "1753448÷354009=？",
        "answer": 0.694878587763653
    },
    {
        "question": "7991837÷275891=？",
        "answer": 1.4619090841813285
    },
    {
        "question": "36228518÷2820360=？",
        "answer": 1.1087460220837817
    },
    {
        "question": "205×4643263=？",
        "answer": 8.97857714438032
    },
    {
        "question": "66×557400=？",
        "answer": 7.5657108999191545
    },
    {
        "question": "2650×144002=？",
        "answer": 8.581614397857974
    },
    {
        "question": "918200938÷8322547=？",
        "answer": 2.0426814756583034
    },
    {
        "question": "112273571÷677=？",
        "answer": 5.219688867454292
    },
    {
        "question": "17920491÷266335=？",
        "answer": 1.8279216623145025
    },
    {
        "question": "8196÷657=？",
        "answer": 1.0960365801693766
    },
    {
        "question": "5×164452=？",
        "answer": 5.915009163904051
    },
    {
        "question": "21955983÷9561814=？",
        "answer": 0.3610125944632958
    },
    {
        "question": "243538980÷34988=？",
        "answer": 3.8426493649213422
    },
    {
        "question": "1408369÷1051520=？",
        "answer": 0.12689891970831713
    },
    {
        "question": "43870710÷37250=？",
        "answer": 3.071048385964057
    },
    {
        "question": "10×4561=？",
        "answer": 4.659060072240938
    },
    {
        "question": "27882749÷1939249=？",
        "answer": 1.1577020130829014
    },
    {
        "question": "1537824÷509=？",
        "answer": 3.4801888520866573
    },
    {
        "question": "38996538÷572=？",
        "answer": 4.833630024535172
    },
    {
        "question": "797746224÷403=？",
        "answer": 6.296559711068099
    },
    {
        "question": "4533970÷3368757=？",
        "answer": 0.1290089572360084
    },
    {
        "question": "94×386=？",
        "answer": 4.5597151582714535
    },
    {
        "question": "935102224÷20741873=？",
        "answer": 1.6540111191006575
    },
    {
        "question": "3×15653=？",
        "answer": 4.671718839962172
    },
    {
        "question": "7285×211=？",
        "answer": 6.186712011403702
    },
    {
        "question": "155521×1377=？",
        "answer": 8.330722980361536
    },
    {
        "question": "21×1402442=？",
        "answer": 7.469104204162433
    },
    {
        "question": "53935049÷604289=？",
        "answer": 1.9506263888590332
    },
    {
        "question": "44389710÷2574724=？",
        "answer": 1.2365516265087813
    },
    {
        "question": "94120715÷10192=？",
        "answer": 3.965425802698589
    },
    {
        "question": "157438387÷1689=？",
        "answer": 4.969480982071468
    },
    {
        "question": "104×3700=？",
        "answer": 5.585235063365776
    },
    {
        "question": "27×917407=？",
        "answer": 7.393925813721874
    },
    {
        "question": "9887123÷364219=？",
        "answer": 1.433707339360527
    },
    {
        "question": "50×1066893=？",
        "answer": 7.7270908700212875
    },
    {
        "question": "3582×164828=？",
        "answer": 8.771156570503841
    },
    {
        "question": "262316÷108293=？",
        "answer": 0.38422439627312766
    },
    {
        "question": "1×244761=？",
        "answer": 5.388742218889682
    },
    {
        "question": "3×639=？",
        "answer": 3.2826221128780624
    },
    {
        "question": "45925×3259=？",
        "answer": 8.17513352544299
    },
    {
        "question": "43675×1601=？",
        "answer": 7.844624245574268
    },
    {
        "question": "9215759÷49070=？",
        "answer": 2.2737150510736264
    },
    {
        "question": "323×987861=？",
        "answer": 8.503898362485693
    },
    {
        "question": "3165844÷848=？",
        "answer": 3.572093658519664
    },
    {
        "question": "39×738=？",
        "answer": 4.459120968849541
    },
    {
        "question": "17734321÷750=？",
        "answer": 4.373753301753541
    },
    {
        "question": "545×910066=？",
        "answer": 8.695469391736651
    },
    {
        "question": "7×314682=？",
        "answer": 6.342969941731903
    },
    {
        "question": "6737454÷47401=？",
        "answer": 2.152708309148948
    },
    {
        "question": "180×1512=？",
        "answer": 5.434824296268494
    },
    {
        "question": "6616÷754=？",
        "answer": 0.9432241506747162
    },
    {
        "question": "215614217÷956=？",
        "answer": 5.353219501349383
    },
    {
        "question": "8×9686=？",
        "answer": 4.889234451702464
    },
    {
        "question": "462351÷260=？",
        "answer": 3.2499984533127093
    },
    {
        "question": "56409761÷65260=？",
        "answer": 2.9367071902345185
    },
    {
        "question": "238×5090=？",
        "answer": 6.083294739393271
    },
    {
        "question": "11×184565=？",
        "answer": 6.30754203218381
    },
    {
        "question": "55463608÷12580=？",
        "answer": 3.644327476630316
    },
    {
        "question": "49866212÷8336415=？",
        "answer": 0.776827052683149
    },
    {
        "question": "6701796÷74739=？",
        "answer": 1.952643921211695
    },
    {
        "question": "338079819÷1877=？",
        "answer": 5.255554974575882
    },
    {
        "question": "14366068÷1625885=？",
        "answer": 0.946248093393768
    },
    {
        "question": "1102×203984=？",
        "answer": 8.351777698293512
    },
    {
        "question": "2916573÷3849=？",
        "answer": 2.879524939927029
    },
    {
        "question": "74050×5237=？",
        "answer": 8.588607636758713
    },
    {
        "question": "7×882=？",
        "answer": 3.7905666251460763
    },
    {
        "question": "2845833÷9960=？",
        "answer": 2.4559500726771786
    },
    {
        "question": "1×53798=？",
        "answer": 4.730766130590014
    },
    {
        "question": "62357÷389=？",
        "answer": 2.2049356117532177
    },
    {
        "question": "14×62284674=？",
        "answer": 8.940509231357275
    },
    {
        "question": "14×6206234=？",
        "answer": 7.938956181884959
    },
    {
        "question": "28×33752=？",
        "answer": 5.975457543716044
    },
    {
        "question": "302641÷219=？",
        "answer": 3.1404836484622947
    },
    {
        "question": "232×2729=？",
        "answer": 5.801491520560797
    },
    {
        "question": "153×497255=？",
        "answer": 7.881270589555233
    },
    {
        "question": "26×685=？",
        "answer": 4.250663919463244
    },
    {
        "question": "5385×1508=？",
        "answer": 6.909587049167755
    },
    {
        "question": "180×735537=？",
        "answer": 8.121877029198348
    },
    {
        "question": "427×1912=？",
        "answer": 5.911915762965105
    },
    {
        "question": "614031587÷19533522=？",
        "answer": 1.4974101566838174
    },
    {
        "question": "2244557÷3501=？",
        "answer": 2.8069385279194625
    },
    {
        "question": "1×84544=？",
        "answer": 4.927082791598415
    },
    {
        "question": "1460÷1037=？",
        "answer": 0.14857409939539612
    },
    {
        "question": "24047×1834=？",
        "answer": 7.644460234716893
    },
    {
        "question": "2005×259=？",
        "answer": 5.715414141037453
    },
    {
        "question": "725616348÷29756491=？",
        "answer": 1.3871253425197032
    },
    {
        "question": "134923578÷600=？",
        "answer": 5.351936599218106
    },
    {
        "question": "88930177÷27431605=？",
        "answer": 0.5107979381532869
    },
    {
        "question": "38628710÷17999555=？",
        "answer": 0.3316484369417393
    },
    {
        "question": "275222÷105710=？",
        "answer": 0.4155670736579272
    },
    {
        "question": "84×9767=？",
        "answer": 5.91404047378066
    },
    {
        "question": "259×633=？",
        "answer": 5.214703474098607
    },
    {
        "question": "105825×2173=？",
        "answer": 8.361648003466572
    },
    {
        "question": "6111×327=？",
        "answer": 6.300660036380113
    },
    {
        "question": "277527269÷2754=？",
        "answer": 5.003341726112168
    },
    {
        "question": "2×7411=？",
        "answer": 4.170906808930748
    },
    {
        "question": "25910÷1629=？",
        "answer": 1.2015463286773154
    },
    {
        "question": "86930×4073=？",
        "answer": 8.549084089711176
    },
    {
        "question": "100068580÷2551645=？",
        "answer": 1.5934774844479402
    },
    {
        "question": "130667÷3662=？",
        "answer": 1.5524475802277904
    },
    {
        "question": "163×7514=？",
        "answer": 6.088058795131324
    },
    {
        "question": "831598530÷83207=？",
        "answer": 3.999753849013584
    },
    {
        "question": "3×274776741=？",
        "answer": 8.916101222980311
    },
    {
        "question": "163916÷2264=？",
        "answer": 1.8597449250296414
    },
    {
        "question": "373×2378201=？",
        "answer": 8.947957389198951
    },
    {
        "question": "162755428÷69385=？",
        "answer": 3.370269888861069
    },
    {
        "question": "191625761÷10289=？",
        "answer": 4.270080725349372
    },
    {
        "question": "87779×4452=？",
        "answer": 8.591945784610044
    },
    {
        "question": "290×1231490=？",
        "answer": 8.552828887510982
    },
    {
        "question": "80670428÷17966188=？",
        "answer": 0.6522584212448638
    },
    {
        "question": "60×704=？",
        "answer": 4.625723909525756
    },
    {
        "question": "161×534042=？",
        "answer": 7.934401289710143
    },
    {
        "question": "6×38835195=？",
        "answer": 8.367376740567163
    },
    {
        "question": "2×120725863=？",
        "answer": 8.382830314269794
    },
    {
        "question": "18798×9516=？",
        "answer": 8.252566078630577
    },
    {
        "question": "1×100671=？",
        "answer": 5.002904382630707
    },
    {
        "question": "1869×2653=？",
        "answer": 6.695346551361161
    },
    {
        "question": "36075329÷12233630=？",
        "answer": 0.4696549591232389
    },
    {
        "question": "165100372÷785=？",
        "answer": 5.322878395060032
    },
    {
        "question": "514641172÷36993337=？",
        "answer": 1.1433810186142943
    },
    {
        "question": "777×4318=？",
        "answer": 6.525703656799126
    },
    {
        "question": "17176×3176=？",
        "answer": 7.736802525183251
    },
    {
        "question": "82×6097050=？",
        "answer": 8.698933608933446
    },
    {
        "question": "8×35575155=？",
        "answer": 8.454236787961843
    },
    {
        "question": "1×162429647=？",
        "answer": 8.210665300480276
    },
    {
        "question": "4×227752=？",
        "answer": 5.959522190738751
    },
    {
        "question": "11×1913417=？",
        "answer": 7.323202313347279
    },
    {
        "question": "3257×5594=？",
        "answer": 7.260540220600381
    },
    {
        "question": "27534÷478=？",
        "answer": 1.7604414114661842
    },
    {
        "question": "2×78716=？",
        "answer": 5.197093012717541
    },
    {
        "question": "141304÷81775=？",
        "answer": 0.2375339031303757
    },
    {
        "question": "805448×349=？",
        "answer": 8.448862934418282
    },
    {
        "question": "25×3988=？",
        "answer": 4.998695158311656
    },
    {
        "question": "982599379÷11658=？",
        "answer": 4.925752434342592
    },
    {
        "question": "708×148044=？",
        "answer": 8.020424068471524
    },
    {
        "question": "9×18229=？",
        "answer": 5.215005354375493
    },
    {
        "question": "137605×3925=？",
        "answer": 8.732473875743539
    },
    {
        "question": "1583648×558=？",
        "answer": 8.946292855581277
    },
    {
        "question": "6×1230230=？",
        "answer": 6.868137563768493
    },
    {
        "question": "1×2635=？",
        "answer": 3.4207806195485655
    },
    {
        "question": "339×7835=？",
        "answer": 6.424238699007691
    },
    {
        "question": "196415×1726=？",
        "answer": 8.530215442694036
    },
    {
        "question": "205×1806366=？",
        "answer": 8.568559611283597
    },
    {
        "question": "4644739÷354010=？",
        "answer": 1.1179457848173107
    },
    {
        "question": "6×103455=？",
        "answer": 5.7929027354282665
    },
    {
        "question": "867071738÷384=？",
        "answer": 6.353723806359741
    },
    {
        "question": "1×350575208=？",
        "answer": 8.544781200378717
    },
    {
        "question": "296671030÷19490=？",
        "answer": 4.182463300305339
    },
    {
        "question": "246344746÷8543418=？",
        "answer": 1.4599116487337185
    },
    {
        "question": "1×908=？",
        "answer": 2.958085848521085
    },
    {
        "question": "651174809÷3861423=？",
        "answer": 2.2269502122563134
    },
    {
        "question": "63485×251=？",
        "answer": 7.2023448454065715
    },
    {
        "question": "1×9215794=？",
        "answer": 6.9645327584333945
    },
    {
        "question": "2×1421536=？",
        "answer": 6.453787858215504
    },
    {
        "question": "6×40728=？",
        "answer": 5.388044334412926
    },
    {
        "question": "265×1058318=？",
        "answer": 8.447862056659034
    },
    {
        "question": "1211846÷141483=？",
        "answer": 0.9327431736883943
    },
    {
        "question": "59×460892=？",
        "answer": 7.43445118150238
    },
    {
        "question": "65×1154215=？",
        "answer": 7.875200070676232
    },
    {
        "question": "182081752÷378=？",
        "answer": 5.682774623701739
    },
    {
        "question": "2733804÷39634=？",
        "answer": 1.8386994695740588
    },
    {
        "question": "348×434794=？",
        "answer": 8.179862786295358
    },
    {
        "question": "1186×2984=？",
        "answer": 6.548883507828875
    },
    {
        "question": "6×10444913=？",
        "answer": 7.797056077296689
    },
    {
        "question": "285241234÷124814=？",
        "answer": 3.3589490050622355
    },
    {
        "question": "4039794÷51177=？",
        "answer": 1.8972843959087298
    },
    {
        "question": "3×34687=？",
        "answer": 5.017287995040656
    },
    {
        "question": "20215×2485=？",
        "answer": 7.701000138739044
    },
    {
        "question": "110×251043=？",
        "answer": 7.4411408013136935
    },
    {
        "question": "2764×275=？",
        "answer": 5.880870732532424
    },
    {
        "question": "57205÷4261=？",
        "answer": 1.1279224557378165
    },
    {
        "question": "43×8177666=？",
        "answer": 8.546097824292506
    },
    {
        "question": "21305685÷9997786=？",
        "answer": 0.328591665225592
    },
    {
        "question": "79×10143348=？",
        "answer": 8.90380841689291
    },
    {
        "question": "907933062÷2694=？",
        "answer": 5.527656239649938
    },
    {
        "question": "8502079÷870=？",
        "answer": 3.9900058834282315
    },
    {
        "question": "174480999÷327116=？",
        "answer": 2.7270463521614206
    },
    {
        "question": "1×116680266=？",
        "answer": 8.066997410526833
    },
    {
        "question": "384÷309=？",
        "answer": 0.09437274494269612
    },
    {
        "question": "60902600÷2406956=？",
        "answer": 1.4031676822529042
    },
    {
        "question": "44708133÷17445797=？",
        "answer": 0.40869571952110645
    },
    {
        "question": "7×2951=？",
        "answer": 4.315067249514216
    },
    {
        "question": "1172912÷976=？",
        "answer": 3.079815611884423
    },
    {
        "question": "117×41838=？",
        "answer": 6.689756777334724
    },
    {
        "question": "21983314÷419692=？",
        "answer": 1.719162472276722
    },
    {
        "question": "5×751931=？",
        "answer": 6.575147994270586
    },
    {
        "question": "2×293414=？",
        "answer": 5.768510827658261
    },
    {
        "question": "28273×8567=？",
        "answer": 8.384200660085092
    },
    {
        "question": "11×8181803=？",
        "answer": 7.954241703581038
    },
    {
        "question": "155563761÷534267=？",
        "answer": 2.4641500843576485
    },
    {
        "question": "75×16945=？",
        "answer": 6.104102836565097
    },
    {
        "question": "4×3684012=？",
        "answer": 7.168381027490476
    },
    {
        "question": "256×549565=？",
        "answer": 8.148259031446885
    },
    {
        "question": "30032010÷65388=？",
        "answer": 2.6620863459360895
    },
    {
        "question": "3282944÷1467669=？",
        "answer": 0.34963535346634705
    },
    {
        "question": "121828145÷114232=？",
        "answer": 3.0279598509447103
    },
    {
        "question": "6393×1144=？",
        "answer": 6.86413072889087
    },
    {
        "question": "1×7460=？",
        "answer": 3.8727388274726686
    },
    {
        "question": "157883÷1214=？",
        "answer": 2.114116683271212
    },
    {
        "question": "79956×320=？",
        "answer": 7.4080010376356675
    },
    {
        "question": "205036363÷113275133=？",
        "answer": 0.2576963088205969
    },
    {
        "question": "1007541÷324=？",
        "answer": 3.492717717769275
    },
    {
        "question": "147974623÷18484=？",
        "answer": 3.903391282331752
    },
    {
        "question": "502870÷266029=？",
        "answer": 0.27652674549729256
    },
    {
        "question": "237319÷49702=？",
        "answer": 0.6789586446454623
    },
    {
        "question": "6×21555=？",
        "answer": 5.111699277573551
    },
    {
        "question": "6×510=？",
        "answer": 3.48572142648158
    },
    {
        "question": "4075÷796=？",
        "answer": 0.7092145453383264
    },
    {
        "question": "3×77438=？",
        "answer": 5.366075382592052
    },
    {
        "question": "2023835÷1114215=？",
        "answer": 0.25920610147741974
    },
    {
        "question": "114387605÷635858=？",
        "answer": 2.2550188273097582
    },
    {
        "question": "3216÷735=？",
        "answer": 0.6410287009922188
    },
    {
        "question": "77573÷705=？",
        "answer": 2.0415214703565123
    },
    {
        "question": "28684÷525=？",
        "answer": 1.7374804104237234
    },
    {
        "question": "363×1272=？",
        "answer": 5.664393736348508
    },
    {
        "question": "1010634×866=？",
        "answer": 8.94211179680814
    },
    {
        "question": "146295÷2085=？",
        "answer": 1.846123423961694
    },
    {
        "question": "2×93748164=？",
        "answer": 8.27299276675732
    },
    {
        "question": "5142×169029=？",
        "answer": 8.939093294432363
    },
    {
        "question": "21135892÷913575=？",
        "answer": 1.3642763745355808
    },
    {
        "question": "11034925÷2577075=？",
        "answer": 0.6316423278769915
    },
    {
        "question": "7×456178=？",
        "answer": 6.504232376831719
    },
    {
        "question": "13028672÷115946=？",
        "answer": 2.0506443801638805
    },
    {
        "question": "13×793=？",
        "answer": 4.01321653962444
    },
    {
        "question": "33227288÷5080092=？",
        "answer": 0.8156233183682449
    },
    {
        "question": "2188382÷44207=？",
        "answer": 1.6946320903648688
    },
    {
        "question": "875906580÷3739781=？",
        "answer": 2.369611618025791
    },
    {
        "question": "383627953÷2617=？",
        "answer": 5.166106521821618
    },
    {
        "question": "140×46031=？",
        "answer": 6.809178445500834
    },
    {
        "question": "327034÷484=？",
        "answer": 2.829747544669653
    },
    {
        "question": "7×298138=？",
        "answer": 6.319515373774287
    },
    {
        "question": "4244×861=？",
        "answer": 6.5627785266829575
    },
    {
        "question": "170282362÷808=？",
        "answer": 5.323758304905118
    },
    {
        "question": "2318×640=？",
        "answer": 6.171293405611465
    },
    {
        "question": "141×13034=？",
        "answer": 6.264296829314961
    },
    {
        "question": "14261÷1024=？",
        "answer": 1.143850023241736
    },
    {
        "question": "2×928704=？",
        "answer": 6.268907311755986
    },
    {
        "question": "4×5642079=？",
        "answer": 7.353499154151186
    },
    {
        "question": "78225×1082=？",
        "answer": 7.9275728325887815
    },
    {
        "question": "776576×216=？",
        "answer": 8.224637715742848
    },
    {
        "question": "281184÷9042=？",
        "answer": 1.4927261020228917
    },
    {
        "question": "191024504÷2794313=？",
        "answer": 1.8348140294733273
    },
    {
        "question": "279×354534=？",
        "answer": 7.995262093862719
    },
    {
        "question": "9×2237879=？",
        "answer": 7.304079110374757
    },
    {
        "question": "3035×36465=？",
        "answer": 8.044034913310293
    },
    {
        "question": "29594197÷353=？",
        "answer": 4.923431855064662
    },
    {
        "question": "65629×11615=？",
        "answer": 8.882115001026262
    },
    {
        "question": "78579144÷531=？",
        "answer": 5.170212772443677
    },
    {
        "question": "14768027÷12301=？",
        "answer": 3.0793820591932435
    },
    {
        "question": "28062407÷3144515=？",
        "answer": 0.9505712483337424
    },
    {
        "question": "245689861÷22212663=？",
        "answer": 1.0437866068675687
    },
    {
        "question": "45848673÷74381=？",
        "answer": 2.7898647575404434
    },
    {
        "question": "2×1650528=？",
        "answer": 6.518652891880961
    },
    {
        "question": "840097÷245719=？",
        "answer": 0.5338906946313254
    },
    {
        "question": "113×138665=？",
        "answer": 7.195045299473531
    },
    {
        "question": "58×16603183=？",
        "answer": 8.98361934827897
    },
    {
        "question": "24362÷234=？",
        "answer": 2.0174970814484534
    },
    {
        "question": "16×218=？",
        "answer": 3.5425764762605296
    },
    {
        "question": "3614094÷665=？",
        "answer": 3.7351777987575576
    },
    {
        "question": "200×2539=？",
        "answer": 5.705692696537703
    },
    {
        "question": "153×243651=？",
        "answer": 7.571459628983468
    },
    {
        "question": "19535×2029=？",
        "answer": 7.5980954625941495
    },
    {
        "question": "3×534=？",
        "answer": 3.204662511748219
    },
    {
        "question": "597×12794=？",
        "answer": 6.882980677510913
    },
    {
        "question": "1079×29178=？",
        "answer": 7.498076964634731
    },
    {
        "question": "65565×1779=？",
        "answer": 8.06684801362926
    },
    {
        "question": "188×1179775=？",
        "answer": 8.345957038285245
    },
    {
        "question": "301×1146=？",
        "answer": 5.537751113225214
    },
    {
        "question": "2×65404=？",
        "answer": 5.116634305529611
    },
    {
        "question": "455740617÷124934=？",
        "answer": 3.5620370909989543
    },
    {
        "question": "913164780÷248196=？",
        "answer": 3.5657543747661
    },
    {
        "question": "215×635872=？",
        "answer": 8.135808161588601
    },
    {
        "question": "126×32335=？",
        "answer": 6.610043410400698
    },
    {
        "question": "85608946÷6934536=？",
        "answer": 1.0915017430386698
    },
    {
        "question": "299144÷18764=？",
        "answer": 1.2025548722460049
    },
    {
        "question": "2852÷597=？",
        "answer": 0.6791751900504589
    },
    {
        "question": "98707448÷16474=？",
        "answer": 3.7775508620783373
    },
    {
        "question": "1×215=？",
        "answer": 2.3324384599156054
    },
    {
        "question": "3×10926=？",
        "answer": 4.5155824508982265
    },
    {
        "question": "89×12418=？",
        "answer": 6.043441662154877
    },
    {
        "question": "13005×50140=？",
        "answer": 8.814294686154089
    },
    {
        "question": "173636682÷5928745=？",
        "answer": 1.466678706972765
    },
    {
        "question": "87182947÷7465712=？",
        "answer": 1.0673603127484292
    },
    {
        "question": "15275×9257=？",
        "answer": 8.150451482643875
    },
    {
        "question": "1987558÷11039=？",
        "answer": 2.255390077551345
    },
    {
        "question": "190246276÷245293=？",
        "answer": 2.8896310095818944
    },
    {
        "question": "19×5583219=？",
        "answer": 8.025638264201104
    },
    {
        "question": "100532368÷5776259=？",
        "answer": 1.24065925410711
    },
    {
        "question": "1×2265907=？",
        "answer": 6.355242081072101
    },
    {
        "question": "268083×1012=？",
        "answer": 8.433449787358434
    },
    {
        "question": "235714891÷79782245=？",
        "answer": 0.4704807666152909
    },
    {
        "question": "138362766÷249744=？",
        "answer": 2.743524172106908
    },
    {
        "question": "1×132480=？",
        "answer": 5.122150319440805
    },
    {
        "question": "13×1106777=？",
        "answer": 7.158003477769543
    },
    {
        "question": "108×25415=？",
        "answer": 6.438513869525672
    },
    {
        "question": "281225799÷85790=？",
        "answer": 3.5156184915136532
    },
    {
        "question": "16896069÷525=？",
        "answer": 4.507626371018906
    },
    {
        "question": "13×162214=？",
        "answer": 6.324031685908018
    },
    {
        "question": "26747×259=？",
        "answer": 6.840574841783917
    },
    {
        "question": "247138×2107=？",
        "answer": 8.716604063371491
    },
    {
        "question": "45027618÷329400=？",
        "answer": 2.1357553781825374
    },
    {
        "question": "12×49841125=？",
        "answer": 8.776769082583531
    },
    {
        "question": "1×206599=？",
        "answer": 5.315128215075505
    },
    {
        "question": "15250539÷12635=？",
        "answer": 3.081709946973695
    },
    {
        "question": "11×9961580=？",
        "answer": 8.039720912222569
    },
    {
        "question": "128988399÷16864315=？",
        "answer": 0.8835819467643015
    },
    {
        "question": "8×403=？",
        "answer": 3.508395033133053
    },
    {
        "question": "11915÷618=？",
        "answer": 1.285105571593659
    },
    {
        "question": "1×111379=？",
        "answer": 5.0468033143219975
    },
    {
        "question": "342742455÷463=？",
        "answer": 5.869386912157872
    },
    {
        "question": "25364×416=？",
        "answer": 7.023311075141667
    },
    {
        "question": "28151997÷2799680=？",
        "answer": 1.0024008126960975
    },
    {
        "question": "153692458÷302=？",
        "answer": 5.706645613356208
    },
    {
        "question": "256530286÷2425=？",
        "answer": 5.024426902401261
    },
    {
        "question": "125114÷231=？",
        "answer": 2.7336939291822295
    },
    {
        "question": "32812165÷927953=？",
        "answer": 1.5485089066436408
    },
    {
        "question": "11×2197194=？",
        "answer": 7.383261089557042
    },
    {
        "question": "180×260115=？",
        "answer": 7.670437902394881
    },
    {
        "question": "1077432÷7076=？",
        "answer": 2.1826020458185846
    },
    {
        "question": "1831÷250=？",
        "answer": 0.8647483356296588
    },
    {
        "question": "212558224÷132376=？",
        "answer": 3.2056686588391874
    },
    {
        "question": "20516047÷4615704=？",
        "answer": 0.6478557351004323
    },
    {
        "question": "58462439÷530=？",
        "answer": 5.042601060170982
    },
    {
        "question": "122287862÷3512=？",
        "answer": 4.541828844912366
    },
    {
        "question": "138842÷778=？",
        "answer": 2.251541264007293
    },
    {
        "question": "2×1387=？",
        "answer": 3.443106456737266
    },
    {
        "question": "10814199÷7982=？",
        "answer": 3.131882633636128
    },
    {
        "question": "598591÷257=？",
        "answer": 3.367197059470705
    },
    {
        "question": "476938177÷163672902=？",
        "answer": 0.4644853046325302
    },
    {
        "question": "63973153÷13202=？",
        "answer": 3.685358027597545
    },
    {
        "question": "49768×1814=？",
        "answer": 7.955587471058689
    },
    {
        "question": "1×248233=？",
        "answer": 5.394859515942865
    },
    {
        "question": "3683×268868=？",
        "answer": 8.99574083550586
    },
    {
        "question": "1236347÷854664=？",
        "answer": 0.1603449682852025
    },
    {
        "question": "41869811÷207681=？",
        "answer": 2.3045042342070867
    },
    {
        "question": "4277471÷261=？",
        "answer": 4.214546566495507
    },
    {
        "question": "11×15806596=？",
        "answer": 8.240231038481491
    },
    {
        "question": "14536682÷7308118=？",
        "answer": 0.2986597390074248
    },
    {
        "question": "29440695÷1493282=？",
        "answer": 1.294806227931548
    },
    {
        "question": "1102623÷169666=？",
        "answer": 0.8128322261865751
    },
    {
        "question": "138292÷252=？",
        "answer": 2.7393965167222234
    },
    {
        "question": "1×38272=？",
        "answer": 4.582881157972298
    },
    {
        "question": "65×508270=？",
        "answer": 7.5190078334143085
    },
    {
        "question": "785×95784=？",
        "answer": 7.876162626240882
    },
    {
        "question": "43293507÷69255=？",
        "answer": 2.795971633750756
    },
    {
        "question": "41×6494140=？",
        "answer": 8.425305503586264
    },
    {
        "question": "3157×3545=？",
        "answer": 7.048890821411303
    },
    {
        "question": "42072÷1535=？",
        "answer": 1.4378847779921957
    },
    {
        "question": "79×11025=？",
        "answer": 5.9400056894303175
    },
    {
        "question": "15×17246518=？",
        "answer": 8.412792685071901
    },
    {
        "question": "25469×3526=？",
        "answer": 7.953294201375771
    },
    {
        "question": "72401860÷553838=？",
        "answer": 2.1163669730455132
    },
    {
        "question": "174×24473=？",
        "answer": 6.62923645848384
    },
    {
        "question": "565669100÷13863106=？",
        "answer": 1.6107019118514425
    },
    {
        "question": "297536×1492=？",
        "answer": 8.647308343303624
    },
    {
        "question": "172582792÷7438=？",
        "answer": 4.365541316591401
    },
    {
        "question": "5×1226596=？",
        "answer": 6.787671548430555
    },
    {
        "question": "32945615÷207270=？",
        "answer": 2.20126117158619
    },
    {
        "question": "33251376÷1719645=？",
        "answer": 1.2863708205800601
    },
    {
        "question": "2094140÷277=？",
        "answer": 3.8785259432330275
    },
    {
        "question": "749÷544=？",
        "answer": 0.1388829180012866
    },
    {
        "question": "69816÷14490=？",
        "answer": 0.6828865774874906
    },
    {
        "question": "9×73921=？",
        "answer": 5.823010342807549
    },
    {
        "question": "17243009÷356=？",
        "answer": 4.685163056907246
    },
    {
        "question": "591740×1014=？",
        "answer": 8.778168882381681
    },
    {
        "question": "516×1880420=？",
        "answer": 8.986904563290121
    },
    {
        "question": "6×53724768=？",
        "answer": 8.50832579913461
    },
    {
        "question": "32×11830=？",
        "answer": 5.578134722947836
    },
    {
        "question": "4×317465=？",
        "answer": 6.103755843334727
    },
    {
        "question": "66×110842=？",
        "answer": 6.864248289002906
    },
    {
        "question": "152×395360=？",
        "answer": 7.778836316002777
    },
    {
        "question": "40887616÷493=？",
        "answer": 4.9187448699704746
    },
    {
        "question": "5663×2150=？",
        "answer": 7.0854850215421346
    },
    {
        "question": "889470852÷1480459=？",
        "answer": 2.778735336312277
    },
    {
        "question": "71089200÷26245584=？",
        "answer": 0.4327473860813459
    },
    {
        "question": "4712÷551=？",
        "answer": 0.9320536829272601
    },
    {
        "question": "3×265739628=？",
        "answer": 8.9015775774342
    },
    {
        "question": "825626×904=？",
        "answer": 8.872951791452701
    },
    {
        "question": "7793×12423=？",
        "answer": 7.985931161461223
    },
    {
        "question": "593274÷152669=？",
        "answer": 0.5895044550473534
    },
    {
        "question": "13×8674=？",
        "answer": 5.05216277011958
    },
    {
        "question": "138508359÷600=？",
        "answer": 5.363324733544105
    },
    {
        "question": "4758÷301=？",
        "answer": 1.1988579421074042
    },
    {
        "question": "110673265÷129831=？",
        "answer": 2.9306643201837135
    },
    {
        "question": "2×273665006=？",
        "answer": 8.738249262665862
    },
    {
        "question": "293×1892844=？",
        "answer": 8.743982443123544
    },
    {
        "question": "42327100÷354=？",
        "answer": 5.077615252204384
    },
    {
        "question": "34427×8929=？",
        "answer": 8.48770200250316
    },
    {
        "question": "5125÷667=？",
        "answer": 0.8855680358112429
    },
    {
        "question": "45911763÷118051=？",
        "answer": 2.589854299581642
    },
    {
        "question": "225485×398=？",
        "answer": 7.953000728558603
    },
    {
        "question": "182287672÷178560=？",
        "answer": 3.0089731213294058
    },
    {
        "question": "90384643÷1005077=？",
        "answer": 1.9538953122062486
    },
    {
        "question": "86905÷10235=？",
        "answer": 0.9289569169063155
    },
    {
        "question": "438710811÷489073=？",
        "answer": 2.952804649094361
    },
    {
        "question": "8×346=？",
        "answer": 3.44216608578472
    },
    {
        "question": "8194×17182=？",
        "answer": 8.14856967431663
    },
    {
        "question": "8565÷349=？",
        "answer": 1.3899019403423494
    },
    {
        "question": "180×367=？",
        "answer": 4.819938569355395
    },
    {
        "question": "4976554÷2254=？",
        "answer": 3.3439748091990587
    },
    {
        "question": "15×9796242=？",
        "answer": 8.167150764169694
    },
    {
        "question": "4×368=？",
        "answer": 3.16790781000148
    },
    {
        "question": "231×33696=？",
        "answer": 6.891190329397537
    },
    {
        "question": "8954058÷34250=？",
        "answer": 2.417359327374931
    },
    {
        "question": "276×6850=？",
        "answer": 6.276599653557644
    },
    {
        "question": "6×6237=？",
        "answer": 4.573126994434776
    },
    {
        "question": "37470÷1951=？",
        "answer": 1.2834264236992798
    },
    {
        "question": "2×129302672=？",
        "answer": 8.412637495199174
    },
    {
        "question": "1883×468926=？",
        "answer": 8.945954633249192
    },
    {
        "question": "105632×2302=？",
        "answer": 8.38590082194399
    },
    {
        "question": "704×3073=？",
        "answer": 6.335135219398491
    },
    {
        "question": "4499473÷14987=？",
        "answer": 2.4774469427789136
    },
    {
        "question": "909674366÷123272986=？",
        "answer": 0.8680180408846
    },
    {
        "question": "122×778=？",
        "answer": 4.977339427664437
    },
    {
        "question": "290876463÷41453200=？",
        "answer": 0.8461505188845609
    },
    {
        "question": "156×92363=？",
        "answer": 7.158622628947438
    },
    {
        "question": "74558÷13761=？",
        "answer": 0.7338442548079395
    },
    {
        "question": "2×4916606=？",
        "answer": 6.992695402473188
    },
    {
        "question": "277×49299=？",
        "answer": 7.135317879033635
    },
    {
        "question": "34362÷490=？",
        "answer": 1.8458823534684592
    },
    {
        "question": "21555×4757=？",
        "answer": 8.010881178609809
    },
    {
        "question": "243091730÷16419670=？",
        "answer": 1.170405759874323
    },
    {
        "question": "14480301÷1953447=？",
        "answer": 0.8699759569256718
    },
    {
        "question": "312860991÷369148=？",
        "answer": 2.9281508968061774
    },
    {
        "question": "30885÷1281=？",
        "answer": 1.3821984759290262
    },
    {
        "question": "198958542÷109816=？",
        "answer": 3.2580969690201695
    },
    {
        "question": "349040÷7985=？",
        "answer": 1.640600279504262
    },
    {
        "question": "3×6548814=？",
        "answer": 7.293283910452974
    },
    {
        "question": "20058×16198=？",
        "answer": 8.5117490216062
    },
    {
        "question": "800373191÷600078=？",
        "answer": 3.1250848282460164
    },
    {
        "question": "45×10719654=？",
        "answer": 8.683393281565323
    },
    {
        "question": "495×384=？",
        "answer": 5.2789364233011
    },
    {
        "question": "1×34036=？",
        "answer": 4.531938514984746
    },
    {
        "question": "10858917÷130201=？",
        "answer": 1.9211721938013908
    },
    {
        "question": "4×35677822=？",
        "answer": 8.154458325758151
    },
    {
        "question": "244876308÷13540=？",
        "answer": 4.257328104431779
    },
    {
        "question": "161778172÷4153476=？",
        "answer": 1.5905082185030477
    },
    {
        "question": "365×2323=？",
        "answer": 5.92834207425671
    },
    {
        "question": "1341608÷100823=？",
        "answer": 1.124066023524176
    },
    {
        "question": "79×15585=？",
        "answer": 6.0903338979033
    },
    {
        "question": "17×41429=？",
        "answer": 5.847753371941272
    },
    {
        "question": "296294211÷413083=？",
        "answer": 2.85568584390399
    },
    {
        "question": "315237÷972=？",
        "answer": 2.5109709208987754
    },
    {
        "question": "19×1137=？",
        "answer": 4.334514065640564
    },
    {
        "question": "86191×7474=？",
        "answer": 8.809015012999593
    },
    {
        "question": "13426592÷21629=？",
        "answer": 2.792929351376592
    },
    {
        "question": "8018443÷7000870=？",
        "answer": 0.05893803305951925
    },
    {
        "question": "994534÷150911=？",
        "answer": 0.8188987379473509
    },
    {
        "question": "8061896÷54786=？",
        "answer": 2.1677675982069546
    },
    {
        "question": "2711×958=？",
        "answer": 6.41449502665903
    },
    {
        "question": "2369×112463=？",
        "answer": 8.42557472504703
    },
    {
        "question": "251×5082=？",
        "answer": 6.105708382195389
    },
    {
        "question": "15474013÷4102262=？",
        "answer": 0.5765795632884545
    },
    {
        "question": "30×3814272=？",
        "answer": 8.058532914558924
    },
    {
        "question": "71029÷311=？",
        "answer": 2.3586753113619703
    },
    {
        "question": "18×3836622=？",
        "answer": 7.839221517905761
    },
    {
        "question": "159×1249062=？",
        "answer": 8.297981120412437
    },
    {
        "question": "68803434÷28621=？",
        "answer": 3.38092531087527
    },
    {
        "question": "2492482÷21889=？",
        "answer": 2.056406109385921
    },
    {
        "question": "18×39795678=？",
        "answer": 8.855108413290719
    },
    {
        "question": "90840×433=？",
        "answer": 7.594765021901063
    },
    {
        "question": "67006×1002=？",
        "answer": 7.826981414533878
    },
    {
        "question": "8236÷5734=？",
        "answer": 0.15725864933552808
    },
    {
        "question": "7607×452=？",
        "answer": 6.536351851066401
    },
    {
        "question": "1885336÷2347=？",
        "answer": 2.904875670748063
    },
    {
        "question": "1380536÷1023=？",
        "answer": 3.1301721024333475
    },
    {
        "question": "46×102020=？",
        "answer": 6.671443150876742
    },
    {
        "question": "126329386÷321923=？",
        "answer": 2.5937523790908084
    },
    {
        "question": "12×546065=？",
        "answer": 6.816425587399158
    },
    {
        "question": "19×179772=？",
        "answer": 6.533475651017222
    },
    {
        "question": "2×28554865=？",
        "answer": 7.756710106937889
    },
    {
        "question": "4102×211=？",
        "answer": 5.93727811133004
    },
    {
        "question": "5149×7314=？",
        "answer": 7.57587784782926
    },
    {
        "question": "3×3562=？",
        "answer": 4.0288151698468875
    },
    {
        "question": "288707101÷115163=？",
        "answer": 3.399144496120033
    },
    {
        "question": "3×473=？",
        "answer": 3.151982395457474
    },
    {
        "question": "392280301÷33277618=？",
        "answer": 1.0714442677784985
    },
    {
        "question": "209808÷492=？",
        "answer": 2.6298569410978794
    },
    {
        "question": "79623÷20951=？",
        "answer": 0.5798337798563371
    },
    {
        "question": "154191422÷3677574=？",
        "answer": 1.6224987933080561
    },
    {
        "question": "863×3834=？",
        "answer": 6.519662904257253
    },
    {
        "question": "3446÷580=？",
        "answer": 0.7738872795490724
    },
    {
        "question": "240×1469981=？",
        "answer": 8.547522963093467
    },
    {
        "question": "23×7969410=？",
        "answer": 8.263154006443946
    },
    {
        "question": "486×707=？",
        "answer": 5.5360556830591925
    },
    {
        "question": "8×4581006=？",
        "answer": 7.564050847588194
    },
    {
        "question": "24987778÷103864=？",
        "answer": 2.3812625947829735
    },
    {
        "question": "67922702÷747226=？",
        "answer": 1.9585629791181256
    },
    {
        "question": "13×160873=？",
        "answer": 6.32042651303132
    },
    {
        "question": "43×205=？",
        "answer": 3.945222316635341
    },
    {
        "question": "3956×10523=？",
        "answer": 7.6193958533235335
    },
    {
        "question": "132267563÷12327560=？",
        "answer": 1.0305762268601162
    },
    {
        "question": "1059×57327=？",
        "answer": 7.783255175254985
    },
    {
        "question": "102757376÷66653727=？",
        "answer": 0.1879885672689895
    },
    {
        "question": "22653157÷806=？",
        "answer": 4.448793693114941
    },
    {
        "question": "1481÷347=？",
        "answer": 0.6302255837303348
    },
    {
        "question": "11×31622674=？",
        "answer": 8.541391276065724
    },
    {
        "question": "3×27200857=？",
        "answer": 7.911703842007823
    },
    {
        "question": "4×2256=？",
        "answer": 3.955399086639267
    },
    {
        "question": "76×562=？",
        "answer": 4.630549907849852
    },
    {
        "question": "179607322÷30862=？",
        "answer": 3.7648999705249104
    },
    {
        "question": "119936849÷36384702=？",
        "answer": 0.518033812508502
    },
    {
        "question": "582038÷49241=？",
        "answer": 1.0726244755986762
    },
    {
        "question": "2×2278304=？",
        "answer": 6.658641668310422
    },
    {
        "question": "15872288÷3894999=？",
        "answer": 0.6101321845739708
    },
    {
        "question": "971531853÷410929=？",
        "answer": 3.37369025281999
    },
    {
        "question": "1×259313424=？",
        "answer": 8.413824999678033
    },
    {
        "question": "160253813÷340867=？",
        "answer": 2.6722234133349936
    },
    {
        "question": "5736697÷304906=？",
        "answer": 1.2744959414061616
    },
    {
        "question": "7×135517=？",
        "answer": 5.977091818937526
    },
    {
        "question": "24×282521=？",
        "answer": 6.831261976504785
    },
    {
        "question": "3×16952996=？",
        "answer": 7.706367714266974
    },
    {
        "question": "21739270÷9157=？",
        "answer": 3.375491742293267
    },
    {
        "question": "55826÷41416=？",
        "answer": 0.12966835926975961
    },
    {
        "question": "101060÷257=？",
        "answer": 2.594646170570917
    },
    {
        "question": "12×76891143=？",
        "answer": 8.965057562861315
    },
    {
        "question": "8065×3042=？",
        "answer": 7.38976358144196
    },
    {
        "question": "14332×3739=？",
        "answer": 7.7290622646482925
    },
    {
        "question": "1×22858=？",
        "answer": 4.359038228379384
    },
    {
        "question": "229331÷1169=？",
        "answer": 2.2926482536376733
    },
    {
        "question": "485760÷367=？",
        "answer": 3.1217556856272783
    },
    {
        "question": "719×1064811=？",
        "answer": 8.88400141933957
    },
    {
        "question": "8194×229=？",
        "answer": 6.273331441957011
    },
    {
        "question": "17×3994506=？",
        "answer": 7.831911999211095
    },
    {
        "question": "1×747=？",
        "answer": 2.873320601815399
    },
    {
        "question": "2×3103=？",
        "answer": 3.792811771248147
    },
    {
        "question": "724×35567=？",
        "answer": 7.410785801121699
    },
    {
        "question": "556357219÷11187=？",
        "answer": 4.696640089517709
    },
    {
        "question": "369×10786=？",
        "answer": 6.599886782111204
    },
    {
        "question": "922÷640=？",
        "answer": 0.15855094706974218
    },
    {
        "question": "29×4024313=？",
        "answer": 8.067089749491162
    },
    {
        "question": "46189284÷717=？",
        "answer": 4.80902207444497
    },
    {
        "question": "242309×479=？",
        "answer": 8.064705058702492
    },
    {
        "question": "26613÷1265=？",
        "answer": 1.3230033084536057
    },
    {
        "question": "11×5662283=？",
        "answer": 7.794384256698601
    },
    {
        "question": "1×31597467=？",
        "answer": 7.499652268947051
    },
    {
        "question": "65904÷1393=？",
        "answer": 1.674960658188379
    },
    {
        "question": "3085773×279=？",
        "answer": 8.934968177990545
    },
    {
        "question": "71431419÷4605=？",
        "answer": 4.190659643027607
    },
    {
        "question": "682504039÷803=？",
        "answer": 5.92938968055898
    },
    {
        "question": "70093÷872=？",
        "answer": 1.9051581633740393
    },
    {
        "question": "1×26661=？",
        "answer": 4.4258764348879325
    },
    {
        "question": "1×51093=？",
        "answer": 4.708361403664738
    },
    {
        "question": "188412365÷4144253=？",
        "answer": 1.6576631404501854
    },
    {
        "question": "2703674÷881709=？",
        "answer": 0.4866290507913501
    },
    {
        "question": "34599068÷966951=？",
        "answer": 1.5536599334219177
    },
    {
        "question": "289×1213=？",
        "answer": 5.544758643623121
    },
    {
        "question": "62698813÷5968=？",
        "answer": 4.021430504477273
    },
    {
        "question": "25033×22267=？",
        "answer": 8.746174608485042
    },
    {
        "question": "5235×3893=？",
        "answer": 7.309201089733023
    },
    {
        "question": "232×23995=？",
        "answer": 6.74560873915934
    },
    {
        "question": "15×6396737=？",
        "answer": 7.982049754247723
    },
    {
        "question": "54361022÷27563951=？",
        "answer": 0.2949461437707181
    },
    {
        "question": "17×10653588=？",
        "answer": 8.257944818934433
    },
    {
        "question": "29535×491=？",
        "answer": 7.161418467316768
    },
    {
        "question": "502018777÷32098105=？",
        "answer": 1.194240567966848
    },
    {
        "question": "138×4622=？",
        "answer": 5.804709027544327
    },
    {
        "question": "758081786÷230635=？",
        "answer": 3.516790847926436
    },
    {
        "question": "275678037÷5458899=？",
        "answer": 1.7032971085592048
    },
    {
        "question": "484795032÷19538725=？",
        "answer": 1.394661940282132
    },
    {
        "question": "104081×9502=？",
        "answer": 8.995186482315383
    },
    {
        "question": "2182196÷1718627=？",
        "answer": 0.10371212500056833
    },
    {
        "question": "816267390÷11189=？",
        "answer": 4.86304117287036
    },
    {
        "question": "75220577÷1650310=？",
        "answer": 1.65877112920296
    },
    {
        "question": "798540×682=？",
        "answer": 8.736081050101776
    },
    {
        "question": "15201×41352=？",
        "answer": 8.798368678169968
    },
    {
        "question": "6324÷780=？",
        "answer": 0.9088972585696911
    },
    {
        "question": "406189540÷1923609=？",
        "answer": 2.324611935125175
    },
    {
        "question": "45811×4892=？",
        "answer": 8.350456220379183
    },
    {
        "question": "197116157÷1317=？",
        "answer": 5.175136448548302
    },
    {
        "question": "16×50042017=？",
        "answer": 8.903454788759566
    },
    {
        "question": "4×7047=？",
        "answer": 4.45006426282523
    },
    {
        "question": "14663135÷11673=？",
        "answer": 3.0990443475131926
    },
    {
        "question": "11756÷1479=？",
        "answer": 0.9002914034036825
    },
    {
        "question": "19744×7401=？",
        "answer": 8.164725546562547
    },
    {
        "question": "9561784÷970360=？",
        "answer": 0.99360604296917
    },
    {
        "question": "525×98260=？",
        "answer": 7.71253606320476
    },
    {
        "question": "813694÷3815=？",
        "answer": 2.3289665713248464
    },
    {
        "question": "63×1609612=？",
        "answer": 8.006061750599269
    },
    {
        "question": "6×650247=？",
        "answer": 6.591229607581502
    },
    {
        "question": "197482÷8950=？",
        "answer": 1.3437044815735173
    },
    {
        "question": "9371÷253=？",
        "answer": 1.5686654167032965
    },
    {
        "question": "668×3008=？",
        "answer": 6.30305429439515
    },
    {
        "question": "1212005×395=？",
        "answer": 8.680101507096934
    },
    {
        "question": "264928841÷180269144=？",
        "answer": 0.16720784304581757
    },
    {
        "question": "6×42403943=？",
        "answer": 8.405557492436834
    },
    {
        "question": "15566×225=？",
        "answer": 6.544359544224115
    },
    {
        "question": "182×5651=？",
        "answer": 6.012196695282973
    },
    {
        "question": "21413123÷445=？",
        "answer": 4.682320000673954
    },
    {
        "question": "13779×386=？",
        "answer": 6.725805004809341
    },
    {
        "question": "40×14388=？",
        "answer": 5.760060420474436
    },
    {
        "question": "1690588÷2009=？",
        "answer": 2.9250578452270752
    },
    {
        "question": "3475÷864=？",
        "answer": 0.6044410664472394
    },
    {
        "question": "325491÷5385=？",
        "answer": 1.7813532769618394
    },
    {
        "question": "1829565÷426177=？",
        "answer": 0.6327578355998197
    },
    {
        "question": "437×2629=？",
        "answer": 6.060272023076784
    },
    {
        "question": "11085286÷514562=？",
        "answer": 1.3333091916260793
    },
    {
        "question": "1×70539510=？",
        "answer": 7.848432438531992
    },
    {
        "question": "128×876=？",
        "answer": 5.049714075815949
    },
    {
        "question": "1348×2418=？",
        "answer": 6.513146188724054
    },
    {
        "question": "3207÷885=？",
        "answer": 0.559155689230615
    },
    {
        "question": "17346862÷38957=？",
        "answer": 2.6486354181931464
    },
    {
        "question": "360×112099=？",
        "answer": 7.605904239174758
    },
    {
        "question": "107×157119=？",
        "answer": 7.22561248402508
    },
    {
        "question": "137906×3452=？",
        "answer": 8.677653948869528
    },
    {
        "question": "6592012÷554=？",
        "answer": 4.075508224544525
    },
    {
        "question": "63×10581095=？",
        "answer": 8.823871163074319
    },
    {
        "question": "8489÷2945=？",
        "answer": 0.45977123445879026
    },
    {
        "question": "14798444÷232016=？",
        "answer": 1.8046981181838095
    },
    {
        "question": "18×906=？",
        "answer": 4.212400702780119
    },
    {
        "question": "1745×257=？",
        "answer": 5.6517285546264935
    },
    {
        "question": "3904÷3266=？",
        "answer": 0.07749362859400485
    },
    {
        "question": "5462300÷4596485=？",
        "answer": 0.07494970155084066
    },
    {
        "question": "127220147÷581=？",
        "answer": 5.340379760667916
    },
    {
        "question": "1343÷514=？",
        "answer": 0.4171128936734396
    },
    {
        "question": "1944788÷158993=？",
        "answer": 1.087494262082935
    },
    {
        "question": "22×233=？",
        "answer": 3.709778601848225
    },
    {
        "question": "501046866÷11216=？",
        "answer": 4.650040349382903
    },
    {
        "question": "5978809÷316=？",
        "answer": 4.276927596981542
    },
    {
        "question": "3×4276=？",
        "answer": 4.108158951256403
    },
    {
        "question": "9054058÷176235=？",
        "answer": 1.7107511093863927
    },
    {
        "question": "13664635÷1770=？",
        "answer": 3.8876247692568486
    },
    {
        "question": "18447÷388=？",
        "answer": 1.6770940221701036
    },
    {
        "question": "361×236=？",
        "answer": 4.930419204875765
    },
    {
        "question": "452459842÷802919=？",
        "answer": 2.7509083044823956
    },
    {
        "question": "1×4000110=？",
        "answer": 6.602071934262
    },
    {
        "question": "1×5194039=？",
        "answer": 6.715505206252315
    },
    {
        "question": "822897243÷1125779=？",
        "answer": 2.86389246410577
    },
    {
        "question": "4×359=？",
        "answer": 3.1571544399062814
    },
    {
        "question": "165704147÷6665846=？",
        "answer": 1.395478101436971
    },
    {
        "question": "52415×3800=？",
        "answer": 8.29923918674938
    },
    {
        "question": "1×13372471=？",
        "answer": 7.126211664742143
    },
    {
        "question": "102713464÷1223425=？",
        "answer": 1.9240500251835706
    },
    {
        "question": "1×725307=？",
        "answer": 5.860521868895226
    },
    {
        "question": "15038÷10647=？",
        "answer": 0.14996282642235406
    },
    {
        "question": "243013÷60543=？",
        "answer": 0.6035655697158971
    },
    {
        "question": "10478×20127=？",
        "answer": 8.32405744070746
    },
    {
        "question": "4181920÷308321=？",
        "answer": 1.1323726146284894
    },
    {
        "question": "41713781÷700372=？",
        "answer": 1.774950781530457
    },
    {
        "question": "401252504÷7524237=？",
        "answer": 1.726955289025765
    },
    {
        "question": "1648849÷75081=？",
        "answer": 1.341650836862248
    },
    {
        "question": "370884496÷18997873=？",
        "answer": 1.2905336988879577
    },
    {
        "question": "40×24329991=？",
        "answer": 8.988201939607277
    },
    {
        "question": "7×1042=？",
        "answer": 3.8629657589777624
    },
    {
        "question": "2727300÷1398487=？",
        "answer": 0.2900744788556556
    },
    {
        "question": "18×506090=？",
        "answer": 6.959500261128305
    },
    {
        "question": "13289×311=？",
        "answer": 6.616252690449489
    },
    {
        "question": "941993×222=？",
        "answer": 8.320400649990152
    },
    {
        "question": "1395×706=？",
        "answer": 5.99337890866142
    },
    {
        "question": "30×43745=？",
        "answer": 6.118049675586495
    },
    {
        "question": "948177666÷309080=？",
        "answer": 3.486818817872726
    },
    {
        "question": "50780÷21748=？",
        "answer": 0.3682733722080303
    },
    {
        "question": "9691÷221=？",
        "answer": 1.6419763198851622
    },
    {
        "question": "2×109853=？",
        "answer": 5.341841917327021
    },
    {
        "question": "5278×65754=？",
        "answer": 8.540391563199254
    },
    {
        "question": "172083×1008=？",
        "answer": 8.239198500805095
    },
    {
        "question": "582892÷316=？",
        "answer": 3.265901012193755
    },
    {
        "question": "9259871÷74924=？",
        "answer": 2.0919839813435597
    },
    {
        "question": "804×1287=？",
        "answer": 6.014834595652838
    },
    {
        "question": "53461469÷4468=？",
        "answer": 4.077927723568955
    },
    {
        "question": "1668×5782=？",
        "answer": 6.984274133636359
    },
    {
        "question": "296×827=？",
        "answer": 5.388797220611485
    },
    {
        "question": "2282÷831=？",
        "answer": 0.43871461629808484
    },
    {
        "question": "19453×268=？",
        "answer": 6.7171213808204175
    },
    {
        "question": "88×361=？",
        "answer": 4.501989874055827
    },
    {
        "question": "115×752623=？",
        "answer": 7.937275326487942
    },
    {
        "question": "19×250=？",
        "answer": 3.6766936096248664
    },
    {
        "question": "28×32086=？",
        "answer": 5.953473610506725
    },
    {
        "question": "61×2943=？",
        "answer": 5.254120097110378
    },
    {
        "question": "22748813÷1170521=？",
        "answer": 1.288579531067314
    },
    {
        "question": "1468×42565=？",
        "answer": 7.795778693308442
    },
    {
        "question": "120×300308=？",
        "answer": 7.556748147709069
    },
    {
        "question": "54×3585=？",
        "answer": 5.2868829198267875
    },
    {
        "question": "93381÷32877=？",
        "answer": 0.45336633874839133
    },
    {
        "question": "328873÷111322=？",
        "answer": 0.47044721977059767
    },
    {
        "question": "869068107÷7576=？",
        "answer": 5.059613846512422
    },
    {
        "question": "271×720=？",
        "answer": 5.290301787305674
    },
    {
        "question": "8791969÷199696=？",
        "answer": 1.643716782274098
    },
    {
        "question": "543477400÷203279012=？",
        "answer": 0.427088947827935
    },
    {
        "question": "2×59312158=？",
        "answer": 8.074173721255942
    },
    {
        "question": "140307939÷680738=？",
        "answer": 2.314102250903825
    },
    {
        "question": "66824÷3256=？",
        "answer": 1.312248072180638
    },
    {
        "question": "105588308÷18079233=？",
        "answer": 0.7664358287201335
    },
    {
        "question": "768233×988=？",
        "answer": 8.880249903248709
    },
    {
        "question": "431020971÷4852298=？",
        "answer": 1.9485509360832194
    },
    {
        "question": "57744÷5552=？",
        "answer": 1.0170574072686334
    },
    {
        "question": "751÷207=？",
        "answer": 0.5596695915472506
    },
    {
        "question": "14768×5492=？",
        "answer": 7.9090522122465545
    },
    {
        "question": "54023891÷832=？",
        "answer": 4.812462534178505
    },
    {
        "question": "1471×53481=？",
        "answer": 7.895812191931194
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1042=？",
        "answer": 3.0178677189635055
    },
    {
        "question": "1125×745=？",
        "answer": 5.923308795195674
    },
    {
        "question": "510×567=？",
        "answer": 5.461153234990843
    },
    {
        "question": "6×7149252=？",
        "answer": 7.632411855923756
    },
    {
        "question": "694×433580=？",
        "answer": 8.47842871148988
    },
    {
        "question": "6337981÷30190=？",
        "answer": 2.322087819905099
    },
    {
        "question": "1524×45359=？",
        "answer": 7.839648438389553
    },
    {
        "question": "908642÷22926=？",
        "answer": 1.598064519188277
    },
    {
        "question": "15×280=？",
        "answer": 3.6232492903979003
    },
    {
        "question": "18565139÷8190=？",
        "answer": 3.3554143034423194
    },
    {
        "question": "43587435÷2597=？",
        "answer": 4.2248893631112
    },
    {
        "question": "57×5990205=？",
        "answer": 8.533316540974216
    },
    {
        "question": "855521917÷2030=？",
        "answer": 5.6247351019840535
    },
    {
        "question": "21449611÷2053=？",
        "answer": 4.019030471062256
    },
    {
        "question": "441224÷152408=？",
        "answer": 0.4616513634696389
    },
    {
        "question": "2827×1841=？",
        "answer": 6.7163795969935345
    },
    {
        "question": "343259731÷1844936=？",
        "answer": 2.26964155253272
    },
    {
        "question": "18×1310249=？",
        "answer": 7.3726263420185605
    },
    {
        "question": "2961×5260=？",
        "answer": 7.1924241515430385
    },
    {
        "question": "362÷239=？",
        "answer": 0.18031066958502803
    },
    {
        "question": "208123691÷57420=？",
        "answer": 3.5592583311907386
    },
    {
        "question": "188282×4945=？",
        "answer": 8.968975098826473
    },
    {
        "question": "108185×2336=？",
        "answer": 8.402639887853942
    },
    {
        "question": "17×21611020=？",
        "answer": 8.565124186638075
    },
    {
        "question": "785×206545=？",
        "answer": 8.209884342871256
    },
    {
        "question": "78049×216=？",
        "answer": 7.226821094202614
    },
    {
        "question": "96×525805=？",
        "answer": 7.703095944635103
    },
    {
        "question": "1164÷372=？",
        "answer": 0.4954100404319722
    },
    {
        "question": "5161504÷446412=？",
        "answer": 1.063040407885576
    },
    {
        "question": "714722×762=？",
        "answer": 8.73609212175132
    },
    {
        "question": "6×21759=？",
        "answer": 5.1157901825650525
    },
    {
        "question": "129959÷653=？",
        "answer": 2.298893179629998
    },
    {
        "question": "23398918÷5727=？",
        "answer": 3.6112685923526326
    },
    {
        "question": "190×1011=？",
        "answer": 5.28350475654383
    },
    {
        "question": "1243×747263=？",
        "answer": 8.967944607761668
    },
    {
        "question": "200855944÷9184594=？",
        "answer": 1.3398247251719992
    },
    {
        "question": "3×33582=？",
        "answer": 5.003227812010036
    },
    {
        "question": "1×12939998=？",
        "answer": 7.111934209208336
    },
    {
        "question": "596580÷17508=？",
        "answer": 1.532432151857292
    },
    {
        "question": "202592407÷364352=？",
        "answer": 2.745102006526971
    },
    {
        "question": "22406646÷2340303=？",
        "answer": 0.9811047635073741
    },
    {
        "question": "612761099÷861918=？",
        "answer": 2.8518252359491933
    },
    {
        "question": "862×1539=？",
        "answer": 6.122745885656191
    },
    {
        "question": "2343953÷972670=？",
        "answer": 0.38198337797111054
    },
    {
        "question": "62828×977=？",
        "answer": 7.78804779878425
    },
    {
        "question": "7×6131945=？",
        "answer": 7.632696290843753
    },
    {
        "question": "125289258÷4347244=？",
        "answer": 1.4596998204800093
    },
    {
        "question": "87×622=？",
        "answer": 4.733309637309437
    },
    {
        "question": "3×1629119=？",
        "answer": 6.68907406349457
    },
    {
        "question": "541236÷1104=？",
        "answer": 2.6904176023398216
    },
    {
        "question": "9429102÷4722=？",
        "answer": 3.3003443510322428
    },
    {
        "question": "26491745÷3643=？",
        "answer": 3.8616513947907225
    },
    {
        "question": "478165÷10643=？",
        "answer": 1.6525137219600414
    },
    {
        "question": "8969039÷933668=？",
        "answer": 0.9825534381555481
    },
    {
        "question": "1524×25083=？",
        "answer": 7.582364445156211
    },
    {
        "question": "191239403÷1474=？",
        "answer": 5.113079895747684
    },
    {
        "question": "6115438÷1388647=？",
        "answer": 0.6438357072781619
    },
    {
        "question": "15223152÷357=？",
        "answer": 4.629836367628545
    },
    {
        "question": "2×246508069=？",
        "answer": 8.692861135361692
    },
    {
        "question": "101×378039=？",
        "answer": 7.581857979469326
    },
    {
        "question": "86090÷3483=？",
        "answer": 1.3929992333596217
    },
    {
        "question": "344×1611590=？",
        "answer": 8.743813006476321
    },
    {
        "question": "4×96715=？",
        "answer": 5.5875538274794865
    },
    {
        "question": "3316923÷3410=？",
        "answer": 2.9879810108075833
    },
    {
        "question": "316065÷63106=？",
        "answer": 0.6997057530464712
    },
    {
        "question": "18557889÷1004476=？",
        "answer": 1.2665890081696376
    },
    {
        "question": "2×1217624=？",
        "answer": 6.386543195344128
    },
    {
        "question": "99623746÷7483=？",
        "answer": 4.124287122594355
    },
    {
        "question": "3590×207014=？",
        "answer": 8.871094165615661
    },
    {
        "question": "977×79262=？",
        "answer": 7.888959590308986
    },
    {
        "question": "62703054÷392612=？",
        "answer": 2.2033251245171788
    },
    {
        "question": "1101×2914=？",
        "answer": 6.506276866405723
    },
    {
        "question": "466896×213=？",
        "answer": 7.997599756689807
    },
    {
        "question": "30894799÷3637=？",
        "answer": 3.9291420730071387
    },
    {
        "question": "106369×711=？",
        "answer": 7.878684677085562
    },
    {
        "question": "13115÷3008=？",
        "answer": 0.6394904630067678
    },
    {
        "question": "4931026÷1126=？",
        "answer": 3.641398901942146
    },
    {
        "question": "3609625÷422=？",
        "answer": 3.932149634907941
    },
    {
        "question": "265×46127=？",
        "answer": 7.087201083892719
    },
    {
        "question": "61×156117=？",
        "answer": 6.978780032142371
    },
    {
        "question": "4×15792211=？",
        "answer": 7.800502929308254
    },
    {
        "question": "319÷226=？",
        "answer": 0.14968224390978024
    },
    {
        "question": "9679833÷1050=？",
        "answer": 3.964678565696709
    },
    {
        "question": "21389÷211=？",
        "answer": 2.005908025176873
    },
    {
        "question": "4×6130103=？",
        "answer": 7.389527763065925
    },
    {
        "question": "678834÷1343=？",
        "answer": 2.7036875735440917
    },
    {
        "question": "13074×12985=？",
        "answer": 8.229850434595221
    },
    {
        "question": "1×2743562=？",
        "answer": 6.438314778985763
    },
    {
        "question": "1082961÷734336=？",
        "answer": 0.16871799739993243
    },
    {
        "question": "29073×709=？",
        "answer": 7.314136083473002
    },
    {
        "question": "5×530=？",
        "answer": 3.423245873936808
    },
    {
        "question": "1×4309950=？",
        "answer": 6.63447223191246
    },
    {
        "question": "285564737÷3508312=？",
        "answer": 1.9106063685630157
    },
    {
        "question": "189219÷1810=？",
        "answer": 2.0192861680890823
    },
    {
        "question": "164748÷61386=？",
        "answer": 0.4287508160208363
    },
    {
        "question": "12304202÷1192=？",
        "answer": 4.013777196991794
    },
    {
        "question": "1×256957=？",
        "answer": 5.409860453194433
    },
    {
        "question": "1×647=？",
        "answer": 2.8109042806687006
    },
    {
        "question": "57×48842=？",
        "answer": 6.444668294958029
    },
    {
        "question": "151737÷38908=？",
        "answer": 0.5910525861510353
    },
    {
        "question": "956÷223=？",
        "answer": 0.6321530292279394
    },
    {
        "question": "224361429÷232=？",
        "answer": 5.9854602125583565
    },
    {
        "question": "19042×12659=？",
        "answer": 8.382111960685908
    },
    {
        "question": "3×14248488=？",
        "answer": 7.6308900356890135
    },
    {
        "question": "11888446÷1431=？",
        "answer": 3.9194854557006003
    },
    {
        "question": "69×518874=？",
        "answer": 7.553911000130528
    },
    {
        "question": "1286528÷13958=？",
        "answer": 1.9645960486459892
    },
    {
        "question": "33×3254=？",
        "answer": 5.0309314884787275
    },
    {
        "question": "1×46189885=？",
        "answer": 7.664546880975111
    },
    {
        "question": "10625÷2662=？",
        "answer": 0.6011208875836929
    },
    {
        "question": "4×114826=？",
        "answer": 5.662100227630776
    },
    {
        "question": "12×200768=？",
        "answer": 6.381875738729257
    },
    {
        "question": "2463707÷3167=？",
        "answer": 2.890940994077662
    },
    {
        "question": "236292÷215=？",
        "answer": 3.041010558311477
    },
    {
        "question": "1×4956969=？",
        "answer": 6.695216202913414
    },
    {
        "question": "4652×15276=？",
        "answer": 7.851649355757691
    },
    {
        "question": "275613258÷20658754=？",
        "answer": 1.125195980691761
    },
    {
        "question": "3×12958=？",
        "answer": 4.58965923032897
    },
    {
        "question": "47×10084=？",
        "answer": 5.675730694940126
    },
    {
        "question": "11224544÷675=？",
        "answer": 4.220864933877176
    },
    {
        "question": "2722×8744=？",
        "answer": 7.376598269808962
    },
    {
        "question": "22409097÷4593=？",
        "answer": 3.6883279110806146
    },
    {
        "question": "244÷242=？",
        "answer": 0.0035744603582981357
    },
    {
        "question": "890543÷780178=？",
        "answer": 0.057461194666992045
    },
    {
        "question": "3837×10394=？",
        "answer": 7.600774511685157
    },
    {
        "question": "239142411÷84715=？",
        "answer": 3.4506962882494365
    },
    {
        "question": "1×150642681=？",
        "answer": 8.177948036251472
    },
    {
        "question": "88058568÷327=？",
        "answer": 5.430223866065369
    },
    {
        "question": "2351099÷362696=？",
        "answer": 0.8117281507862738
    },
    {
        "question": "6647÷244=？",
        "answer": 1.4352358524354114
    },
    {
        "question": "9186700÷858027=？",
        "answer": 1.0296585800843412
    },
    {
        "question": "2×109039566=？",
        "answer": 8.338614109912276
    },
    {
        "question": "504001÷10487=？",
        "answer": 1.6817801301357291
    },
    {
        "question": "17515÷3191=？",
        "answer": 0.7394833374602008
    },
    {
        "question": "41659×6572=？",
        "answer": 8.43740639551411
    },
    {
        "question": "85×661=？",
        "answer": 4.749620385199933
    },
    {
        "question": "8239781÷455608=？",
        "answer": 1.2573243277774198
    },
    {
        "question": "4×6183=？",
        "answer": 4.393259237826838
    },
    {
        "question": "1×8138290=？",
        "answer": 6.910533161451864
    },
    {
        "question": "109490÷14380=？",
        "answer": 0.8816155697216104
    },
    {
        "question": "12×241983=？",
        "answer": 6.462966102666383
    },
    {
        "question": "3019093÷269=？",
        "answer": 4.050124211213712
    },
    {
        "question": "101311052÷594219=？",
        "answer": 2.2317102908882864
    },
    {
        "question": "67526×2451=？",
        "answer": 8.218814335674189
    },
    {
        "question": "1×22037=？",
        "answer": 4.343152471662257
    },
    {
        "question": "6696×54883=？",
        "answer": 8.565253287622603
    },
    {
        "question": "961219036÷2078992=？",
        "answer": 2.66496954483176
    },
    {
        "question": "83630×3409=？",
        "answer": 8.454989098013682
    },
    {
        "question": "62×30374=？",
        "answer": 6.274893678108542
    },
    {
        "question": "1×120009=？",
        "answer": 5.079213816912375
    },
    {
        "question": "181×5438=？",
        "answer": 5.9931177781206655
    },
    {
        "question": "98671695÷4736780=？",
        "answer": 1.3187093742886127
    },
    {
        "question": "1×147111899=？",
        "answer": 8.167647801626535
    },
    {
        "question": "12×71389168=？",
        "answer": 8.932813566581446
    },
    {
        "question": "1×63768969=？",
        "answer": 7.804609395484504
    },
    {
        "question": "516×148401=？",
        "answer": 7.88408652907304
    },
    {
        "question": "1296918÷206=？",
        "answer": 3.7990452975242452
    },
    {
        "question": "760185425÷8611148=？",
        "answer": 1.9458584851143665
    },
    {
        "question": "37345×286=？",
        "answer": 7.028598496903789
    },
    {
        "question": "62×12526999=？",
        "answer": 8.890238732252914
    },
    {
        "question": "108×607=？",
        "answer": 4.816612446562207
    },
    {
        "question": "39507÷388=？",
        "answer": 2.0078423267925722
    },
    {
        "question": "1×295597332=？",
        "answer": 8.470700509888868
    },
    {
        "question": "414895166÷3727=？",
        "answer": 5.046578982080543
    },
    {
        "question": "46×7083=？",
        "answer": 5.512975073479963
    },
    {
        "question": "379×997641=？",
        "answer": 8.577613498982931
    },
    {
        "question": "820019÷4763=？",
        "answer": 2.2359433336764676
    },
    {
        "question": "569650904÷15921280=？",
        "answer": 1.5536308107668473
    },
    {
        "question": "14108570÷3744193=？",
        "answer": 0.5761247702724915
    },
    {
        "question": "172503119÷1833359=？",
        "answer": 1.9735494370312971
    },
    {
        "question": "31239406÷235=？",
        "answer": 5.123634905143039
    },
    {
        "question": "1124703×618=？",
        "answer": 8.842026328656017
    },
    {
        "question": "399524÷80027=？",
        "answer": 0.698306336497398
    },
    {
        "question": "46865632÷736212=？",
        "answer": 1.8038515860023425
    },
    {
        "question": "17308269÷10825=？",
        "answer": 3.203825731230183
    },
    {
        "question": "11335173÷10883=？",
        "answer": 3.0176795236425193
    },
    {
        "question": "140699737÷2661316=？",
        "answer": 1.7231968406605869
    },
    {
        "question": "18832÷8465=？",
        "answer": 0.34726948305440547
    },
    {
        "question": "23×13634=？",
        "answer": 5.496351125680031
    },
    {
        "question": "985968983÷4846779=？",
        "answer": 2.30841003542783
    },
    {
        "question": "732317674÷571272=？",
        "answer": 3.1078565773516678
    },
    {
        "question": "3273×9606=？",
        "answer": 7.497488587610948
    },
    {
        "question": "1294×288645=？",
        "answer": 8.572298315246089
    },
    {
        "question": "43804÷1307=？",
        "answer": 1.5252381827091546
    },
    {
        "question": "24×108179=？",
        "answer": 6.414354204244818
    },
    {
        "question": "232×1933=？",
        "answer": 5.651719838919453
    },
    {
        "question": "115873408÷658=？",
        "answer": 5.245757886750552
    },
    {
        "question": "3361231÷7849=？",
        "answer": 2.631684031222515
    },
    {
        "question": "221×7560=？",
        "answer": 6.222914069186317
    },
    {
        "question": "3055×188698=？",
        "answer": 8.760778511703935
    },
    {
        "question": "2×107082862=？",
        "answer": 8.330749965707797
    },
    {
        "question": "1085×51073=？",
        "answer": 7.743621107008948
    },
    {
        "question": "274×1221=？",
        "answer": 5.524466226765271
    },
    {
        "question": "3884×5510=？",
        "answer": 7.330430820087752
    },
    {
        "question": "2×199218=？",
        "answer": 5.600358571456
    },
    {
        "question": "2×3468803=？",
        "answer": 6.841209631786717
    },
    {
        "question": "3×2341158=？",
        "answer": 6.846551979058161
    },
    {
        "question": "410860153÷2334=？",
        "answer": 5.245593171831988
    },
    {
        "question": "98×1120=？",
        "answer": 5.040444098362676
    },
    {
        "question": "193191÷473=？",
        "answer": 2.6111257497610216
    },
    {
        "question": "423913÷1250=？",
        "answer": 2.5303667221298616
    },
    {
        "question": "8×26323506=？",
        "answer": 8.323433719010225
    },
    {
        "question": "10501460÷294=？",
        "answer": 4.552902352073467
    },
    {
        "question": "2×439=？",
        "answer": 2.9434945159061026
    },
    {
        "question": "114424740÷682=？",
        "answer": 5.224735559624475
    },
    {
        "question": "396×474927=？",
        "answer": 8.2743220462165
    },
    {
        "question": "377509652÷2413927=？",
        "answer": 2.194203927574124
    },
    {
        "question": "925÷531=？",
        "answer": 0.24104721165756354
    },
    {
        "question": "5385×783=？",
        "answer": 6.624947469691944
    },
    {
        "question": "559301519÷267601=？",
        "answer": 3.3201582668079754
    },
    {
        "question": "1073803÷685=？",
        "answer": 3.195234041472124
    },
    {
        "question": "1×466083=？",
        "answer": 5.66846326268192
    },
    {
        "question": "654÷367=？",
        "answer": 0.2509116840721779
    },
    {
        "question": "21111×332=？",
        "answer": 6.8456468894510945
    },
    {
        "question": "1×264=？",
        "answer": 2.4216039268698313
    },
    {
        "question": "111599996÷38424=？",
        "answer": 3.4630616054045436
    },
    {
        "question": "4421÷617=？",
        "answer": 0.8552353508726322
    },
    {
        "question": "2347×24391=？",
        "answer": 7.757742695799122
    },
    {
        "question": "17×2818816=？",
        "answer": 7.680515649327667
    },
    {
        "question": "59×13087461=？",
        "answer": 8.887707412154446
    },
    {
        "question": "2×181121=？",
        "answer": 5.558998802992846
    },
    {
        "question": "4236850÷636879=？",
        "answer": 0.8229861596575658
    },
    {
        "question": "6×3031384=？",
        "answer": 7.2597922044081065
    },
    {
        "question": "76197415÷375=？",
        "answer": 5.307908970406127
    },
    {
        "question": "45×90489=？",
        "answer": 6.609808302597631
    },
    {
        "question": "17172÷10468=？",
        "answer": 0.2149571658395578
    },
    {
        "question": "160×19468=？",
        "answer": 6.493441320227394
    },
    {
        "question": "240300×302=？",
        "answer": 7.860760713761051
    },
    {
        "question": "40×1181701=？",
        "answer": 7.674567594373309
    },
    {
        "question": "3509×64201=？",
        "answer": 8.352725160943132
    },
    {
        "question": "205597265÷5057239=？",
        "answer": 1.6091038546343055
    },
    {
        "question": "686027380÷88249317=？",
        "answer": 0.8906300962769504
    },
    {
        "question": "834×278=？",
        "answer": 5.365210846555815
    },
    {
        "question": "1276×177080=？",
        "answer": 8.354020187691955
    },
    {
        "question": "2811×188759=？",
        "answer": 8.724768513496237
    },
    {
        "question": "21×618523=？",
        "answer": 7.113575148395685
    },
    {
        "question": "1×426=？",
        "answer": 2.629409599102719
    },
    {
        "question": "1×5882894=？",
        "answer": 6.769591023191149
    },
    {
        "question": "127279×4536=？",
        "answer": 8.761429800391163
    },
    {
        "question": "1480×254=？",
        "answer": 5.575095432014895
    },
    {
        "question": "260075239÷9810496=？",
        "answer": 1.423408041224201
    },
    {
        "question": "227001815÷11715=？",
        "answer": 4.287287036688923
    },
    {
        "question": "1513×6860=？",
        "answer": 7.0161630437299385
    },
    {
        "question": "14×4368=？",
        "answer": 4.786410665374919
    },
    {
        "question": "23010570÷21969797=？",
        "answer": 0.020101332731780584
    },
    {
        "question": "278936÷7641=？",
        "answer": 1.5623543690553063
    },
    {
        "question": "17133×670=？",
        "answer": 7.05990821758526
    },
    {
        "question": "11×942=？",
        "answer": 4.015443587951102
    },
    {
        "question": "2635107÷6868=？",
        "answer": 2.5839679681891328
    },
    {
        "question": "49678÷6426=？",
        "answer": 0.8882233819262945
    },
    {
        "question": "68×2000=？",
        "answer": 5.133538908370218
    },
    {
        "question": "5000×5409=？",
        "answer": 7.432086985778083
    },
    {
        "question": "325744÷386=？",
        "answer": 2.9262891203548027
    },
    {
        "question": "14090120÷3187=？",
        "answer": 3.645532628366348
    },
    {
        "question": "2044×46471=？",
        "answer": 7.977662909536748
    },
    {
        "question": "355004861÷151401=？",
        "answer": 3.370105556112131
    },
    {
        "question": "296564141÷304=？",
        "answer": 5.989245053618626
    },
    {
        "question": "3955134÷1626908=？",
        "answer": 0.38579820726856207
    },
    {
        "question": "94×3152145=？",
        "answer": 8.471734040606133
    },
    {
        "question": "22858218÷8636786=？",
        "answer": 0.42269021139072277
    },
    {
        "question": "292404964÷99609=？",
        "answer": 3.467686161001523
    },
    {
        "question": "100092÷49626=？",
        "answer": 0.30469009603349534
    },
    {
        "question": "1040927×226=？",
        "answer": 8.371528712741672
    },
    {
        "question": "1552×397396=？",
        "answer": 8.790115208315315
    },
    {
        "question": "793582576÷39999=？",
        "answer": 4.297542989995709
    },
    {
        "question": "13×16330=？",
        "answer": 5.326929537043505
    },
    {
        "question": "3×109093=？",
        "answer": 5.514918139506862
    },
    {
        "question": "319963×1149=？",
        "answer": 8.565419788805425
    },
    {
        "question": "14126÷333=？",
        "answer": 1.6275749684088288
    },
    {
        "question": "1×131372307=？",
        "answer": 8.118503826528006
    },
    {
        "question": "18×1922=？",
        "answer": 4.539025888435833
    },
    {
        "question": "1688×18497=？",
        "answer": 7.494473738849605
    },
    {
        "question": "3×3199=？",
        "answer": 3.9821354948037695
    },
    {
        "question": "2×75968=？",
        "answer": 5.181660688602459
    },
    {
        "question": "72×613=？",
        "answer": 4.644792970949683
    },
    {
        "question": "4×92036962=？",
        "answer": 8.566022266161474
    },
    {
        "question": "53387÷7996=？",
        "answer": 0.8245627315899193
    },
    {
        "question": "6×98618993=？",
        "answer": 8.772111814014009
    },
    {
        "question": "2069×1075=？",
        "answer": 6.347168954917358
    },
    {
        "question": "26960142÷1334=？",
        "answer": 4.305566345732827
    },
    {
        "question": "76×65126=？",
        "answer": 6.6945679971664545
    },
    {
        "question": "33320×317=？",
        "answer": 7.023764254952502
    },
    {
        "question": "1×980=？",
        "answer": 2.9912260756924947
    },
    {
        "question": "100736686÷285205=？",
        "answer": 2.5480305245183947
    },
    {
        "question": "442×16010=？",
        "answer": 6.849813601268392
    },
    {
        "question": "10×5398779=？",
        "answer": 7.732295549911521
    },
    {
        "question": "27×757236=？",
        "answer": 7.31059501687507
    },
    {
        "question": "115561÷99716=？",
        "answer": 0.06404644240348373
    },
    {
        "question": "78513959÷40972492=？",
        "answer": 0.28245449773472764
    },
    {
        "question": "347741÷166140=？",
        "answer": 0.32078169256098454
    },
    {
        "question": "823413÷293297=？",
        "answer": 0.44831009852849946
    },
    {
        "question": "152965÷1248=？",
        "answer": 2.088377485695187
    },
    {
        "question": "7002583÷1031=？",
        "answer": 3.8319995998348486
    },
    {
        "question": "795×205=？",
        "answer": 5.212120989712225
    },
    {
        "question": "31498×16845=？",
        "answer": 8.72475399397851
    },
    {
        "question": "2×4072652=？",
        "answer": 6.910907297737068
    },
    {
        "question": "10×1982965=？",
        "answer": 7.297315048829099
    },
    {
        "question": "11113÷4007=？",
        "answer": 0.44301197191505476
    },
    {
        "question": "508704÷280112=？",
        "answer": 0.2591334381532138
    },
    {
        "question": "1×5443=？",
        "answer": 3.735838334317074
    },
    {
        "question": "12721285÷8483626=？",
        "answer": 0.17594946797138675
    },
    {
        "question": "53×5726=？",
        "answer": 5.482127213286369
    },
    {
        "question": "65696÷305=？",
        "answer": 2.333239088343712
    },
    {
        "question": "165×273=？",
        "answer": 4.653646591254662
    },
    {
        "question": "6×407143=？",
        "answer": 6.3878982227618994
    },
    {
        "question": "346×1380419=？",
        "answer": 8.679087027055205
    },
    {
        "question": "4×5661797=？",
        "answer": 7.355014285293765
    },
    {
        "question": "455×856=？",
        "answer": 5.590485161334265
    },
    {
        "question": "131905×3149=？",
        "answer": 8.618433918891423
    },
    {
        "question": "260820÷2224=？",
        "answer": 2.069206107664461
    },
    {
        "question": "34541870÷198175=？",
        "answer": 2.2412969784881085
    },
    {
        "question": "2×357875107=？",
        "answer": 8.854761486542055
    },
    {
        "question": "135607801÷49966443=？",
        "answer": 0.4336062394718915
    },
    {
        "question": "5891234÷39639=？",
        "answer": 2.172083583559786
    },
    {
        "question": "603×15768=？",
        "answer": 6.978093923411538
    },
    {
        "question": "3111004÷2697592=？",
        "answer": 0.06192430450747164
    },
    {
        "question": "2×354912=？",
        "answer": 5.851150679276657
    },
    {
        "question": "321×993=？",
        "answer": 5.503454280900253
    },
    {
        "question": "255621310÷98366099=？",
        "answer": 0.41475160768293096
    },
    {
        "question": "52219548÷22480=？",
        "answer": 3.366036801456325
    },
    {
        "question": "147299÷62352=？",
        "answer": 0.3733494100168529
    },
    {
        "question": "72×19247=？",
        "answer": 6.141695542744378
    },
    {
        "question": "2850592÷748=？",
        "answer": 3.5810334641210404
    },
    {
        "question": "3×56455236=？",
        "answer": 8.228825481945279
    },
    {
        "question": "986267617÷13224283=？",
        "answer": 1.8726226392054972
    },
    {
        "question": "794244484÷164692100=？",
        "answer": 0.6832814400482121
    },
    {
        "question": "411×399805=？",
        "answer": 8.215690043020926
    },
    {
        "question": "1×6985=？",
        "answer": 3.844166410450201
    },
    {
        "question": "70601560÷508=？",
        "answer": 5.14295058497053
    },
    {
        "question": "335849848÷85216=？",
        "answer": 3.595624011321521
    },
    {
        "question": "69179606÷12350=？",
        "answer": 3.748311126643613
    },
    {
        "question": "702325÷278=？",
        "answer": 3.4024933319440396
    },
    {
        "question": "86×2368=？",
        "answer": 5.30888014929445
    },
    {
        "question": "163058÷88257=？",
        "answer": 0.26659295016825424
    },
    {
        "question": "353482109÷560846=？",
        "answer": 2.799523810687703
    },
    {
        "question": "269078879÷1422=？",
        "answer": 5.276980013321906
    },
    {
        "question": "10325×91577=？",
        "answer": 8.975676472562416
    },
    {
        "question": "1903565÷613605=？",
        "answer": 0.49167882118933987
    },
    {
        "question": "10763÷452=？",
        "answer": 1.3767949054642235
    },
    {
        "question": "57×11900942=？",
        "answer": 8.8314561943096
    },
    {
        "question": "17×45618=？",
        "answer": 5.889585162248671
    },
    {
        "question": "778181959÷85332412=？",
        "answer": 0.9599671365643184
    },
    {
        "question": "316×26279=？",
        "answer": 6.919295917526507
    },
    {
        "question": "201566469÷1993672=？",
        "answer": 2.004764578505973
    },
    {
        "question": "834×441770=？",
        "answer": 8.56636227082677
    },
    {
        "question": "35360×16538=？",
        "answer": 8.76699524393468
    },
    {
        "question": "89×546=？",
        "answer": 4.68658264934965
    },
    {
        "question": "909984131÷254820=？",
        "answer": 3.5528003074531163
    },
    {
        "question": "18×16776363=？",
        "answer": 8.479970319746535
    },
    {
        "question": "8507186÷287=？",
        "answer": 4.47190403153236
    },
    {
        "question": "72138143÷10969809=？",
        "answer": 0.8179658924427378
    },
    {
        "question": "5×14544687=？",
        "answer": 7.8616743840521
    },
    {
        "question": "3447×5261=？",
        "answer": 7.258509585205107
    },
    {
        "question": "174×1346643=？",
        "answer": 8.369801726203452
    },
    {
        "question": "37×288=？",
        "answer": 4.027594211826226
    },
    {
        "question": "86×3329542=？",
        "answer": 8.456882948848222
    },
    {
        "question": "289849613÷253=？",
        "answer": 6.05905220367216
    },
    {
        "question": "19096÷3391=？",
        "answer": 0.7506146162206119
    },
    {
        "question": "6413280÷234946=？",
        "answer": 1.4361121458942145
    },
    {
        "question": "4×80364592=？",
        "answer": 8.507124735522686
    },
    {
        "question": "1×452=？",
        "answer": 2.655138434811382
    },
    {
        "question": "101949÷473=？",
        "answer": 2.333521829478242
    },
    {
        "question": "28111334÷1630618=？",
        "answer": 1.2365292230934488
    },
    {
        "question": "587448167÷67339=？",
        "answer": 3.9407028902974592
    },
    {
        "question": "10406887÷300226=？",
        "answer": 1.5398725388757555
    },
    {
        "question": "27181÷270=？",
        "answer": 2.0029016664013173
    },
    {
        "question": "304×102688=？",
        "answer": 7.494393279024163
    },
    {
        "question": "228882011÷3549047=？",
        "answer": 1.8094999098623172
    },
    {
        "question": "711957653÷288=？",
        "answer": 6.393061674957174
    },
    {
        "question": "35099÷3476=？",
        "answer": 1.004214975450775
    },
    {
        "question": "18050112÷995679=？",
        "answer": 1.2583605535631592
    },
    {
        "question": "541×5072=？",
        "answer": 6.4383765099802455
    },
    {
        "question": "1928×3060=？",
        "answer": 6.770828456048392
    },
    {
        "question": "83500÷5087=？",
        "answer": 1.2152247378522474
    },
    {
        "question": "1×253774096=？",
        "answer": 8.404447289396156
    },
    {
        "question": "4×52904670=？",
        "answer": 8.325554001089296
    },
    {
        "question": "184×764545=？",
        "answer": 8.14822087544791
    },
    {
        "question": "18068581÷3199=？",
        "answer": 3.751909806883684
    },
    {
        "question": "752×108361=？",
        "answer": 7.911090844819864
    },
    {
        "question": "7417120÷15830=？",
        "answer": 2.670754390563925
    },
    {
        "question": "64919951÷28113072=？",
        "answer": 0.36346987849361206
    },
    {
        "question": "2272×20890=？",
        "answer": 7.6763467670192895
    },
    {
        "question": "50×36928=？",
        "answer": 6.266325791475637
    },
    {
        "question": "1779÷1019=？",
        "answer": 0.24200176407749865
    },
    {
        "question": "84×149830=？",
        "answer": 7.099878065580258
    },
    {
        "question": "1945072×246=？",
        "answer": 8.679870789178448
    },
    {
        "question": "11238×15811=？",
        "answer": 8.249648366429083
    },
    {
        "question": "547504÷88756=？",
        "answer": 0.7901895749398806
    },
    {
        "question": "21×48360=？",
        "answer": 6.006705586922654
    },
    {
        "question": "1294×9811=？",
        "answer": 7.103647552045771
    },
    {
        "question": "21×2522=？",
        "answer": 4.723964376970982
    },
    {
        "question": "164×2233=？",
        "answer": 5.563732571119136
    },
    {
        "question": "22×531=？",
        "answer": 4.067517201903676
    },
    {
        "question": "899035449÷992301=？",
        "answer": 2.9571333872980903
    },
    {
        "question": "27×119093=？",
        "answer": 6.507249999607211
    },
    {
        "question": "19400×202=？",
        "answer": 6.59315309937685
    },
    {
        "question": "902769÷1574=？",
        "answer": 2.7585719094893575
    },
    {
        "question": "203890÷143729=？",
        "answer": 0.15185152190186088
    },
    {
        "question": "31489÷12103=？",
        "answer": 0.41526583562471253
    },
    {
        "question": "2292×2874=？",
        "answer": 6.818701377093559
    },
    {
        "question": "167080×1536=？",
        "answer": 8.409315682288577
    },
    {
        "question": "6×1835071=？",
        "answer": 7.041804122411369
    },
    {
        "question": "4589613÷778=？",
        "answer": 3.7707964700180994
    },
    {
        "question": "562166440÷25649=？",
        "answer": 4.340794478138135
    },
    {
        "question": "45990÷25329=？",
        "answer": 0.2590453655811548
    },
    {
        "question": "5570÷417=？",
        "answer": 1.1257191401999713
    },
    {
        "question": "7×391=？",
        "answer": 3.4372747974101237
    },
    {
        "question": "5×688893=？",
        "answer": 6.537121776144606
    },
    {
        "question": "6473×2266=？",
        "answer": 7.166365512545309
    },
    {
        "question": "1872×150540=？",
        "answer": 8.449957756100341
    },
    {
        "question": "18×1281642=？",
        "answer": 7.363039236107329
    },
    {
        "question": "373×5675=？",
        "answer": 6.325674697673848
    },
    {
        "question": "9×11725565=？",
        "answer": 8.023376287945457
    },
    {
        "question": "17×1137=？",
        "answer": 4.286209386066009
    },
    {
        "question": "29×22600=？",
        "answer": 5.816506437046357
    },
    {
        "question": "277×431=？",
        "answer": 5.07695703922518
    },
    {
        "question": "20101035÷314330=？",
        "answer": 1.8058325872321142
    },
    {
        "question": "7280587÷412745=？",
        "answer": 1.2464845749608215
    },
    {
        "question": "7×743842=？",
        "answer": 6.716578736561104
    },
    {
        "question": "1330×2020=？",
        "answer": 6.429203010413709
    },
    {
        "question": "2×16067=？",
        "answer": 4.506964789348663
    },
    {
        "question": "1×2878517=？",
        "answer": 6.459168798663271
    },
    {
        "question": "2754×756=？",
        "answer": 6.318485731422111
    },
    {
        "question": "5×1120=？",
        "answer": 3.7481880270062002
    },
    {
        "question": "16×207775=？",
        "answer": 6.521713273638326
    },
    {
        "question": "1492×259=？",
        "answer": 5.587068587217902
    },
    {
        "question": "257718569÷46269=？",
        "answer": 3.7458555979247983
    },
    {
        "question": "36376289÷11719=？",
        "answer": 3.491927837307675
    },
    {
        "question": "85×813=？",
        "answer": 4.839509471308361
    },
    {
        "question": "217648÷13472=？",
        "answer": 1.2083226065592783
    },
    {
        "question": "11526777÷720871=？",
        "answer": 1.2038503366743956
    },
    {
        "question": "22101÷599=？",
        "answer": 1.5669851021852352
    },
    {
        "question": "1873×74520=？",
        "answer": 8.144810623599442
    },
    {
        "question": "429×1761=？",
        "answer": 5.8782166481520015
    },
    {
        "question": "11644827÷1130=？",
        "answer": 4.013054597390417
    },
    {
        "question": "197×3330=？",
        "answer": 5.816910459667913
    },
    {
        "question": "12140÷472=？",
        "answer": 1.410276688105151
    },
    {
        "question": "606184287÷7355=？",
        "answer": 4.916021997697126
    },
    {
        "question": "29163×209=？",
        "answer": 6.784978483961022
    },
    {
        "question": "17×1687924=？",
        "answer": 7.457801809684686
    },
    {
        "question": "156226825÷33125532=？",
        "answer": 0.673592744858982
    },
    {
        "question": "661×7011=？",
        "answer": 6.665981426597529
    },
    {
        "question": "3×83256932=？",
        "answer": 8.397541657907224
    },
    {
        "question": "209183060÷42953683=？",
        "answer": 0.6875261040117475
    },
    {
        "question": "7496877÷1351=？",
        "answer": 3.7442250364860157
    },
    {
        "question": "7819172÷3773540=？",
        "answer": 0.3164118085755024
    },
    {
        "question": "14971370÷1974767=？",
        "answer": 0.8797456823913752
    },
    {
        "question": "125×1228704=？",
        "answer": 8.186357285113663
    },
    {
        "question": "104486×2755=？",
        "answer": 8.459179706744312
    },
    {
        "question": "27935×2325=？",
        "answer": 7.812571632922156
    },
    {
        "question": "243960924÷1681=？",
        "answer": 5.161752556136098
    },
    {
        "question": "371×647=？",
        "answer": 5.380278190283747
    },
    {
        "question": "334×2289=？",
        "answer": 5.883392259486107
    },
    {
        "question": "5×717=？",
        "answer": 3.554489160003819
    },
    {
        "question": "65078÷1116=？",
        "answer": 1.7657700029774812
    },
    {
        "question": "35×4602=？",
        "answer": 5.2070146586829
    },
    {
        "question": "2×32332427=？",
        "answer": 7.810668301362659
    },
    {
        "question": "5138692÷1189=？",
        "answer": 3.6356707333507696
    },
    {
        "question": "1467118÷221908=？",
        "answer": 0.8202920862100135
    },
    {
        "question": "4141÷1503=？",
        "answer": 0.44014624991546997
    },
    {
        "question": "17627÷567=？",
        "answer": 1.4925953456179561
    },
    {
        "question": "41957606÷129823=？",
        "answer": 2.509459059675104
    },
    {
        "question": "615÷369=？",
        "answer": 0.2218487496163564
    },
    {
        "question": "6×782859=？",
        "answer": 6.671834799113166
    },
    {
        "question": "282648×1230=？",
        "answer": 8.541151028205155
    },
    {
        "question": "19698×626=？",
        "answer": 7.090996466323413
    },
    {
        "question": "62746×242=？",
        "answer": 7.181401411140707
    },
    {
        "question": "145610÷10354=？",
        "answer": 1.148083041224631
    },
    {
        "question": "5420155÷28879=？",
        "answer": 2.2734295554817736
    },
    {
        "question": "2×60052783=？",
        "answer": 8.079563134189533
    },
    {
        "question": "213649482÷297=？",
        "answer": 5.856945394876423
    },
    {
        "question": "610632÷233=？",
        "answer": 3.4184236386144313
    },
    {
        "question": "16519297÷177458=？",
        "answer": 1.968895978822142
    },
    {
        "question": "4×57375633=？",
        "answer": 8.36078748127878
    },
    {
        "question": "35×206695=？",
        "answer": 6.859398015420362
    },
    {
        "question": "138420955÷8771617=？",
        "answer": 1.1981221806413058
    },
    {
        "question": "48291÷4634=？",
        "answer": 1.017910169319453
    },
    {
        "question": "3583÷474=？",
        "answer": 0.8784684664920255
    },
    {
        "question": "30593429÷11966=？",
        "answer": 3.4076791581883157
    },
    {
        "question": "340385073÷64584864=？",
        "answer": 0.7218397571989384
    },
    {
        "question": "17882×48188=？",
        "answer": 8.935354992214053
    },
    {
        "question": "1652×114886=？",
        "answer": 8.278277151801515
    },
    {
        "question": "31223839÷15905=？",
        "answer": 3.292952625475728
    },
    {
        "question": "137550×1406=？",
        "answer": 8.286445915409507
    },
    {
        "question": "14528046÷1421=？",
        "answer": 4.00961312835379
    },
    {
        "question": "40791÷4099=？",
        "answer": 0.9978864339522586
    },
    {
        "question": "23×5847=？",
        "answer": 5.128660929854877
    },
    {
        "question": "414×73724=？",
        "answer": 7.484609231569186
    },
    {
        "question": "2×54863=？",
        "answer": 5.040309547525696
    },
    {
        "question": "16232994÷230880=？",
        "answer": 1.8470123143799784
    },
    {
        "question": "51426÷19395=？",
        "answer": 0.4234929615499738
    },
    {
        "question": "75×1280=？",
        "answer": 4.982271233039568
    },
    {
        "question": "614×58789=？",
        "answer": 7.557464444050516
    },
    {
        "question": "118415×2048=？",
        "answer": 8.384736671621525
    },
    {
        "question": "2532944÷32436=？",
        "answer": 1.8925982964809007
    },
    {
        "question": "200190578÷556=？",
        "answer": 5.556368841906395
    },
    {
        "question": "3228637÷5048=？",
        "answer": 2.8058998732131255
    },
    {
        "question": "73×433102=？",
        "answer": 7.4999130493616315
    },
    {
        "question": "374228÷276393=？",
        "answer": 0.13160923880773087
    },
    {
        "question": "1823305÷308=？",
        "answer": 3.772308606426344
    },
    {
        "question": "177707003÷3056=？",
        "answer": 4.764551192726239
    },
    {
        "question": "96×39137=？",
        "answer": 6.574858765312498
    },
    {
        "question": "153688388÷45616=？",
        "answer": 3.52752385544566
    },
    {
        "question": "751997÷464=？",
        "answer": 3.209698127475532
    },
    {
        "question": "11710852÷14822=？",
        "answer": 2.897681683531731
    },
    {
        "question": "2478×22547=？",
        "answer": 7.747190066873993
    },
    {
        "question": "30189×10483=？",
        "answer": 8.500334313206043
    },
    {
        "question": "1558299÷241=？",
        "answer": 3.810633749395414
    },
    {
        "question": "44×315=？",
        "answer": 4.141763230275788
    },
    {
        "question": "314873×2822=？",
        "answer": 8.948692431395806
    },
    {
        "question": "169×12620=？",
        "answer": 6.3289460595217895
    },
    {
        "question": "750626÷701079=？",
        "answer": 0.0296566447993889
    },
    {
        "question": "1655÷456=？",
        "answer": 0.5598331554473026
    },
    {
        "question": "282895773÷732233=？",
        "answer": 2.586977160715207
    },
    {
        "question": "141×1591187=？",
        "answer": 8.350940334599732
    },
    {
        "question": "4815×544=？",
        "answer": 6.418195191158733
    },
    {
        "question": "75×133448=？",
        "answer": 7.000373332744356
    },
    {
        "question": "13×288679=？",
        "answer": 6.574358544515106
    },
    {
        "question": "3329454÷364846=？",
        "answer": 0.9602634298087905
    },
    {
        "question": "12×19569168=？",
        "answer": 8.370753607694894
    },
    {
        "question": "6675×434=？",
        "answer": 6.461940999549124
    },
    {
        "question": "294488947÷211784143=？",
        "answer": 0.14317555925141373
    },
    {
        "question": "7903×14405=？",
        "answer": 8.056305244555656
    },
    {
        "question": "215005483÷288=？",
        "answer": 5.873057047534427
    },
    {
        "question": "18690×1096=？",
        "answer": 7.311419855527182
    },
    {
        "question": "255491÷3752=？",
        "answer": 1.833112776449889
    },
    {
        "question": "882646÷16920=？",
        "answer": 1.717386198699562
    },
    {
        "question": "15×31095=？",
        "answer": 5.668781820205223
    },
    {
        "question": "1×7028=？",
        "answer": 3.8468317528232574
    },
    {
        "question": "89088331÷5717=？",
        "answer": 4.192652630630796
    },
    {
        "question": "318244÷180152=？",
        "answer": 0.24712113654178006
    },
    {
        "question": "6796170÷19532=？",
        "answer": 2.541517518201538
    },
    {
        "question": "7322×936=？",
        "answer": 6.835905573283617
    },
    {
        "question": "204×100351=？",
        "answer": 7.311151872025367
    },
    {
        "question": "12×918016=？",
        "answer": 7.042031496585638
    },
    {
        "question": "2×1479=？",
        "answer": 3.4709981696608736
    },
    {
        "question": "18×450204=？",
        "answer": 6.908681854431091
    },
    {
        "question": "14577558÷4598780=？",
        "answer": 0.5010421440768879
    },
    {
        "question": "917981÷2254=？",
        "answer": 2.609879780732386
    },
    {
        "question": "644×108819=？",
        "answer": 7.8455905979677665
    },
    {
        "question": "10999135÷7388818=？",
        "answer": 0.17278356324751815
    },
    {
        "question": "433×190292=？",
        "answer": 7.915908427000416
    },
    {
        "question": "117×723=？",
        "answer": 4.927324159040692
    },
    {
        "question": "914171948÷103364=？",
        "answer": 3.9466585831427157
    },
    {
        "question": "104×1800=？",
        "answer": 5.272305844402086
    },
    {
        "question": "14814486÷6796672=？",
        "answer": 0.33839027604745603
    },
    {
        "question": "7×20651=？",
        "answer": 5.1600391267072405
    },
    {
        "question": "57×4681=？",
        "answer": 5.426213496799933
    },
    {
        "question": "6×151955343=？",
        "answer": 8.959867225576973
    },
    {
        "question": "513×5599=？",
        "answer": 6.4582278326068
    },
    {
        "question": "470×1518566=？",
        "answer": 8.853531529931134
    },
    {
        "question": "16717÷12902=？",
        "answer": 0.11250130490231297
    },
    {
        "question": "498×751198=？",
        "answer": 8.572983765747644
    },
    {
        "question": "8×52390478=？",
        "answer": 8.622342347871944
    },
    {
        "question": "11×56441716=？",
        "answer": 8.792992894315693
    },
    {
        "question": "61523÷2397=？",
        "answer": 1.4093694704528195
    },
    {
        "question": "2223÷1489=？",
        "answer": 0.17404476494681442
    },
    {
        "question": "1746×206017=？",
        "answer": 8.555947298095843
    },
    {
        "question": "9405506÷2271252=？",
        "answer": 0.6171168420653019
    },
    {
        "question": "28767325÷16956=？",
        "answer": 3.2295760719381494
    },
    {
        "question": "712110932÷37905=？",
        "answer": 4.27385115193482
    },
    {
        "question": "12378×10484=？",
        "answer": 8.113177490631358
    },
    {
        "question": "31291×14753=？",
        "answer": 8.66429978499551
    },
    {
        "question": "167690÷111331=？",
        "answer": 0.17789105471071626
    },
    {
        "question": "1237÷995=？",
        "answer": 0.09454661888339519
    },
    {
        "question": "15×62626=？",
        "answer": 5.972845932717642
    },
    {
        "question": "10×2595139=？",
        "answer": 7.414160624348746
    },
    {
        "question": "1×428=？",
        "answer": 2.6314437690131722
    },
    {
        "question": "89892÷39051=？",
        "answer": 0.3620888835500983
    },
    {
        "question": "749982312÷1033=？",
        "answer": 5.860950699350238
    },
    {
        "question": "43×68297=？",
        "answer": 6.4678700829498394
    },
    {
        "question": "949317529÷5162108=？",
        "answer": 2.264584413651837
    },
    {
        "question": "17684987÷4794571=？",
        "answer": 0.566854990682193
    },
    {
        "question": "1106626÷226=？",
        "answer": 3.6898924305296488
    },
    {
        "question": "609568÷21396=？",
        "answer": 1.4546895708995826
    },
    {
        "question": "79×4179751=？",
        "answer": 8.518777501642745
    },
    {
        "question": "5873×228=？",
        "answer": 6.126794847843411
    },
    {
        "question": "1942×206=？",
        "answer": 5.60211644594114
    },
    {
        "question": "98×3139969=？",
        "answer": 8.488151436123863
    },
    {
        "question": "9×198655=？",
        "answer": 6.252342009840433
    },
    {
        "question": "111077787÷3107=？",
        "answer": 4.553285965471226
    },
    {
        "question": "461×82662=？",
        "answer": 7.581006834180196
    },
    {
        "question": "551751543÷19729=？",
        "answer": 4.4466384835512045
    },
    {
        "question": "6246393÷2928=？",
        "answer": 3.3290582325737987
    },
    {
        "question": "7024404÷597643=？",
        "answer": 1.070167644413283
    },
    {
        "question": "17549×4944=？",
        "answer": 7.9383308360532325
    },
    {
        "question": "17300638÷5586=？",
        "answer": 3.4909611876464925
    },
    {
        "question": "10602228÷58928=？",
        "answer": 2.2550754379454223
    },
    {
        "question": "842763717÷692=？",
        "answer": 6.08559973546236
    },
    {
        "question": "390060817÷2870=？",
        "answer": 5.133250429339493
    },
    {
        "question": "12294440÷519834=？",
        "answer": 1.373844070486915
    },
    {
        "question": "8446÷5383=？",
        "answer": 0.19562669727320106
    },
    {
        "question": "338×79948=？",
        "answer": 7.431724304071876
    },
    {
        "question": "9114214÷827697=？",
        "answer": 1.0418478404225069
    },
    {
        "question": "1×51306=？",
        "answer": 4.710168156817845
    },
    {
        "question": "145692435÷4047837=？",
        "answer": 1.5562139860207083
    },
    {
        "question": "117990871÷2377=？",
        "answer": 4.695819225343237
    },
    {
        "question": "857×1830=？",
        "answer": 6.195431911653627
    },
    {
        "question": "7×392953=？",
        "answer": 6.439438648757871
    },
    {
        "question": "7330×414=？",
        "answer": 6.482104315762027
    },
    {
        "question": "2×2147424=？",
        "answer": 6.63294779821863
    },
    {
        "question": "92738×8193=？",
        "answer": 8.880700680467815
    },
    {
        "question": "7×269=？",
        "answer": 3.274850320016665
    },
    {
        "question": "37×173503=？",
        "answer": 6.807508712543638
    },
    {
        "question": "78×84366=？",
        "answer": 6.818262061313996
    },
    {
        "question": "61791353÷19327=？",
        "answer": 3.5047632580933588
    },
    {
        "question": "8×152511=？",
        "answer": 6.086391155704357
    },
    {
        "question": "3061÷1126=？",
        "answer": 0.43432493908200726
    },
    {
        "question": "5849090÷26987=？",
        "answer": 2.335933694855557
    },
    {
        "question": "114881÷35177=？",
        "answer": 0.5139894085347827
    },
    {
        "question": "43740÷3519=？",
        "answer": 1.0944595118664266
    },
    {
        "question": "24299514÷11348=？",
        "answer": 3.3306782604979994
    },
    {
        "question": "99×79874=？",
        "answer": 6.898040628553359
    },
    {
        "question": "114448917÷306040=？",
        "answer": 2.5728334941236266
    },
    {
        "question": "2×1909=？",
        "answer": 3.581835924057648
    },
    {
        "question": "160×5738352=？",
        "answer": 8.96290716772464
    },
    {
        "question": "2×46640888=？",
        "answer": 7.969796806064782
    },
    {
        "question": "62155÷297=？",
        "answer": 2.3207196214732613
    },
    {
        "question": "4211×112558=？",
        "answer": 8.675761609103168
    },
    {
        "question": "673487181÷505698=？",
        "answer": 3.124438097844627
    },
    {
        "question": "5×1360969=？",
        "answer": 6.832818237340772
    },
    {
        "question": "65535859÷8905=？",
        "answer": 3.8668450724435193
    },
    {
        "question": "2×357117953=？",
        "answer": 8.85384167921674
    },
    {
        "question": "923144178÷775255582=？",
        "answer": 0.0758246331365048
    },
    {
        "question": "13835÷663=？",
        "answer": 1.3194656350721976
    },
    {
        "question": "2301×26486=？",
        "answer": 7.784932993383463
    },
    {
        "question": "135163×2340=？",
        "answer": 8.500073679969843
    },
    {
        "question": "2×208418=？",
        "answer": 5.619965219711307
    },
    {
        "question": "225×38526=？",
        "answer": 6.9379364384115005
    },
    {
        "question": "782149421÷266967=？",
        "answer": 3.466832146944241
    },
    {
        "question": "12044÷2198=？",
        "answer": 0.73874305875325
    },
    {
        "question": "27302÷3574=？",
        "answer": 0.8830399141513107
    },
    {
        "question": "5854808÷537466=？",
        "answer": 1.0371616615117736
    },
    {
        "question": "4×1144=？",
        "answer": 3.6604860157849677
    },
    {
        "question": "3607157÷1630458=？",
        "answer": 0.34485542919593387
    },
    {
        "question": "3697÷413=？",
        "answer": 0.9518993989167058
    },
    {
        "question": "322383279÷19283441=？",
        "answer": 1.2231879748339434
    },
    {
        "question": "99×1456366=？",
        "answer": 8.158905726034446
    },
    {
        "question": "921464÷411588=？",
        "answer": 0.3500156684953757
    },
    {
        "question": "51184×8272=？",
        "answer": 8.6267447484899
    },
    {
        "question": "77×665=？",
        "answer": 4.709312370475587
    },
    {
        "question": "144823402÷849=？",
        "answer": 5.231931054892542
    },
    {
        "question": "77514×572=？",
        "answer": 7.646776177410824
    },
    {
        "question": "39426609÷5693088=？",
        "answer": 0.8404415290202242
    },
    {
        "question": "162127÷28686=？",
        "answer": 0.7521853525060347
    },
    {
        "question": "4×11699988=？",
        "answer": 7.670245407643658
    },
    {
        "question": "355755752÷107040303=？",
        "answer": 0.5216046008714089
    },
    {
        "question": "74555396÷276=？",
        "answer": 5.43156999923443
    },
    {
        "question": "93559875÷3565181=？",
        "answer": 1.419008049539456
    },
    {
        "question": "25961380÷815=？",
        "answer": 4.503170165307303
    },
    {
        "question": "35×216643=？",
        "answer": 6.879812705362087
    },
    {
        "question": "198665÷388=？",
        "answer": 2.709289636001001
    },
    {
        "question": "10038832÷7931=？",
        "answer": 3.102355236490821
    },
    {
        "question": "7×534=？",
        "answer": 3.572639297042813
    },
    {
        "question": "138985÷2227=？",
        "answer": 1.7952477143801204
    },
    {
        "question": "1×217944602=？",
        "answer": 8.338346116984605
    },
    {
        "question": "259103×1139=？",
        "answer": 8.469996165532324
    },
    {
        "question": "51472762÷227=？",
        "answer": 5.3555516156845115
    },
    {
        "question": "96853312÷408=？",
        "answer": 5.37545431337186
    },
    {
        "question": "278056345÷920667=？",
        "answer": 2.4800302329801136
    },
    {
        "question": "2×1669=？",
        "answer": 3.5234863323432277
    },
    {
        "question": "453340÷24884=？",
        "answer": 1.26050384761652
    },
    {
        "question": "101455049÷1322571=？",
        "answer": 1.8848546692531711
    },
    {
        "question": "11×178392=？",
        "answer": 6.29276805967278
    },
    {
        "question": "3×107049513=？",
        "answer": 8.506705950620145
    },
    {
        "question": "688715÷800=？",
        "answer": 2.934949554896073
    },
    {
        "question": "3967×538=？",
        "answer": 6.3292444761405395
    },
    {
        "question": "179×353=？",
        "answer": 4.800627736367716
    },
    {
        "question": "189482×560=？",
        "answer": 8.025755987104656
    },
    {
        "question": "408818198÷1405=？",
        "answer": 5.463853895358837
    },
    {
        "question": "64703719÷580155=？",
        "answer": 2.0473852039795757
    },
    {
        "question": "77×619=？",
        "answer": 4.6781813741926
    },
    {
        "question": "350831÷610=？",
        "answer": 2.7597681263483143
    },
    {
        "question": "294×930=？",
        "answer": 5.4368302789660925
    },
    {
        "question": "25934510÷196525=？",
        "answer": 2.1204602420104828
    },
    {
        "question": "4159335÷1138=？",
        "answer": 3.56288163853967
    },
    {
        "question": "83182÷1291=？",
        "answer": 1.8091031159183215
    },
    {
        "question": "127×151241=？",
        "answer": 7.283473261195292
    },
    {
        "question": "1×68643981=？",
        "answer": 7.836602462430933
    },
    {
        "question": "712381609÷739067=？",
        "answer": 2.9840288880183343
    },
    {
        "question": "225929×568=？",
        "answer": 8.108320315775384
    },
    {
        "question": "169×1249341=？",
        "answer": 8.32456769719578
    },
    {
        "question": "9277×6985=？",
        "answer": 7.811573967047673
    },
    {
        "question": "590×551=？",
        "answer": 5.512003610493929
    },
    {
        "question": "15×2271235=？",
        "answer": 7.532353331154385
    },
    {
        "question": "1655×465=？",
        "answer": 5.886250951001691
    },
    {
        "question": "2527×76339=？",
        "answer": 8.285351708545225
    },
    {
        "question": "841167945÷511=？",
        "answer": 6.216461814218529
    },
    {
        "question": "533608÷6299=？",
        "answer": 1.9279507236714588
    },
    {
        "question": "417827239÷31304=？",
        "answer": 4.125396914207343
    },
    {
        "question": "30256×8499=？",
        "answer": 8.410179340741065
    },
    {
        "question": "2744×117041=？",
        "answer": 8.506722130786168
    },
    {
        "question": "24037610÷1787=？",
        "answer": 4.12876673214739
    },
    {
        "question": "141×1043312=？",
        "answer": 8.167633315248617
    },
    {
        "question": "331209÷5081=？",
        "answer": 1.81415293452269
    },
    {
        "question": "129683×2053=？",
        "answer": 8.42527199800605
    },
    {
        "question": "151441×5211=？",
        "answer": 8.897164541879025
    },
    {
        "question": "15073×37724=？",
        "answer": 8.754817435329603
    },
    {
        "question": "36907×8304=？",
        "answer": 8.486396085337077
    },
    {
        "question": "8×2334=？",
        "answer": 4.271190838701295
    },
    {
        "question": "50303404÷3877604=？",
        "answer": 1.1130339197694052
    },
    {
        "question": "22×1267513=？",
        "answer": 7.445375103107116
    },
    {
        "question": "37378÷488=？",
        "answer": 1.8841962376885413
    },
    {
        "question": "6357387÷7723=？",
        "answer": 2.9154926146680302
    },
    {
        "question": "4×5467095=？",
        "answer": 7.339816611884475
    },
    {
        "question": "2250×1449=？",
        "answer": 6.513250903582537
    },
    {
        "question": "7×72414950=？",
        "answer": 8.704926275165162
    },
    {
        "question": "831÷406=？",
        "answer": 0.3110749902069169
    },
    {
        "question": "20×122393=？",
        "answer": 6.388786575660562
    },
    {
        "question": "3×6794183=？",
        "answer": 7.309258495048762
    },
    {
        "question": "844×776=？",
        "answer": 5.816204167883844
    },
    {
        "question": "575219307÷12634=？",
        "answer": 4.65829258197719
    },
    {
        "question": "11×157889=？",
        "answer": 6.239744559272217
    },
    {
        "question": "2910918×247=？",
        "answer": 8.85672692487879
    },
    {
        "question": "1554246÷1056602=？",
        "answer": 0.16760832993295968
    },
    {
        "question": "926×849=？",
        "answer": 5.895518676925887
    },
    {
        "question": "500749207÷5318=？",
        "answer": 4.973871937210112
    },
    {
        "question": "194206÷228=？",
        "answer": 2.9303277963194128
    },
    {
        "question": "4618×68561=？",
        "answer": 8.50053107196705
    },
    {
        "question": "13399÷219=？",
        "answer": 1.7866282722793365
    },
    {
        "question": "307441286÷5756=？",
        "answer": 4.727641402811344
    },
    {
        "question": "133167785÷455=？",
        "answer": 5.4663877794618925
    },
    {
        "question": "282×70199=？",
        "answer": 7.296580033874021
    },
    {
        "question": "756586391÷96610=？",
        "answer": 3.8938364431015393
    },
    {
        "question": "129694×4475=？",
        "answer": 8.763712924547379
    },
    {
        "question": "2283×144285=？",
        "answer": 8.517727095280616
    },
    {
        "question": "788981÷15063=？",
        "answer": 1.7191550686939767
    },
    {
        "question": "136257÷70138=？",
        "answer": 0.28840544503014104
    },
    {
        "question": "1069×28486=？",
        "answer": 7.48360917516117
    },
    {
        "question": "150×125373=？",
        "answer": 7.274295277100971
    },
    {
        "question": "23663×1777=？",
        "answer": 7.623757231531377
    },
    {
        "question": "39×37590=？",
        "answer": 6.1661369327403115
    },
    {
        "question": "1×105077=？",
        "answer": 5.021507664970099
    },
    {
        "question": "45×315027=？",
        "answer": 7.1515602912109735
    },
    {
        "question": "2×179496=？",
        "answer": 5.555084770599023
    },
    {
        "question": "7285×7825=？",
        "answer": 7.755913902324495
    },
    {
        "question": "73124×9547=？",
        "answer": 8.843926862544693
    },
    {
        "question": "223×72748=？",
        "answer": 7.210125921174788
    },
    {
        "question": "521665÷177631=？",
        "answer": 0.4678729389046853
    },
    {
        "question": "4×1209=？",
        "answer": 3.6844862921887342
    },
    {
        "question": "1×8165803=？",
        "answer": 6.911998898358844
    },
    {
        "question": "476580÷237=？",
        "answer": 3.303387466922931
    },
    {
        "question": "299873÷18703=？",
        "answer": 1.2050260906029098
    },
    {
        "question": "233003÷72775=？",
        "answer": 0.5053792986536174
    },
    {
        "question": "20032106÷2632=？",
        "answer": 3.8814407246661577
    },
    {
        "question": "4370260÷950222=？",
        "answer": 0.662682194036955
    },
    {
        "question": "875830272÷12197=？",
        "answer": 4.856166928154896
    },
    {
        "question": "520789÷2881=？",
        "answer": 2.257118544296327
    },
    {
        "question": "733780046÷4827064=？",
        "answer": 2.1818828406380115
    },
    {
        "question": "8820÷1098=？",
        "answer": 0.9048662450177466
    },
    {
        "question": "1665695÷179447=？",
        "answer": 0.9676592799161807
    },
    {
        "question": "260452×1855=？",
        "answer": 8.684071610661723
    },
    {
        "question": "7042311÷5976068=？",
        "answer": 0.07129966976359911
    },
    {
        "question": "2×59103491=？",
        "answer": 8.072643129290752
    },
    {
        "question": "7264×4902=？",
        "answer": 7.551549142429088
    },
    {
        "question": "159902÷572=？",
        "answer": 2.4464578669953103
    },
    {
        "question": "118777605÷3104636=？",
        "answer": 1.5827238749638737
    },
    {
        "question": "5×1409341=？",
        "answer": 6.84798609077443
    },
    {
        "question": "739×271=？",
        "answer": 5.301613729269231
    },
    {
        "question": "15670806÷3179=？",
        "answer": 3.692800806291557
    },
    {
        "question": "700566310÷64346803=？",
        "answer": 1.0369222740735162
    },
    {
        "question": "1144095÷207=？",
        "answer": 3.7424917421668744
    },
    {
        "question": "868394205÷11626=？",
        "answer": 4.873286598021847
    },
    {
        "question": "116460×1130=？",
        "answer": 8.119255229255426
    },
    {
        "question": "154162380÷639463=？",
        "answer": 2.3821629856460476
    },
    {
        "question": "58×2822051=？",
        "answer": 8.213992851605802
    },
    {
        "question": "727×220=？",
        "answer": 5.203957091681244
    },
    {
        "question": "33×1998=？",
        "answer": 4.819109423767851
    },
    {
        "question": "92152277÷3312=？",
        "answer": 4.444415742601424
    },
    {
        "question": "11×16615880=？",
        "answer": 8.26191603221885
    },
    {
        "question": "556331×812=？",
        "answer": 8.654889289710198
    },
    {
        "question": "8×1254156=？",
        "answer": 7.001441547191119
    },
    {
        "question": "4560400÷12145=？",
        "answer": 2.5746054178596904
    },
    {
        "question": "16141×1498=？",
        "answer": 7.383442250876419
    },
    {
        "question": "1×42688626=？",
        "answer": 7.630312176583726
    },
    {
        "question": "6635454÷4683=？",
        "answer": 3.151346485009847
    },
    {
        "question": "1×3460=？",
        "answer": 3.5390760987927767
    },
    {
        "question": "793÷199=？",
        "answer": 0.6004201109078972
    },
    {
        "question": "574×21920=？",
        "answer": 7.099752442210305
    },
    {
        "question": "89587043÷9564=？",
        "answer": 3.971605634623401
    },
    {
        "question": "7091×4804=？",
        "answer": 7.532310484105405
    },
    {
        "question": "1×4998=？",
        "answer": 3.6987962517904314
    },
    {
        "question": "1641×757=？",
        "answer": 6.094204460553166
    },
    {
        "question": "39×287=？",
        "answer": 4.048946503760492
    },
    {
        "question": "55452854÷3973=？",
        "answer": 4.144805337901496
    },
    {
        "question": "113249015÷854=？",
        "answer": 5.122576562672023
    },
    {
        "question": "1×648504558=？",
        "answer": 8.811913032860025
    },
    {
        "question": "53×860=？",
        "answer": 4.658774320844357
    },
    {
        "question": "6×217=？",
        "answer": 3.114610984232173
    },
    {
        "question": "89259444÷1070398=？",
        "answer": 1.9211088883174314
    },
    {
        "question": "17282×40097=？",
        "answer": 8.840705881345004
    },
    {
        "question": "40548843÷124166=？",
        "answer": 2.5139757762108386
    },
    {
        "question": "203752÷4095=？",
        "answer": 1.6968479743079736
    },
    {
        "question": "329071963÷5015683=？",
        "answer": 1.8169608013761709
    },
    {
        "question": "83×2546671=？",
        "answer": 8.32505093521423
    },
    {
        "question": "70923÷2204=？",
        "answer": 1.5075755075315598
    },
    {
        "question": "42×7302872=？",
        "answer": 8.486742979074288
    },
    {
        "question": "18156547÷1435702=？",
        "answer": 1.1019689528273906
    },
    {
        "question": "130×460889=？",
        "answer": 7.777539695284233
    },
    {
        "question": "18829×10256=？",
        "answer": 8.285805267612847
    },
    {
        "question": "45616612÷9060694=？",
        "answer": 0.7019615630191672
    },
    {
        "question": "6×185499=？",
        "answer": 6.046492823118252
    },
    {
        "question": "2504390÷1822321=？",
        "answer": 0.13807708107474354
    },
    {
        "question": "35571971÷157079=？",
        "answer": 2.3549898017942934
    },
    {
        "question": "668×3514=？",
        "answer": 6.3705782196348215
    },
    {
        "question": "38×255691=？",
        "answer": 6.98749903829537
    },
    {
        "question": "624642÷4964=？",
        "answer": 2.0997994093649557
    },
    {
        "question": "19×7575=？",
        "answer": 5.158136238127171
    },
    {
        "question": "652834167÷1219=？",
        "answer": 5.728799170138542
    },
    {
        "question": "144×35032=？",
        "answer": 6.702827424279318
    },
    {
        "question": "5233×15931=？",
        "answer": 7.920993772364471
    },
    {
        "question": "3×12630736=？",
        "answer": 7.5785499125929405
    },
    {
        "question": "1707×711=？",
        "answer": 6.0841031218445
    },
    {
        "question": "205×308=？",
        "answer": 4.800304577556199
    },
    {
        "question": "439115305÷583603=？",
        "answer": 2.8764610586328083
    },
    {
        "question": "32615÷4052=？",
        "answer": 0.9057479461702637
    },
    {
        "question": "1351571÷3581=？",
        "answer": 2.576834543745963
    },
    {
        "question": "120119829÷41187902=？",
        "answer": 0.46484503453813214
    },
    {
        "question": "41804045÷289049=？",
        "answer": 2.1602468353447537
    },
    {
        "question": "7186×6175=？",
        "answer": 7.647124174800334
    },
    {
        "question": "18151÷207=？",
        "answer": 1.9429302113266906
    },
    {
        "question": "1×905=？",
        "answer": 2.9566485792052033
    },
    {
        "question": "189×184518=？",
        "answer": 7.542500542794976
    },
    {
        "question": "70918857÷899=？",
        "answer": 4.897002035723105
    },
    {
        "question": "240×690696=？",
        "answer": 8.219498182612847
    },
    {
        "question": "8324273÷24422=？",
        "answer": 2.5325650878398673
    },
    {
        "question": "177783÷381=？",
        "answer": 2.6689652547540157
    },
    {
        "question": "97×204=？",
        "answer": 4.2964019016921435
    },
    {
        "question": "10450181÷13048=？",
        "answer": 2.9035798645794917
    },
    {
        "question": "626540149÷44856342=？",
        "answer": 1.1451250517134304
    },
    {
        "question": "536453389÷11838926=？",
        "answer": 1.6562196872730175
    },
    {
        "question": "233883÷27014=？",
        "answer": 0.9374097603362832
    },
    {
        "question": "74868974÷10625=？",
        "answer": 3.8479729429005265
    },
    {
        "question": "67936576÷16529923=？",
        "answer": 0.613832824128231
    },
    {
        "question": "2099×3820=？",
        "answer": 6.904075801494109
    },
    {
        "question": "25156261÷1469=？",
        "answer": 4.233624296160345
    },
    {
        "question": "500083438÷151820=？",
        "answer": 3.5177134845258906
    },
    {
        "question": "15720715÷220455=？",
        "answer": 1.853152341238445
    },
    {
        "question": "892×4089=？",
        "answer": 6.561981964930459
    },
    {
        "question": "84583÷746=？",
        "answer": 2.0545442572202184
    },
    {
        "question": "3257304÷9005=？",
        "answer": 2.558374575447215
    },
    {
        "question": "15×25598=？",
        "answer": 5.584297293785702
    },
    {
        "question": "71×1055644=？",
        "answer": 7.874775832350226
    },
    {
        "question": "29×934638=？",
        "answer": 7.433041432253439
    },
    {
        "question": "90273154÷34571409=？",
        "answer": 0.41684153617606545
    },
    {
        "question": "18×10022=？",
        "answer": 5.256226903509764
    },
    {
        "question": "59×6298641=？",
        "answer": 8.570098867465882
    },
    {
        "question": "506660÷447=？",
        "answer": 3.054409095654501
    },
    {
        "question": "72×61434=？",
        "answer": 6.6457412898132135
    },
    {
        "question": "38371997÷52998=？",
        "answer": 2.8597549210233706
    },
    {
        "question": "534÷298=？",
        "answer": 0.25332499295230115
    },
    {
        "question": "443048÷12351=？",
        "answer": 1.5547486586952015
    },
    {
        "question": "157131473÷2799=？",
        "answer": 4.749260283271781
    },
    {
        "question": "34616915÷614122=？",
        "answer": 1.7510337060760788
    },
    {
        "question": "2×34456541=？",
        "answer": 7.838301673302615
    },
    {
        "question": "11791÷309=？",
        "answer": 1.5815921599420975
    },
    {
        "question": "25436527÷792175=？",
        "answer": 1.5066366816983856
    },
    {
        "question": "65354003÷3208804=？",
        "answer": 1.3089290033630536
    },
    {
        "question": "37763103÷6601531=？",
        "answer": 0.7574230061185031
    },
    {
        "question": "126584×1688=？",
        "answer": 8.329751257363986
    },
    {
        "question": "3520×3376=？",
        "answer": 7.074945101431749
    },
    {
        "question": "209839÷147246=？",
        "answer": 0.15384270210582476
    },
    {
        "question": "259886776÷1380=？",
        "answer": 5.274905095153098
    },
    {
        "question": "67110426÷245=？",
        "answer": 5.437623911251969
    },
    {
        "question": "2×4520=？",
        "answer": 3.9561684304753633
    },
    {
        "question": "2×73887=？",
        "answer": 5.169598029120899
    },
    {
        "question": "1×132179=？",
        "answer": 5.121162461892675
    },
    {
        "question": "4093103÷1339410=？",
        "answer": 0.48513913644829004
    },
    {
        "question": "606395×975=？",
        "answer": 8.771760227383613
    },
    {
        "question": "7354085÷717=？",
        "answer": 4.011009489557405
    },
    {
        "question": "5×404=？",
        "answer": 3.305351369446624
    },
    {
        "question": "152×312615=？",
        "answer": 7.676853400594472
    },
    {
        "question": "90×496958=？",
        "answer": 7.650562195679693
    },
    {
        "question": "1168637÷948=？",
        "answer": 3.0908712949711563
    },
    {
        "question": "129803853÷1433=？",
        "answer": 4.957041393529282
    },
    {
        "question": "143326059÷65315=？",
        "answer": 3.341312228165428
    },
    {
        "question": "687131÷52558=？",
        "answer": 1.116400711660047
    },
    {
        "question": "2×58235=？",
        "answer": 5.066214075471244
    },
    {
        "question": "1×47155716=？",
        "answer": 7.67353434345295
    },
    {
        "question": "22448562÷16835083=？",
        "answer": 0.12497326450795672
    },
    {
        "question": "8×2435=？",
        "answer": 4.289588952542597
    },
    {
        "question": "13364602÷7970=？",
        "answer": 3.224497708529402
    },
    {
        "question": "376958348÷1143438=？",
        "answer": 2.51808074442853
    },
    {
        "question": "368639351÷385716=？",
        "answer": 2.9803340384819195
    },
    {
        "question": "184048330÷1128298=？",
        "answer": 2.212508062820705
    },
    {
        "question": "4893956÷334=？",
        "answer": 4.165913593618365
    },
    {
        "question": "84258037÷9464458=？",
        "answer": 0.9495155886202816
    },
    {
        "question": "11712002÷175267=？",
        "answer": 1.8249309848577582
    },
    {
        "question": "1×22644724=？",
        "answer": 7.3549670317530245
    },
    {
        "question": "18644806÷321=？",
        "answer": 4.764052836463394
    },
    {
        "question": "48366÷30018=？",
        "answer": 0.20715841826942175
    },
    {
        "question": "218×9603=？",
        "answer": 6.3208634224684
    },
    {
        "question": "101562×1201=？",
        "answer": 8.086274251991469
    },
    {
        "question": "1×328593091=？",
        "answer": 8.51665842771706
    },
    {
        "question": "52743780÷6277=？",
        "answer": 3.9244191225995477
    },
    {
        "question": "5×743034=？",
        "answer": 6.569978691144435
    },
    {
        "question": "3×18635=？",
        "answer": 4.747450651809521
    },
    {
        "question": "3133÷2537=？",
        "answer": 0.0916399276599744
    },
    {
        "question": "517895532÷448281620=？",
        "answer": 0.0626912315612798
    },
    {
        "question": "1612046×495=？",
        "answer": 8.901982629244534
    },
    {
        "question": "10155073÷462=？",
        "answer": 4.342041074132827
    },
    {
        "question": "7108×788=？",
        "answer": 6.7482736366228195
    },
    {
        "question": "27669×29584=？",
        "answer": 8.913050357172535
    },
    {
        "question": "16352275÷1821122=？",
        "answer": 0.9532391412658846
    },
    {
        "question": "834419388÷5334715=？",
        "answer": 2.1942731637266815
    },
    {
        "question": "27128×1243=？",
        "answer": 7.527888905411674
    },
    {
        "question": "584033515÷255920=？",
        "answer": 3.3583335429163483
    },
    {
        "question": "285×64658=？",
        "answer": 7.265467126903329
    },
    {
        "question": "2132023÷1219=？",
        "answer": 3.242788179876493
    },
    {
        "question": "10780357÷1022739=？",
        "answer": 1.022868325921505
    },
    {
        "question": "2×78849=？",
        "answer": 5.197826185437516
    },
    {
        "question": "18013426÷8169697=？",
        "answer": 0.34339037018570595
    },
    {
        "question": "22908÷2254=？",
        "answer": 1.007033262731204
    },
    {
        "question": "455868565÷1531488=？",
        "answer": 2.4737260476687375
    },
    {
        "question": "58×10869653=？",
        "answer": 8.799643673565456
    },
    {
        "question": "478×1461=？",
        "answer": 5.844078112546415
    },
    {
        "question": "1×419=？",
        "answer": 2.622214022966295
    },
    {
        "question": "4019×441=？",
        "answer": 6.248556595659873
    },
    {
        "question": "1177795÷4316=？",
        "answer": 2.4359882703006606
    },
    {
        "question": "101525×249=？",
        "answer": 7.4027723452578105
    },
    {
        "question": "1034922÷188820=？",
        "answer": 0.7388596258235116
    },
    {
        "question": "3163×1873=？",
        "answer": 6.77263696929096
    },
    {
        "question": "1604×709=？",
        "answer": 6.055850599131211
    },
    {
        "question": "204×4413256=？",
        "answer": 8.9543892877493
    },
    {
        "question": "150131÷31742=？",
        "answer": 0.6748360900704282
    },
    {
        "question": "212×2483713=？",
        "answer": 8.721437271387632
    },
    {
        "question": "87496015÷965=？",
        "answer": 4.957460960216563
    },
    {
        "question": "33×5674600=？",
        "answer": 8.272449193599389
    },
    {
        "question": "581509÷139810=？",
        "answer": 0.6190182049688977
    },
    {
        "question": "26×6753=？",
        "answer": 5.244470097691001
    },
    {
        "question": "160×4545307=？",
        "answer": 8.861683204406033
    },
    {
        "question": "10×2721=？",
        "answer": 4.434728541779758
    },
    {
        "question": "7×1094=？",
        "answer": 3.8841153620116686
    },
    {
        "question": "121178743÷4187610=？",
        "answer": 1.4614602149732645
    },
    {
        "question": "15×631366=？",
        "answer": 6.976372449836518
    },
    {
        "question": "641214÷101295=？",
        "answer": 0.8014149872149939
    },
    {
        "question": "762457÷40072=？",
        "answer": 1.2793743372858168
    },
    {
        "question": "2×10738240=？",
        "answer": 7.331963101894932
    },
    {
        "question": "29025÷9561=？",
        "answer": 0.48226891021721635
    },
    {
        "question": "97028÷2866=？",
        "answer": 1.529620893470321
    },
    {
        "question": "7×1399=？",
        "answer": 3.9909157545060845
    },
    {
        "question": "1×6238041=？",
        "answer": 6.795048224864094
    },
    {
        "question": "7×8042723=？",
        "answer": 7.7505011514069535
    },
    {
        "question": "54957861÷2870=？",
        "answer": 4.282147924588711
    },
    {
        "question": "328584÷344=？",
        "answer": 2.9800879695984586
    },
    {
        "question": "29374740÷4283=？",
        "answer": 3.8362259568980313
    },
    {
        "question": "146×1642263=？",
        "answer": 8.379795564172257
    },
    {
        "question": "878135÷75605=？",
        "answer": 1.0650107695278708
    },
    {
        "question": "16430÷2114=？",
        "answer": 0.8905325804636542
    },
    {
        "question": "3795947÷1531273=？",
        "answer": 0.39426751512499625
    },
    {
        "question": "2641×2481=？",
        "answer": 6.8163951654791335
    },
    {
        "question": "3067492÷898446=？",
        "answer": 0.5332914592734661
    },
    {
        "question": "680002×318=？",
        "answer": 8.334937310025502
    },
    {
        "question": "212×1950=？",
        "answer": 5.616370472291269
    },
    {
        "question": "26071684÷17275626=？",
        "answer": 0.17873529021678966
    },
    {
        "question": "106738982÷262=？",
        "answer": 5.610021765177701
    },
    {
        "question": "258372554÷772789=？",
        "answer": 2.5241854465751774
    },
    {
        "question": "666936718÷589706781=？",
        "answer": 0.05344850629808412
    },
    {
        "question": "137213909÷30423069=？",
        "answer": 0.6541951144265666
    },
    {
        "question": "39193×393=？",
        "answer": 7.187601057884668
    },
    {
        "question": "517210÷16800=？",
        "answer": 1.4883576314330629
    },
    {
        "question": "2×3884054=？",
        "answer": 6.890315254937795
    },
    {
        "question": "88×40516=？",
        "answer": 6.552109234611425
    },
    {
        "question": "825770÷1156=？",
        "answer": 2.8539012669401003
    },
    {
        "question": "675×70993=？",
        "answer": 7.680519301673405
    },
    {
        "question": "467772÷6410=？",
        "answer": 1.86317619263702
    },
    {
        "question": "88548÷4529=？",
        "answer": 1.2911764357096187
    },
    {
        "question": "1396187÷216=？",
        "answer": 3.810489838790357
    },
    {
        "question": "1060×11774=？",
        "answer": 7.096229896740921
    },
    {
        "question": "21926251÷6122411=？",
        "answer": 0.5540419007627027
    },
    {
        "question": "8×1444011=？",
        "answer": 7.062660488550429
    },
    {
        "question": "120434÷205=？",
        "answer": 2.7689952498517245
    },
    {
        "question": "403607÷49574=？",
        "answer": 0.910704727425378
    },
    {
        "question": "14159164÷118289=？",
        "answer": 2.078093251708214
    },
    {
        "question": "1×202905991=？",
        "answer": 8.307294870196626
    },
    {
        "question": "1724613÷6796=？",
        "answer": 2.40443828525831
    },
    {
        "question": "873760727÷6851069=？",
        "answer": 2.105634179036111
    },
    {
        "question": "20×207723=？",
        "answer": 6.618514581847915
    },
    {
        "question": "162368×2285=？",
        "answer": 8.569386645611488
    },
    {
        "question": "4×2440=？",
        "answer": 3.9894498176666917
    },
    {
        "question": "8724÷254=？",
        "answer": 1.5358819402867245
    },
    {
        "question": "32394÷622=？",
        "answer": 1.7166741931640674
    },
    {
        "question": "7381÷4001=？",
        "answer": 0.26594665394822
    },
    {
        "question": "85×167193=？",
        "answer": 7.152637016251425
    },
    {
        "question": "205315511÷982=？",
        "answer": 5.320310272529802
    },
    {
        "question": "328488710÷49008887=？",
        "answer": 0.8262456079339952
    },
    {
        "question": "291117901÷617017=？",
        "answer": 2.673771781423902
    },
    {
        "question": "5373916÷51645=？",
        "answer": 2.017262591907023
    },
    {
        "question": "4×3647=？",
        "answer": 4.163995754641744
    },
    {
        "question": "214646357÷4956581=？",
        "answer": 1.6365413142138703
    },
    {
        "question": "5131211÷91310=？",
        "answer": 1.7497015308206085
    },
    {
        "question": "88792×547=？",
        "answer": 7.68636116472051
    },
    {
        "question": "158306713÷9058558=？",
        "answer": 1.2424402621537358
    },
    {
        "question": "53538×525=？",
        "answer": 7.4488214467755975
    },
    {
        "question": "39728×2756=？",
        "answer": 8.039375915446078
    },
    {
        "question": "602902÷204155=？",
        "answer": 0.4702867037676343
    },
    {
        "question": "63×846523=？",
        "answer": 7.726979311824567
    },
    {
        "question": "307541126÷285665841=？",
        "answer": 0.03204488815951181
    },
    {
        "question": "45×365962=？",
        "answer": 7.216648506144906
    },
    {
        "question": "1×99365=？",
        "answer": 4.997233436876133
    },
    {
        "question": "172138407÷10574333=？",
        "answer": 1.2116247968053415
    },
    {
        "question": "4094976÷336=？",
        "answer": 4.08591208338349
    },
    {
        "question": "254×957=？",
        "answer": 5.385745654396781
    },
    {
        "question": "950823÷2619=？",
        "answer": 2.5599641801549646
    },
    {
        "question": "22974676÷347=？",
        "answer": 4.820919920679492
    },
    {
        "question": "6×338=？",
        "answer": 3.3070679506612985
    },
    {
        "question": "15078195÷20809=？",
        "answer": 2.8600981453605323
    },
    {
        "question": "345167÷2159=？",
        "answer": 2.2037766255809594
    },
    {
        "question": "21352684÷252=？",
        "answer": 4.928051932168556
    },
    {
        "question": "9147×55179=？",
        "answer": 8.703052504651602
    },
    {
        "question": "4258÷3525=？",
        "answer": 0.08204653577488626
    },
    {
        "question": "4898×2850=？",
        "answer": 7.1448636407972055
    },
    {
        "question": "101030×2285=？",
        "answer": 8.363336557395094
    },
    {
        "question": "65084493÷21246629=？",
        "answer": 0.48618749161043834
    },
    {
        "question": "110×293820=？",
        "answer": 7.509474039560087
    },
    {
        "question": "24×337386=？",
        "answer": 6.908338299072911
    },
    {
        "question": "53×41033=？",
        "answer": 6.337409139816944
    },
    {
        "question": "3341137÷617=？",
        "answer": 3.73360911978333
    },
    {
        "question": "4×377692=？",
        "answer": 6.179197777339891
    },
    {
        "question": "275502148÷4602089=？",
        "answer": 1.7771699759990387
    },
    {
        "question": "23×8442=？",
        "answer": 5.2881731838359824
    },
    {
        "question": "3×118090=？",
        "answer": 5.549334377323045
    },
    {
        "question": "12700677÷1784=？",
        "answer": 3.852432021272382
    },
    {
        "question": "2373942÷10523=？",
        "answer": 2.35333053369463
    },
    {
        "question": "1382×623=？",
        "answer": 5.934996089697349
    },
    {
        "question": "8816897÷114429=？",
        "answer": 1.886779664706031
    },
    {
        "question": "1540×66189=？",
        "answer": 8.008306540544359
    },
    {
        "question": "361322÷180249=？",
        "answer": 0.30202154150238136
    },
    {
        "question": "8868×338=？",
        "answer": 6.476742384720105
    },
    {
        "question": "32×22149557=？",
        "answer": 8.850515022902496
    },
    {
        "question": "11695002÷272=？",
        "answer": 4.633431396381079
    },
    {
        "question": "17564×10255=？",
        "answer": 8.255559093136736
    },
    {
        "question": "46856453÷643073=？",
        "answer": 1.8625091340034008
    },
    {
        "question": "49856×1291=？",
        "answer": 7.808643673922872
    },
    {
        "question": "834262483÷354308952=？",
        "answer": 0.37192058829460706
    },
    {
        "question": "26780837÷65888=？",
        "answer": 2.6090178212556356
    },
    {
        "question": "22123÷1067=？",
        "answer": 1.3166795999126506
    },
    {
        "question": "24428403÷8487=？",
        "answer": 3.459140873844756
    },
    {
        "question": "429×214=？",
        "answer": 4.962871065533915
    },
    {
        "question": "36980478÷748908=？",
        "answer": 1.6935440505960058
    },
    {
        "question": "425×73587=？",
        "answer": 7.495190027989223
    },
    {
        "question": "6731487÷1562=？",
        "answer": 3.634429981868503
    },
    {
        "question": "2181×72347=？",
        "answer": 8.198076192596181
    },
    {
        "question": "24×907977=？",
        "answer": 7.338286089241947
    },
    {
        "question": "233276×2129=？",
        "answer": 8.696045721261983
    },
    {
        "question": "3×440187=？",
        "answer": 6.120758467149548
    },
    {
        "question": "2750×3520=？",
        "answer": 6.985875357308394
    },
    {
        "question": "1700×3320=？",
        "answer": 6.75158700508231
    },
    {
        "question": "14×268=？",
        "answer": 3.5742628297070267
    },
    {
        "question": "4778×65017=？",
        "answer": 8.49227307191657
    },
    {
        "question": "16949432÷14045898=？",
        "answer": 0.08160563866050581
    },
    {
        "question": "315×7259=？",
        "answer": 6.359187350192898
    },
    {
        "question": "152647÷1125=？",
        "answer": 2.1325357510006073
    },
    {
        "question": "27×1965=？",
        "answer": 4.724726318870433
    },
    {
        "question": "914866182÷177845237=？",
        "answer": 0.7113153356818629
    },
    {
        "question": "1367974÷240163=？",
        "answer": 0.7555717432411424
    },
    {
        "question": "18×12885656=？",
        "answer": 8.36537903819031
    },
    {
        "question": "328484÷69578=？",
        "answer": 0.6740422796106605
    },
    {
        "question": "4870×48234=？",
        "answer": 8.370882240260597
    },
    {
        "question": "10467×412=？",
        "answer": 6.634719440200908
    },
    {
        "question": "116812×1391=？",
        "answer": 8.210814589772584
    },
    {
        "question": "981×9187=？",
        "answer": 6.9548427237552
    },
    {
        "question": "9632257÷55940=？",
        "answer": 2.236005599522847
    },
    {
        "question": "44×199436=？",
        "answer": 6.943256231616139
    },
    {
        "question": "420114858÷2166=？",
        "answer": 5.287709589004237
    },
    {
        "question": "1×92994=？",
        "answer": 4.968454928651225
    },
    {
        "question": "3274303×262=？",
        "answer": 8.933420157336164
    },
    {
        "question": "3×312=？",
        "answer": 2.971275848738105
    },
    {
        "question": "5379×7693=？",
        "answer": 7.616797276719593
    },
    {
        "question": "367342724÷17680=？",
        "answer": 4.317589181467286
    },
    {
        "question": "692189578÷3731548=？",
        "answer": 2.2683360235725276
    },
    {
        "question": "929427150÷519=？",
        "answer": 6.253047996891082
    },
    {
        "question": "61558282÷8557795=？",
        "answer": 0.8569246119675308
    },
    {
        "question": "448341÷2695=？",
        "answer": 2.221049686629597
    },
    {
        "question": "10×7679=？",
        "answer": 4.885304667588968
    },
    {
        "question": "103985787÷200844=？",
        "answer": 2.7141151208778926
    },
    {
        "question": "2054870÷21583=？",
        "answer": 1.978672540995049
    },
    {
        "question": "208483÷44111=？",
        "answer": 0.6745237443828266
    },
    {
        "question": "94970÷8031=？",
        "answer": 1.072816812097256
    },
    {
        "question": "634983256÷2583687=？",
        "answer": 2.390522373412574
    },
    {
        "question": "14×23035275=？",
        "answer": 8.508521436997547
    },
    {
        "question": "306×18518=？",
        "answer": 6.753315506242871
    },
    {
        "question": "70666824÷1824515=？",
        "answer": 1.5880681349199006
    },
    {
        "question": "296037664÷452106=？",
        "answer": 2.8161066978899467
    },
    {
        "question": "66565÷913=？",
        "answer": 1.8627751588080574
    },
    {
        "question": "102276086÷1482=？",
        "answer": 4.838925896028479
    },
    {
        "question": "236624249÷7595121=？",
        "answer": 1.4935245514856657
    },
    {
        "question": "46×133034=？",
        "answer": 6.786720481109722
    },
    {
        "question": "3655÷535=？",
        "answer": 0.8345335992726508
    },
    {
        "question": "7×149303=？",
        "answer": 6.019166574265444
    },
    {
        "question": "374×115451=？",
        "answer": 7.635269301191233
    },
    {
        "question": "46×1790=？",
        "answer": 4.915610862661468
    },
    {
        "question": "844828702÷594=？",
        "answer": 6.152982215071794
    },
    {
        "question": "12911142÷15947=？",
        "answer": 2.908285663403797
    },
    {
        "question": "178135160÷266=？",
        "answer": 5.82586801156279
    },
    {
        "question": "1×101268224=？",
        "answer": 8.005473193570166
    },
    {
        "question": "5476434÷4187=？",
        "answer": 3.1165948971858435
    },
    {
        "question": "32798362÷4857451=？",
        "answer": 0.8294437266204605
    },
    {
        "question": "213722893÷6756=？",
        "answer": 4.500161403357136
    },
    {
        "question": "44×1042386=？",
        "answer": 7.661481246340009
    },
    {
        "question": "442624321÷5067563=？",
        "answer": 1.9412361169924475
    },
    {
        "question": "792×2294=？",
        "answer": 6.259318595154743
    },
    {
        "question": "36799÷14376=？",
        "answer": 0.40819795293176464
    },
    {
        "question": "8230×2426=？",
        "answer": 7.300290631742824
    },
    {
        "question": "9×7591=？",
        "answer": 4.834541500865077
    },
    {
        "question": "5947862÷401010=？",
        "answer": 1.1712056808622737
    },
    {
        "question": "2259676÷273414=？",
        "answer": 0.9172254244073705
    },
    {
        "question": "25736×6209=？",
        "answer": 8.203562707739897
    },
    {
        "question": "22975÷742=？",
        "answer": 1.4908516147791218
    },
    {
        "question": "563286×859=？",
        "answer": 8.684722121176474
    },
    {
        "question": "1×2174148=？",
        "answer": 6.3372891043296535
    },
    {
        "question": "964418066÷205=？",
        "answer": 6.672511476164616
    },
    {
        "question": "8×10023=？",
        "answer": 4.9040877173497375
    },
    {
        "question": "8134204÷227839=？",
        "answer": 1.5526869941845691
    },
    {
        "question": "3×90075346=？",
        "answer": 8.43172719374188
    },
    {
        "question": "121406×388=？",
        "answer": 7.673071876110222
    },
    {
        "question": "786÷673=？",
        "answer": 0.06740748181543108
    },
    {
        "question": "73327÷2393=？",
        "answer": 1.486321218618672
    },
    {
        "question": "2×109367165=？",
        "answer": 8.339916950205012
    },
    {
        "question": "8×597904=？",
        "answer": 6.679721445868051
    },
    {
        "question": "191×240=？",
        "answer": 4.661244608959334
    },
    {
        "question": "1677×4539=？",
        "answer": 6.881493245348935
    },
    {
        "question": "4038737÷206108=？",
        "answer": 1.2921507240348251
    },
    {
        "question": "218420×894=？",
        "answer": 8.290629921564683
    },
    {
        "question": "40508731÷340517=？",
        "answer": 2.0754098398907606
    },
    {
        "question": "354175456÷1538812=？",
        "answer": 2.3620328973561167
    },
    {
        "question": "1542860÷168641=？",
        "answer": 0.9613633509205436
    },
    {
        "question": "391872÷31816=？",
        "answer": 1.0904986554416962
    },
    {
        "question": "4339835÷1201=？",
        "answer": 3.557930210599991
    },
    {
        "question": "5040816÷2910=？",
        "answer": 3.2386078561128078
    },
    {
        "question": "6817×4807=？",
        "answer": 7.515467416127103
    },
    {
        "question": "321258÷580=？",
        "answer": 2.7434259577572555
    },
    {
        "question": "260×159700=？",
        "answer": 7.618278264109301
    },
    {
        "question": "68×8055038=？",
        "answer": 8.738576506269839
    },
    {
        "question": "15×893963=？",
        "answer": 7.12741080332323
    },
    {
        "question": "107903×2059=？",
        "answer": 8.346689866049168
    },
    {
        "question": "3593×11144=？",
        "answer": 7.6024983206205565
    },
    {
        "question": "74682÷234=？",
        "answer": 2.5040000825221362
    },
    {
        "question": "1373738÷206=？",
        "answer": 3.8240366913906594
    },
    {
        "question": "109434÷2097=？",
        "answer": 1.7175538432534965
    },
    {
        "question": "1454×104827=？",
        "answer": 8.183037563605568
    },
    {
        "question": "7×12854=？",
        "answer": 4.954136335588638
    },
    {
        "question": "1456128÷425=？",
        "answer": 3.534810622983248
    },
    {
        "question": "4×22310508=？",
        "answer": 7.950569450409875
    },
    {
        "question": "5650918÷717655=？",
        "answer": 0.8962032903450875
    },
    {
        "question": "140×4477=？",
        "answer": 5.797115130061683
    },
    {
        "question": "5×51373=？",
        "answer": 5.409704932049904
    },
    {
        "question": "269386×1473=？",
        "answer": 8.598577768516398
    },
    {
        "question": "69764747÷3853=？",
        "answer": 4.257837014599661
    },
    {
        "question": "51869×2367=？",
        "answer": 8.089106133093125
    },
    {
        "question": "381159681÷34896877=？",
        "answer": 1.038320392098187
    },
    {
        "question": "4102746÷601963=？",
        "answer": 0.8335048328146433
    },
    {
        "question": "2496726÷85431=？",
        "answer": 1.4657553939113566
    },
    {
        "question": "2×3620270=？",
        "answer": 6.859770957119079
    },
    {
        "question": "38178958÷3363=？",
        "answer": 4.055097203913639
    },
    {
        "question": "23002×1860=？",
        "answer": 7.6312785433312165
    },
    {
        "question": "3×9977822=？",
        "answer": 7.4761570067674725
    },
    {
        "question": "140308200÷53059773=？",
        "answer": 0.42231766548875543
    },
    {
        "question": "175×624319=？",
        "answer": 8.038444600772147
    },
    {
        "question": "8×1188603=？",
        "answer": 6.978126809062378
    },
    {
        "question": "2×125863=？",
        "answer": 5.400928074798935
    },
    {
        "question": "99×90811=？",
        "answer": 6.953773652699627
    },
    {
        "question": "296×8503=？",
        "answer": 6.400863890135488
    },
    {
        "question": "78969243÷1509854=？",
        "answer": 1.7185230210055131
    },
    {
        "question": "11×2093=？",
        "answer": 4.362161913496911
    },
    {
        "question": "1×854=？",
        "answer": 2.931457870689005
    },
    {
        "question": "1832350÷937=？",
        "answer": 3.2912688416266795
    },
    {
        "question": "126×67653=？",
        "answer": 6.930657604802983
    },
    {
        "question": "8607×20524=？",
        "answer": 8.247113808949008
    },
    {
        "question": "101571336÷739=？",
        "answer": 5.138126726507811
    },
    {
        "question": "318060204÷21630062=？",
        "answer": 1.167451568867079
    },
    {
        "question": "1×752681036=？",
        "answer": 8.876610974006496
    },
    {
        "question": "26115790÷201=？",
        "answer": 5.11370711031528
    },
    {
        "question": "105850459÷1988386=？",
        "answer": 1.7261920489337585
    },
    {
        "question": "2012263÷1433=？",
        "answer": 3.1474385513862733
    },
    {
        "question": "1051055÷764603=？",
        "answer": 0.13818944486103552
    },
    {
        "question": "10669101÷60116=？",
        "answer": 2.249137750657435
    },
    {
        "question": "4×13076591=？",
        "answer": 7.718554531734201
    },
    {
        "question": "26582655÷1711=？",
        "answer": 4.1913483453299385
    },
    {
        "question": "186500÷2700=？",
        "answer": 1.8393150719857192
    },
    {
        "question": "9×39398=？",
        "answer": 5.549716685300179
    },
    {
        "question": "666×9092=？",
        "answer": 6.782133656223234
    },
    {
        "question": "1×565580=？",
        "answer": 5.752494043569587
    },
    {
        "question": "40×4564930=？",
        "answer": 8.261494113648046
    },
    {
        "question": "46924930÷2966=？",
        "answer": 4.199232486745157
    },
    {
        "question": "61613×342=？",
        "answer": 7.323698461606984
    },
    {
        "question": "150554975÷208242=？",
        "answer": 2.8591267849130606
    },
    {
        "question": "372496630÷4293054=？",
        "answer": 1.9383559967443516
    },
    {
        "question": "22×19783257=？",
        "answer": 8.638720473679115
    },
    {
        "question": "907332÷9345=？",
        "answer": 1.987186922233242
    },
    {
        "question": "18285628÷12541=？",
        "answer": 3.163777712454005
    },
    {
        "question": "23720542÷477=？",
        "answer": 4.696606229131029
    },
    {
        "question": "160×311=？",
        "answer": 4.696880371682762
    },
    {
        "question": "359830279÷325=？",
        "answer": 6.044214344582434
    },
    {
        "question": "3×3665006=？",
        "answer": 7.041195944683101
    },
    {
        "question": "756721536÷2098=？",
        "answer": 5.557130610137609
    },
    {
        "question": "371223÷4366=？",
        "answer": 1.929551144750316
    },
    {
        "question": "2×782=？",
        "answer": 3.1942367487238292
    },
    {
        "question": "449×38577=？",
        "answer": 7.2385747920430505
    },
    {
        "question": "174×1161=？",
        "answer": 5.3053814680211735
    },
    {
        "question": "3646×8559=？",
        "answer": 7.4942396906956965
    },
    {
        "question": "513561031÷43079671=？",
        "answer": 1.0763196841289804
    },
    {
        "question": "165603×654=？",
        "answer": 8.034645948355521
    },
    {
        "question": "1476÷1315=？",
        "answer": 0.05016060466124612
    },
    {
        "question": "56689435÷38236455=？",
        "answer": 0.17102450766719618
    },
    {
        "question": "2230135÷17922=？",
        "answer": 2.0949446806345864
    },
    {
        "question": "34×2639722=？",
        "answer": 7.953037108979042
    },
    {
        "question": "136874÷10323=？",
        "answer": 1.1225150319042887
    },
    {
        "question": "164718×946=？",
        "answer": 8.192632196855886
    },
    {
        "question": "373198682÷1865408=？",
        "answer": 2.3011662663605916
    },
    {
        "question": "8567456÷8214951=？",
        "answer": 0.018246905367956045
    },
    {
        "question": "1×21593=？",
        "answer": 4.334312984758231
    },
    {
        "question": "84965÷7340=？",
        "answer": 1.0635440018311528
    },
    {
        "question": "24×11275492=？",
        "answer": 8.432346742880076
    },
    {
        "question": "2595031÷1019=？",
        "answer": 3.405968366250699
    },
    {
        "question": "237750÷56767=？",
        "answer": 0.6220245822008827
    },
    {
        "question": "191785×3869=？",
        "answer": 8.870413366591466
    },
    {
        "question": "23849193÷3250=？",
        "answer": 3.865590327152962
    },
    {
        "question": "3×1205875=？",
        "answer": 6.558423546251984
    },
    {
        "question": "1390×266=？",
        "answer": 5.567896436885162
    },
    {
        "question": "178×138245=？",
        "answer": 7.391069435148721
    },
    {
        "question": "714×207=？",
        "answer": 5.169668557233092
    },
    {
        "question": "827×2022=？",
        "answer": 6.223286660807529
    },
    {
        "question": "1×8473=？",
        "answer": 3.928037206406883
    },
    {
        "question": "1282897÷9447=？",
        "answer": 2.1328978742008724
    },
    {
        "question": "85392043÷24326=？",
        "answer": 3.5453467017466345
    },
    {
        "question": "11769÷486=？",
        "answer": 1.384103293586905
    },
    {
        "question": "3055703÷1282651=？",
        "answer": 0.37700263648681986
    },
    {
        "question": "8×103879=？",
        "answer": 5.919617747196684
    },
    {
        "question": "344×354=？",
        "answer": 5.085561704597318
    },
    {
        "question": "33361÷28151=？",
        "answer": 0.0737452334090458
    },
    {
        "question": "1×300=？",
        "answer": 2.4771212547196626
    },
    {
        "question": "1×3982=？",
        "answer": 3.6001012556913907
    },
    {
        "question": "930143486÷87545676=？",
        "answer": 1.0263152483991533
    },
    {
        "question": "6327×4714=？",
        "answer": 7.474587412647454
    },
    {
        "question": "226799011÷552=？",
        "answer": 5.613702078672538
    },
    {
        "question": "325255182÷5286=？",
        "answer": 4.789097065718724
    },
    {
        "question": "7×89323=？",
        "answer": 5.796061340862002
    },
    {
        "question": "235755383÷80999706=？",
        "answer": 0.46397817521591206
    },
    {
        "question": "4361728÷38416=？",
        "answer": 2.0551464365072003
    },
    {
        "question": "361×446945=？",
        "answer": 8.207761285068615
    },
    {
        "question": "1334×189296=？",
        "answer": 8.402297266596195
    },
    {
        "question": "11672÷1878=？",
        "answer": 0.793449690955303
    },
    {
        "question": "3501×143691=？",
        "answer": 8.70162167797551
    },
    {
        "question": "723831296÷30688=？",
        "answer": 4.372668771101827
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1386=？",
        "answer": 3.141763230275788
    },
    {
        "question": "131426÷342=？",
        "answer": 2.5846551841260887
    },
    {
        "question": "29×218553=？",
        "answer": 6.801954770172825
    },
    {
        "question": "142614063÷22886=？",
        "answer": 3.794592459276484
    },
    {
        "question": "1343444÷240310=？",
        "answer": 0.7474477246139841
    },
    {
        "question": "2790×40325=？",
        "answer": 8.051178579334596
    },
    {
        "question": "1767862÷1950=？",
        "answer": 2.9574137494403145
    },
    {
        "question": "8×293733=？",
        "answer": 6.371042727906335
    },
    {
        "question": "3781394÷78156=？",
        "answer": 1.6846896065423371
    },
    {
        "question": "114094812÷6802836=？",
        "answer": 1.2245758957903174
    },
    {
        "question": "10591×2498=？",
        "answer": 7.42252940207556
    },
    {
        "question": "55116×2973=？",
        "answer": 8.214472600670486
    },
    {
        "question": "1324396÷398155=？",
        "answer": 0.5219656864730396
    },
    {
        "question": "9×1772=？",
        "answer": 4.202706226990357
    },
    {
        "question": "396×243385=？",
        "answer": 7.9839889947498435
    },
    {
        "question": "10×18993290=？",
        "answer": 8.278600199338815
    },
    {
        "question": "21041×1670=？",
        "answer": 7.545782847511488
    },
    {
        "question": "159359334÷60088=？",
        "answer": 3.4235897570928553
    },
    {
        "question": "63×9330872=？",
        "answer": 8.769262781312845
    },
    {
        "question": "491517÷587=？",
        "answer": 2.922900442036539
    },
    {
        "question": "836042÷6872=？",
        "answer": 2.08514494469007
    },
    {
        "question": "22382107÷27641=？",
        "answer": 2.908347216645544
    },
    {
        "question": "253×1489=？",
        "answer": 5.576015218927994
    },
    {
        "question": "1436558÷30273=？",
        "answer": 1.676267704117121
    },
    {
        "question": "48627743÷1065=？",
        "answer": 4.659534504989128
    },
    {
        "question": "1×238145450=？",
        "answer": 8.376842288309211
    },
    {
        "question": "2187×2249=？",
        "answer": 6.691838238473269
    },
    {
        "question": "412869060÷209540=？",
        "answer": 3.294545398919342
    },
    {
        "question": "123203÷1418=？",
        "answer": 1.9389450522052465
    },
    {
        "question": "623×20975=？",
        "answer": 7.116190016159908
    },
    {
        "question": "96203175÷689=？",
        "answer": 5.14497018341736
    },
    {
        "question": "347606÷320=？",
        "answer": 3.0359372858445317
    },
    {
        "question": "10×153348=？",
        "answer": 6.1856781161865975
    },
    {
        "question": "272501466÷392057=？",
        "answer": 2.84201963063843
    },
    {
        "question": "67125×4555=？",
        "answer": 8.48537268001663
    },
    {
        "question": "415233÷472=？",
        "answer": 2.9443498624596667
    },
    {
        "question": "1757×15155=？",
        "answer": 7.425327702198936
    },
    {
        "question": "2×18536=？",
        "answer": 4.5690460164459
    },
    {
        "question": "11694110÷6485=？",
        "answer": 3.2560571942674432
    },
    {
        "question": "952683÷646=？",
        "answer": 3.168715897592966
    },
    {
        "question": "112889×1225=？",
        "answer": 8.140787714664116
    },
    {
        "question": "186501696÷107872804=？",
        "answer": 0.23777081778227413
    },
    {
        "question": "447980859÷44088160=？",
        "answer": 1.0069374840611025
    },
    {
        "question": "20×4642=？",
        "answer": 4.96773513178388
    },
    {
        "question": "323182÷25435=？",
        "answer": 1.1040154222689402
    },
    {
        "question": "8×254=？",
        "answer": 3.307923703611882
    },
    {
        "question": "647289÷5627=？",
        "answer": 2.0608213115458582
    },
    {
        "question": "2772×122438=？",
        "answer": 8.530709452810363
    },
    {
        "question": "2441×3917=？",
        "answer": 6.980521350965055
    },
    {
        "question": "10×48524263=？",
        "answer": 8.685958947925133
    },
    {
        "question": "2796÷216=？",
        "answer": 1.1120834159227129
    },
    {
        "question": "58180172÷84058=？",
        "answer": 2.8401959482499533
    },
    {
        "question": "202539160÷12494556=？",
        "answer": 1.2097881766022291
    },
    {
        "question": "372724×1790=？",
        "answer": 8.82424038920726
    },
    {
        "question": "41×612=？",
        "answer": 4.399535278865296
    },
    {
        "question": "942771776÷18443101=？",
        "answer": 1.7085726278720899
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1127851=？",
        "answer": 6.0522517289451825
    },
    {
        "question": "46×18313932=？",
        "answer": 8.925539428991135
    },
    {
        "question": "17×2401=？",
        "answer": 4.610841081435301
    },
    {
        "question": "6617÷5385=？",
        "answer": 0.08947542700959508
    },
    {
        "question": "1595997÷101624=？",
        "answer": 1.1960357855902706
    },
    {
        "question": "22033939÷253767=？",
        "answer": 1.9386569972348646
    },
    {
        "question": "40898×479=？",
        "answer": 7.292037584008668
    },
    {
        "question": "19×6969061=？",
        "answer": 8.121927866857066
    },
    {
        "question": "2323×184421=？",
        "answer": 8.631859582400942
    },
    {
        "question": "6×5861=？",
        "answer": 4.5461229717652625
    },
    {
        "question": "560658372÷3021196=？",
        "answer": 2.2685194105863578
    },
    {
        "question": "12221÷417=？",
        "answer": 1.4669706891253351
    },
    {
        "question": "8005146÷2431314=？",
        "answer": 0.5175282062597398
    },
    {
        "question": "133×47766=？",
        "answer": 6.802970515269854
    },
    {
        "question": "348043÷272712=？",
        "answer": 0.10592865506594011
    },
    {
        "question": "2479×2585=？",
        "answer": 6.806737074197783
    },
    {
        "question": "27×1045=？",
        "answer": 4.45048005460606
    },
    {
        "question": "132×323=？",
        "answer": 4.6297764535369526
    },
    {
        "question": "19×303473=？",
        "answer": 6.760873658892524
    },
    {
        "question": "4772×58932=？",
        "answer": 8.449051615177533
    },
    {
        "question": "432×520590=？",
        "answer": 8.351979568316652
    },
    {
        "question": "6246×227=？",
        "answer": 6.151627837087302
    },
    {
        "question": "1495×130961=？",
        "answer": 8.291783175289316
    },
    {
        "question": "12922546÷6758014=？",
        "answer": 0.28152899965697264
    },
    {
        "question": "9007859÷1505=？",
        "answer": 3.7770850796199036
    },
    {
        "question": "5×61163773=？",
        "answer": 8.485464272157717
    },
    {
        "question": "486÷449=？",
        "answer": 0.03438992825897024
    },
    {
        "question": "365448÷148345=？",
        "answer": 0.3915526765369493
    },
    {
        "question": "2980×5259=？",
        "answer": 7.195119434889713
    },
    {
        "question": "3×188143719=？",
        "answer": 8.751610979107287
    },
    {
        "question": "17471÷10920=？",
        "answer": 0.20409512534647675
    },
    {
        "question": "53665972÷275=？",
        "answer": 5.290366305894608
    },
    {
        "question": "78015249÷34983348=？",
        "answer": 0.3483181286878617
    },
    {
        "question": "113803÷11655=？",
        "answer": 0.9896414329394752
    },
    {
        "question": "14269÷902=？",
        "answer": 1.1991870004150555
    },
    {
        "question": "50061×2282=？",
        "answer": 8.057815160746813
    },
    {
        "question": "3039×1754=？",
        "answer": 6.726760289109965
    },
    {
        "question": "2×188104410=？",
        "answer": 8.575428973118742
    },
    {
        "question": "18516458÷6651=？",
        "answer": 3.444670966575863
    },
    {
        "question": "944382358÷129955=？",
        "answer": 3.8613548718539583
    },
    {
        "question": "2×2551331=？",
        "answer": 6.707796801646653
    },
    {
        "question": "5914×41071=？",
        "answer": 8.38541659740934
    },
    {
        "question": "468422÷2900=？",
        "answer": 2.2082392861406297
    },
    {
        "question": "1548×271017=？",
        "answer": 8.622767489932098
    },
    {
        "question": "115569957÷2089=？",
        "answer": 4.742906511709252
    },
    {
        "question": "3778973÷27094=？",
        "answer": 2.1445006625129324
    },
    {
        "question": "378843143÷200171=？",
        "answer": 3.277058272199892
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1879527=？",
        "answer": 6.274048568872278
    },
    {
        "question": "502970264÷149845=？",
        "answer": 3.5259000539152687
    },
    {
        "question": "169×1630732=？",
        "answer": 8.44026929809744
    },
    {
        "question": "5043×328=？",
        "answer": 6.218562811870813
    },
    {
        "question": "4738×388=？",
        "answer": 6.264426781980953
    },
    {
        "question": "1434×445=？",
        "answer": 5.804909162312713
    },
    {
        "question": "27×234=？",
        "answer": 3.8005796215691303
    },
    {
        "question": "1578901×474=？",
        "answer": 8.87413324147236
    },
    {
        "question": "21510888÷1426=？",
        "answer": 4.178538813534548
    },
    {
        "question": "41502270÷328=？",
        "answer": 5.102198007735655
    },
    {
        "question": "3×2303555=？",
        "answer": 6.839519840707687
    },
    {
        "question": "33×237=？",
        "answer": 3.8932622858879915
    },
    {
        "question": "23×163883=？",
        "answer": 6.576261741454425
    },
    {
        "question": "88508691÷514550=？",
        "answer": 2.23555833525733
    },
    {
        "question": "29×16806=？",
        "answer": 5.687862357106168
    },
    {
        "question": "70×7157300=？",
        "answer": 8.699847261170353
    },
    {
        "question": "190×3871=？",
        "answer": 5.866576772271784
    },
    {
        "question": "10135265÷463=？",
        "answer": 4.340254117367081
    },
    {
        "question": "420×202047=？",
        "answer": 7.928701696806766
    },
    {
        "question": "44023608÷3675237=？",
        "answer": 1.0784002826465102
    },
    {
        "question": "355×89246=？",
        "answer": 7.500817113224679
    },
    {
        "question": "3550÷1085=？",
        "answer": 0.5147986148705458
    },
    {
        "question": "19×16735=？",
        "answer": 5.502379317646625
    },
    {
        "question": "6×3296=？",
        "answer": 4.296138453408722
    },
    {
        "question": "12487×5961=？",
        "answer": 7.871777233546931
    },
    {
        "question": "182636×199=？",
        "answer": 7.560439463301046
    },
    {
        "question": "1×129119=？",
        "answer": 5.1109901538699125
    },
    {
        "question": "2035043÷657005=？",
        "answer": 0.49100491552247755
    },
    {
        "question": "1639×1076=？",
        "answer": 6.2463912249008695
    },
    {
        "question": "182020695÷12791973=？",
        "answer": 1.1531832342038333
    },
    {
        "question": "20×7456=？",
        "answer": 5.173535895009906
    },
    {
        "question": "5686705÷4170=？",
        "answer": 3.1347246446701527
    },
    {
        "question": "15×39860=？",
        "answer": 5.77662855342015
    },
    {
        "question": "83×634=？",
        "answer": 4.721167350257806
    },
    {
        "question": "4868×1518=？",
        "answer": 6.868622341117489
    },
    {
        "question": "1966×5592=？",
        "answer": 7.041150676233742
    },
    {
        "question": "56×5109=？",
        "answer": 5.456523929688464
    },
    {
        "question": "61253×674=？",
        "answer": 7.615787260617431
    },
    {
        "question": "2817648÷349=？",
        "answer": 3.9070613101441354
    },
    {
        "question": "47×1093308=？",
        "answer": 7.710840383890227
    },
    {
        "question": "3296146÷611=？",
        "answer": 3.7319652299154296
    },
    {
        "question": "19×147601=？",
        "answer": 6.447842900804423
    },
    {
        "question": "332460657÷17191804=？",
        "answer": 1.2864188075705787
    },
    {
        "question": "2514109÷152729=？",
        "answer": 1.2164625945306726
    },
    {
        "question": "3380946÷522388=？",
        "answer": 0.8110450423142169
    },
    {
        "question": "14061955÷329716=？",
        "answer": 1.6299056813115527
    },
    {
        "question": "1×223446758=？",
        "answer": 8.349174057842095
    },
    {
        "question": "9×364=？",
        "answer": 3.5153438930883807
    },
    {
        "question": "53×7966=？",
        "answer": 5.625516171674098
    },
    {
        "question": "24×91325=？",
        "answer": 6.340800922595561
    },
    {
        "question": "5587×1079=？",
        "answer": 6.780200116043075
    },
    {
        "question": "14496÷239=？",
        "answer": 1.7828502793846002
    },
    {
        "question": "30×326808=？",
        "answer": 6.99141393389378
    },
    {
        "question": "414217202÷200=？",
        "answer": 6.316198135056054
    },
    {
        "question": "2994636÷32993=？",
        "answer": 1.9579222341158857
    },
    {
        "question": "1×18751126=？",
        "answer": 7.273027352111935
    },
    {
        "question": "469672680÷34195=？",
        "answer": 4.137832690733916
    },
    {
        "question": "1799÷1754=？",
        "answer": 0.011001574315529694
    },
    {
        "question": "172979996÷40650852=？",
        "answer": 0.6289262303385725
    },
    {
        "question": "226885÷842=？",
        "answer": 2.430493692915181
    },
    {
        "question": "27×7160=？",
        "answer": 5.286276786466843
    },
    {
        "question": "197371÷913=？",
        "answer": 2.3348125639847463
    },
    {
        "question": "17194407÷296=？",
        "answer": 4.764095491427173
    },
    {
        "question": "5602÷232=？",
        "answer": 1.3828551195966499
    },
    {
        "question": "3428÷2180=？",
        "answer": 0.19658431964655573
    },
    {
        "question": "73×20579=？",
        "answer": 6.176747127289649
    },
    {
        "question": "3628×1263=？",
        "answer": 6.6610706289433885
    },
    {
        "question": "427×2270370=？",
        "answer": 8.98652451453706
    },
    {
        "question": "268664644÷17714511=？",
        "answer": 1.1808813491134857
    },
    {
        "question": "2×23773991=？",
        "answer": 7.677132089625438
    },
    {
        "question": "5×19699209=？",
        "answer": 7.993418792232025
    },
    {
        "question": "1207×5900=？",
        "answer": 6.852559281739493
    },
    {
        "question": "59796×5156=？",
        "answer": 8.488985041900047
    },
    {
        "question": "787×149417=？",
        "answer": 8.070374744739205
    },
    {
        "question": "8925259÷2803888=？",
        "answer": 0.5028601657066036
    },
    {
        "question": "43708÷2460=？",
        "answer": 1.2496258273012575
    },
    {
        "question": "2489×281819=？",
        "answer": 8.845995166137758
    },
    {
        "question": "775560925÷362000=？",
        "answer": 3.330907349414021
    },
    {
        "question": "139075922÷593=？",
        "answer": 5.370197254401471
    },
    {
        "question": "33034960÷49403=？",
        "answer": 2.82522046300253
    },
    {
        "question": "3×16685=？",
        "answer": 4.699447465710474
    },
    {
        "question": "5720×1842=？",
        "answer": 7.022685654653855
    },
    {
        "question": "7059393÷3599304=？",
        "answer": 0.29254883091353623
    },
    {
        "question": "1653×31764=？",
        "answer": 7.72020804092042
    },
    {
        "question": "2627947÷3406=？",
        "answer": 2.8873719585702755
    },
    {
        "question": "905937÷89966=？",
        "answer": 1.003019585704777
    },
    {
        "question": "115093×2504=？",
        "answer": 8.459683235015966
    },
    {
        "question": "9861932÷5771078=？",
        "answer": 0.23270505952754666
    },
    {
        "question": "79×2223881=？",
        "answer": 8.24473863569954
    },
    {
        "question": "12467152÷8688502=？",
        "answer": 0.1568223490220198
    },
    {
        "question": "14×721058=？",
        "answer": 7.004098235303148
    },
    {
        "question": "84×339011=？",
        "answer": 7.454493076187665
    },
    {
        "question": "8312×15248=？",
        "answer": 8.102918417843371
    },
    {
        "question": "18032403÷956=？",
        "answer": 4.275595712433055
    },
    {
        "question": "479807676÷2341=？",
        "answer": 5.311665777867194
    },
    {
        "question": "1×4534817=？",
        "answer": 6.656559766039164
    },
    {
        "question": "165372158÷2321095=？",
        "answer": 1.852769477659989
    },
    {
        "question": "84175×789=？",
        "answer": 7.822260128269546
    },
    {
        "question": "13554÷263=？",
        "answer": 1.7121117328142488
    },
    {
        "question": "39016÷404=？",
        "answer": 1.984861377472905
    },
    {
        "question": "93337÷1512=？",
        "answer": 1.7905020466911719
    },
    {
        "question": "115056921÷809753=？",
        "answer": 2.1525601821608626
    },
    {
        "question": "545232809÷245099=？",
        "answer": 3.34724044197215
    },
    {
        "question": "115293519÷267=？",
        "answer": 5.635293633600149
    },
    {
        "question": "156582853÷19141=？",
        "answer": 3.9127795785539203
    },
    {
        "question": "24×3241258=？",
        "answer": 7.8909248434061965
    },
    {
        "question": "3×1784016=？",
        "answer": 6.728519999760075
    },
    {
        "question": "18×62694=？",
        "answer": 6.052498484664849
    },
    {
        "question": "381817719÷248355883=？",
        "answer": 0.18678162688632943
    },
    {
        "question": "52674÷5186=？",
        "answer": 1.0067637869753414
    },
    {
        "question": "110×234=？",
        "answer": 4.410608542568368
    },
    {
        "question": "66276871÷56522=？",
        "answer": 3.0691444760164854
    },
    {
        "question": "5460×225=？",
        "answer": 6.0893751608160995
    },
    {
        "question": "295×5003=？",
        "answer": 6.169052518861572
    },
    {
        "question": "9550638÷23098=？",
        "answer": 2.616458007204141
    },
    {
        "question": "4×892233=？",
        "answer": 6.552538273283172
    },
    {
        "question": "45225×8483=？",
        "answer": 8.583928042533515
    },
    {
        "question": "217273÷1325=？",
        "answer": 2.2147898826562606
    },
    {
        "question": "190×665132=？",
        "answer": 8.101661443523271
    },
    {
        "question": "7541×56644=？",
        "answer": 8.630582854901244
    },
    {
        "question": "23×743=？",
        "answer": 4.232716649778168
    },
    {
        "question": "74484÷3543=？",
        "answer": 1.3226918390998446
    },
    {
        "question": "30494÷10828=？",
        "answer": 0.4496661488637275
    },
    {
        "question": "4213188÷1765=？",
        "answer": 3.377866128833565
    },
    {
        "question": "143460÷709=？",
        "answer": 2.3060845913163517
    },
    {
        "question": "24×41429=？",
        "answer": 5.997515692274605
    },
    {
        "question": "63480275÷4059=？",
        "answer": 4.19421974815689
    },
    {
        "question": "833401×984=？",
        "answer": 8.913849115663977
    },
    {
        "question": "881694734÷2034215=？",
        "answer": 2.6369213945264818
    },
    {
        "question": "283×62703=？",
        "answer": 7.249074755498184
    },
    {
        "question": "1×6422525=？",
        "answer": 6.807705803454681
    },
    {
        "question": "59×678=？",
        "answer": 4.602081705509208
    },
    {
        "question": "7472×5460=？",
        "answer": 7.610629505926775
    },
    {
        "question": "1×26115=？",
        "answer": 4.416890030173012
    },
    {
        "question": "106862÷822=？",
        "answer": 2.1139514805197845
    },
    {
        "question": "2345÷301=？",
        "answer": 0.8915763514572587
    },
    {
        "question": "267590×1394=？",
        "answer": 8.571732653313802
    },
    {
        "question": "4252605÷5590=？",
        "answer": 2.8812432375863395
    },
    {
        "question": "10802×272=？",
        "answer": 6.4680730769793735
    },
    {
        "question": "6×512270=？",
        "answer": 6.4876501734746
    },
    {
        "question": "2701057÷176634=？",
        "answer": 1.1844594451873973
    },
    {
        "question": "51×123692=？",
        "answer": 6.799911787867656
    },
    {
        "question": "167×12811=？",
        "answer": 6.330299502338905
    },
    {
        "question": "61103÷705=？",
        "answer": 1.9378734165156575
    },
    {
        "question": "1146×42059=？",
        "answer": 7.683043560264965
    },
    {
        "question": "15533÷222=？",
        "answer": 1.8449023677956264
    },
    {
        "question": "6578×102783=？",
        "answer": 8.830015158740501
    },
    {
        "question": "21×64406=？",
        "answer": 6.131145622427773
    },
    {
        "question": "3026×292=？",
        "answer": 5.946251775135586
    },
    {
        "question": "87×10585=？",
        "answer": 5.964210114974049
    },
    {
        "question": "428393÷1336=？",
        "answer": 2.5060359076472505
    },
    {
        "question": "14987762÷6463158=？",
        "answer": 0.36529201511864745
    },
    {
        "question": "1448569÷3445=？",
        "answer": 2.623749960631686
    },
    {
        "question": "113388÷67263=？",
        "answer": 0.2267908616393511
    },
    {
        "question": "1×19701471=？",
        "answer": 7.2944986537419325
    },
    {
        "question": "76×366=？",
        "answer": 4.444294677675202
    },
    {
        "question": "6×3714152=？",
        "answer": 7.3480109234574265
    },
    {
        "question": "77263×762=？",
        "answer": 7.7699265384431335
    },
    {
        "question": "1×167939=？",
        "answer": 5.22515156283233
    },
    {
        "question": "4662×86115=？",
        "answer": 8.603651075107859
    },
    {
        "question": "28515×2107=？",
        "answer": 7.778737911529225
    },
    {
        "question": "27869762÷5672485=？",
        "answer": 0.6913599038406925
    },
    {
        "question": "2605×789=？",
        "answer": 6.312884730844964
    },
    {
        "question": "83113880÷55504=？",
        "answer": 3.175349274427436
    },
    {
        "question": "716049097÷56883=？",
        "answer": 4.0999603084484875
    },
    {
        "question": "1×30299584=？",
        "answer": 7.481436665870467
    },
    {
        "question": "366743÷7998=？",
        "answer": 1.661380433446145
    },
    {
        "question": "60377669÷10666745=？",
        "answer": 0.7528444292698298
    },
    {
        "question": "3×90375=？",
        "answer": 5.43316956502225
    },
    {
        "question": "27324×3049=？",
        "answer": 7.920701701028149
    },
    {
        "question": "5×2693=？",
        "answer": 4.129206357747529
    },
    {
        "question": "118213÷257=？",
        "answer": 2.6627321156320023
    },
    {
        "question": "251805962÷21956729=？",
        "answer": 1.0594983670175582
    },
    {
        "question": "14850÷1848=？",
        "answer": 0.9050244867691433
    },
    {
        "question": "400×97461=？",
        "answer": 7.590890854480912
    },
    {
        "question": "2×558=？",
        "answer": 3.04766419460156
    },
    {
        "question": "10×101002=？",
        "answer": 6.004329973588227
    },
    {
        "question": "2388470÷6758=？",
        "answer": 2.548301603327541
    },
    {
        "question": "4655026÷218=？",
        "answer": 4.329465617410929
    },
    {
        "question": "1773÷704=？",
        "answer": 0.4011360764588056
    },
    {
        "question": "160×3729=？",
        "answer": 5.775712366017232
    },
    {
        "question": "825611÷2627=？",
        "answer": 2.4973153978433307
    },
    {
        "question": "13252×21770=？",
        "answer": 8.460139856251017
    },
    {
        "question": "2×5679=？",
        "answer": 4.055301864347441
    },
    {
        "question": "3943087÷630163=？",
        "answer": 0.7963834594222643
    },
    {
        "question": "914118049÷22352=？",
        "answer": 4.611685895277489
    },
    {
        "question": "8×4558051=？",
        "answer": 7.561869167181334
    },
    {
        "question": "393×58364=？",
        "answer": 7.360537599162248
    },
    {
        "question": "353×2721225=？",
        "answer": 8.98253915757499
    },
    {
        "question": "5577412÷3147475=？",
        "answer": 0.24847043749636766
    },
    {
        "question": "1292955÷122182=？",
        "answer": 1.024576180129578
    },
    {
        "question": "58×2402355=？",
        "answer": 8.144065177791024
    },
    {
        "question": "25×2192=？",
        "answer": 4.738780558484369
    },
    {
        "question": "21197÷7897=？",
        "answer": 0.42881226180061494
    },
    {
        "question": "202314800÷259=？",
        "answer": 5.892727889936354
    },
    {
        "question": "1114688÷1027=？",
        "answer": 3.035582882226613
    },
    {
        "question": "6764422÷4626541=？",
        "answer": 0.16497427813047788
    },
    {
        "question": "56819663÷7628=？",
        "answer": 3.872087969200305
    },
    {
        "question": "1315755×451=？",
        "answer": 8.773351570932682
    },
    {
        "question": "64394705÷9071=？",
        "answer": 3.851194991040179
    },
    {
        "question": "5×4248339=？",
        "answer": 7.327189168707736
    },
    {
        "question": "691×14203=？",
        "answer": 6.991858134421801
    },
    {
        "question": "18748324÷25981=？",
        "answer": 2.8583065872844853
    },
    {
        "question": "154915÷5114=？",
        "answer": 1.481332747663671
    },
    {
        "question": "11×2224455=？",
        "answer": 7.388616309695261
    },
    {
        "question": "22×29258=？",
        "answer": 5.808667316396517
    },
    {
        "question": "19114×2516=？",
        "answer": 7.682062218445969
    },
    {
        "question": "950692209÷3825=？",
        "answer": 5.395408495356297
    },
    {
        "question": "5941633÷11475=？",
        "answer": 2.714153128788942
    },
    {
        "question": "28825÷303=？",
        "answer": 1.9783266874644316
    },
    {
        "question": "1350854÷708971=？",
        "answer": 0.27997994209572674
    },
    {
        "question": "735177÷64217=？",
        "answer": 1.0587418987529433
    },
    {
        "question": "21×9098566=？",
        "answer": 8.281192244487798
    },
    {
        "question": "3×38504751=？",
        "answer": 8.062635573988779
    },
    {
        "question": "31716825÷769804=？",
        "answer": 1.6149095425330535
    },
    {
        "question": "15700401÷1324=？",
        "answer": 4.07402275965353
    },
    {
        "question": "601192553÷527=？",
        "answer": 6.05720297710978
    },
    {
        "question": "3192603÷571541=？",
        "answer": 0.7470975270547398
    },
    {
        "question": "159575÷4759=？",
        "answer": 1.5254491483030854
    },
    {
        "question": "77254×341=？",
        "answer": 7.420675354247346
    },
    {
        "question": "324069277÷107387=？",
        "answer": 3.4796861502667085
    },
    {
        "question": "1×5269=？",
        "answer": 3.721728198572788
    },
    {
        "question": "138×17306=？",
        "answer": 6.378075785780251
    },
    {
        "question": "925988307÷13942388=？",
        "answer": 1.8222683381590183
    },
    {
        "question": "125674÷7205=？",
        "answer": 1.2416114530412545
    },
    {
        "question": "32811808÷529=？",
        "answer": 4.792574489554449
    },
    {
        "question": "7×677284=？",
        "answer": 6.675868856069774
    },
    {
        "question": "54×389=？",
        "answer": 4.322343361148676
    },
    {
        "question": "1312854×565=？",
        "answer": 8.8702648795297
    },
    {
        "question": "435×293=？",
        "answer": 5.105356877308747
    },
    {
        "question": "16702×24933=？",
        "answer": 8.619543016378607
    },
    {
        "question": "1587683÷5971=？",
        "answer": 2.424716723449777
    },
    {
        "question": "245070÷592=？",
        "answer": 2.61696844405637
    },
    {
        "question": "1×984318=？",
        "answer": 5.993135427023009
    },
    {
        "question": "896096519÷3016=？",
        "answer": 5.472923453057616
    },
    {
        "question": "868×35784=？",
        "answer": 7.492208610341092
    },
    {
        "question": "91465×271=？",
        "answer": 7.394224229588168
    },
    {
        "question": "9390880÷3110=？",
        "answer": 3.479945901986548
    },
    {
        "question": "1730×2713=？",
        "answer": 6.6714958968903915
    },
    {
        "question": "24861860÷1195709=？",
        "answer": 1.3179081184085546
    },
    {
        "question": "138559859÷3686=？",
        "answer": 4.575082101847714
    },
    {
        "question": "6×470=？",
        "answer": 3.450249108319361
    },
    {
        "question": "141046115÷27168=？",
        "answer": 3.7153034598055927
    },
    {
        "question": "412×8035=？",
        "answer": 6.519883097132498
    },
    {
        "question": "6×25627=？",
        "answer": 5.186849019279432
    },
    {
        "question": "1059×19435=？",
        "answer": 7.313480505074771
    },
    {
        "question": "19697630÷1004683=？",
        "answer": 1.2923849216793004
    },
    {
        "question": "10432×535=？",
        "answer": 6.746721360409073
    },
    {
        "question": "20×2203=？",
        "answer": 4.644044492814749
    },
    {
        "question": "4679425÷120765=？",
        "answer": 1.5882514052673602
    },
    {
        "question": "1×35196958=？",
        "answer": 7.546505129929741
    },
    {
        "question": "2×1529893=？",
        "answer": 6.485691053191022
    },
    {
        "question": "1390158÷338568=？",
        "answer": 0.6134182552414312
    },
    {
        "question": "3×159262962=？",
        "answer": 8.67923604326859
    },
    {
        "question": "682633×336=？",
        "answer": 8.36052655660273
    },
    {
        "question": "7×754=？",
        "answer": 3.7224693858840308
    },
    {
        "question": "79×3351=？",
        "answer": 5.422801519125713
    },
    {
        "question": "3660×52959=？",
        "answer": 8.287420861324126
    },
    {
        "question": "142×133064=？",
        "answer": 7.276348918895288
    },
    {
        "question": "66929÷3664=？",
        "answer": 1.2616588711726906
    },
    {
        "question": "1496×306=？",
        "answer": 5.660653020010023
    },
    {
        "question": "10360÷933=？",
        "answer": 1.0454781116627143
    },
    {
        "question": "1299×116776=？",
        "answer": 8.180962746087632
    },
    {
        "question": "146410×247=？",
        "answer": 7.5582676938925655
    },
    {
        "question": "18408×18758=？",
        "answer": 8.538193137184061
    },
    {
        "question": "21332035÷134647=？",
        "answer": 2.1998356060040436
    },
    {
        "question": "1684526÷127039=？",
        "answer": 1.1225406520296577
    },
    {
        "question": "128241729÷2594=？",
        "answer": 4.69405939294813
    },
    {
        "question": "42503769÷2825574=？",
        "answer": 1.1773207569178898
    },
    {
        "question": "96595941÷814=？",
        "answer": 5.07433447268221
    },
    {
        "question": "205040909÷357157=？",
        "answer": 2.7589813521427784
    },
    {
        "question": "8×11809=？",
        "answer": 4.975303109595326
    },
    {
        "question": "199785÷280=？",
        "answer": 2.85340484663295
    },
    {
        "question": "2692720÷53580=？",
        "answer": 1.701188486776872
    },
    {
        "question": "18×7176162=？",
        "answer": 8.111164739335543
    },
    {
        "question": "785×112730=？",
        "answer": 7.946909163746724
    },
    {
        "question": "4311552÷2283453=？",
        "answer": 0.27604155131869096
    },
    {
        "question": "890×360=？",
        "answer": 5.5056925074122
    },
    {
        "question": "7×498=？",
        "answer": 3.5423273827739745
    },
    {
        "question": "24894442÷3261213=？",
        "answer": 0.8827232313048841
    },
    {
        "question": "6127÷310=？",
        "answer": 1.2958861864976814
    },
    {
        "question": "47×1180159=？",
        "answer": 7.744038380640786
    },
    {
        "question": "5218÷239=？",
        "answer": 1.3391061738160643
    },
    {
        "question": "6160×141598=？",
        "answer": 8.940637831372003
    },
    {
        "question": "383137522÷3382910=？",
        "answer": 2.054064242211307
    },
    {
        "question": "2720×146813=？",
        "answer": 8.601333417232057
    },
    {
        "question": "16349925÷5426=？",
        "answer": 3.479035975389636
    },
    {
        "question": "9400971÷13799=？",
        "answer": 2.833325098332438
    },
    {
        "question": "525275×1171=？",
        "answer": 8.788943626504794
    },
    {
        "question": "187754235÷467453=？",
        "answer": 2.603851790446415
    },
    {
        "question": "318954864÷82325=？",
        "answer": 3.5881974900599034
    },
    {
        "question": "11012×25623=？",
        "answer": 8.450496179307573
    },
    {
        "question": "14×308495=？",
        "answer": 6.635376165181999
    },
    {
        "question": "38871÷203=？",
        "answer": 2.2821296755736102
    },
    {
        "question": "7×176537=？",
        "answer": 6.091933782099518
    },
    {
        "question": "353×1447=？",
        "answer": 5.70824323650686
    },
    {
        "question": "11329181÷631=？",
        "answer": 4.254169156088205
    },
    {
        "question": "10×1660325=？",
        "answer": 7.22019310725177
    },
    {
        "question": "6×15962=？",
        "answer": 4.981238556856091
    },
    {
        "question": "7515÷570=？",
        "answer": 1.1200541292504356
    },
    {
        "question": "205323÷14913=？",
        "answer": 1.1388725833073448
    },
    {
        "question": "12588×14612=？",
        "answer": 8.264666397781061
    },
    {
        "question": "126248×1049=？",
        "answer": 8.121999995017177
    },
    {
        "question": "31439540÷4647588=？",
        "answer": 0.8302485614459835
    },
    {
        "question": "10333172÷116898=？",
        "answer": 1.946426577553566
    },
    {
        "question": "1×20094=？",
        "answer": 4.30306639792351
    },
    {
        "question": "122450110÷55025=？",
        "answer": 3.3473991283731306
    },
    {
        "question": "1291095÷5850=？",
        "answer": 2.343802333161655
    },
    {
        "question": "134816185÷4253=？",
        "answer": 4.501046650688878
    },
    {
        "question": "29358929÷18338819=？",
        "answer": 0.20436884453121232
    },
    {
        "question": "13245÷7093=？",
        "answer": 0.2712220027847189
    },
    {
        "question": "2557×5288=？",
        "answer": 7.1310221745039195
    },
    {
        "question": "24335667÷143407=？",
        "answer": 2.2296729033448
    },
    {
        "question": "121475÷103757=？",
        "answer": 0.06846950154299404
    },
    {
        "question": "321853÷2687=？",
        "answer": 2.0783898951205986
    },
    {
        "question": "260×13937=？",
        "answer": 6.559142648012484
    },
    {
        "question": "65607332÷57981=？",
        "answer": 3.0536666756428077
    },
    {
        "question": "261070490÷245387371=？",
        "answer": 0.026905576536803612
    },
    {
        "question": "25468÷13359=？",
        "answer": 0.2802208913409188
    },
    {
        "question": "902×6011=？",
        "answer": 6.7341532655105585
    },
    {
        "question": "6415÷1294=？",
        "answer": 0.6952623843782657
    },
    {
        "question": "106993581÷1601=？",
        "answer": 4.824966391374305
    },
    {
        "question": "63×253=？",
        "answer": 4.2024610706294
    },
    {
        "question": "77×115876=？",
        "answer": 6.950484220265557
    },
    {
        "question": "44513911÷35066=？",
        "answer": 3.1036095246774624
    },
    {
        "question": "92610901÷739=？",
        "answer": 5.098017671024778
    },
    {
        "question": "12×302=？",
        "answer": 3.5591881890047756
    },
    {
        "question": "699×916673=？",
        "answer": 8.806691615425972
    },
    {
        "question": "66×295146=？",
        "answer": 7.289580837313213
    },
    {
        "question": "33790÷4587=？",
        "answer": 0.8672594516429137
    },
    {
        "question": "1×471650=？",
        "answer": 5.673619838774741
    },
    {
        "question": "201×4999=？",
        "answer": 6.002079194173079
    },
    {
        "question": "3×292756=？",
        "answer": 5.943627059369917
    },
    {
        "question": "1×12281=？",
        "answer": 4.089233731365399
    },
    {
        "question": "799002997÷17479=？",
        "answer": 4.660031825957299
    },
    {
        "question": "896539602÷5540892=？",
        "answer": 2.208989792788549
    },
    {
        "question": "1568397÷477=？",
        "answer": 3.5169376238786114
    },
    {
        "question": "402655×395=？",
        "answer": 8.201530191974134
    },
    {
        "question": "143×6279373=？",
        "answer": 8.953252318744534
    },
    {
        "question": "2316260÷356=？",
        "answer": 3.8133373093396994
    },
    {
        "question": "92×33843=？",
        "answer": 6.493256681289881
    },
    {
        "question": "1382737×692=？",
        "answer": 8.980845678535365
    },
    {
        "question": "343869810÷780=？",
        "answer": 5.644299445984262
    },
    {
        "question": "105134×644=？",
        "answer": 7.830629055552532
    },
    {
        "question": "319×2179=？",
        "answer": 5.842047913303436
    },
    {
        "question": "2×259007793=？",
        "answer": 8.714342826949794
    },
    {
        "question": "65124÷40839=？",
        "answer": 0.20266596838948137
    },
    {
        "question": "479681566÷119451167=？",
        "answer": 0.6037626319709286
    },
    {
        "question": "1×65394=？",
        "answer": 4.815537902966021
    },
    {
        "question": "2×4417=？",
        "answer": 3.9461573949223725
    },
    {
        "question": "108774481÷7461973=？",
        "answer": 1.1636733465232323
    },
    {
        "question": "1828×18252=？",
        "answer": 7.523286651498436
    },
    {
        "question": "209126÷2058=？",
        "answer": 2.006962660261041
    },
    {
        "question": "5392686÷66019=？",
        "answer": 1.9121361916352766
    },
    {
        "question": "2×22215422=？",
        "answer": 7.647684563095953
    },
    {
        "question": "5409794÷6908=？",
        "answer": 2.893828398989962
    },
    {
        "question": "10223498÷185952=？",
        "answer": 1.7401986626050985
    },
    {
        "question": "53822×2681=？",
        "answer": 8.15925664588749
    },
    {
        "question": "114509832÷507=？",
        "answer": 5.3538348181725
    },
    {
        "question": "55×65001=？",
        "answer": 6.553282727539272
    },
    {
        "question": "389279777÷5525115=？",
        "answer": 1.8479205209232934
    },
    {
        "question": "10×4606256=？",
        "answer": 7.663348070905204
    },
    {
        "question": "439152092÷1521691=？",
        "answer": 2.4602884839513455
    },
    {
        "question": "132611867÷103051661=？",
        "answer": 0.10952739320686043
    },
    {
        "question": "437210÷107371=？",
        "answer": 0.6098030887757155
    },
    {
        "question": "11×297=？",
        "answer": 3.514149134475437
    },
    {
        "question": "1476056÷701=？",
        "answer": 3.323384816505211
    },
    {
        "question": "1×350=？",
        "answer": 2.5440680443502757
    },
    {
        "question": "86718691÷3498=？",
        "answer": 4.39429290851928
    },
    {
        "question": "487246471÷66491=？",
        "answer": 3.864985837690017
    },
    {
        "question": "1×570605379=？",
        "answer": 8.756335861360677
    },
    {
        "question": "9×38506=？",
        "answer": 5.539770915931351
    },
    {
        "question": "44418745÷8676=？",
        "answer": 3.7092467405579526
    },
    {
        "question": "50391×866=？",
        "answer": 7.639870868951656
    },
    {
        "question": "9×5749=？",
        "answer": 4.713834818085299
    },
    {
        "question": "136439429÷1135=？",
        "answer": 5.079944031684464
    },
    {
        "question": "767×224109=？",
        "answer": 8.235254661679278
    },
    {
        "question": "3×248037=？",
        "answer": 5.871637724647741
    },
    {
        "question": "9×1566=？",
        "answer": 4.14903426716125
    },
    {
        "question": "6318402÷12238=？",
        "answer": 2.7128968050015825
    },
    {
        "question": "94×1630019=？",
        "answer": 8.185320520302469
    },
    {
        "question": "4×1887=？",
        "answer": 3.8778318914928938
    },
    {
        "question": "3844797×251=？",
        "answer": 8.984547136071754
    },
    {
        "question": "1222×49808=？",
        "answer": 7.784370309244975
    },
    {
        "question": "3×196014=？",
        "answer": 5.769408346002719
    },
    {
        "question": "407492÷191144=？",
        "answer": 0.3287584168773634
    },
    {
        "question": "276÷199=？",
        "answer": 0.14205600565551105
    },
    {
        "question": "2756×99755=？",
        "answer": 8.439213886195763
    },
    {
        "question": "2388173÷2357=？",
        "answer": 3.005706201500837
    },
    {
        "question": "23×3057=？",
        "answer": 4.847023274743682
    },
    {
        "question": "1×45810840=？",
        "answer": 7.6609682551906255
    },
    {
        "question": "1×13130001=？",
        "answer": 7.118264759165981
    },
    {
        "question": "3×116459=？",
        "answer": 5.54329431134564
    },
    {
        "question": "113850×2809=？",
        "answer": 8.504884774152739
    },
    {
        "question": "8789×441=？",
        "answer": 6.588378053940055
    },
    {
        "question": "94623398÷1372082=？",
        "answer": 1.838618472875207
    },
    {
        "question": "2084838÷2028=？",
        "answer": 3.0120043635935843
    },
    {
        "question": "38×7257=？",
        "answer": 5.440540719698352
    },
    {
        "question": "27×979=？",
        "answer": 4.4221464559621255
    },
    {
        "question": "103×1777=？",
        "answer": 5.262524652510474
    },
    {
        "question": "421192315÷20059458=？",
        "answer": 1.3221612441779855
    },
    {
        "question": "5360357÷839=？",
        "answer": 3.8054317538579103
    },
    {
        "question": "2671669÷7783=？",
        "answer": 2.5356356208180553
    },
    {
        "question": "3817913÷721=？",
        "answer": 3.723890763044239
    },
    {
        "question": "1436×12540=？",
        "answer": 7.2554519764009795
    },
    {
        "question": "72×306=？",
        "answer": 4.343053922912849
    },
    {
        "question": "16×1439=？",
        "answer": 4.36218077659253
    },
    {
        "question": "1×906=？",
        "answer": 2.957128197676813
    },
    {
        "question": "1×144433572=？",
        "answer": 8.159668151957437
    },
    {
        "question": "1×381318=？",
        "answer": 5.581287306496237
    },
    {
        "question": "87×7019=？",
        "answer": 5.7857944950308315
    },
    {
        "question": "15×13045265=？",
        "answer": 8.291544164789258
    },
    {
        "question": "2162×10336=？",
        "answer": 7.349208190268301
    },
    {
        "question": "331509×1029=？",
        "answer": 8.532910698143585
    },
    {
        "question": "137670399÷362=？",
        "answer": 5.580132000566761
    },
    {
        "question": "7244366÷42735=？",
        "answer": 2.2292166753354086
    },
    {
        "question": "560967359÷56379622=？",
        "answer": 0.9978154319080558
    },
    {
        "question": "44005×4239=？",
        "answer": 8.270765441896222
    },
    {
        "question": "29387×1879=？",
        "answer": 7.74208203306846
    },
    {
        "question": "782117÷1135=？",
        "answer": 2.838275864233487
    },
    {
        "question": "5191164÷8078=？",
        "answer": 2.8079609005553703
    },
    {
        "question": "4×56523=？",
        "answer": 5.354285195616821
    },
    {
        "question": "932036÷67650=？",
        "answer": 1.1391648864196964
    },
    {
        "question": "20102844÷1685=？",
        "answer": 4.0766575972944095
    },
    {
        "question": "21×286=？",
        "answer": 3.778585327862962
    },
    {
        "question": "2×6777390=？",
        "answer": 7.132092473184569
    },
    {
        "question": "4×8412342=？",
        "answer": 7.526976911748997
    },
    {
        "question": "427×4313=？",
        "answer": 6.2652073331709754
    },
    {
        "question": "4×99295=？",
        "answer": 5.59898737147409
    },
    {
        "question": "7573446÷952=？",
        "answer": 3.9006565847818075
    },
    {
        "question": "418365442÷30890=？",
        "answer": 4.131737895261994
    },
    {
        "question": "11×1017=？",
        "answer": 4.04871363808097
    },
    {
        "question": "98435059÷3545=？",
        "answer": 4.443533566416899
    },
    {
        "question": "27×5868=？",
        "answer": 5.199853869330233
    },
    {
        "question": "7029835÷755=？",
        "answer": 3.9689981800150353
    },
    {
        "question": "75×87872=？",
        "answer": 6.818911774612342
    },
    {
        "question": "116479÷607=？",
        "answer": 2.2830589423879855
    },
    {
        "question": "1826×70195=？",
        "answer": 8.107806951571037
    },
    {
        "question": "978466038÷674508589=？",
        "answer": 0.16155827191581199
    },
    {
        "question": "1×528503=？",
        "answer": 5.723047456884217
    },
    {
        "question": "33162716÷251465=？",
        "answer": 2.120172545116438
    },
    {
        "question": "4226÷825=？",
        "answer": 0.7094755441663695
    },
    {
        "question": "63×5394=？",
        "answer": 5.531251491570454
    },
    {
        "question": "42366288÷20561175=？",
        "answer": 0.313972484701387
    },
    {
        "question": "2×1441885=？",
        "answer": 6.459960619530716
    },
    {
        "question": "6940591÷3004279=？",
        "answer": 0.36365619068231436
    },
    {
        "question": "51×18182=？",
        "answer": 5.967211829526797
    },
    {
        "question": "70885608÷8588=？",
        "answer": 3.9166660329780836
    },
    {
        "question": "79728103÷2393=？",
        "answer": 4.522668732274937
    },
    {
        "question": "622÷303=？",
        "answer": 0.31234775618851374
    },
    {
        "question": "15×2006=？",
        "answer": 4.4784221877400805
    },
    {
        "question": "47593052÷481=？",
        "answer": 4.995398479323407
    },
    {
        "question": "43305×1369=？",
        "answer": 7.772941491070392
    },
    {
        "question": "128687826÷77192=？",
        "answer": 3.221965170751071
    },
    {
        "question": "365736308÷4542555=？",
        "answer": 1.9058678821730546
    },
    {
        "question": "177872858÷65982745=？",
        "answer": 0.43067930420427764
    },
    {
        "question": "8×14683=？",
        "answer": 5.069904785782856
    },
    {
        "question": "711769005÷10076872=？",
        "answer": 1.8490133300709033
    },
    {
        "question": "95655351÷379=？",
        "answer": 5.402070059688198
    },
    {
        "question": "8891×364=？",
        "answer": 6.510051993894604
    },
    {
        "question": "1054785×498=？",
        "answer": 8.72039328786334
    },
    {
        "question": "1387841÷671=？",
        "answer": 3.3156171932279137
    },
    {
        "question": "154837648÷16474086=？",
        "answer": 0.9730752369088718
    },
    {
        "question": "31752÷649=？",
        "answer": 1.6895263890987378
    },
    {
        "question": "125470÷55524=？",
        "answer": 0.3540591524453397
    },
    {
        "question": "6979559÷714389=？",
        "answer": 0.9898932240430466
    },
    {
        "question": "93784×760=？",
        "answer": 7.852942344258806
    },
    {
        "question": "1340×184067=？",
        "answer": 8.392080732428086
    },
    {
        "question": "353×14210=？",
        "answer": 6.700368783315293
    },
    {
        "question": "915400×327=？",
        "answer": 8.476158660751567
    },
    {
        "question": "8238÷4684=？",
        "answer": 0.24520490122007324
    },
    {
        "question": "397391306÷461933=？",
        "answer": 2.9346393726332285
    },
    {
        "question": "16×1755=？",
        "answer": 4.448397103457768
    },
    {
        "question": "320÷312=？",
        "answer": 0.010995384301463145
    },
    {
        "question": "109930÷3837=？",
        "answer": 1.4571244287711687
    },
    {
        "question": "66686988÷802=？",
        "answer": 4.919866734131942
    },
    {
        "question": "2535÷719=？",
        "answer": 0.5472490732864722
    },
    {
        "question": "664×288233=？",
        "answer": 8.281911781374951
    },
    {
        "question": "6×67700555=？",
        "answer": 8.608743479370847
    },
    {
        "question": "1×86298556=？",
        "answer": 7.936003528896223
    },
    {
        "question": "32765÷743=？",
        "answer": 1.6444213585315821
    },
    {
        "question": "9050×4768=？",
        "answer": 7.634984825937384
    },
    {
        "question": "7×71407133=？",
        "answer": 8.698839636493659
    },
    {
        "question": "2492×37656=？",
        "answer": 7.972382223285675
    },
    {
        "question": "135932÷496=？",
        "answer": 2.4378400303341556
    },
    {
        "question": "5×55764=？",
        "answer": 5.445323922862512
    },
    {
        "question": "7691×4916=？",
        "answer": 7.577594685569389
    },
    {
        "question": "444×706543=？",
        "answer": 8.496521568138466
    },
    {
        "question": "1645825÷2455=？",
        "answer": 2.826332158490898
    },
    {
        "question": "1939359÷365=？",
        "answer": 3.725365345492521
    },
    {
        "question": "1×736697=？",
        "answer": 5.8672889013112455
    },
    {
        "question": "17×10613172=？",
        "answer": 8.256294123961464
    },
    {
        "question": "834913421÷68665509=？",
        "answer": 1.0849027985521666
    },
    {
        "question": "6131÷4672=？",
        "answer": 0.11802848202289118
    },
    {
        "question": "2×10771065=？",
        "answer": 7.333288642393367
    },
    {
        "question": "138×62053=？",
        "answer": 6.932641869044216
    },
    {
        "question": "441×4106=？",
        "answer": 6.257857534502412
    },
    {
        "question": "2×7607208=？",
        "answer": 7.182255286773379
    },
    {
        "question": "782265×846=？",
        "answer": 8.820724262571886
    },
    {
        "question": "2144÷270=？",
        "answer": 0.8998610168617451
    },
    {
        "question": "76×2934=？",
        "answer": 5.348273701788055
    },
    {
        "question": "233473712÷30186=？",
        "answer": 3.8884324205072986
    },
    {
        "question": "2156×341=？",
        "answer": 5.866403135507198
    },
    {
        "question": "729082031÷5650278=？",
        "answer": 2.110706578599496
    },
    {
        "question": "11×26071318=？",
        "answer": 8.457555672048013
    },
    {
        "question": "7711543÷816=？",
        "answer": 3.975451125826204
    },
    {
        "question": "182577189÷498=？",
        "answer": 5.564217173536774
    },
    {
        "question": "7686×1605=？",
        "answer": 7.091175416869221
    },
    {
        "question": "402837577÷3697=？",
        "answer": 5.037280524522416
    },
    {
        "question": "514339439÷45666=？",
        "answer": 4.051656854510872
    },
    {
        "question": "754×2131=？",
        "answer": 6.205954795583976
    },
    {
        "question": "16202×7808=？",
        "answer": 8.102108432494576
    },
    {
        "question": "8×342569=？",
        "answer": 6.437838046911342
    },
    {
        "question": "4×205823=？",
        "answer": 5.915553895354754
    },
    {
        "question": "106184350÷10386=？",
        "answer": 4.009612194630629
    },
    {
        "question": "61282÷1148=？",
        "answer": 1.727391042433187
    },
    {
        "question": "209530×2617=？",
        "answer": 8.739049935630472
    },
    {
        "question": "7×3941024=？",
        "answer": 7.440707119649164
    },
    {
        "question": "71×155307=？",
        "answer": 7.042449379417765
    },
    {
        "question": "16×5360=？",
        "answer": 4.933284772348695
    },
    {
        "question": "2856337÷4800=？",
        "answer": 2.774568208237726
    },
    {
        "question": "1903×132113=？",
        "answer": 8.400384342846886
    },
    {
        "question": "295221093÷11503543=？",
        "answer": 1.4093157635835498
    },
    {
        "question": "7×67565667=？",
        "answer": 8.674824108438584
    },
    {
        "question": "211879÷54858=？",
        "answer": 0.5868479443880881
    },
    {
        "question": "47×26968=？",
        "answer": 6.102946597448633
    },
    {
        "question": "324886975÷27660=？",
        "answer": 4.0698801246790595
    },
    {
        "question": "58408÷303=？",
        "answer": 2.2850297069304264
    },
    {
        "question": "2×3492435=？",
        "answer": 6.844158327585772
    },
    {
        "question": "63288×455=？",
        "answer": 7.459332768162152
    },
    {
        "question": "247399793÷1278=？",
        "answer": 5.286868478095638
    },
    {
        "question": "4182×44379=？",
        "answer": 8.268561540452115
    },
    {
        "question": "15×54367295=？",
        "answer": 8.911428984630541
    },
    {
        "question": "1503815÷257648=？",
        "answer": 0.7661676368517093
    },
    {
        "question": "8×314=？",
        "answer": 3.4000196350651586
    },
    {
        "question": "47×17336041=？",
        "answer": 8.911047783361733
    },
    {
        "question": "1×665=？",
        "answer": 2.8228216453031045
    },
    {
        "question": "40884÷1460=？",
        "answer": 1.4472005238310652
    },
    {
        "question": "1343×5894=？",
        "answer": 6.8984861441826215
    },
    {
        "question": "825987758÷69580309=？",
        "answer": 1.0744872575916848
    },
    {
        "question": "986520851÷133335=？",
        "answer": 3.8691621036318966
    },
    {
        "question": "156×26828=？",
        "answer": 6.621712896023076
    },
    {
        "question": "5×3770301=？",
        "answer": 7.275346027597734
    },
    {
        "question": "12×1951=？",
        "answer": 4.369438515442143
    },
    {
        "question": "14765×249=？",
        "answer": 6.5654327983968335
    },
    {
        "question": "405×65912=？",
        "answer": 7.426419513064304
    },
    {
        "question": "46×69890=？",
        "answer": 6.507172872155398
    },
    {
        "question": "117010577÷87838=？",
        "answer": 3.12454268224962
    },
    {
        "question": "57361×590=？",
        "answer": 7.529468725618071
    },
    {
        "question": "324613480÷1950=？",
        "answer": 5.221331939149447
    },
    {
        "question": "27677962÷3551438=？",
        "answer": 0.8917298714508577
    },
    {
        "question": "373225÷2676=？",
        "answer": 2.1444846176142778
    },
    {
        "question": "1×414115890=？",
        "answer": 8.61712189509286
    },
    {
        "question": "133×108225=？",
        "answer": 7.15817923545228
    },
    {
        "question": "3651257÷17384=？",
        "answer": 2.322292689276727
    },
    {
        "question": "219529390÷534177=？",
        "answer": 2.6138074859206797
    },
    {
        "question": "1098517×280=？",
        "answer": 8.48796481353554
    },
    {
        "question": "69×1787=？",
        "answer": 5.0909736432429
    },
    {
        "question": "375681443÷25361280=？",
        "answer": 1.1706485744858321
    },
    {
        "question": "44112316÷35089=？",
        "answer": 3.099388868404594
    },
    {
        "question": "345×498018=？",
        "answer": 8.235064134940222
    },
    {
        "question": "186877÷212=？",
        "answer": 2.945219992682581
    },
    {
        "question": "152×1089398=？",
        "answer": 8.21903016157166
    },
    {
        "question": "272440417÷10659=？",
        "answer": 4.407555074137524
    },
    {
        "question": "706186078÷827=？",
        "answer": 5.931413641925204
    },
    {
        "question": "15163×9726=？",
        "answer": 8.168719400205598
    },
    {
        "question": "240×11110=？",
        "answer": 6.425925300652474
    },
    {
        "question": "91123498÷61081=？",
        "answer": 3.1737242442719102
    },
    {
        "question": "203650÷204=？",
        "answer": 2.999254246996118
    },
    {
        "question": "23354505÷901=？",
        "answer": 4.41364587584719
    },
    {
        "question": "299406×416=？",
        "answer": 8.0953538298428
    },
    {
        "question": "248×76994=？",
        "answer": 7.280908563551684
    },
    {
        "question": "1216525×380=？",
        "answer": 8.664904634873771
    },
    {
        "question": "77628×6802=？",
        "answer": 8.722655024784817
    },
    {
        "question": "274140869÷30684=？",
        "answer": 3.95106181103901
    },
    {
        "question": "4×2981=？",
        "answer": 4.076421967360593
    },
    {
        "question": "89456434÷103706=？",
        "answer": 2.935807698312198
    },
    {
        "question": "249944020÷44288646=？",
        "answer": 0.7515503473991003
    },
    {
        "question": "2×742=？",
        "answer": 3.171433900943008
    },
    {
        "question": "485155648÷709=？",
        "answer": 5.835234856456493
    },
    {
        "question": "505×832750=？",
        "answer": 8.623806019481876
    },
    {
        "question": "10×6696=？",
        "answer": 4.825815444985204
    },
    {
        "question": "3087662÷101265=？",
        "answer": 1.4841703858986421
    },
    {
        "question": "160975÷52781=？",
        "answer": 0.4842808195669866
    },
    {
        "question": "84×15338=？",
        "answer": 6.110048019495495
    },
    {
        "question": "21694614÷2256535=？",
        "answer": 0.9829098533421824
    },
    {
        "question": "5844864÷8393=？",
        "answer": 2.8428571872116666
    },
    {
        "question": "88×91045=？",
        "answer": 6.903738772396046
    },
    {
        "question": "929651×561=？",
        "answer": 8.717282802045775
    },
    {
        "question": "4×41533978=？",
        "answer": 8.22046351985448
    },
    {
        "question": "5716×91451=？",
        "answer": 8.718280678888256
    },
    {
        "question": "6×6452899=？",
        "answer": 7.587906118018903
    },
    {
        "question": "92818÷3867=？",
        "answer": 1.3802580341310218
    },
    {
        "question": "16077×28520=？",
        "answer": 8.661354532943102
    },
    {
        "question": "37×10335=？",
        "answer": 5.582512205030302
    },
    {
        "question": "3198395÷39152=？",
        "answer": 1.9121781458412068
    },
    {
        "question": "5186×9753=？",
        "answer": 7.703970736649122
    },
    {
        "question": "1×802146=？",
        "answer": 5.9042534221789245
    },
    {
        "question": "89×234=？",
        "answer": 4.318605864055056
    },
    {
        "question": "16×85863=？",
        "answer": 6.137926041044447
    },
    {
        "question": "1×283842=？",
        "answer": 5.453076658276716
    },
    {
        "question": "187584÷1493=？",
        "answer": 2.0991359846972975
    },
    {
        "question": "111787969÷1422=？",
        "answer": 4.895495469427966
    },
    {
        "question": "322777919÷1963=？",
        "answer": 5.215983517700156
    },
    {
        "question": "24828÷488=？",
        "answer": 1.7065219147106487
    },
    {
        "question": "5×155904=？",
        "answer": 5.891827262280744
    },
    {
        "question": "356×89091=？",
        "answer": 7.501283831664553
    },
    {
        "question": "332129199÷340581=？",
        "answer": 2.98908664178883
    },
    {
        "question": "319×182433=？",
        "answer": 7.764894082957498
    },
    {
        "question": "348236225÷24092525=？",
        "answer": 1.1599916279649825
    },
    {
        "question": "310888533÷7794905=？",
        "answer": 1.600793876943558
    },
    {
        "question": "11×54737=？",
        "answer": 5.779673676274913
    },
    {
        "question": "2219166÷9800=？",
        "answer": 2.354963714231064
    },
    {
        "question": "535948939÷729025=？",
        "answer": 2.866380993937509
    },
    {
        "question": "43614×4863=？",
        "answer": 8.32653018880899
    },
    {
        "question": "382296477÷185722459=？",
        "answer": 0.3135358706849357
    },
    {
        "question": "2×264=？",
        "answer": 2.722633922533812
    },
    {
        "question": "28240044÷1614=？",
        "answer": 4.242961838655978
    },
    {
        "question": "340×2704136=？",
        "answer": 8.963507446976147
    },
    {
        "question": "706428255÷48942=？",
        "answer": 4.159386348695781
    },
    {
        "question": "613669÷76179=？",
        "answer": 0.9060989177024688
    },
    {
        "question": "17×2193668=？",
        "answer": 7.571619821427214
    },
    {
        "question": "18×225=？",
        "answer": 3.6074550232146687
    },
    {
        "question": "705÷388=？",
        "answer": 0.25935739139719144
    },
    {
        "question": "17750÷7690=？",
        "answer": 0.3632720175896819
    },
    {
        "question": "886666941÷46137=？",
        "answer": 4.283711164627014
    },
    {
        "question": "427×366=？",
        "answer": 5.193908960419434
    },
    {
        "question": "217200051÷15329=？",
        "answer": 4.151346098673482
    },
    {
        "question": "102356÷216=？",
        "answer": 2.675659554475012
    },
    {
        "question": "257456076÷66963257=？",
        "answer": 0.5848665767151869
    },
    {
        "question": "22366÷1669=？",
        "answer": 1.1271319838832161
    },
    {
        "question": "1770215÷177817=？",
        "answer": 0.9980527375741511
    },
    {
        "question": "1×3867=？",
        "answer": 3.5873741720730656
    },
    {
        "question": "16276×957=？",
        "answer": 7.192459618958091
    },
    {
        "question": "12×289=？",
        "answer": 3.540079088804173
    },
    {
        "question": "2×54977102=？",
        "answer": 8.04121183887278
    },
    {
        "question": "748872÷319349=？",
        "answer": 0.37014203224807213
    },
    {
        "question": "191×82902=？",
        "answer": 7.199598375222445
    },
    {
        "question": "59×902475=？",
        "answer": 7.726287191735153
    },
    {
        "question": "1174×18415=？",
        "answer": 7.334839820102528
    },
    {
        "question": "2018×5982=？",
        "answer": 7.081767570596191
    },
    {
        "question": "4050850÷79512=？",
        "answer": 1.7071134842821005
    },
    {
        "question": "665523×807=？",
        "answer": 8.730036603699526
    },
    {
        "question": "22533414÷648450=？",
        "answer": 1.540950501352707
    },
    {
        "question": "1019×597738=？",
        "answer": 8.784685050122395
    },
    {
        "question": "1972×117334=？",
        "answer": 8.364330786938934
    },
    {
        "question": "229×4396=？",
        "answer": 6.002893166091341
    },
    {
        "question": "452×10241=？",
        "answer": 6.66548080095095
    },
    {
        "question": "153527÷1405=？",
        "answer": 2.038508439414841
    },
    {
        "question": "4×11969452=？",
        "answer": 7.6801342587916785
    },
    {
        "question": "118367159÷4249333=？",
        "answer": 1.4449104579646936
    },
    {
        "question": "4129×1553=？",
        "answer": 6.807016338603261
    },
    {
        "question": "1×3915=？",
        "answer": 3.592731766393962
    },
    {
        "question": "3174×50656=？",
        "answer": 8.20623781560109
    },
    {
        "question": "70447283÷3754=？",
        "answer": 4.273369979680109
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1121377=？",
        "answer": 6.049751644257999
    },
    {
        "question": "29372049÷2824725=？",
        "answer": 1.016958070405693
    },
    {
        "question": "50771070÷45091906=？",
        "answer": 0.05151772326819697
    },
    {
        "question": "172×1378473=？",
        "answer": 8.374926710954094
    },
    {
        "question": "126070993÷14784=？",
        "answer": 3.930823219697999
    },
    {
        "question": "1024×12302=？",
        "answer": 7.100275679327541
    },
    {
        "question": "594162×458=？",
        "answer": 8.434770350786161
    },
    {
        "question": "3×2306574=？",
        "answer": 6.840088647015836
    },
    {
        "question": "13541÷4485=？",
        "answer": 0.47988829070943045
    },
    {
        "question": "17265281÷194322=？",
        "answer": 1.9486516794118867
    },
    {
        "question": "208901174÷3258944=？",
        "answer": 1.8068639828324276
    },
    {
        "question": "11×16046=？",
        "answer": 5.246759473024701
    },
    {
        "question": "10×1454=？",
        "answer": 4.162564406523019
    },
    {
        "question": "74830680÷1537436=？",
        "answer": 1.6872826456318946
    },
    {
        "question": "25665436÷254783=？",
        "answer": 2.003178199374037
    },
    {
        "question": "1×40385=？",
        "answer": 4.6062200872173475
    },
    {
        "question": "396918122÷359756=？",
        "answer": 3.0426928820240975
    },
    {
        "question": "220×3741271=？",
        "answer": 8.915441848400764
    },
    {
        "question": "13779×1464=？",
        "answer": 7.304758776859959
    },
    {
        "question": "922061÷640870=？",
        "answer": 0.15798971111016044
    },
    {
        "question": "230348630÷2080=？",
        "answer": 5.044322298664316
    },
    {
        "question": "314697682÷9950=？",
        "answer": 4.5000704632532385
    },
    {
        "question": "461÷412=？",
        "answer": 0.04880370935651357
    },
    {
        "question": "584423÷32883=？",
        "answer": 1.2497558668129987
    },
    {
        "question": "6779×49851=？",
        "answer": 8.528839508495452
    },
    {
        "question": "111908448÷953473=？",
        "answer": 2.069554473368386
    },
    {
        "question": "1016532÷16382=？",
        "answer": 1.7927541330003514
    },
    {
        "question": "49594526÷2019=？",
        "answer": 4.390297424901639
    },
    {
        "question": "1×733048=？",
        "answer": 5.86513241318494
    },
    {
        "question": "253043÷3293=？",
        "answer": 1.8856025970881172
    },
    {
        "question": "91986229÷11953=？",
        "answer": 3.8862458957003154
    },
    {
        "question": "11409709÷2824=？",
        "answer": 3.606409875675096
    },
    {
        "question": "5×45459861=？",
        "answer": 8.356598107809765
    },
    {
        "question": "622792774÷224=？",
        "answer": 6.444095546656762
    },
    {
        "question": "42×19265430=？",
        "answer": 8.908027997208801
    },
    {
        "question": "192×1505906=？",
        "answer": 8.461099092364115
    },
    {
        "question": "143419÷9321=？",
        "answer": 1.1871441820499662
    },
    {
        "question": "676370÷179278=？",
        "answer": 0.5766573378461857
    },
    {
        "question": "129828580÷36010=？",
        "answer": 3.556947185654012
    },
    {
        "question": "47×4337=？",
        "answer": 5.3092872800844795
    },
    {
        "question": "2024×489228=？",
        "answer": 8.995721813231729
    },
    {
        "question": "457203÷427223=？",
        "answer": 0.029454446064661292
    },
    {
        "question": "31×609=？",
        "answer": 4.275978986467148
    },
    {
        "question": "8×27169195=？",
        "answer": 8.337166757826575
    },
    {
        "question": "18295÷1278=？",
        "answer": 1.155801560000245
    },
    {
        "question": "1×546591496=？",
        "answer": 8.737662870552755
    },
    {
        "question": "17179000÷20838=？",
        "answer": 2.916141845991625
    },
    {
        "question": "2×64698=？",
        "answer": 5.111920851257119
    },
    {
        "question": "904×79116=？",
        "answer": 7.854432752266691
    },
    {
        "question": "16×3094348=？",
        "answer": 7.694689136874108
    },
    {
        "question": "204×613455=？",
        "answer": 8.097412877979606
    },
    {
        "question": "264×1020199=？",
        "answer": 8.430288820369356
    },
    {
        "question": "459159÷6250=？",
        "answer": 1.8660830840216274
    },
    {
        "question": "12266÷8958=？",
        "answer": 0.13649190224280514
    },
    {
        "question": "20×596740=？",
        "answer": 7.0768151456197605
    },
    {
        "question": "1×44509=？",
        "answer": 4.648447836938991
    },
    {
        "question": "251×9897=？",
        "answer": 6.3951772917460445
    },
    {
        "question": "1197×12819=？",
        "answer": 7.18594829794327
    },
    {
        "question": "23×4446=？",
        "answer": 5.009697294380564
    },
    {
        "question": "723846019÷20564907=？",
        "answer": 1.5465194403611444
    },
    {
        "question": "1149×7096=？",
        "answer": 6.911333635511955
    },
    {
        "question": "15025×1789=？",
        "answer": 7.42942482124215
    },
    {
        "question": "17×154334=？",
        "answer": 6.418910533674595
    },
    {
        "question": "59055÷50564=？",
        "answer": 0.06741525118998103
    },
    {
        "question": "207×226=？",
        "answer": 4.670078784604319
    },
    {
        "question": "209713736÷2069=？",
        "answer": 5.005866386502678
    },
    {
        "question": "413423÷319945=？",
        "answer": 0.11131930656811358
    },
    {
        "question": "795391827÷346571974=？",
        "answer": 0.3607876841050716
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1640058=？",
        "answer": 6.214859206971201
    },
    {
        "question": "25×34531=？",
        "answer": 5.936149164148436
    },
    {
        "question": "2761848÷2257422=？",
        "answer": 0.08758702003423426
    },
    {
        "question": "32230×3125=？",
        "answer": 8.003110327192429
    },
    {
        "question": "296580561÷1330=？",
        "answer": 5.34829104137229
    },
    {
        "question": "161775698÷292397=？",
        "answer": 2.742940369874941
    },
    {
        "question": "78965÷12003=？",
        "answer": 0.8181448336092749
    },
    {
        "question": "11129543÷204=？",
        "answer": 4.736847164325431
    },
    {
        "question": "15×6390=？",
        "answer": 4.981592117214081
    },
    {
        "question": "9993×230=？",
        "answer": 6.361423723428432
    },
    {
        "question": "1×153276345=？",
        "answer": 8.185475135750277
    },
    {
        "question": "410598199÷53303120=？",
        "answer": 0.886664409701589
    },
    {
        "question": "32189767÷13036671=？",
        "answer": 0.39255112754221144
    },
    {
        "question": "17737806÷3863508=？",
        "answer": 0.6619180848124443
    },
    {
        "question": "359×224=？",
        "answer": 4.905342466912482
    },
    {
        "question": "609506982÷3293410=？",
        "answer": 2.267332885051169
    },
    {
        "question": "1×4951=？",
        "answer": 3.6946929263314843
    },
    {
        "question": "10572913÷4930981=？",
        "answer": 0.3312613294813713
    },
    {
        "question": "82546442÷553239=？",
        "answer": 2.173785570955421
    },
    {
        "question": "792707070÷10513=？",
        "answer": 4.877386067184813
    },
    {
        "question": "1107038×245=？",
        "answer": 8.433328613018382
    },
    {
        "question": "82626012÷343252=？",
        "answer": 2.381503715360857
    },
    {
        "question": "48004÷11894=？",
        "answer": 0.6059494929112706
    },
    {
        "question": "100394474÷2819=？",
        "answer": 4.551614732780478
    },
    {
        "question": "30×1345=？",
        "answer": 4.605843539058089
    },
    {
        "question": "162062875÷65427=？",
        "answer": 3.3939265318250067
    },
    {
        "question": "95×3595=？",
        "answer": 5.533422500007749
    },
    {
        "question": "9×692=？",
        "answer": 3.7943486038960827
    },
    {
        "question": "485045570÷221=？",
        "answer": 6.341390268772491
    },
    {
        "question": "67×2566=？",
        "answer": 5.235331454739736
    },
    {
        "question": "90×4841=？",
        "answer": 5.639177592080214
    },
    {
        "question": "61604951÷682=？",
        "answer": 4.9558312418192365
    },
    {
        "question": "38×2615158=？",
        "answer": 7.997281529382335
    },
    {
        "question": "4×713381=？",
        "answer": 6.455381529600496
    },
    {
        "question": "4×15548079=？",
        "answer": 7.793736729948942
    },
    {
        "question": "18753×746=？",
        "answer": 7.1458095810951345
    },
    {
        "question": "3×110241636=？",
        "answer": 8.51946690431678
    },
    {
        "question": "81739÷849=？",
        "answer": 1.983521629978472
    },
    {
        "question": "8×6387=？",
        "answer": 4.708386903149929
    },
    {
        "question": "302652÷127655=？",
        "answer": 0.3749057182342886
    },
    {
        "question": "214×1594963=？",
        "answer": 8.533164386082696
    },
    {
        "question": "3×2333=？",
        "answer": 3.845035993513415
    },
    {
        "question": "847860÷15381=？",
        "answer": 1.7413395746167133
    },
    {
        "question": "186×1960215=？",
        "answer": 8.561816652407424
    },
    {
        "question": "2008×23120=？",
        "answer": 7.666751538221473
    },
    {
        "question": "528751÷1740=？",
        "answer": 2.4827019534604444
    },
    {
        "question": "14235÷3433=？",
        "answer": 0.6176836680572237
    },
    {
        "question": "119249÷1869=？",
        "answer": 1.8048454444356017
    },
    {
        "question": "3×112496999=？",
        "answer": 8.528262191965943
    },
    {
        "question": "5×51054=？",
        "answer": 5.406999778376446
    },
    {
        "question": "2259112÷1003276=？",
        "answer": 0.3525173391349085
    },
    {
        "question": "275×298493=？",
        "answer": 7.914266844716021
    },
    {
        "question": "109×28096=？",
        "answer": 6.486070992166632
    },
    {
        "question": "8095×100907=？",
        "answer": 8.912138147729921
    },
    {
        "question": "18140÷607=？",
        "answer": 1.475448591648819
    },
    {
        "question": "34250÷1764=？",
        "answer": 1.2881619950326435
    },
    {
        "question": "16001÷1603=？",
        "answer": 0.9992136028587028
    },
    {
        "question": "16942÷861=？",
        "answer": 1.2939615259515058
    },
    {
        "question": "835088÷142048=？",
        "answer": 0.769297119684043
    },
    {
        "question": "169×455=？",
        "answer": 4.885898101270786
    },
    {
        "question": "15143706÷382997=？",
        "answer": 1.5970367974710347
    },
    {
        "question": "2739379÷438=？",
        "answer": 3.796178011644666
    },
    {
        "question": "866986÷12014=？",
        "answer": 1.8583244569792488
    },
    {
        "question": "3×3882=？",
        "answer": 4.066176785772006
    },
    {
        "question": "80892÷28927=？",
        "answer": 0.44660217759595017
    },
    {
        "question": "2427×184079=？",
        "answer": 8.650074022715787
    },
    {
        "question": "1×6669=？",
        "answer": 3.824060717418653
    },
    {
        "question": "15×2145=？",
        "answer": 4.507518555576424
    },
    {
        "question": "29159÷2453=？",
        "answer": 1.0750750776834188
    },
    {
        "question": "3437×434=？",
        "answer": 6.173669261649736
    },
    {
        "question": "45×229072=？",
        "answer": 7.013184521390536
    },
    {
        "question": "13755×4879=？",
        "answer": 7.826791412837968
    },
    {
        "question": "1298030×389=？",
        "answer": 8.703234331296912
    },
    {
        "question": "69951×2790=？",
        "answer": 8.290398130698694
    },
    {
        "question": "5×1529=？",
        "answer": 3.883377489748339
    },
    {
        "question": "40602×4146=？",
        "answer": 8.226176724624954
    },
    {
        "question": "10×7375742=？",
        "answer": 7.867805716893729
    },
    {
        "question": "51217702÷8127341=？",
        "answer": 0.7994716070583991
    },
    {
        "question": "10883×2734=？",
        "answer": 7.473547139404006
    },
    {
        "question": "1952783÷14800=？",
        "answer": 2.1203922702694347
    },
    {
        "question": "222309÷131603=？",
        "answer": 0.22769125562039305
    },
    {
        "question": "228503×843=？",
        "answer": 8.284719480890098
    },
    {
        "question": "401650616÷25044810=？",
        "answer": 1.205130696059446
    },
    {
        "question": "19883÷5477=？",
        "answer": 0.5599391715846976
    },
    {
        "question": "30118040÷689751=？",
        "answer": 1.6401343669552229
    },
    {
        "question": "354408675÷3587622=？",
        "answer": 1.994697665211557
    },
    {
        "question": "301214114÷172587=？",
        "answer": 3.2418672380861207
    },
    {
        "question": "79×4397=？",
        "answer": 5.540783556910148
    },
    {
        "question": "1×23780=？",
        "answer": 4.376211850282672
    },
    {
        "question": "1059×11429=？",
        "answer": 7.0829041928228875
    },
    {
        "question": "7712243÷573362=？",
        "answer": 1.1287517986408517
    },
    {
        "question": "4068÷3340=？",
        "answer": 0.08563447743914251
    },
    {
        "question": "1×80856966=？",
        "answer": 7.9077174412497095
    },
    {
        "question": "34359887÷6639=？",
        "answer": 3.7139490582422856
    },
    {
        "question": "29440531÷1141=？",
        "answer": 4.411659994409278
    },
    {
        "question": "231×329=？",
        "answer": 4.880807877842119
    },
    {
        "question": "100×5761=？",
        "answer": 5.760497875226527
    },
    {
        "question": "21168÷1682=？",
        "answer": 1.0998538353815324
    },
    {
        "question": "60392÷16651=？",
        "answer": 0.5595390915516866
    },
    {
        "question": "1217÷575=？",
        "answer": 0.3256227335404345
    },
    {
        "question": "42848618÷626=？",
        "answer": 4.835362485939033
    },
    {
        "question": "138266×1853=？",
        "answer": 8.408590818316581
    },
    {
        "question": "244×607383=？",
        "answer": 8.170852458653421
    },
    {
        "question": "1×314554452=？",
        "answer": 8.49769583628736
    },
    {
        "question": "2×440=？",
        "answer": 2.9444826721501687
    },
    {
        "question": "2×6594=？",
        "answer": 4.120178938471115
    },
    {
        "question": "605039106÷560956=？",
        "answer": 3.032854648071142
    },
    {
        "question": "10×627=？",
        "answer": 3.7972675408307164
    },
    {
        "question": "175269407÷4340004=？",
        "answer": 1.606215987504723
    },
    {
        "question": "3324967÷4327=？",
        "answer": 2.885600444127911
    },
    {
        "question": "1×2902=？",
        "answer": 3.4626974081017172
    },
    {
        "question": "14892485÷381=？",
        "answer": 4.59204219566565
    },
    {
        "question": "45289827÷291996=？",
        "answer": 2.190623759581472
    },
    {
        "question": "473711550÷588=？",
        "answer": 5.906136647716869
    },
    {
        "question": "84683248÷6089=？",
        "answer": 4.143251532843933
    },
    {
        "question": "1932×726=？",
        "answer": 6.146943742779568
    },
    {
        "question": "905229551÷7414803=？",
        "answer": 2.086659105976477
    },
    {
        "question": "8655×456=？",
        "answer": 6.5962319148758475
    },
    {
        "question": "8×3490=？",
        "answer": 4.445915413951123
    },
    {
        "question": "28501÷316=？",
        "answer": 1.9551730155256462
    },
    {
        "question": "657103÷1039=？",
        "answer": 2.801017902406845
    },
    {
        "question": "41353÷4989=？",
        "answer": 0.9184935174750185
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1733=？",
        "answer": 3.238798562713917
    },
    {
        "question": "8×67390=？",
        "answer": 5.731685443363646
    },
    {
        "question": "223002332÷10744=？",
        "answer": 4.317143404954481
    },
    {
        "question": "74207÷1648=？",
        "answer": 1.653487667162987
    },
    {
        "question": "1820÷483=？",
        "answer": 0.5761242572335626
    },
    {
        "question": "4453×504=？",
        "answer": 6.351083231576748
    },
    {
        "question": "70785455÷279=？",
        "answer": 5.404339824724301
    },
    {
        "question": "7024688÷1304=？",
        "answer": 3.7313494485139693
    },
    {
        "question": "2×102487109=？",
        "answer": 8.311699238204582
    },
    {
        "question": "259870046÷1961=？",
        "answer": 5.122278629632317
    },
    {
        "question": "35×441=？",
        "answer": 4.188506633818114
    },
    {
        "question": "8691754÷598=？",
        "answer": 4.162406242132877
    },
    {
        "question": "14141×18135=？",
        "answer": 8.408997682186788
    },
    {
        "question": "92404×445=？",
        "answer": 7.614050782421033
    },
    {
        "question": "2399593÷369774=？",
        "answer": 0.812201215106243
    },
    {
        "question": "1686×4647=？",
        "answer": 6.894030242767592
    },
    {
        "question": "121314699÷50737=？",
        "answer": 3.378588640516979
    },
    {
        "question": "387265×734=？",
        "answer": 8.453704308273887
    },
    {
        "question": "1615×1066=？",
        "answer": 6.235929731357675
    },
    {
        "question": "21469×1417=？",
        "answer": 7.483181666244203
    },
    {
        "question": "257017÷1295=？",
        "answer": 2.2976920816144832
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1668890=？",
        "answer": 6.222427712372857
    },
    {
        "question": "821×74965=？",
        "answer": 7.789201702448358
    },
    {
        "question": "1×393=？",
        "answer": 2.5943925503754266
    },
    {
        "question": "79372÷4382=？",
        "answer": 1.2579949504855157
    },
    {
        "question": "757×201202=？",
        "answer": 8.18272817290507
    },
    {
        "question": "2388×4865=？",
        "answer": 7.065117167061702
    },
    {
        "question": "13156783÷133449=？",
        "answer": 1.9938343880092795
    },
    {
        "question": "129675540÷291836=？",
        "answer": 2.6477192010691986
    },
    {
        "question": "20863815÷516122=？",
        "answer": 1.606641351649205
    },
    {
        "question": "604336873÷293859=？",
        "answer": 3.313140096730971
    },
    {
        "question": "9325×783=？",
        "answer": 6.863410602538669
    },
    {
        "question": "82×2153=？",
        "answer": 5.246857882207204
    },
    {
        "question": "172×329=？",
        "answer": 4.752724344857524
    },
    {
        "question": "219727302÷30018=？",
        "answer": 3.864502269840384
    },
    {
        "question": "222×77691=？",
        "answer": 7.236723685957804
    },
    {
        "question": "2657939÷6302=？",
        "answer": 2.6250666107757334
    },
    {
        "question": "387791049÷123403950=？",
        "answer": 0.4972687193438582
    },
    {
        "question": "177351÷521=？",
        "answer": 2.5319959183004164
    },
    {
        "question": "271013372÷2721131=？",
        "answer": 1.9982412698355785
    },
    {
        "question": "27×610978=？",
        "answer": 7.217389336675489
    },
    {
        "question": "9124609÷6358=？",
        "answer": 3.1568937399299632
    },
    {
        "question": "7106÷501=？",
        "answer": 1.1517874772860635
    },
    {
        "question": "237×1551=？",
        "answer": 5.565360143823709
    },
    {
        "question": "621340÷1065=？",
        "answer": 2.765979705310582
    },
    {
        "question": "551477312÷41572=？",
        "answer": 4.122726731478603
    },
    {
        "question": "9659×650=？",
        "answer": 6.797845522710268
    },
    {
        "question": "16930372÷3921667=？",
        "answer": 0.6351957869761283
    },
    {
        "question": "21644552÷1897=？",
        "answer": 4.0572812703050305
    },
    {
        "question": "202×1990233=？",
        "answer": 8.604255292434608
    },
    {
        "question": "7169323÷4219449=？",
        "answer": 0.23022240514122522
    },
    {
        "question": "168889748÷813911=？",
        "answer": 2.3170263696802635
    },
    {
        "question": "9409521÷178082=？",
        "answer": 1.722947491360344
    },
    {
        "question": "7×24465=？",
        "answer": 5.233643260110214
    },
    {
        "question": "76734÷7073=？",
        "answer": 1.0353841796679912
    },
    {
        "question": "415084013÷14784=？",
        "answer": 4.4483440529315725
    },
    {
        "question": "1467504÷255309=？",
        "answer": 0.7595131691218037
    },
    {
        "question": "2584480÷13189=？",
        "answer": 2.292161307471536
    },
    {
        "question": "17×25144596=？",
        "answer": 8.63089358355116
    },
    {
        "question": "206867×534=？",
        "answer": 8.043232473354225
    },
    {
        "question": "3881×6071=？",
        "answer": 7.372203875612964
    },
    {
        "question": "166139528÷833=？",
        "answer": 5.299827970899831
    },
    {
        "question": "45200961÷57586=？",
        "answer": 2.8948307553687407
    },
    {
        "question": "473989459÷11896616=？",
        "answer": 1.6003452399367477
    },
    {
        "question": "479264×356=？",
        "answer": 8.232024806083103
    },
    {
        "question": "123873323÷29618=？",
        "answer": 3.621422059256916
    },
    {
        "question": "35529÷22085=？",
        "answer": 0.2064855804050875
    },
    {
        "question": "222477÷8165=？",
        "answer": 1.4353289305615982
    },
    {
        "question": "97357205÷4549867=？",
        "answer": 1.3303693956557996
    },
    {
        "question": "4×10785=？",
        "answer": 4.634880140766526
    },
    {
        "question": "109585÷1862=？",
        "answer": 1.769771435321867
    },
    {
        "question": "120×5710818=？",
        "answer": 8.835879565754475
    },
    {
        "question": "2×13822=？",
        "answer": 4.441600884296931
    },
    {
        "question": "1877256×316=？",
        "answer": 8.773210583692759
    },
    {
        "question": "43×3474=？",
        "answer": 5.1742982696906665
    },
    {
        "question": "2449209÷2894=？",
        "answer": 2.9275273198663356
    },
    {
        "question": "64×4328=？",
        "answer": 5.4424672260824005
    },
    {
        "question": "1×694=？",
        "answer": 2.841359470454855
    },
    {
        "question": "586277×287=？",
        "answer": 8.225984753618748
    },
    {
        "question": "3×32140906=？",
        "answer": 7.98417936937645
    },
    {
        "question": "4×132458447=？",
        "answer": 8.72413965021274
    },
    {
        "question": "3415×765=？",
        "answer": 6.417052143171169
    },
    {
        "question": "1500÷847=？",
        "answer": 0.24820784872497434
    },
    {
        "question": "1674×32691=？",
        "answer": 7.738183659273995
    },
    {
        "question": "171279×1146=？",
        "answer": 8.292888736328369
    },
    {
        "question": "153×5056=？",
        "answer": 5.888498496091928
    },
    {
        "question": "3×32827=？",
        "answer": 4.993352449877331
    },
    {
        "question": "39267×593=？",
        "answer": 7.367082415790407
    },
    {
        "question": "414×1053092=？",
        "answer": 8.639466654706204
    },
    {
        "question": "38×218=？",
        "answer": 3.918240090221415
    },
    {
        "question": "14019÷4588=？",
        "answer": 0.4850936265147457
    },
    {
        "question": "1×772989=？",
        "answer": 5.888173313745891
    },
    {
        "question": "4×776185=？",
        "answer": 6.492025236946369
    },
    {
        "question": "1×33937164=？",
        "answer": 7.530675547156324
    },
    {
        "question": "717632376÷811=？",
        "answer": 5.946881169471712
    },
    {
        "question": "606605÷16858=？",
        "answer": 1.556099936202668
    },
    {
        "question": "82741×2796=？",
        "answer": 8.364257932507412
    },
    {
        "question": "39431×3240=？",
        "answer": 8.10638280145622
    },
    {
        "question": "2795×531=？",
        "answer": 6.171476333303911
    },
    {
        "question": "415×1291=？",
        "answer": 5.728974338978513
    },
    {
        "question": "38×7844=？",
        "answer": 5.474321181612557
    },
    {
        "question": "24×7304304=？",
        "answer": 8.243790081645168
    },
    {
        "question": "2×14374728=？",
        "answer": 7.45862963134101
    },
    {
        "question": "3×2017=？",
        "answer": 3.781827152932428
    },
    {
        "question": "3×7588501=？",
        "answer": 7.357277250414517
    },
    {
        "question": "1419009÷1749=？",
        "answer": 2.9091953404805184
    },
    {
        "question": "35751530÷828=？",
        "answer": 4.63526429554352
    },
    {
        "question": "37120386÷7520530=？",
        "answer": 0.6933640355906336
    },
    {
        "question": "560873÷958=？",
        "answer": 2.7674990248278415
    },
    {
        "question": "40951972÷3888=？",
        "answer": 4.022548563348861
    },
    {
        "question": "184228÷29410=？",
        "answer": 0.7968606128703486
    },
    {
        "question": "31×118254=？",
        "answer": 6.564177533718091
    },
    {
        "question": "4705882÷5672=？",
        "answer": 2.918904810866572
    },
    {
        "question": "234×249=？",
        "answer": 4.765415204505879
    },
    {
        "question": "39760704÷607969=？",
        "answer": 1.8155726299743762
    },
    {
        "question": "24×21446=？",
        "answer": 5.711557543364172
    },
    {
        "question": "108×8990221=？",
        "answer": 8.987194123293682
    },
    {
        "question": "189746÷65711=？",
        "answer": 0.46053455298279183
    },
    {
        "question": "340×5267=？",
        "answer": 6.253042235399736
    },
    {
        "question": "2×367846642=？",
        "answer": 8.86669679147127
    },
    {
        "question": "6×1099=？",
        "answer": 3.8191489428071344
    },
    {
        "question": "89×543154=？",
        "answer": 7.684312988845012
    },
    {
        "question": "392536227÷737726=？",
        "answer": 2.725984654023907
    },
    {
        "question": "1468×371446=？",
        "answer": 8.7366217414919
    },
    {
        "question": "441×977813=？",
        "answer": 8.63469439636859
    },
    {
        "question": "166745064÷21443=？",
        "answer": 3.8907674411737445
    },
    {
        "question": "1×546=？",
        "answer": 2.7371926427047373
    },
    {
        "question": "4393×24511=？",
        "answer": 8.032122233229051
    },
    {
        "question": "51245183÷37963043=？",
        "answer": 0.13029203151337831
    },
    {
        "question": "102545839÷343=？",
        "answer": 5.47562392266257
    },
    {
        "question": "919680285÷209=？",
        "answer": 6.643490590590727
    },
    {
        "question": "1×163006=？",
        "answer": 5.212203590409686
    },
    {
        "question": "88452879÷46132=？",
        "answer": 3.2827096897117958
    },
    {
        "question": "7×1254729=？",
        "answer": 6.943647975780633
    },
    {
        "question": "11×75726=？",
        "answer": 5.920637702278527
    },
    {
        "question": "41634×12842=？",
        "answer": 8.728080803454402
    },
    {
        "question": "1244102×366=？",
        "answer": 8.658337073644047
    },
    {
        "question": "1×244934=？",
        "answer": 5.389049074987845
    },
    {
        "question": "3197×237922=？",
        "answer": 8.88117723819483
    },
    {
        "question": "11792×7751=？",
        "answer": 7.960945207403908
    },
    {
        "question": "484×26393=？",
        "answer": 7.106334119405038
    },
    {
        "question": "652÷586=？",
        "answer": 0.04634997971382951
    },
    {
        "question": "5×3143267=？",
        "answer": 7.196351277399939
    },
    {
        "question": "9086510÷2577=？",
        "answer": 3.5472826903276418
    },
    {
        "question": "74980679÷60994604=？",
        "answer": 0.0896579528804011
    },
    {
        "question": "34×275=？",
        "answer": 3.9708116108725178
    },
    {
        "question": "3281÷216=？",
        "answer": 1.1815524792351169
    },
    {
        "question": "4245944÷8820=？",
        "answer": 2.682505676800994
    },
    {
        "question": "104805×218=？",
        "answer": 7.358838495914629
    },
    {
        "question": "67180×3367=？",
        "answer": 8.354483115893734
    },
    {
        "question": "1012×31375=？",
        "answer": 7.501764246992875
    },
    {
        "question": "50×699=？",
        "answer": 4.5434471800817
    },
    {
        "question": "77270÷3140=？",
        "answer": 1.3910812641718138
    },
    {
        "question": "92004×447=？",
        "answer": 7.614114232435796
    },
    {
        "question": "172×2382=？",
        "answer": 5.612470204054308
    },
    {
        "question": "364421÷38420=？",
        "answer": 0.9770460350017858
    },
    {
        "question": "21335832÷1671=？",
        "answer": 4.106133133133375
    },
    {
        "question": "448062÷5356=？",
        "answer": 1.9224975447538177
    },
    {
        "question": "5913×3610=？",
        "answer": 7.329315080904763
    },
    {
        "question": "4281×340=？",
        "answer": 6.163024144876564
    },
    {
        "question": "17825500÷214283=？",
        "answer": 1.9200540025833073
    },
    {
        "question": "40×627=？",
        "answer": 4.3993275321586784
    },
    {
        "question": "1×19630043=？",
        "answer": 7.292921250931757
    },
    {
        "question": "344024751÷548=？",
        "answer": 5.797809130703538
    },
    {
        "question": "593445784÷2614209=？",
        "answer": 2.3560407433641855
    },
    {
        "question": "8246748÷316609=？",
        "answer": 1.4157594677560772
    },
    {
        "question": "9546÷264=？",
        "answer": 1.558217503160394
    },
    {
        "question": "425×240956=？",
        "answer": 8.01032667510733
    },
    {
        "question": "13003872÷3023=？",
        "answer": 3.6336345388102775
    },
    {
        "question": "2×368755003=？",
        "answer": 8.86776791688221
    },
    {
        "question": "1×54709749=？",
        "answer": 7.738064722305069
    },
    {
        "question": "162090730÷21212=？",
        "answer": 3.8831765597273056
    },
    {
        "question": "15×40220360=？",
        "answer": 8.780537212569358
    },
    {
        "question": "30065×5075=？",
        "answer": 8.183497254766769
    },
    {
        "question": "20×129247=？",
        "answer": 6.412450466976836
    },
    {
        "question": "3305029÷117219=？",
        "answer": 1.4501772624806124
    },
    {
        "question": "16133277÷89181=？",
        "answer": 2.257450252630225
    },
    {
        "question": "723842÷38937=？",
        "answer": 1.2692812917291243
    },
    {
        "question": "19834315÷551051=？",
        "answer": 1.5562254113815972
    },
    {
        "question": "8887×5678=？",
        "answer": 7.7029505683581085
    },
    {
        "question": "32×13757=？",
        "answer": 5.643673715599064
    },
    {
        "question": "9660×3094=？",
        "answer": 7.475497435778842
    },
    {
        "question": "14634÷2742=？",
        "answer": 0.7272956002438804
    },
    {
        "question": "7442964÷155957=？",
        "answer": 1.678741045932287
    },
    {
        "question": "616×260448=？",
        "answer": 8.20530173896559
    },
    {
        "question": "754312057÷1849=？",
        "answer": 5.610614138419053
    },
    {
        "question": "42×1391=？",
        "answer": 4.7665764203899466
    },
    {
        "question": "1726×20645=？",
        "answer": 7.551855678589912
    },
    {
        "question": "1793537÷809=？",
        "answer": 3.3457618188254625
    },
    {
        "question": "59616250÷7624=？",
        "answer": 3.8931817667981843
    },
    {
        "question": "2794×108969=？",
        "answer": 8.48352936720701
    },
    {
        "question": "281429639÷360486=？",
        "answer": 2.8924814306745144
    },
    {
        "question": "3282×19743=？",
        "answer": 7.811551722236732
    },
    {
        "question": "2127472÷201081=？",
        "answer": 1.0244928166148444
    },
    {
        "question": "100063819÷454096=？",
        "answer": 2.343129397648234
    },
    {
        "question": "606466÷266829=？",
        "answer": 0.35657342964965466
    },
    {
        "question": "3807307÷474=？",
        "answer": 3.9048395556368334
    },
    {
        "question": "24023÷3349=？",
        "answer": 0.8557120937489218
    },
    {
        "question": "7283×32066=？",
        "answer": 8.368355098187255
    },
    {
        "question": "363917411÷7321=？",
        "answer": 4.696432427299274
    },
    {
        "question": "886407÷51539=？",
        "answer": 1.2354971892676174
    },
    {
        "question": "1×260475=？",
        "answer": 5.415766046702462
    },
    {
        "question": "682×386=？",
        "answer": 5.420371679328234
    },
    {
        "question": "271144895÷7988109=？",
        "answer": 1.5307574498280965
    },
    {
        "question": "1778×921=？",
        "answer": 6.214191386831044
    },
    {
        "question": "203664924÷5291=？",
        "answer": 4.585378477949485
    },
    {
        "question": "1×86667=？",
        "answer": 4.9378537636113355
    },
    {
        "question": "414×305268=？",
        "answer": 8.101681622485396
    },
    {
        "question": "104218247÷381=？",
        "answer": 5.437018788178826
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1577=？",
        "answer": 3.197831693328903
    },
    {
        "question": "2×14548027=？",
        "answer": 7.463834094063986
    },
    {
        "question": "6525÷286=？",
        "answer": 1.3582144828812754
    },
    {
        "question": "4660173÷8437=？",
        "answer": 2.7422139902331737
    },
    {
        "question": "1449×395=？",
        "answer": 5.757665481097635
    },
    {
        "question": "3×999=？",
        "answer": 3.476686742945645
    },
    {
        "question": "7371114÷436338=？",
        "answer": 1.2277100912859529
    },
    {
        "question": "1×142009=？",
        "answer": 5.152315869217399
    },
    {
        "question": "13512÷2296=？",
        "answer": 0.7697477528370164
    },
    {
        "question": "5×2719=？",
        "answer": 4.133379211923519
    },
    {
        "question": "92511÷11567=？",
        "answer": 0.9029726399167287
    },
    {
        "question": "87786311÷44790524=？",
        "answer": 0.292240656026401
    },
    {
        "question": "10139511÷241731=？",
        "answer": 1.6226846620532522
    },
    {
        "question": "14×10438=？",
        "answer": 5.16474532819768
    },
    {
        "question": "1×40072828=？",
        "answer": 7.602849992331786
    },
    {
        "question": "158×112202=？",
        "answer": 7.248657685240184
    },
    {
        "question": "52426×242=？",
        "answer": 7.103362089149094
    },
    {
        "question": "56957947÷11596977=？",
        "answer": 0.691209531304012
    },
    {
        "question": "10×164825=？",
        "answer": 6.21702308441574
    },
    {
        "question": "40×51120=？",
        "answer": 6.310650836478306
    },
    {
        "question": "1×5580=？",
        "answer": 3.7466341989375787
    },
    {
        "question": "127015÷5782=？",
        "answer": 1.341776925216193
    },
    {
        "question": "374793721÷23085360=？",
        "answer": 1.2104556549897612
    },
    {
        "question": "79266013÷567354=？",
        "answer": 2.14523289306733
    },
    {
        "question": "862×2875=？",
        "answer": 6.394145114850362
    },
    {
        "question": "7758384÷4916=？",
        "answer": 3.1981593969189017
    },
    {
        "question": "13366÷8617=？",
        "answer": 0.19064536384210137
    },
    {
        "question": "10×361=？",
        "answer": 3.5575072019056577
    },
    {
        "question": "13×1542=？",
        "answer": 4.302027726021775
    },
    {
        "question": "403307×1124=？",
        "answer": 8.656402071140464
    },
    {
        "question": "42249×482=？",
        "answer": 7.308863472243577
    },
    {
        "question": "933×2461=？",
        "answer": 6.360993257449302
    },
    {
        "question": "1×3276=？",
        "answer": 3.5153438930883807
    },
    {
        "question": "851×2408=？",
        "answer": 6.311586042670375
    },
    {
        "question": "1×12915=？",
        "answer": 4.111094410509336
    },
    {
        "question": "142×94701=？",
        "answer": 7.128642909365094
    },
    {
        "question": "39090839÷563=？",
        "answer": 4.841566596869211
    },
    {
        "question": "27×1545=？",
        "answer": 4.620292247919841
    },
    {
        "question": "6×115977634=？",
        "answer": 8.842525495068083
    },
    {
        "question": "12977835÷1614=？",
        "answer": 3.9052987178582397
    },
    {
        "question": "1×259379127=？",
        "answer": 8.41393502420197
    },
    {
        "question": "1×54583664=？",
        "answer": 7.737062684898791
    },
    {
        "question": "207352339÷14383=？",
        "answer": 4.1588594582539535
    },
    {
        "question": "53823×14615=？",
        "answer": 8.895766720611618
    },
    {
        "question": "46326002÷1595202=？",
        "answer": 1.4630091361187363
    },
    {
        "question": "115×41824=？",
        "answer": 6.682123406254062
    },
    {
        "question": "403280÷4307=？",
        "answer": 1.9714318126674941
    },
    {
        "question": "391×186383=？",
        "answer": 7.8625830552052225
    },
    {
        "question": "960721÷34189=？",
        "answer": 1.4487108856399022
    },
    {
        "question": "3×338=？",
        "answer": 3.0060379549973173
    },
    {
        "question": "9×8251455=？",
        "answer": 7.8707730449899485
    },
    {
        "question": "13783796÷1438476=？",
        "answer": 0.9814662165580622
    },
    {
        "question": "28237458÷22819=？",
        "answer": 3.092528989609628
    },
    {
        "question": "1181×25813=？",
        "answer": 7.484088379016426
    },
    {
        "question": "2×313=？",
        "answer": 2.7965743332104296
    },
    {
        "question": "719317375÷368=？",
        "answer": 6.2910727320700435
    },
    {
        "question": "1×11189=？",
        "answer": 4.048791273848409
    },
    {
        "question": "109837÷39095=？",
        "answer": 0.44862744495255813
    },
    {
        "question": "363560567÷8497497=？",
        "answer": 1.6312857521368134
    },
    {
        "question": "8×648=？",
        "answer": 3.714664992862537
    },
    {
        "question": "97854937÷2622043=？",
        "answer": 1.5719429320801404
    },
    {
        "question": "555×1068921=？",
        "answer": 8.773238592417634
    },
    {
        "question": "16×2892223=？",
        "answer": 7.665351758116499
    },
    {
        "question": "5058÷2633=？",
        "answer": 0.28352796590231777
    },
    {
        "question": "17661956÷17622=？",
        "answer": 3.000983601597076
    },
    {
        "question": "393×2347402=？",
        "answer": 8.964980020643656
    },
    {
        "question": "1×4119=？",
        "answer": 3.6147917919564176
    },
    {
        "question": "2682514÷972811=？",
        "answer": 0.4405135245059154
    },
    {
        "question": "369843025÷665546=？",
        "answer": 2.7448393549768926
    },
    {
        "question": "24508×1173=？",
        "answer": 7.458605883775445
    },
    {
        "question": "834110460÷4152469=？",
        "answer": 2.3029171684775926
    },
    {
        "question": "456580÷282=？",
        "answer": 3.209267775444857
    },
    {
        "question": "291×675156=？",
        "answer": 8.293297120500638
    },
    {
        "question": "2×12787475=？",
        "answer": 7.407814793322797
    },
    {
        "question": "10455125÷20890=？",
        "answer": 2.6993907895679983
    },
    {
        "question": "55×60637=？",
        "answer": 6.523100396041805
    },
    {
        "question": "301315416÷18959705=？",
        "answer": 1.2011897760307004
    },
    {
        "question": "1×658=？",
        "answer": 2.8182258936139557
    },
    {
        "question": "1472×420=？",
        "answer": 5.7911571003993805
    },
    {
        "question": "11311501÷460=？",
        "answer": 4.390762406556392
    },
    {
        "question": "124893÷312=？",
        "answer": 2.6023835037106458
    },
    {
        "question": "132322433÷74133087=？",
        "answer": 0.25162139251711596
    },
    {
        "question": "1×449=？",
        "answer": 2.6522463410033232
    },
    {
        "question": "45×1138=？",
        "answer": 4.709354775834396
    },
    {
        "question": "2×88460=？",
        "answer": 5.247776930697566
    },
    {
        "question": "34113539÷3617250=？",
        "answer": 0.9745482509230369
    },
    {
        "question": "16239×490=？",
        "answer": 6.900755361839237
    },
    {
        "question": "2957×29771=？",
        "answer": 7.944644747254398
    },
    {
        "question": "76499150÷51250734=？",
        "answer": 0.1739565200049296
    },
    {
        "question": "117764966÷24645094=？",
        "answer": 0.6792856320731028
    },
    {
        "question": "933÷275=？",
        "answer": 0.5305489499162372
    },
    {
        "question": "26×45992=？",
        "answer": 6.077655643608736
    },
    {
        "question": "1704025÷14663=？",
        "answer": 2.0652531275031993
    },
    {
        "question": "215790÷43518=？",
        "answer": 0.6953623871750587
    },
    {
        "question": "2×372=？",
        "answer": 2.8715729355458786
    },
    {
        "question": "10×3782013=？",
        "answer": 7.577723017321967
    },
    {
        "question": "766610626÷46684789=？",
        "answer": 1.215399434443514
    },
    {
        "question": "13871÷765=？",
        "answer": 1.258446336577689
    },
    {
        "question": "13×25040=？",
        "answer": 5.512577676845229
    },
    {
        "question": "3189÷714=？",
        "answer": 0.6499563074667848
    },
    {
        "question": "822212023÷834069=？",
        "answer": 2.9937818430800403
    },
    {
        "question": "2745×119769=？",
        "answer": 8.51688677225568
    },
    {
        "question": "5×21796=？",
        "answer": 5.03734680356809
    },
    {
        "question": "253×12446=？",
        "answer": 6.49815031782427
    },
    {
        "question": "5151463÷1036002=？",
        "answer": 0.6965699910704302
    },
    {
        "question": "22×6694863=？",
        "answer": 8.168164375097376
    },
    {
        "question": "13038024÷2708=？",
        "answer": 3.682563116127936
    },
    {
        "question": "4×79494616=？",
        "answer": 8.502397707145805
    },
    {
        "question": "1×310316928=？",
        "answer": 8.491805467290465
    },
    {
        "question": "7×854=？",
        "answer": 3.776555910703262
    },
    {
        "question": "345829317÷1881=？",
        "answer": 5.264473011408452
    },
    {
        "question": "7245096÷1639=？",
        "answer": 3.6454651908252442
    },
    {
        "question": "20099×10575=？",
        "answer": 8.327454826239428
    },
    {
        "question": "64008÷1860=？",
        "answer": 1.5367213131835658
    },
    {
        "question": "5×87726=？",
        "answer": 5.642098331830549
    },
    {
        "question": "4×88018=？",
        "answer": 5.546631487356388
    },
    {
        "question": "433×2090=？",
        "answer": 5.95663418246442
    },
    {
        "question": "5×5215483=？",
        "answer": 7.416264538483313
    },
    {
        "question": "9×5730=？",
        "answer": 4.712397131406715
    },
    {
        "question": "1556435÷1139151=？",
        "answer": 0.13554969260739003
    },
    {
        "question": "217976530÷293=？",
        "answer": 5.871542114350423
    },
    {
        "question": "175359370÷11066=？",
        "answer": 4.199938310672862
    },
    {
        "question": "4×442216=？",
        "answer": 6.2476944432432076
    },
    {
        "question": "21804405÷4052545=？",
        "answer": 0.7308163941043456
    },
    {
        "question": "717105624÷11696=？",
        "answer": 4.787545768915806
    },
    {
        "question": "19326×982=？",
        "answer": 7.278253462990285
    },
    {
        "question": "173245×508=？",
        "answer": 7.944524421635617
    },
    {
        "question": "23×40780=？",
        "answer": 5.972175057459714
    },
    {
        "question": "157×1219=？",
        "answer": 5.281903358027615
    },
    {
        "question": "5326×21676=？",
        "answer": 8.062380304443275
    },
    {
        "question": "1489263÷3911=？",
        "answer": 2.5806835838569406
    },
    {
        "question": "181053988÷10242=？",
        "answer": 4.247423323781795
    },
    {
        "question": "5×15459451=？",
        "answer": 7.888164071414828
    },
    {
        "question": "8×54077=？",
        "answer": 5.636102577477581
    },
    {
        "question": "189001×1893=？",
        "answer": 8.553614715985363
    },
    {
        "question": "26×20230=？",
        "answer": 5.7209692307416224
    },
    {
        "question": "4519÷333=？",
        "answer": 1.132598107824882
    },
    {
        "question": "39359×9903=？",
        "answer": 8.59081083476459
    },
    {
        "question": "2709×99270=？",
        "answer": 8.429627026912684
    },
    {
        "question": "162179÷160486=？",
        "answer": 0.004557465515482892
    },
    {
        "question": "15×248=？",
        "answer": 3.5705429398818973
    },
    {
        "question": "4931313÷943320=？",
        "answer": 0.7183035265956996
    },
    {
        "question": "100261÷29250=？",
        "answer": 0.5350061615196783
    },
    {
        "question": "481053969÷5385120=？",
        "answer": 1.9509984168058787
    },
    {
        "question": "40×547620=？",
        "answer": 7.340539292241749
    },
    {
        "question": "4×192877969=？",
        "answer": 8.887342615611832
    },
    {
        "question": "46408×2577=？",
        "answer": 8.077707271010445
    },
    {
        "question": "11701÷665=？",
        "answer": 1.2454013340433447
    },
    {
        "question": "345×24138=？",
        "answer": 6.920520378028179
    },
    {
        "question": "259296906÷104372=？",
        "answer": 3.3952133290857955
    },
    {
        "question": "533307÷213=？",
        "answer": 3.398597680678082
    },
    {
        "question": "280315÷44990=？",
        "answer": 0.7945303448477632
    },
    {
        "question": "511×1648=？",
        "answer": 5.92537810749581
    },
    {
        "question": "2422401÷12758=？",
        "answer": 2.278463439288229
    },
    {
        "question": "8×1339023=？",
        "answer": 7.029878023815227
    },
    {
        "question": "5221798÷4462970=？",
        "answer": 0.0681961000359024
    },
    {
        "question": "152023619÷435855=？",
        "answer": 2.5425690344732605
    },
    {
        "question": "27175832÷5722348=？",
        "answer": 0.6766085835350056
    },
    {
        "question": "270303664÷84271924=？",
        "answer": 0.506169023306314
    },
    {
        "question": "7×3592641=？",
        "answer": 7.400511861864439
    },
    {
        "question": "26214360÷34792=？",
        "answer": 2.8770598646130874
    },
    {
        "question": "1×180501029=？",
        "answer": 8.256479682074076
    },
    {
        "question": "106744÷3052=？",
        "answer": 1.5437589437338988
    },
    {
        "question": "2254×11984=？",
        "answer": 7.431555712065479
    },
    {
        "question": "690968787÷869=？",
        "answer": 5.9004386530675985
    },
    {
        "question": "677×446745=？",
        "answer": 8.48064836923706
    },
    {
        "question": "1616090×327=？",
        "answer": 8.72301329561803
    },
    {
        "question": "27506032÷47815=？",
        "answer": 2.7598637837926097
    },
    {
        "question": "519594÷91210=？",
        "answer": 0.7556216716973658
    },
    {
        "question": "973×1740=？",
        "answer": 6.228662088550951
    },
    {
        "question": "155976138÷4161604=？",
        "answer": 1.573797410639307
    },
    {
        "question": "22×4344=？",
        "answer": 4.980312497402997
    },
    {
        "question": "17998811÷4792=？",
        "answer": 3.574727007211246
    },
    {
        "question": "33853453÷2271=？",
        "answer": 4.173385838428135
    },
    {
        "question": "659060×1003=？",
        "answer": 8.82022588704197
    },
    {
        "question": "66×12091439=？",
        "answer": 8.90202192478729
    },
    {
        "question": "123117895÷33638=？",
        "answer": 3.5634910153314276
    },
    {
        "question": "496324÷3417=？",
        "answer": 2.162120297437358
    },
    {
        "question": "101030265÷3245405=？",
        "answer": 1.493182591217319
    },
    {
        "question": "222660÷41073=？",
        "answer": 0.7340857795543817
    },
    {
        "question": "118966069÷16962266=？",
        "answer": 0.8459392419399824
    },
    {
        "question": "72280989÷18646457=？",
        "answer": 0.5884277622575018
    },
    {
        "question": "1×896=？",
        "answer": 2.9523080096621253
    },
    {
        "question": "795392164÷15119=？",
        "answer": 4.721058241077684
    },
    {
        "question": "349458÷256=？",
        "answer": 3.135155021738905
    },
    {
        "question": "2×14006250=？",
        "answer": 7.447351869543118
    },
    {
        "question": "2×4102=？",
        "answer": 3.9140256516963285
    },
    {
        "question": "115917439÷69409203=？",
        "answer": 0.22273171997679414
    },
    {
        "question": "112746496÷727641=？",
        "answer": 2.1901858914669345
    },
    {
        "question": "2442×9795=？",
        "answer": 7.3787500999396185
    },
    {
        "question": "44078382÷7603=？",
        "answer": 3.7632406538558754
    },
    {
        "question": "24×1114725=？",
        "answer": 7.427378982895802
    },
    {
        "question": "6×955=？",
        "answer": 3.75815462196739
    },
    {
        "question": "82564×8630=？",
        "answer": 8.852801520887956
    },
    {
        "question": "6465÷2322=？",
        "answer": 0.44470631381385783
    },
    {
        "question": "6905244÷2248376=？",
        "answer": 0.4873100883576311
    },
    {
        "question": "663306÷11196=？",
        "answer": 1.7726510359756913
    },
    {
        "question": "1233÷238=？",
        "answer": 0.7143861195392197
    },
    {
        "question": "8944586÷696061=？",
        "answer": 1.1089129429479312
    },
    {
        "question": "36×7360=？",
        "answer": 5.423180315104786
    },
    {
        "question": "456×1129=？",
        "answer": 5.711658784589403
    },
    {
        "question": "60794612÷430=？",
        "answer": 5.150396635496484
    },
    {
        "question": "6311×29126=？",
        "answer": 8.264379025351387
    },
    {
        "question": "307479354÷41281=？",
        "answer": 3.872065750774045
    },
    {
        "question": "4×88639=？",
        "answer": 5.54968483915307
    },
    {
        "question": "610311353÷553553633=？",
        "answer": 0.04239174336029689
    },
    {
        "question": "8674438÷145957=？",
        "answer": 1.7740164189817804
    },
    {
        "question": "1766×3565=？",
        "answer": 6.799050233429434
    },
    {
        "question": "30×3076=？",
        "answer": 4.965107585849056
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1958=？",
        "answer": 3.291812687467119
    },
    {
        "question": "21306×1045=？",
        "answer": 7.347618213132332
    },
    {
        "question": "747552623÷1380=？",
        "answer": 5.733762683269636
    },
    {
        "question": "305222541÷6378488=？",
        "answer": 1.6798988607480831
    },
    {
        "question": "184404×1065=？",
        "answer": 8.293119945094789
    },
    {
        "question": "161×3334=？",
        "answer": 5.7297914715238365
    },
    {
        "question": "205406932÷135420819=？",
        "answer": 0.1809296599222705
    },
    {
        "question": "18582192÷2497712=？",
        "answer": 0.8715545827291201
    },
    {
        "question": "4882055÷64802=？",
        "answer": 1.8770142579463809
    },
    {
        "question": "670718784÷2461=？",
        "answer": 5.435428855562129
    },
    {
        "question": "14398÷2860=？",
        "answer": 0.7019361360989795
    },
    {
        "question": "85877744÷24716=？",
        "answer": 3.540902440497634
    },
    {
        "question": "12×222732=？",
        "answer": 6.426963862834913
    },
    {
        "question": "124212940÷85885485=？",
        "answer": 0.16024706875382022
    },
    {
        "question": "309552022÷5094=？",
        "answer": 4.783674704550836
    },
    {
        "question": "48803885÷4540=？",
        "answer": 4.031398542237919
    },
    {
        "question": "364879÷39866=？",
        "answer": 0.9615462065695678
    },
    {
        "question": "356×204744=？",
        "answer": 7.862661181640633
    },
    {
        "question": "38638×25471=？",
        "answer": 8.99306063399653
    },
    {
        "question": "219927009÷186115=？",
        "answer": 3.072497191226619
    },
    {
        "question": "136965÷100452=？",
        "answer": 0.13465101385996647
    },
    {
        "question": "1535774÷1145155=？",
        "answer": 0.1274630372414664
    },
    {
        "question": "1122239÷15738=？",
        "answer": 1.8531358162382865
    },
    {
        "question": "59464199÷2348715=？",
        "answer": 1.4034252517838395
    },
    {
        "question": "94×23223=？",
        "answer": 6.3390461757760415
    },
    {
        "question": "714547÷107989=？",
        "answer": 0.8206512806570081
    },
    {
        "question": "22×39124818=？",
        "answer": 8.934875011139534
    },
    {
        "question": "9529×8717=？",
        "answer": 7.91941437293363
    },
    {
        "question": "5379380÷12336=？",
        "answer": 2.6395578632689682
    },
    {
        "question": "1355×17963=？",
        "answer": 7.386318165105318
    },
    {
        "question": "21×6631=？",
        "answer": 5.143798322645928
    },
    {
        "question": "120040÷8145=？",
        "answer": 1.1684348981082868
    },
    {
        "question": "283×6435=？",
        "answer": 6.260334986764696
    },
    {
        "question": "140×263576=？",
        "answer": 7.567033898572558
    },
    {
        "question": "66548714÷8731=？",
        "answer": 3.8820756792827527
    },
    {
        "question": "425×209515=？",
        "answer": 7.949604051309794
    },
    {
        "question": "10×12710=？",
        "answer": 5.1041455505540085
    },
    {
        "question": "13×12882=？",
        "answer": 5.223926647126729
    },
    {
        "question": "5×32356442=？",
        "answer": 8.208930763731082
    },
    {
        "question": "32×2398683=？",
        "answer": 7.885122835521834
    },
    {
        "question": "64×10950389=？",
        "answer": 8.845609521247031
    },
    {
        "question": "482919173÷3263756=？",
        "answer": 2.1701567650038913
    },
    {
        "question": "6508685÷1287301=？",
        "answer": 0.7038131469349732
    },
    {
        "question": "2294812÷552114=？",
        "answer": 0.6187183525026215
    },
    {
        "question": "70×314=？",
        "answer": 4.342027688087472
    },
    {
        "question": "1319÷334=？",
        "answer": 0.5964983287348008
    },
    {
        "question": "3×98592629=？",
        "answer": 8.470965702071757
    },
    {
        "question": "18×172453=？",
        "answer": 6.491943258878407
    },
    {
        "question": "1782082÷144375=？",
        "answer": 1.091435686374952
    },
    {
        "question": "8×104727=？",
        "answer": 5.923148649944226
    },
    {
        "question": "172×3154=？",
        "answer": 5.734390135900433
    },
    {
        "question": "1429138÷10976=？",
        "answer": 2.1146300686681894
    },
    {
        "question": "151640×2326=？",
        "answer": 8.547423486146826
    },
    {
        "question": "6×2668422=？",
        "answer": 7.204405762951513
    },
    {
        "question": "22×663=？",
        "answer": 4.163936209226979
    },
    {
        "question": "77667÷20608=？",
        "answer": 0.5762006845474537
    },
    {
        "question": "4026÷2160=？",
        "answer": 0.2704200194017048
    },
    {
        "question": "16×36925352=？",
        "answer": 8.771444626678612
    },
    {
        "question": "156903×630=？",
        "answer": 7.99497179687092
    },
    {
        "question": "7907390÷4879071=？",
        "answer": 0.20969602115281158
    },
    {
        "question": "285703670÷1651574=？",
        "answer": 2.238017781788198
    },
    {
        "question": "71×235=？",
        "answer": 4.222326210990811
    },
    {
        "question": "3570×2052=？",
        "answer": 6.864845572551972
    },
    {
        "question": "5778×104193=？",
        "answer": 8.779616080238561
    },
    {
        "question": "776949×276=？",
        "answer": 8.331301594115157
    },
    {
        "question": "547652167÷11939=？",
        "answer": 4.661536858266872
    },
    {
        "question": "13095×49895=？",
        "answer": 8.815162529723159
    },
    {
        "question": "846482696÷226476=？",
        "answer": 3.5725958986326174
    },
    {
        "question": "10434762÷47821=？",
        "answer": 2.3388638944180897
    },
    {
        "question": "13598108÷2867=？",
        "answer": 3.676050793194283
    },
    {
        "question": "4409840÷37038=？",
        "answer": 2.0757753051153456
    },
    {
        "question": "29856×217=？",
        "answer": 6.811491355914935
    },
    {
        "question": "3312449÷15425=？",
        "answer": 2.3319240276919366
    },
    {
        "question": "16×8482420=？",
        "answer": 8.132639755043533
    },
    {
        "question": "15×11172096=？",
        "answer": 8.22422591792238
    },
    {
        "question": "4966306÷5732=？",
        "answer": 2.937727293464489
    },
    {
        "question": "4230×13610=？",
        "answer": 7.760198492578377
    },
    {
        "question": "3459678÷414=？",
        "answer": 3.9220353387901685
    },
    {
        "question": "203744942÷211191=？",
        "answer": 2.9844114295171944
    },
    {
        "question": "3725÷548=？",
        "answer": 0.8323457185999426
    },
    {
        "question": "226765÷54563=？",
        "answer": 0.6186777834751256
    },
    {
        "question": "19×4096=？",
        "answer": 4.891113548920603
    },
    {
        "question": "43743×1440=？",
        "answer": 7.799271056776915
    },
    {
        "question": "10337×17606=？",
        "answer": 8.260055213793795
    },
    {
        "question": "7915771÷45758=？",
        "answer": 2.238026187787343
    },
    {
        "question": "1120669÷24680=？",
        "answer": 1.6571322032635758
    },
    {
        "question": "92339×320=？",
        "answer": 7.470535145298798
    },
    {
        "question": "6×1722483=？",
        "answer": 7.014306194726659
    },
    {
        "question": "1×10628875=？",
        "answer": 7.026487299598756
    },
    {
        "question": "431479844÷680590=？",
        "answer": 2.802074949383349
    },
    {
        "question": "63263254÷1335796=？",
        "answer": 1.6754113878160346
    },
    {
        "question": "370×8212=？",
        "answer": 6.482650664765549
    },
    {
        "question": "31789464÷655579=？",
        "answer": 1.6856581718931312
    },
    {
        "question": "11463047÷1450=？",
        "answer": 3.897932070841229
    },
    {
        "question": "38×19397686=？",
        "answer": 8.867533521527927
    },
    {
        "question": "1×430325=？",
        "answer": 5.633796577425011
    },
    {
        "question": "87×547009=？",
        "answer": 7.677513724506313
    },
    {
        "question": "327×292229=？",
        "answer": 7.980271064583789
    },
    {
        "question": "439952163÷57678=？",
        "answer": 3.882395264530093
    },
    {
        "question": "353×1125=？",
        "answer": 5.598927227835204
    },
    {
        "question": "17×12957=？",
        "answer": 5.342953380145435
    },
    {
        "question": "168×7331=？",
        "answer": 6.090472501231949
    },
    {
        "question": "37×1099=？",
        "answer": 4.609199416490486
    },
    {
        "question": "627419711÷121859=？",
        "answer": 3.7117005484659864
    },
    {
        "question": "219357960÷43623=？",
        "answer": 3.701437869420923
    },
    {
        "question": "2×271722026=？",
        "answer": 8.73515483975925
    },
    {
        "question": "45578÷888=？",
        "answer": 1.710342298286012
    },
    {
        "question": "88056877÷14424629=？",
        "answer": 0.7856586268715896
    },
    {
        "question": "4×69056738=？",
        "answer": 8.44126605126583
    },
    {
        "question": "14×450237=？",
        "answer": 6.799569217670038
    },
    {
        "question": "46044591÷102121=？",
        "answer": 2.6540635607209464
    },
    {
        "question": "11286946÷23462=？",
        "answer": 2.6822114168058415
    },
    {
        "question": "2×63479596=？",
        "answer": 8.10366414979706
    },
    {
        "question": "1×3334723=？",
        "answer": 6.523059764918921
    },
    {
        "question": "1147351÷121818=？",
        "answer": 0.9739848334920456
    },
    {
        "question": "23×23222369=？",
        "answer": 8.727634357671128
    },
    {
        "question": "626783÷103423=？",
        "answer": 0.7825000775133449
    },
    {
        "question": "29265863÷977345=？",
        "answer": 1.4763134397390942
    },
    {
        "question": "10781÷9289=？",
        "answer": 0.06469008316123168
    },
    {
        "question": "41018×1607=？",
        "answer": 7.818990357511946
    },
    {
        "question": "1496570÷2689=？",
        "answer": 2.745506232954077
    },
    {
        "question": "5799÷839=？",
        "answer": 0.8395911479195152
    },
    {
        "question": "1235×77166=？",
        "answer": 7.979092946209623
    },
    {
        "question": "21×25257=？",
        "answer": 5.724601058973017
    },
    {
        "question": "563119974÷373=？",
        "answer": 6.178892100334549
    },
    {
        "question": "2211×5207=？",
        "answer": 7.061176320254407
    },
    {
        "question": "872139948÷403=？",
        "answer": 6.3352811334789205
    },
    {
        "question": "188×678=？",
        "answer": 5.105387543130743
    },
    {
        "question": "32072×498=？",
        "answer": 7.203355386002182
    },
    {
        "question": "1×3461=？",
        "answer": 3.539201599294128
    },
    {
        "question": "15893143÷909=？",
        "answer": 4.2426459077915135
    },
    {
        "question": "3×9848948=？",
        "answer": 7.470511099207687
    },
    {
        "question": "141939÷2329=？",
        "answer": 1.7849322526427318
    },
    {
        "question": "179881298÷136307864=？",
        "answer": 0.12046510044114976
    },
    {
        "question": "1226×349152=？",
        "answer": 8.631505004276677
    },
    {
        "question": "3855÷286=？",
        "answer": 1.1296583492579328
    },
    {
        "question": "36916÷1808=？",
        "answer": 1.3100162111755431
    },
    {
        "question": "43876516÷5050=？",
        "answer": 3.9389407571457657
    },
    {
        "question": "362×22350=？",
        "answer": 6.907986098001121
    },
    {
        "question": "72234×7143=？",
        "answer": 8.712622314961687
    },
    {
        "question": "5054008÷446=？",
        "answer": 4.054301066317956
    },
    {
        "question": "71582493÷13857889=？",
        "answer": 0.7131097411046455
    },
    {
        "question": "199037263÷75736=？",
        "answer": 3.4196320268748277
    },
    {
        "question": "267499382÷94380=？",
        "answer": 3.4524428100071396
    },
    {
        "question": "21142163÷6742987=？",
        "answer": 0.4962970944007555
    },
    {
        "question": "1×12270783=？",
        "answer": 7.0888722759894085
    },
    {
        "question": "27043018÷429=？",
        "answer": 4.799597865040739
    },
    {
        "question": "57806604÷789=？",
        "answer": 4.864900453150956
    },
    {
        "question": "16736÷1763=？",
        "answer": 0.9773993548878582
    },
    {
        "question": "445587723÷4766211=？",
        "answer": 1.9707599518480579
    },
    {
        "question": "173569÷3741=？",
        "answer": 1.6664844531310514
    },
    {
        "question": "6857÷353=？",
        "answer": 1.2883594440775523
    },
    {
        "question": "231927993÷37944=？",
        "answer": 3.7862100581745675
    },
    {
        "question": "3036÷647=？",
        "answer": 0.6713974865547424
    },
    {
        "question": "651×273762=？",
        "answer": 8.250954153565447
    },
    {
        "question": "1658562÷1080137=？",
        "answer": 0.1862528678074575
    },
    {
        "question": "3905161÷3425=？",
        "answer": 3.0569783676269298
    },
    {
        "question": "6×73028=？",
        "answer": 5.6416406572710525
    },
    {
        "question": "1098744÷592819=？",
        "answer": 0.2679744020582531
    },
    {
        "question": "6×1365607=？",
        "answer": 6.913476984657267
    },
    {
        "question": "16492265÷4358=？",
        "answer": 3.577993078579081
    },
    {
        "question": "890÷317=？",
        "answer": 0.44833074442716125
    },
    {
        "question": "197009249÷7277288=？",
        "answer": 1.432517052933316
    },
    {
        "question": "3794878÷139483=？",
        "answer": 1.4346765388890692
    },
    {
        "question": "247×39039=？",
        "answer": 6.984195637765484
    },
    {
        "question": "479×2341=？",
        "answer": 6.049736927111187
    },
    {
        "question": "7616×323=？",
        "answer": 6.390929457707521
    },
    {
        "question": "118540906÷30354633=？",
        "answer": 0.5916432557568031
    },
    {
        "question": "291×179953=？",
        "answer": 7.719052080167032
    },
    {
        "question": "4×377379=？",
        "answer": 6.178837720654833
    },
    {
        "question": "1×4044=？",
        "answer": 3.6068111469189637
    },
    {
        "question": "61343902÷199801=？",
        "answer": 2.4871737398604443
    },
    {
        "question": "86641×2587=？",
        "answer": 8.350519884937404
    },
    {
        "question": "98918321÷6469=？",
        "answer": 4.184439585070572
    },
    {
        "question": "2476×832=？",
        "answer": 6.313873966638805
    },
    {
        "question": "453085861÷15067893=？",
        "answer": 1.4781279822608124
    },
    {
        "question": "949974÷181135=？",
        "answer": 0.7197093437434586
    },
    {
        "question": "409325×891=？",
        "answer": 8.561945974532323
    },
    {
        "question": "12284515÷330=？",
        "answer": 4.570844075070762
    },
    {
        "question": "1745922÷17913=？",
        "answer": 1.9888565115630294
    },
    {
        "question": "798×1176=？",
        "answer": 5.972410213090849
    },
    {
        "question": "6×323=？",
        "answer": 3.2873537727147464
    },
    {
        "question": "6921660÷3867=？",
        "answer": 3.2528360903582585
    },
    {
        "question": "32066÷200=？",
        "answer": 2.205014792569004
    },
    {
        "question": "70072950÷6324908=？",
        "answer": 1.0444961884436137
    },
    {
        "question": "3238×18809=？",
        "answer": 7.78464255086478
    },
    {
        "question": "35510÷1839=？",
        "answer": 1.285768943063538
    },
    {
        "question": "110×3117889=？",
        "answer": 8.535253334963715
    },
    {
        "question": "5374×10998=？",
        "answer": 7.77161137744301
    },
    {
        "question": "1×680011=？",
        "answer": 5.832515938001327
    },
    {
        "question": "442×225634=？",
        "answer": 7.998826811911325
    },
    {
        "question": "5559978÷1061246=？",
        "answer": 0.7192570068151054
    },
    {
        "question": "118183×689=？",
        "answer": 7.910774231979342
    },
    {
        "question": "93145÷1094=？",
        "answer": 1.9301422250427882
    },
    {
        "question": "249×21515=？",
        "answer": 6.728940697514311
    },
    {
        "question": "635474845÷5655=？",
        "answer": 5.050665754607445
    },
    {
        "question": "35349369÷15857=？",
        "answer": 3.348160639684637
    },
    {
        "question": "3×34052776=？",
        "answer": 8.009273776323527
    },
    {
        "question": "59×7582841=？",
        "answer": 8.65068396126624
    },
    {
        "question": "93×449=？",
        "answer": 4.620729289557258
    },
    {
        "question": "19649812÷435=？",
        "answer": 4.654869142654865
    },
    {
        "question": "2632×5230=？",
        "answer": 7.138787573809192
    },
    {
        "question": "15×7267463=？",
        "answer": 8.037474088430141
    },
    {
        "question": "118×1701=？",
        "answer": 5.302586320918694
    },
    {
        "question": "208×2784=？",
        "answer": 5.7627325659012865
    },
    {
        "question": "430971316÷1311=？",
        "answer": 5.516845674253784
    },
    {
        "question": "24815739÷435=？",
        "answer": 4.75623795583856
    },
    {
        "question": "755×268=？",
        "answer": 5.306081745657977
    },
    {
        "question": "57204×14011=？",
        "answer": 8.903895531046537
    },
    {
        "question": "6512÷3653=？",
        "answer": 0.25106471966922816
    },
    {
        "question": "1767143÷1256956=？",
        "answer": 0.14795161933803613
    },
    {
        "question": "3×33456=？",
        "answer": 5.001595270193259
    },
    {
        "question": "2×267551638=？",
        "answer": 8.728437609812541
    },
    {
        "question": "89487660÷933586=？",
        "answer": 1.981608821494031
    },
    {
        "question": "5266562÷62492=？",
        "answer": 1.9257027771409956
    },
    {
        "question": "248892÷1000=？",
        "answer": 2.396010937541933
    },
    {
        "question": "14618÷529=？",
        "answer": 1.4414322855127684
    },
    {
        "question": "10×39920=？",
        "answer": 5.601190532615333
    },
    {
        "question": "2×552584=？",
        "answer": 6.043428301484595
    },
    {
        "question": "132487÷58797=？",
        "answer": 0.3528180985286098
    },
    {
        "question": "2×743210=？",
        "answer": 6.17214154018509
    },
    {
        "question": "10437103÷517896=？",
        "answer": 1.304337412651735
    },
    {
        "question": "20520122÷106831=？",
        "answer": 2.2834826448341237
    },
    {
        "question": "10×319=？",
        "answer": 3.503790683057181
    },
    {
        "question": "189501448÷85985=？",
        "answer": 3.3431898372062108
    },
    {
        "question": "33204811÷869=？",
        "answer": 4.582181236152377
    },
    {
        "question": "716776÷1457=？",
        "answer": 2.6919239035307543
    },
    {
        "question": "91427×772=？",
        "answer": 7.848691769804811
    },
    {
        "question": "66279453÷21955937=？",
        "answer": 0.4798269396040624
    },
    {
        "question": "28×3653=？",
        "answer": 5.009807703554136
    },
    {
        "question": "25×24339408=？",
        "answer": 8.784250019482272
    },
    {
        "question": "1474129÷148545=？",
        "answer": 0.9966774518873801
    },
    {
        "question": "13178÷393=？",
        "answer": 1.5254569528360908
    },
    {
        "question": "735÷434=？",
        "answer": 0.2287976095716842
    },
    {
        "question": "4028618÷457=？",
        "answer": 3.9452398887736497
    },
    {
        "question": "6×2217=？",
        "answer": 4.1239169434981315
    },
    {
        "question": "1822508÷1079=？",
        "answer": 3.2276479986710136
    },
    {
        "question": "2×91251=？",
        "answer": 5.261267628157998
    },
    {
        "question": "1×35011=？",
        "answer": 4.544204515457395
    },
    {
        "question": "937640÷30778=？",
        "answer": 1.4837957308863556
    },
    {
        "question": "23×102464=？",
        "answer": 6.37229914192078
    },
    {
        "question": "2×669=？",
        "answer": 3.1264561134318045
    },
    {
        "question": "212456÷9434=？",
        "answer": 1.3525731286610427
    },
    {
        "question": "1×743442789=？",
        "answer": 8.871247553385752
    },
    {
        "question": "6941÷1543=？",
        "answer": 0.6530561183392111
    },
    {
        "question": "538403593÷312871690=？",
        "answer": 0.23574168140220825
    },
    {
        "question": "68525382÷528514=？",
        "answer": 2.1127949692455403
    },
    {
        "question": "5340÷1971=？",
        "answer": 0.43285463274911323
    },
    {
        "question": "10159×1970=？",
        "answer": 7.301317186485865
    },
    {
        "question": "4×25486=？",
        "answer": 5.008361670098737
    },
    {
        "question": "6055531÷1037=？",
        "answer": 3.76637347536066
    },
    {
        "question": "36360719÷252=？",
        "answer": 5.159231921629914
    },
    {
        "question": "1440×565679=？",
        "answer": 8.910932548591704
    },
    {
        "question": "23×4693=？",
        "answer": 5.033178390230088
    },
    {
        "question": "72×20267=？",
        "answer": 6.164121963926947
    },
    {
        "question": "109792693÷55612372=？",
        "answer": 0.29540201844105335
    },
    {
        "question": "92164×5280=？",
        "answer": 8.687195237790787
    },
    {
        "question": "62484×876=？",
        "answer": 7.738272929891398
    },
    {
        "question": "467573296÷8208597=？",
        "answer": 1.7555807652560806
    },
    {
        "question": "124667÷100189=？",
        "answer": 0.0949314668193568
    },
    {
        "question": "8034×13889=？",
        "answer": 8.047602805306342
    },
    {
        "question": "354583426÷9942127=？",
        "answer": 1.5522391253870893
    },
    {
        "question": "7651502÷2861=？",
        "answer": 3.427228838300373
    },
    {
        "question": "328749÷327415=？",
        "answer": 0.0017658684019542206
    },
    {
        "question": "484145648÷300141=？",
        "answer": 3.2076507071471227
    },
    {
        "question": "444002÷2743=？",
        "answer": 2.2091591187871344
    },
    {
        "question": "20×42589=？",
        "answer": 5.930327438518183
    },
    {
        "question": "26779÷7888=？",
        "answer": 0.5308274533197336
    },
    {
        "question": "58×6248539=？",
        "answer": 8.559206478361336
    },
    {
        "question": "23758890÷149717=？",
        "answer": 2.2005550306037533
    },
    {
        "question": "206638÷84410=？",
        "answer": 0.38881628948303876
    },
    {
        "question": "443566÷344548=？",
        "answer": 0.10970851612263965
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1865=？",
        "answer": 3.2706788361447066
    },
    {
        "question": "6185÷1156=？",
        "answer": 0.7283818698806293
    },
    {
        "question": "72×4588=？",
        "answer": 5.518955905660499
    },
    {
        "question": "767÷612=？",
        "answer": 0.09804394180341976
    },
    {
        "question": "2×14064=？",
        "answer": 4.449138853393678
    },
    {
        "question": "244704÷267=？",
        "answer": 2.9621298071442608
    },
    {
        "question": "280037624÷1544=？",
        "answer": 5.258569088192066
    },
    {
        "question": "4425÷1999=？",
        "answer": 0.34510048091572726
    },
    {
        "question": "2191×249=？",
        "answer": 5.736841724656442
    },
    {
        "question": "284×30294=？",
        "answer": 6.934674961126167
    },
    {
        "question": "24666240÷2164381=？",
        "answer": 1.056769239998673
    },
    {
        "question": "23823914÷2561935=？",
        "answer": 0.9684450058180877
    },
    {
        "question": "22846÷1602=？",
        "answer": 1.154147660710344
    },
    {
        "question": "50486821÷25735115=？",
        "answer": 0.29265191208728164
    },
    {
        "question": "827×870075=？",
        "answer": 8.857062199736975
    },
    {
        "question": "5×1255=？",
        "answer": 3.797613730153076
    },
    {
        "question": "44206392÷1327=？",
        "answer": 4.522614147607299
    },
    {
        "question": "3147122÷766158=？",
        "answer": 0.6135952381965838
    },
    {
        "question": "3×77623191=？",
        "answer": 8.367112746836701
    },
    {
        "question": "2140070÷1788749=？",
        "answer": 0.07787857503552269
    },
    {
        "question": "2273÷322=？",
        "answer": 0.8487435640291399
    },
    {
        "question": "1×263498486=？",
        "answer": 8.420778124202323
    },
    {
        "question": "1×35925479=？",
        "answer": 7.555402567360752
    },
    {
        "question": "26×553580=？",
        "answer": 7.15815373930655
    },
    {
        "question": "2×163442=？",
        "answer": 5.514393663676829
    },
    {
        "question": "9×7901=？",
        "answer": 4.851924571235744
    },
    {
        "question": "2×3195=？",
        "answer": 3.8055008581584002
    },
    {
        "question": "105×665310=？",
        "answer": 7.844213350266146
    },
    {
        "question": "114673534÷55111243=？",
        "answer": 0.31822299038820134
    },
    {
        "question": "4×11279=？",
        "answer": 4.654330587984711
    },
    {
        "question": "380×897=？",
        "answer": 5.532576039660902
    },
    {
        "question": "51×936610=？",
        "answer": 7.679128966445166
    },
    {
        "question": "36431×1040=？",
        "answer": 7.5785044317188826
    },
    {
        "question": "87×10193522=？",
        "answer": 8.9478435171833
    },
    {
        "question": "17×18973575=？",
        "answer": 8.50859808972044
    },
    {
        "question": "99219×412=？",
        "answer": 7.611492061625153
    },
    {
        "question": "954×859=？",
        "answer": 5.913541538535338
    },
    {
        "question": "240219473÷17835=？",
        "answer": 4.1293350961937625
    },
    {
        "question": "14408376÷116192=？",
        "answer": 2.093438806045816
    },
    {
        "question": "67540÷337=？",
        "answer": 2.301931155428054
    },
    {
        "question": "5184×258=？",
        "answer": 6.126284698825767
    },
    {
        "question": "53×155962=？",
        "answer": 6.917294665387028
    },
    {
        "question": "19503967÷602500=？",
        "answer": 1.5101659022176168
    },
    {
        "question": "6579×11553=？",
        "answer": 7.880854659739579
    },
    {
        "question": "241942010÷154759=？",
        "answer": 3.1940553695532072
    },
    {
        "question": "402113÷8129=？",
        "answer": 1.6943109901790598
    },
    {
        "question": "207179793÷193453421=？",
        "answer": 0.029770980694945354
    },
    {
        "question": "5016×439=？",
        "answer": 6.3428220480647814
    },
    {
        "question": "220501÷250=？",
        "answer": 2.9454705547168407
    },
    {
        "question": "456462592÷1168046=？",
        "answer": 2.5919452455454195
    },
    {
        "question": "1809×206591=？",
        "answer": 8.572549964704235
    },
    {
        "question": "89072÷52712=？",
        "answer": 0.2278317094233832
    },
    {
        "question": "20514541÷4481930=？",
        "answer": 0.6605967350219016
    },
    {
        "question": "189×3156020=？",
        "answer": 8.775601550884934
    },
    {
        "question": "1132×3524=？",
        "answer": 6.600882326592263
    },
    {
        "question": "6×11970=？",
        "answer": 4.856245400790054
    },
    {
        "question": "32566÷1428=？",
        "answer": 1.3580362110998527
    },
    {
        "question": "6030087÷440=？",
        "answer": 4.136870901549049
    },
    {
        "question": "323908÷108073=？",
        "answer": 0.4767044672868346
    },
    {
        "question": "123×77085=？",
        "answer": 6.976874988180252
    },
    {
        "question": "9×878=？",
        "answer": 3.8977370253454273
    },
    {
        "question": "523370×740=？",
        "answer": 8.588040544630442
    },
    {
        "question": "4302015÷8352=？",
        "answer": 2.711881434667053
    },
    {
        "question": "467535÷396=？",
        "answer": 3.0721189420913655
    },
    {
        "question": "19×4321483=？",
        "answer": 7.914386409849558
    },
    {
        "question": "29786018÷23661=？",
        "answer": 3.0999793520729075
    },
    {
        "question": "18×59215=？",
        "answer": 6.02770423871916
    },
    {
        "question": "3826977÷347967=？",
        "answer": 1.041317793241071
    },
    {
        "question": "1623×16893=？",
        "answer": 7.438025301886903
    },
    {
        "question": "862236590÷196800=？",
        "answer": 3.641601354598741
    },
    {
        "question": "93×6548236=？",
        "answer": 8.784607271653455
    },
    {
        "question": "538890×1637=？",
        "answer": 8.945548804026497
    },
    {
        "question": "10645025÷866=？",
        "answer": 4.089628793705262
    },
    {
        "question": "81048251÷122267=？",
        "answer": 2.8214343910389834
    },
    {
        "question": "6658971÷247=？",
        "answer": 4.430710170272705
    },
    {
        "question": "2356×383500=？",
        "answer": 8.955940654400063
    },
    {
        "question": "6×1421=？",
        "answer": 3.9307453283111133
    },
    {
        "question": "258089446÷17467861=？",
        "answer": 1.1695305180125104
    },
    {
        "question": "5×226=？",
        "answer": 3.0530784434834195
    },
    {
        "question": "21×1571=？",
        "answer": 4.5183954797738926
    },
    {
        "question": "3804×71708=？",
        "answer": 8.435808118076025
    },
    {
        "question": "98709÷30232=？",
        "answer": 0.5138898732757954
    },
    {
        "question": "3×44677=？",
        "answer": 5.127205257856426
    },
    {
        "question": "105×361=？",
        "answer": 4.578696500975596
    },
    {
        "question": "2887660÷640472=？",
        "answer": 0.6540459089213685
    },
    {
        "question": "22710333÷51056=？",
        "answer": 2.648176715446134
    },
    {
        "question": "95307957÷805=？",
        "answer": 5.073333279839564
    },
    {
        "question": "141813×3830=？",
        "answer": 8.734914818422725
    },
    {
        "question": "4368×4797=？",
        "answer": 7.321252348162578
    },
    {
        "question": "24554×605=？",
        "answer": 7.171877626159169
    },
    {
        "question": "145568÷38371=？",
        "answer": 0.5790627975042499
    },
    {
        "question": "60250÷8372=？",
        "answer": 0.8571278315802571
    },
    {
        "question": "2×1408=？",
        "answer": 3.4496326504700745
    },
    {
        "question": "350241÷26938=？",
        "answer": 1.1140016356327131
    },
    {
        "question": "130×43074=？",
        "answer": 6.74815855602358
    },
    {
        "question": "2287÷540=？",
        "answer": 0.6268724047837799
    },
    {
        "question": "672×268347=？",
        "answer": 8.256066017485047
    },
    {
        "question": "1×357234=？",
        "answer": 5.552952786469811
    },
    {
        "question": "143×6188982=？",
        "answer": 8.946955257060115
    },
    {
        "question": "2740749÷11313=？",
        "answer": 2.3842914771970243
    },
    {
        "question": "94×2297355=？",
        "answer": 8.334355963565518
    },
    {
        "question": "17843×5751=？",
        "answer": 8.011211243081249
    },
    {
        "question": "6647÷814=？",
        "answer": 0.9120012738849396
    },
    {
        "question": "3×29668899=？",
        "answer": 7.949422684855291
    },
    {
        "question": "8774424÷37590=？",
        "answer": 2.368146290953154
    },
    {
        "question": "9260249÷329=？",
        "answer": 4.4494267666879095
    },
    {
        "question": "13699852÷963848=？",
        "answer": 1.1527073249471629
    },
    {
        "question": "1125×1596=？",
        "answer": 6.254185409462092
    },
    {
        "question": "46866÷253=？",
        "answer": 2.267737367013491
    },
    {
        "question": "1229÷260=？",
        "answer": 0.6745785349156361
    },
    {
        "question": "2330800÷3850=？",
        "answer": 2.782044279909612
    },
    {
        "question": "3×220381=？",
        "answer": 5.820295404106085
    },
    {
        "question": "4278032÷548857=？",
        "answer": 0.8917848213301779
    },
    {
        "question": "469829÷51882=？",
        "answer": 0.9569231105562902
    },
    {
        "question": "82771862÷69711222=？",
        "answer": 0.07458002925902518
    },
    {
        "question": "179368658÷6032717=？",
        "answer": 1.473233606186064
    },
    {
        "question": "836×3875=？",
        "answer": 6.510477984281345
    },
    {
        "question": "197×3221026=？",
        "answer": 8.80246045660406
    },
    {
        "question": "2×199432804=？",
        "answer": 8.600826591086127
    },
    {
        "question": "171×7023=？",
        "answer": 6.079518778808441
    },
    {
        "question": "1902×2829=？",
        "answer": 6.730843460058386
    },
    {
        "question": "967073769÷860=？",
        "answer": 6.050961152361342
    },
    {
        "question": "10×4363317=？",
        "answer": 7.639816766126781
    },
    {
        "question": "293×69524=？",
        "answer": 7.309002371250893
    },
    {
        "question": "21×4934=？",
        "answer": 5.015418439887637
    },
    {
        "question": "1130812÷668281=？",
        "answer": 0.22843129470108356
    },
    {
        "question": "2162÷469=？",
        "answer": 0.6636828469022082
    },
    {
        "question": "797955099÷120506=？",
        "answer": 3.8209697832574903
    },
    {
        "question": "58120421÷218979=？",
        "answer": 2.4239262833178237
    },
    {
        "question": "14484328÷272737=？",
        "answer": 1.7251542918048768
    },
    {
        "question": "420×485489=？",
        "answer": 8.30942868469667
    },
    {
        "question": "730251121÷2099932=？",
        "answer": 2.5412670006892135
    },
    {
        "question": "578703407÷10023=？",
        "answer": 4.761458308834757
    },
    {
        "question": "74×19053=？",
        "answer": 6.149195087189713
    },
    {
        "question": "58×1526=？",
        "answer": 4.946982527181799
    },
    {
        "question": "16778846÷13859=？",
        "answer": 3.0830301932472075
    },
    {
        "question": "51558855÷539100=？",
        "answer": 1.9806339323084448
    },
    {
        "question": "4×325=？",
        "answer": 3.113943352306837
    },
    {
        "question": "1×3792=？",
        "answer": 3.5788683286660286
    },
    {
        "question": "9020÷3684=？",
        "answer": 0.38888691601713044
    },
    {
        "question": "27900812÷1802940=？",
        "answer": 1.1896355686848445
    },
    {
        "question": "33356÷28514=？",
        "answer": 0.06811581989746482
    },
    {
        "question": "832×424=？",
        "answer": 5.5474891828834565
    },
    {
        "question": "176895334÷4290=？",
        "answer": 4.615259085412518
    },
    {
        "question": "380203881÷299506=？",
        "answer": 3.1036110186631887
    },
    {
        "question": "17562×9533=？",
        "answer": 8.22380356583959
    },
    {
        "question": "13×13465=？",
        "answer": 5.243149710054366
    },
    {
        "question": "578235053÷125074=？",
        "answer": 3.664937376088811
    },
    {
        "question": "15559917÷3383467=？",
        "answer": 0.6626453310063535
    },
    {
        "question": "2915852÷7069=？",
        "answer": 2.615407495044133
    },
    {
        "question": "24×1003=？",
        "answer": 4.381512174732024
    },
    {
        "question": "44265183÷13247606=？",
        "answer": 0.5239248608246325
    },
    {
        "question": "11×3454131=？",
        "answer": 7.5797314895819845
    },
    {
        "question": "174447×3138=？",
        "answer": 8.738316444450074
    },
    {
        "question": "20773985÷97918=？",
        "answer": 2.3266572793825118
    },
    {
        "question": "544×150901=？",
        "answer": 7.9142910174926095
    },
    {
        "question": "35×2379=？",
        "answer": 4.9204624863875415
    },
    {
        "question": "5770÷312=？",
        "answer": 1.2670212191372887
    },
    {
        "question": "9×56966440=？",
        "answer": 8.709861589407426
    },
    {
        "question": "164714÷359=？",
        "answer": 2.661636065371926
    },
    {
        "question": "10551×2989=？",
        "answer": 7.498819538075885
    },
    {
        "question": "3141×2063=？",
        "answer": 6.811567164371656
    },
    {
        "question": "310850÷196055=？",
        "answer": 0.20017294909386235
    },
    {
        "question": "2209429÷205706=？",
        "answer": 1.0310330907574767
    },
    {
        "question": "35046×7298=？",
        "answer": 8.407842315651967
    },
    {
        "question": "274×9681=？",
        "answer": 6.423670782943955
    },
    {
        "question": "5×1557476=？",
        "answer": 6.8913913674374525
    },
    {
        "question": "2×56802=？",
        "answer": 5.055393623165002
    },
    {
        "question": "27500679÷74153=？",
        "answer": 2.569214690898163
    },
    {
        "question": "10×1438579=？",
        "answer": 7.157933716293777
    },
    {
        "question": "4×959=？",
        "answer": 3.583878598498626
    },
    {
        "question": "36906×4512=？",
        "answer": 8.221466068382677
    },
    {
        "question": "2048540÷136538=？",
        "answer": 1.1761909114059856
    },
    {
        "question": "14×961=？",
        "answer": 4.1288514233467835
    },
    {
        "question": "16×848071=？",
        "answer": 7.132552195310562
    },
    {
        "question": "84795÷14200=？",
        "answer": 0.7760819001327435
    },
    {
        "question": "2501991÷2295551=？",
        "answer": 0.037398797263037346
    },
    {
        "question": "1406868÷705=？",
        "answer": 3.3000642344867823
    },
    {
        "question": "3000062÷188355=？",
        "answer": 1.2021530767382076
    },
    {
        "question": "64318340÷1797=？",
        "answer": 4.553786750016012
    },
    {
        "question": "96113×2344=？",
        "answer": 8.352739740554945
    },
    {
        "question": "13586÷1201=？",
        "answer": 1.0535486028518022
    },
    {
        "question": "15697×274=？",
        "answer": 6.63356722109326
    },
    {
        "question": "7×7605=？",
        "answer": 4.726197258403274
    },
    {
        "question": "4917×2900=？",
        "answer": 7.154098206189118
    },
    {
        "question": "13626073÷7287=？",
        "answer": 3.2718219417637653
    },
    {
        "question": "72×216686=？",
        "answer": 7.193163349056303
    },
    {
        "question": "29007359÷21879=？",
        "answer": 3.122480721604504
    },
    {
        "question": "103×8682=？",
        "answer": 5.951457006207853
    },
    {
        "question": "4×908222=？",
        "answer": 6.560252009001786
    },
    {
        "question": "9942946÷6180=？",
        "answer": 3.206526605685086
    },
    {
        "question": "86376759÷3324=？",
        "answer": 4.414735889452124
    },
    {
        "question": "358419724÷335=？",
        "answer": 6.029347094033211
    },
    {
        "question": "8×37175=？",
        "answer": 5.473340964185935
    },
    {
        "question": "492×231=？",
        "answer": 5.055577082659505
    },
    {
        "question": "861×15065=？",
        "answer": 7.11297228746303
    },
    {
        "question": "1×414718=？",
        "answer": 5.617752885450887
    },
    {
        "question": "2×20854=？",
        "answer": 4.6202193648688725
    },
    {
        "question": "180×238=？",
        "answer": 4.631849462159818
    },
    {
        "question": "9774737÷17067=？",
        "answer": 2.757947892569184
    },
    {
        "question": "237775587÷45492=？",
        "answer": 3.7182322320228405
    },
    {
        "question": "10×17874=？",
        "answer": 5.252221753598687
    },
    {
        "question": "1×446717285=？",
        "answer": 8.65003275711676
    },
    {
        "question": "1137×1334=？",
        "answer": 6.180916294268265
    },
    {
        "question": "8789×2169=？",
        "answer": 7.28019901648641
    },
    {
        "question": "148532÷22711=？",
        "answer": 0.8155837716245442
    },
    {
        "question": "234395040÷17780=？",
        "answer": 4.120016660765521
    },
    {
        "question": "115×2061=？",
        "answer": 5.3747758321328245
    },
    {
        "question": "709311063÷353643276=？",
        "answer": 0.3022713284816206
    },
    {
        "question": "142694×471=？",
        "answer": 7.827426619404901
    },
    {
        "question": "35445017÷3825527=？",
        "answer": 0.9668639174861274
    },
    {
        "question": "20×801=？",
        "answer": 4.204662511748219
    },
    {
        "question": "300×669=？",
        "answer": 5.302547372487486
    },
    {
        "question": "243073÷323=？",
        "answer": 2.876534198740808
    },
    {
        "question": "9997169÷822=？",
        "answer": 4.085005216285439
    },
    {
        "question": "2527÷1380=？",
        "answer": 0.26272615551867823
    },
    {
        "question": "192302996÷458=？",
        "answer": 5.623120572413145
    },
    {
        "question": "77213×1243=？",
        "answer": 7.98216155531102
    },
    {
        "question": "129469255÷35012=？",
        "answer": 3.5679497291692104
    },
    {
        "question": "7×1525=？",
        "answer": 4.028367883697062
    },
    {
        "question": "998962581÷15473020=？",
        "answer": 1.809974133894257
    },
    {
        "question": "3993895÷882942=？",
        "answer": 0.6554644670921427
    },
    {
        "question": "23×294159=？",
        "answer": 6.830309976487251
    },
    {
        "question": "5×15756411=？",
        "answer": 7.896427305027582
    },
    {
        "question": "124826÷389=？",
        "answer": 2.506355452614276
    },
    {
        "question": "236607÷41488=？",
        "answer": 0.7561050896257345
    },
    {
        "question": "97×1686322=？",
        "answer": 8.213712240184245
    },
    {
        "question": "6934424÷1637180=？",
        "answer": 0.6269139621241568
    },
    {
        "question": "16311×2892=？",
        "answer": 7.673678876343867
    },
    {
        "question": "847×32396=？",
        "answer": 7.4383748006246755
    },
    {
        "question": "958628÷13596=？",
        "answer": 1.8482389539814472
    },
    {
        "question": "8744325÷33293=？",
        "answer": 2.4193733598731053
    },
    {
        "question": "136643÷549=？",
        "answer": 2.396015043944188
    },
    {
        "question": "920×148438=？",
        "answer": 8.135332921534728
    },
    {
        "question": "3064078÷4441=？",
        "answer": 2.8388190434456435
    },
    {
        "question": "28591÷247=？",
        "answer": 2.0635323922657545
    },
    {
        "question": "231016968÷161459=？",
        "answer": 3.155581621281384
    },
    {
        "question": "927×139231=？",
        "answer": 8.110815676531356
    },
    {
        "question": "4852844÷3982=？",
        "answer": 3.0858950749752005
    },
    {
        "question": "1×2413565=？",
        "answer": 6.382658999347459
    },
    {
        "question": "126558802÷383570=？",
        "answer": 2.5184477226265756
    },
    {
        "question": "376107÷930=？",
        "answer": 2.606828467913087
    },
    {
        "question": "730×4822=？",
        "answer": 6.546550066161891
    },
    {
        "question": "18×45748=？",
        "answer": 5.915644617539655
    },
    {
        "question": "3755×24812=？",
        "answer": 7.969271713833116
    },
    {
        "question": "6×32905634=？",
        "answer": 8.295421513246415
    },
    {
        "question": "600969329÷251479=？",
        "answer": 3.3783505832458522
    },
    {
        "question": "9284÷637=？",
        "answer": 1.1635956994485297
    },
    {
        "question": "5×38028642=？",
        "answer": 8.279080821400594
    },
    {
        "question": "1×45726=？",
        "answer": 4.6601632120103025
    },
    {
        "question": "59×20563=？",
        "answer": 6.083938487159946
    },
    {
        "question": "861516÷2507=？",
        "answer": 2.5361090135799627
    },
    {
        "question": "80334×379=？",
        "answer": 7.483538601911908
    },
    {
        "question": "138048794÷32808557=？",
        "answer": 0.6240454874969532
    },
    {
        "question": "666÷262=？",
        "answer": 0.40517293785055564
    },
    {
        "question": "5184÷228=？",
        "answer": 1.356730145862083
    },
    {
        "question": "4977×199690=？",
        "answer": 8.997323957725094
    },
    {
        "question": "22×7360=？",
        "answer": 5.209300495159705
    },
    {
        "question": "678829455÷3843=？",
        "answer": 5.247090294005139
    },
    {
        "question": "13×317=？",
        "answer": 3.615002614524588
    },
    {
        "question": "181048334÷10662=？",
        "answer": 4.229955854620888
    },
    {
        "question": "431×376=？",
        "answer": 5.209665115088392
    },
    {
        "question": "10478×5256=？",
        "answer": 7.740933750663652
    },
    {
        "question": "2×3212196=？",
        "answer": 6.807832032619767
    },
    {
        "question": "62818974÷48561043=？",
        "answer": 0.11180283294563591
    },
    {
        "question": "40508202÷194652=？",
        "answer": 2.318284096642012
    },
    {
        "question": "355448493÷11104570=？",
        "answer": 1.5052749311702935
    },
    {
        "question": "3×1509=？",
        "answer": 3.655810494495252
    },
    {
        "question": "23497274÷832=？",
        "answer": 4.450894154898952
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1083816=？",
        "answer": 6.034955558062624
    },
    {
        "question": "14×157184=？",
        "answer": 6.3425363721312555
    },
    {
        "question": "31×457889=？",
        "answer": 7.152121904305226
    },
    {
        "question": "19×83852=？",
        "answer": 6.202267026614136
    },
    {
        "question": "330×4398=？",
        "answer": 6.161769164902659
    },
    {
        "question": "526×1665439=？",
        "answer": 8.942514474577182
    },
    {
        "question": "8×125042=？",
        "answer": 6.0001458984363545
    },
    {
        "question": "664×605509=？",
        "answer": 8.604288682043272
    },
    {
        "question": "6067878÷44483=？",
        "answer": 2.1348427713010394
    },
    {
        "question": "2×1653449=？",
        "answer": 6.519420799473629
    },
    {
        "question": "861442÷705147=？",
        "answer": 0.08694637959802834
    },
    {
        "question": "727239590÷181289=？",
        "answer": 3.6033060599149906
    },
    {
        "question": "1031÷740=？",
        "answer": 0.1440269455525404
    },
    {
        "question": "8×27621701=？",
        "answer": 8.344340406787303
    },
    {
        "question": "18057231÷2426=？",
        "answer": 3.87176035733068
    },
    {
        "question": "5×37289543=？",
        "answer": 8.270557065257144
    },
    {
        "question": "4019682÷11960=？",
        "answer": 2.526460517435083
    },
    {
        "question": "40×6129=？",
        "answer": 5.389449612680073
    },
    {
        "question": "10×373=？",
        "answer": 3.571708831808688
    },
    {
        "question": "23468÷2137=？",
        "answer": 1.0406715573802245
    },
    {
        "question": "40770999÷1570627=？",
        "answer": 1.4142782940171232
    },
    {
        "question": "14×26139404=？",
        "answer": 8.563423716762776
    },
    {
        "question": "3533700÷18801=？",
        "answer": 2.2740487270824787
    },
    {
        "question": "364×456112=？",
        "answer": 8.220172882036072
    },
    {
        "question": "208342163÷1793=？",
        "answer": 5.0651968791146365
    },
    {
        "question": "7385×83818=？",
        "answer": 8.79168779347189
    },
    {
        "question": "1×7407=？",
        "answer": 3.8696423446515946
    },
    {
        "question": "50×77254=？",
        "answer": 6.5868909795908674
    },
    {
        "question": "35×984=？",
        "answer": 4.5370631427816175
    },
    {
        "question": "263699÷28991=？",
        "answer": 0.9588452869297289
    },
    {
        "question": "25164690÷953973=？",
        "answer": 1.421255501581351
    },
    {
        "question": "822639516÷1857=？",
        "answer": 5.646397663539572
    },
    {
        "question": "59×204=？",
        "answer": 4.080482179068043
    },
    {
        "question": "831527÷3307=？",
        "answer": 2.4004421605788604
    },
    {
        "question": "149160163÷5809=？",
        "answer": 4.4095514728038285
    },
    {
        "question": "207039÷1217=？",
        "answer": 2.2307615831178405
    },
    {
        "question": "28866×693=？",
        "answer": 7.301119841898014
    },
    {
        "question": "1358046÷64836=？",
        "answer": 1.3210982671145268
    },
    {
        "question": "34×590696=？",
        "answer": 7.302842947009889
    },
    {
        "question": "424×3316=？",
        "answer": 6.147980378470969
    },
    {
        "question": "2×12374=？",
        "answer": 4.393540107347963
    },
    {
        "question": "50713×2089=？",
        "answer": 8.025057742598937
    },
    {
        "question": "270961077÷599=？",
        "answer": 5.655480087458613
    },
    {
        "question": "20561÷2000=？",
        "answer": 1.0120142374180414
    },
    {
        "question": "91459÷4729=？",
        "answer": 1.286457134539666
    },
    {
        "question": "344919967÷883939=？",
        "answer": 2.591296040183081
    },
    {
        "question": "8×454854=？",
        "answer": 6.5609620052544955
    },
    {
        "question": "748324÷39568=？",
        "answer": 1.2767455749782588
    },
    {
        "question": "137×839197=？",
        "answer": 8.060584489808813
    },
    {
        "question": "41390193÷772275=？",
        "answer": 1.729125475361247
    },
    {
        "question": "2896438÷3528=？",
        "answer": 2.9143356601398156
    },
    {
        "question": "44792÷10507=？",
        "answer": 0.6297217222294001
    },
    {
        "question": "552378÷57753=？",
        "answer": 0.9806618245271532
    },
    {
        "question": "528×3161=？",
        "answer": 6.222458418373392
    },
    {
        "question": "123×644786=？",
        "answer": 7.899320710663303
    },
    {
        "question": "3×348640=？",
        "answer": 6.019498467621843
    },
    {
        "question": "865182×208=？",
        "answer": 8.255170810383083
    },
    {
        "question": "5×2147=？",
        "answer": 4.0308020487722676
    },
    {
        "question": "114×2930=？",
        "answer": 5.523772471690582
    },
    {
        "question": "5578057÷42681=？",
        "answer": 2.116248361609223
    },
    {
        "question": "742419531÷144876224=？",
        "answer": 0.7096522702814012
    },
    {
        "question": "255704÷314=？",
        "answer": 2.9108078737127614
    },
    {
        "question": "818635×784=？",
        "answer": 8.807406371258928
    },
    {
        "question": "19967÷6088=？",
        "answer": 0.5158381741718534
    },
    {
        "question": "5289074÷726521=？",
        "answer": 0.8621314712780713
    },
    {
        "question": "61762160÷21443=？",
        "answer": 3.459436930530779
    },
    {
        "question": "58563552÷597592=？",
        "answer": 1.991222634783697
    },
    {
        "question": "4×426=？",
        "answer": 3.2314695904306814
    },
    {
        "question": "33230658÷255980=？",
        "answer": 2.1133329060954815
    },
    {
        "question": "21×31410719=？",
        "answer": 8.819297172366383
    },
    {
        "question": "1437371÷2076=？",
        "answer": 2.8403415292272736
    },
    {
        "question": "1×319849=？",
        "answer": 5.504944997244731
    },
    {
        "question": "76429180÷3223103=？",
        "answer": 1.3749850157255628
    },
    {
        "question": "13246843÷33483=？",
        "answer": 2.5972880262835045
    },
    {
        "question": "277×32111=？",
        "answer": 6.94913359963
    },
    {
        "question": "231052182÷3901=？",
        "answer": 4.772534123932609
    },
    {
        "question": "136739808÷10618849=？",
        "answer": 1.1098175205813146
    },
    {
        "question": "4×611534=？",
        "answer": 6.388480599228308
    },
    {
        "question": "2344957÷136719=？",
        "answer": 1.2343060101930694
    },
    {
        "question": "226×53519=？",
        "answer": 7.082616429210993
    },
    {
        "question": "16827÷2281=？",
        "answer": 0.8678814094525306
    },
    {
        "question": "227921÷44152=？",
        "answer": 0.712833960638978
    },
    {
        "question": "837615÷70957=？",
        "answer": 1.0720492004607745
    },
    {
        "question": "482544÷29229=？",
        "answer": 1.217722962661042
    },
    {
        "question": "23084÷1458=？",
        "answer": 1.1995535416546694
    },
    {
        "question": "183×624=？",
        "answer": 5.057635679412853
    },
    {
        "question": "70315×8245=？",
        "answer": 8.763238641079063
    },
    {
        "question": "57139×1029=？",
        "answer": 7.769348010209188
    },
    {
        "question": "5303964÷1421=？",
        "answer": 3.57200648975914
    },
    {
        "question": "143×22750=？",
        "answer": 6.512317438458193
    },
    {
        "question": "673678687÷205=？",
        "answer": 6.516698946851016
    },
    {
        "question": "324516430÷37565122=？",
        "answer": 0.936451886032117
    },
    {
        "question": "2369535÷15783=？",
        "answer": 2.1764735714561825
    },
    {
        "question": "20046421÷1143102=？",
        "answer": 1.2439518622425907
    },
    {
        "question": "113063×7695=？",
        "answer": 8.939529128961864
    },
    {
        "question": "5110×262=？",
        "answer": 6.1267221914544585
    },
    {
        "question": "24×124087=？",
        "answer": 6.473937526643071
    },
    {
        "question": "910892063÷4938578=？",
        "answer": 2.2658650004797236
    },
    {
        "question": "999223÷1268=？",
        "answer": 2.8965431684758123
    },
    {
        "question": "28234÷2086=？",
        "answer": 1.1314581062868734
    },
    {
        "question": "1010×203531=？",
        "answer": 8.312951940187105
    },
    {
        "question": "126312794÷25879=？",
        "answer": 3.68849985111757
    },
    {
        "question": "102×6008171=？",
        "answer": 8.787342456493644
    },
    {
        "question": "50270531÷7895=？",
        "answer": 3.8039613382947812
    },
    {
        "question": "1199513÷341=？",
        "answer": 3.5462505801039073
    },
    {
        "question": "23581839÷6571601=？",
        "answer": 0.5549064829602749
    },
    {
        "question": "26850908÷13086391=？",
        "answer": 0.31213908437656157
    },
    {
        "question": "1×18190763=？",
        "answer": 7.259850915651725
    },
    {
        "question": "5×4618750=？",
        "answer": 7.36349446007492
    },
    {
        "question": "95342355÷36595=？",
        "answer": 3.415864123502668
    },
    {
        "question": "107676870÷2952=？",
        "answer": 4.562006069643783
    },
    {
        "question": "2×6065694=？",
        "answer": 7.083910493055787
    },
    {
        "question": "123×3250=？",
        "answer": 5.6017884724182725
    },
    {
        "question": "50737÷6045=？",
        "answer": 0.9239284792899521
    },
    {
        "question": "31906466÷22730=？",
        "answer": 3.1472792681334125
    },
    {
        "question": "24899712÷79510=？",
        "answer": 2.495772570443857
    },
    {
        "question": "59146754÷1638=？",
        "answer": 4.557617017920435
    },
    {
        "question": "29×772863=？",
        "answer": 7.350500514304815
    },
    {
        "question": "7×7548282=？",
        "answer": 7.7229461568325535
    },
    {
        "question": "9×4502=？",
        "answer": 4.6076480001038265
    },
    {
        "question": "31213÷1572=？",
        "answer": 1.2978829706604749
    },
    {
        "question": "2625÷452=？",
        "answer": 0.7639908729305935
    },
    {
        "question": "78480÷65760=？",
        "answer": 0.07679718983989808
    },
    {
        "question": "351×651190=？",
        "answer": 8.359014839154455
    },
    {
        "question": "341365892÷3729781=？",
        "answer": 1.961536793601329
    },
    {
        "question": "7×8806576=？",
        "answer": 7.789905127388123
    },
    {
        "question": "11610540÷38791=？",
        "answer": 2.4761214435141006
    },
    {
        "question": "18415390÷651628=？",
        "answer": 1.4511811833822776
    },
    {
        "question": "32335÷469=？",
        "answer": 1.8385000225680523
    },
    {
        "question": "549976÷35170=？",
        "answer": 1.1941713697318745
    },
    {
        "question": "52165944÷11920=？",
        "answer": 3.6411108154201943
    },
    {
        "question": "575×21153=？",
        "answer": 7.085039814086335
    },
    {
        "question": "237626131÷426=？",
        "answer": 5.746484597833969
    },
    {
        "question": "9812×97461=？",
        "answer": 8.980588402687298
    },
    {
        "question": "12714636÷253865=？",
        "answer": 1.6997011020734196
    },
    {
        "question": "134443653÷81420042=？",
        "answer": 0.21780898220346678
    },
    {
        "question": "11×11160400=？",
        "answer": 8.089072445591292
    },
    {
        "question": "53410÷2009=？",
        "answer": 1.4246426412208881
    },
    {
        "question": "18×785749=？",
        "answer": 7.1505563420792635
    },
    {
        "question": "1919÷255=？",
        "answer": 0.8765347943015164
    },
    {
        "question": "471868÷297=？",
        "answer": 3.2010640770940966
    },
    {
        "question": "190065497÷32633=？",
        "answer": 3.765246284647702
    },
    {
        "question": "466327187÷3053=？",
        "answer": 5.183963931378632
    },
    {
        "question": "524629÷1978=？",
        "answer": 2.4236260062212978
    },
    {
        "question": "12×89739=？",
        "answer": 6.032162471742767
    },
    {
        "question": "60975×1451=？",
        "answer": 7.946819221423504
    },
    {
        "question": "1195172÷518354=？",
        "answer": 0.362803955897832
    },
    {
        "question": "1979828÷24165=？",
        "answer": 1.9134406625565499
    },
    {
        "question": "488×57704=？",
        "answer": 7.44962574118472
    },
    {
        "question": "156×930=？",
        "answer": 5.161607546908397
    },
    {
        "question": "17523×4295=？",
        "answer": 7.876571629126618
    },
    {
        "question": "4665167÷224=？",
        "answer": 4.318619176560859
    },
    {
        "question": "1739×1545=？",
        "answer": 6.429228065763566
    },
    {
        "question": "670×3253=？",
        "answer": 6.33835886598268
    },
    {
        "question": "293809020÷46012=？",
        "answer": 3.805194013473441
    },
    {
        "question": "623528328÷14561=？",
        "answer": 4.631664987162397
    },
    {
        "question": "679×2613=？",
        "answer": 6.249009184007828
    },
    {
        "question": "210837546÷1489726=？",
        "answer": 2.150841555172365
    },
    {
        "question": "602×319259=？",
        "answer": 8.283739640248074
    },
    {
        "question": "94944529÷1239582=？",
        "answer": 1.8841946831785001
    },
    {
        "question": "34306049÷40494=？",
        "answer": 2.927980025065869
    },
    {
        "question": "2627×1927=？",
        "answer": 6.704341787441523
    },
    {
        "question": "1742×454=？",
        "answer": 5.898104003528748
    },
    {
        "question": "82550÷2815=？",
        "answer": 1.4672386784114475
    },
    {
        "question": "183240×1321=？",
        "answer": 8.383923100718572
    },
    {
        "question": "15739279÷15307=？",
        "answer": 3.0120947517004937
    },
    {
        "question": "5444×34241=？",
        "answer": 8.270464556185365
    },
    {
        "question": "30×22917=？",
        "answer": 5.837279019467005
    },
    {
        "question": "33069×540=？",
        "answer": 7.251814821956256
    },
    {
        "question": "170931÷2923=？",
        "answer": 1.766992018036387
    },
    {
        "question": "124524÷1715=？",
        "answer": 1.8609889384028595
    },
    {
        "question": "1276024÷453=？",
        "answer": 3.4497606408437416
    },
    {
        "question": "705521÷98256=？",
        "answer": 0.8561508651229844
    },
    {
        "question": "112450516÷18657=？",
        "answer": 3.7801196410836275
    },
    {
        "question": "13×67653115=？",
        "answer": 8.944231150227413
    },
    {
        "question": "428×210=？",
        "answer": 4.953663063747091
    },
    {
        "question": "396007303÷13617=？",
        "answer": 4.46362175761289
    },
    {
        "question": "80×3267304=？",
        "answer": 8.417279531439918
    },
    {
        "question": "1×480=？",
        "answer": 2.681241237375587
    },
    {
        "question": "38×4445=？",
        "answer": 5.227655361923043
    },
    {
        "question": "55×1039=？",
        "answer": 4.756978237051421
    },
    {
        "question": "68×1579=？",
        "answer": 5.03089104271453
    },
    {
        "question": "1259151÷206511=？",
        "answer": 0.7851346250191483
    },
    {
        "question": "334786794÷437870=？",
        "answer": 2.8834231272962003
    },
    {
        "question": "48×255313=？",
        "answer": 7.088314166102773
    },
    {
        "question": "5192087÷584125=？",
        "answer": 0.9488361669755377
    },
    {
        "question": "38×13343=？",
        "answer": 5.705037082641608
    },
    {
        "question": "234×110643=？",
        "answer": 7.413139800232495
    },
    {
        "question": "195×1103=？",
        "answer": 5.332610123802708
    },
    {
        "question": "28193×472=？",
        "answer": 7.124083289976557
    },
    {
        "question": "467×1635=？",
        "answer": 5.882834637562417
    },
    {
        "question": "127703321÷4671=？",
        "answer": 4.43679232420602
    },
    {
        "question": "793290÷296909=？",
        "answer": 0.4268086174534822
    },
    {
        "question": "4237701÷2217=？",
        "answer": 3.281364617771131
    },
    {
        "question": "10682×13967=？",
        "answer": 8.1737557067795
    },
    {
        "question": "132415÷1791=？",
        "answer": 1.8688415990147502
    },
    {
        "question": "84×303936=？",
        "answer": 7.407061429627787
    },
    {
        "question": "15235541÷3589188=？",
        "answer": 0.62786167315651
    },
    {
        "question": "722080484÷131651=？",
        "answer": 3.739161444991177
    },
    {
        "question": "1×111261=？",
        "answer": 5.046342959007022
    },
    {
        "question": "1×43258660=？",
        "answer": 7.6360730624073
    },
    {
        "question": "1×4813480=？",
        "answer": 6.6824591716622095
    },
    {
        "question": "1310×621=？",
        "answer": 5.910362895832344
    },
    {
        "question": "57351572÷133857=？",
        "answer": 2.6319042389836604
    },
    {
        "question": "436×13671=？",
        "answer": 6.775286772570698
    },
    {
        "question": "57×466=？",
        "answer": 4.424260772362492
    },
    {
        "question": "1173×3188=？",
        "answer": 6.572816324839604
    },
    {
        "question": "10605×10636=？",
        "answer": 8.05228900151211
    },
    {
        "question": "99081÷2814=？",
        "answer": 1.5466662880638642
    },
    {
        "question": "149570745÷430=？",
        "answer": 5.541378201267573
    },
    {
        "question": "116665222÷167225=？",
        "answer": 2.843640207166118
    },
    {
        "question": "8810×65129=？",
        "answer": 8.758750318417606
    },
    {
        "question": "1×360104091=？",
        "answer": 8.556428055246968
    },
    {
        "question": "274557397÷6990850=？",
        "answer": 1.594103165028551
    },
    {
        "question": "2399249÷30929=？",
        "answer": 1.889709443892342
    },
    {
        "question": "1×60287621=？",
        "answer": 7.780228146579611
    },
    {
        "question": "26613954÷479=？",
        "answer": 4.744773888487973
    },
    {
        "question": "366751794÷77221=？",
        "answer": 3.6766368255409825
    },
    {
        "question": "1×23740=？",
        "answer": 4.375480714618573
    },
    {
        "question": "61103÷4147=？",
        "answer": 1.1683284981430384
    },
    {
        "question": "400502÷1445=？",
        "answer": 2.4427368420837325
    },
    {
        "question": "122×2269=？",
        "answer": 5.442194326559684
    },
    {
        "question": "5325144÷2827=？",
        "answer": 3.275005547763945
    },
    {
        "question": "496444÷36389=？",
        "answer": 1.1349001452232284
    },
    {
        "question": "151648213÷941825=？",
        "answer": 2.206867082751849
    },
    {
        "question": "31×356323=？",
        "answer": 7.0432055500070625
    },
    {
        "question": "209747767÷12295032=？",
        "answer": 1.2319676825693946
    },
    {
        "question": "7×3238684=？",
        "answer": 7.355466615764104
    },
    {
        "question": "300×179618=？",
        "answer": 7.731471111042957
    },
    {
        "question": "212376827÷218=？",
        "answer": 5.988650634364813
    },
    {
        "question": "396625396÷4093=？",
        "answer": 4.986338774073105
    },
    {
        "question": "16663154÷231=？",
        "answer": 4.858145228172218
    },
    {
        "question": "4266530÷975=？",
        "answer": 3.6410701880117475
    },
    {
        "question": "2×17151=？",
        "answer": 4.535319442597916
    },
    {
        "question": "47300384÷7426924=？",
        "answer": 0.8040556867107463
    },
    {
        "question": "5363202÷540=？",
        "answer": 3.997030394744656
    },
    {
        "question": "4493×3011=？",
        "answer": 7.131247174105785
    },
    {
        "question": "9×36892=？",
        "answer": 5.521174709405062
    },
    {
        "question": "495642÷142050=？",
        "answer": 0.542726862702752
    },
    {
        "question": "230×688=？",
        "answer": 5.199316274253104
    },
    {
        "question": "388÷324=？",
        "answer": 0.0782867153875951
    },
    {
        "question": "471709795÷163065=？",
        "answer": 3.4613141396161344
    },
    {
        "question": "421165×220=？",
        "answer": 7.966874953738212
    },
    {
        "question": "15768110÷13849753=？",
        "answer": 0.05633761281427473
    },
    {
        "question": "50171×2044=？",
        "answer": 8.010933648861839
    },
    {
        "question": "4×218589=？",
        "answer": 5.941688294598093
    },
    {
        "question": "711039÷346=？",
        "answer": 3.3128173233438547
    },
    {
        "question": "5×3341780=？",
        "answer": 7.2229478598482215
    },
    {
        "question": "694630040÷35547=？",
        "answer": 4.2909506067024
    },
    {
        "question": "6680581÷2126=？",
        "answer": 3.497250973863343
    },
    {
        "question": "1362×1228=？",
        "answer": 6.223375474381915
    },
    {
        "question": "2×538=？",
        "answer": 3.0318122713303706
    },
    {
        "question": "184303889÷155728470=？",
        "answer": 0.07316648260616042
    },
    {
        "question": "2261÷2001=？",
        "answer": 0.053053473709148286
    },
    {
        "question": "22588279÷4567=？",
        "answer": 3.6942521316960266
    },
    {
        "question": "132×39787=？",
        "answer": 6.720315125125695
    },
    {
        "question": "219749÷7196=？",
        "answer": 1.4848357527561635
    },
    {
        "question": "9×129493=？",
        "answer": 6.066488801844703
    },
    {
        "question": "445×658=？",
        "answer": 5.466585904594887
    },
    {
        "question": "2112×135909=？",
        "answer": 8.45794213086592
    },
    {
        "question": "82148×797=？",
        "answer": 7.816055315831378
    },
    {
        "question": "520847160÷11805=？",
        "answer": 4.644644309031142
    },
    {
        "question": "141109÷118258=？",
        "answer": 0.07672418428812597
    },
    {
        "question": "554200678÷3599=？",
        "answer": 5.187485206102357
    },
    {
        "question": "1×663941=？",
        "answer": 5.82212948823415
    },
    {
        "question": "481×360224=？",
        "answer": 8.238717720782772
    },
    {
        "question": "142779846÷2894=？",
        "answer": 4.693168382416904
    },
    {
        "question": "22×2042=？",
        "answer": 4.652478418573097
    },
    {
        "question": "1117317×263=？",
        "answer": 8.468132155105078
    },
    {
        "question": "83921÷910=？",
        "answer": 1.9648292579346458
    },
    {
        "question": "2×78118=？",
        "answer": 5.193781111487137
    },
    {
        "question": "727×49907=？",
        "answer": 7.559695875283279
    },
    {
        "question": "120798÷221=？",
        "answer": 2.7376674702344874
    },
    {
        "question": "36×361889=？",
        "answer": 7.114877883234689
    },
    {
        "question": "34×1233384=？",
        "answer": 7.622577227309952
    },
    {
        "question": "24×9332=？",
        "answer": 5.350185971833321
    },
    {
        "question": "2×8862=？",
        "answer": 4.248561741359574
    },
    {
        "question": "88×521=？",
        "answer": 4.661320395449693
    },
    {
        "question": "957737152÷103698=？",
        "answer": 3.96547595432379
    },
    {
        "question": "56338270÷1506098=？",
        "answer": 1.5729502750060378
    },
    {
        "question": "8316965÷55526=？",
        "answer": 2.1754684851079498
    },
    {
        "question": "24209×2396=？",
        "answer": 7.763463664148206
    },
    {
        "question": "8424235÷913923=？",
        "answer": 0.964620866277769
    },
    {
        "question": "7×7592223=？",
        "answer": 7.72546699578849
    },
    {
        "question": "58×223=？",
        "answer": 4.1117328566110976
    },
    {
        "question": "267×9289=？",
        "answer": 6.394480224243267
    },
    {
        "question": "8×284=？",
        "answer": 3.3564083270389813
    },
    {
        "question": "2508×1376=？",
        "answer": 6.537945966058171
    },
    {
        "question": "10482÷657=？",
        "answer": 1.2028787858067937
    },
    {
        "question": "105×904=？",
        "answer": 4.977357729545301
    },
    {
        "question": "247×19594=？",
        "answer": 6.6848200569725345
    },
    {
        "question": "486×805=？",
        "answer": 5.592432149630162
    },
    {
        "question": "7574610÷50871=？",
        "answer": 2.1728900019954605
    },
    {
        "question": "4574×10926=？",
        "answer": 7.698757356449294
    },
    {
        "question": "3330638÷3144146=？",
        "answer": 0.025024728189261086
    },
    {
        "question": "309946420÷208187314=？",
        "answer": 0.17283236242340733
    },
    {
        "question": "29×134171=？",
        "answer": 6.590056654559185
    },
    {
        "question": "105261992÷58450269=？",
        "answer": 0.25548507022503053
    },
    {
        "question": "248853÷14244=？",
        "answer": 1.2423109156638912
    },
    {
        "question": "5×75324562=？",
        "answer": 8.575906619337422
    },
    {
        "question": "55×205677=？",
        "answer": 7.053548418565904
    },
    {
        "question": "3940012÷13117=？",
        "answer": 2.477663026004123
    },
    {
        "question": "10561÷355=？",
        "answer": 1.4734766895669433
    },
    {
        "question": "3×102569728=？",
        "answer": 8.488140458551648
    },
    {
        "question": "27354700÷2817=？",
        "answer": 3.9872451092302916
    },
    {
        "question": "1×40925622=？",
        "answer": 7.611995288673227
    },
    {
        "question": "55663×710=？",
        "answer": 7.596824957981474
    },
    {
        "question": "13898÷11411=？",
        "answer": 0.08562860197414769
    },
    {
        "question": "25442926÷1765=？",
        "answer": 4.158822345074146
    },
    {
        "question": "71×12501=？",
        "answer": 5.948203103896016
    },
    {
        "question": "10×197991=？",
        "answer": 6.296645449154598
    },
    {
        "question": "86783÷2493=？",
        "answer": 1.541712380667223
    },
    {
        "question": "49×1628883=？",
        "answer": 7.902085970795447
    },
    {
        "question": "28518÷9810=？",
        "answer": 0.4634500572984537
    },
    {
        "question": "689×667=？",
        "answer": 5.662345055824175
    },
    {
        "question": "206269415÷486552=？",
        "answer": 2.627305574796248
    },
    {
        "question": "131×7886=？",
        "answer": 6.014128068392969
    },
    {
        "question": "40×68137=？",
        "answer": 6.435442999454338
    },
    {
        "question": "375777382÷430618=？",
        "answer": 2.9408384568679753
    },
    {
        "question": "11×16147251=？",
        "answer": 8.249491281351597
    },
    {
        "question": "666×154460=？",
        "answer": 8.012290259672653
    },
    {
        "question": "2×343361313=？",
        "answer": 8.836781356677834
    },
    {
        "question": "18×1417=？",
        "answer": 4.406642355350766
    },
    {
        "question": "51635905÷6729=？",
        "answer": 3.885001264811094
    },
    {
        "question": "796771139÷588317=？",
        "answer": 3.1317221965557036
    },
    {
        "question": "1×20403=？",
        "answer": 4.309694029565843
    },
    {
        "question": "1×3991=？",
        "answer": 3.6010817277840235
    },
    {
        "question": "84070×2839=？",
        "answer": 8.37780643994302
    },
    {
        "question": "10×13461=？",
        "answer": 5.129077324252736
    },
    {
        "question": "455307÷22803=？",
        "answer": 1.300312340055893
    },
    {
        "question": "51×352971=？",
        "answer": 7.255309201436629
    },
    {
        "question": "36841×8727=？",
        "answer": 8.507196385998256
    },
    {
        "question": "196×11042=？",
        "answer": 6.3353038141605955
    },
    {
        "question": "6×9087934=？",
        "answer": 7.73661641475192
    },
    {
        "question": "4479927÷867097=？",
        "answer": 0.7132032536219884
    },
    {
        "question": "3642364×211=？",
        "answer": 8.88566580018661
    },
    {
        "question": "1878×35609=？",
        "answer": 7.825255365575703
    },
    {
        "question": "6×548=？",
        "answer": 3.5169318088680126
    },
    {
        "question": "3583118÷412=？",
        "answer": 3.939363894646239
    },
    {
        "question": "1725×17586=？",
        "answer": 7.481956168231372
    },
    {
        "question": "5899÷1143=？",
        "answer": 0.7127321657738659
    },
    {
        "question": "61571283÷3336822=？",
        "answer": 1.2660451631622032
    },
    {
        "question": "13108486÷1348=？",
        "answer": 3.9878626423729138
    },
    {
        "question": "21×17140=？",
        "answer": 5.556230112321098
    },
    {
        "question": "10048911÷172358=？",
        "answer": 1.7656875538356576
    },
    {
        "question": "126666220÷43578=？",
        "answer": 3.4633935158899196
    },
    {
        "question": "15×9871=？",
        "answer": 5.170452410963683
    },
    {
        "question": "8065÷1623=？",
        "answer": 0.6962858518987485
    },
    {
        "question": "1×3911480=？",
        "answer": 6.59234111397311
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1224=？",
        "answer": 3.087781417809542
    },
    {
        "question": "345080281÷46446261=？",
        "answer": 0.8709693846929223
    },
    {
        "question": "398342843÷532=？",
        "answer": 5.8743453863358726
    },
    {
        "question": "101732398÷416272=？",
        "answer": 2.3880820820437205
    },
    {
        "question": "7×3113=？",
        "answer": 4.338277160696772
    },
    {
        "question": "6×4588=？",
        "answer": 4.4397746596128735
    },
    {
        "question": "10660005÷6007=？",
        "answer": 3.2490997764460032
    },
    {
        "question": "6342286÷308=？",
        "answer": 4.3136951057729735
    },
    {
        "question": "14076722÷10810850=？",
        "answer": 0.1146416922748464
    },
    {
        "question": "47×1772210=？",
        "answer": 7.9206130407449065
    },
    {
        "question": "30×339=？",
        "answer": 4.007320952922744
    },
    {
        "question": "322718026÷213=？",
        "answer": 6.180443620947772
    },
    {
        "question": "242899÷141522=？",
        "answer": 0.23460176941687183
    },
    {
        "question": "5986317÷8981=？",
        "answer": 2.823835014395236
    },
    {
        "question": "12×384516=？",
        "answer": 6.6640956618811416
    },
    {
        "question": "59184÷4430=？",
        "answer": 1.1258005877482493
    },
    {
        "question": "1879×1096=？",
        "answer": 6.313737334248876
    },
    {
        "question": "785×1325=？",
        "answer": 6.017085535018079
    },
    {
        "question": "2276482÷73015=？",
        "answer": 1.493852131173095
    },
    {
        "question": "1260×386=？",
        "answer": 5.686957849789318
    },
    {
        "question": "66×14855051=？",
        "answer": 8.99141808269337
    },
    {
        "question": "208×79490=？",
        "answer": 7.218375831946489
    },
    {
        "question": "2×64458=？",
        "answer": 5.11030682177919
    },
    {
        "question": "206×1144=？",
        "answer": 5.372293244826158
    },
    {
        "question": "2341741÷31005=？",
        "answer": 1.8781071241007976
    },
    {
        "question": "234×17844=？",
        "answer": 6.620708071979722
    },
    {
        "question": "2584002÷16696=？",
        "answer": 2.189680409406759
    },
    {
        "question": "1781422÷193880=？",
        "answer": 0.9632338003619991
    },
    {
        "question": "316495753÷55217234=？",
        "answer": 0.7582932389620891
    },
    {
        "question": "34×149742=？",
        "answer": 6.706822546443085
    },
    {
        "question": "394335×279=？",
        "answer": 8.041469528742153
    },
    {
        "question": "22×1116354=？",
        "answer": 7.390224613656934
    },
    {
        "question": "15135055÷6922=？",
        "answer": 3.3397524085408326
    },
    {
        "question": "257×620314=？",
        "answer": 8.202544706292382
    },
    {
        "question": "6761554÷4382979=？",
        "answer": 0.1882771309627959
    },
    {
        "question": "3×2431801=？",
        "answer": 6.8630492874346825
    },
    {
        "question": "19149184÷2832=？",
        "answer": 3.8300570231851987
    },
    {
        "question": "6778×872=？",
        "answer": 6.771618049433926
    },
    {
        "question": "1072×40539=？",
        "answer": 7.638067816841557
    },
    {
        "question": "605786250÷333=？",
        "answer": 6.259875178083954
    },
    {
        "question": "36286×259=？",
        "answer": 6.97303886031506
    },
    {
        "question": "139861×299=？",
        "answer": 7.6213678174262
    },
    {
        "question": "2722474÷1382565=？",
        "answer": 0.294278182470292
    },
    {
        "question": "341744×430=？",
        "answer": 8.16716935397741
    },
    {
        "question": "435273890÷49958=？",
        "answer": 3.940157573022452
    },
    {
        "question": "659262764÷26117=？",
        "answer": 4.402135257876225
    },
    {
        "question": "61059÷442=？",
        "answer": 2.1403274179696234
    },
    {
        "question": "644566657÷234933399=？",
        "answer": 0.4383230739208782
    },
    {
        "question": "346007÷14955=？",
        "answer": 1.3642984676411092
    },
    {
        "question": "563717÷1907=？",
        "answer": 2.4707104389799066
    },
    {
        "question": "70808÷955=？",
        "answer": 1.8700789561565696
    },
    {
        "question": "26×4241907=？",
        "answer": 8.042534490739394
    },
    {
        "question": "277×2547711=？",
        "answer": 8.848629931258497
    },
    {
        "question": "16527423÷581=？",
        "answer": 4.454029010102602
    },
    {
        "question": "591223980÷121044583=？",
        "answer": 0.6888066820754386
    },
    {
        "question": "540×64371=？",
        "answer": 7.541084015745607
    },
    {
        "question": "2812×22247=？",
        "answer": 7.796286771157391
    },
    {
        "question": "15774695÷2939511=？",
        "answer": 0.7296858813063921
    },
    {
        "question": "251355726÷205335=？",
        "answer": 3.0878258005584738
    },
    {
        "question": "18288253÷36138=？",
        "answer": 2.704208107575717
    },
    {
        "question": "150975×203=？",
        "answer": 7.486401076193568
    },
    {
        "question": "4424889÷3704=？",
        "answer": 3.077231402720642
    },
    {
        "question": "31×57433=？",
        "answer": 6.250523195983752
    },
    {
        "question": "84×2473=？",
        "answer": 5.317503402423179
    },
    {
        "question": "6614583÷77891=？",
        "answer": 1.9290151908217748
    },
    {
        "question": "546452÷13489=？",
        "answer": 1.607572265137219
    },
    {
        "question": "43×109200=？",
        "answer": 6.671691093948305
    },
    {
        "question": "7146÷4121=？",
        "answer": 0.23906039734183288
    },
    {
        "question": "1×368=？",
        "answer": 2.5658478186735176
    },
    {
        "question": "94064064÷1047=？",
        "answer": 4.95347705665474
    },
    {
        "question": "98×2924=？",
        "answer": 5.457203443978318
    },
    {
        "question": "3×221466=？",
        "answer": 5.822428316449027
    },
    {
        "question": "31961×656=？",
        "answer": 7.321524198493449
    },
    {
        "question": "141156707÷91793077=？",
        "answer": 0.1868915901812793
    },
    {
        "question": "2984×92870=？",
        "answer": 8.442674264348664
    },
    {
        "question": "1×530937481=？",
        "answer": 8.725043385007583
    },
    {
        "question": "24×125094=？",
        "answer": 6.477447721433948
    },
    {
        "question": "6827601÷2886496=？",
        "answer": 0.37389717332718725
    },
    {
        "question": "17581÷454=？",
        "answer": 1.587987721073506
    },
    {
        "question": "2128953×447=？",
        "answer": 8.978473596939466
    },
    {
        "question": "225163÷108633=？",
        "answer": 0.316535253284877
    },
    {
        "question": "303635748÷109084445=？",
        "answer": 0.44459007473154005
    },
    {
        "question": "148262×1376=？",
        "answer": 8.309648288198
    },
    {
        "question": "2581528÷464=？",
        "answer": 3.745358859337579
    },
    {
        "question": "43552578÷877=？",
        "answer": 4.696014273854501
    },
    {
        "question": "1×17457262=？",
        "answer": 7.241976129888694
    },
    {
        "question": "922952277÷264305=？",
        "answer": 3.5430738665936423
    },
    {
        "question": "279534÷13739=？",
        "answer": 1.30847951557504
    },
    {
        "question": "1956723÷225=？",
        "answer": 3.9393468317744964
    },
    {
        "question": "7×40847608=？",
        "answer": 8.456264669724389
    },
    {
        "question": "34211408÷16220=？",
        "answer": 3.3241200984416768
    },
    {
        "question": "904×44007=？",
        "answer": 7.599690193770094
    },
    {
        "question": "75132×1511=？",
        "answer": 8.055089414171766
    },
    {
        "question": "1700×55435=？",
        "answer": 7.9742329732429305
    },
    {
        "question": "16994÷844=？",
        "answer": 1.3039531672913918
    },
    {
        "question": "606803÷104994=？",
        "answer": 0.7618832377142405
    },
    {
        "question": "119678422÷14317=？",
        "answer": 3.922163829280951
    },
    {
        "question": "377690683÷19701646=？",
        "answer": 1.2826337602555797
    },
    {
        "question": "292309×222=？",
        "answer": 7.812195161652633
    },
    {
        "question": "137429677÷782497=？",
        "answer": 2.244597844589163
    },
    {
        "question": "277600÷6800=？",
        "answer": 1.610910549076581
    },
    {
        "question": "12457×56980=？",
        "answer": 8.851135909351905
    },
    {
        "question": "13875÷6671=？",
        "answer": 0.3180420511421306
    },
    {
        "question": "162×121015=？",
        "answer": 7.292354219681195
    },
    {
        "question": "374901÷36340=？",
        "answer": 1.0135316758755226
    },
    {
        "question": "223117107÷159455312=？",
        "answer": 0.14589387845886892
    },
    {
        "question": "2×6833796=？",
        "answer": 7.135692005918844
    },
    {
        "question": "152197824÷61289765=？",
        "answer": 0.3950204871279824
    },
    {
        "question": "23917272÷269015=？",
        "answer": 1.948935146094347
    },
    {
        "question": "17×2624016=？",
        "answer": 7.649415400210907
    },
    {
        "question": "303366161÷68129457=？",
        "answer": 0.6486322081697349
    },
    {
        "question": "280×1049=？",
        "answer": 5.467933519535777
    },
    {
        "question": "9×2399=？",
        "answer": 4.334272757407155
    },
    {
        "question": "575098÷31996=？",
        "answer": 1.2546461691518025
    },
    {
        "question": "2×1230=？",
        "answer": 3.3909351071033793
    },
    {
        "question": "3×20991928=？",
        "answer": 7.799173582835564
    },
    {
        "question": "211×1079250=？",
        "answer": 8.357404512625997
    },
    {
        "question": "1×10107117=？",
        "answer": 7.004627293123389
    },
    {
        "question": "2563724×231=？",
        "answer": 8.77248324889459
    },
    {
        "question": "28110÷1120=？",
        "answer": 1.399642822937259
    },
    {
        "question": "39156040÷168930=？",
        "answer": 2.365091981430217
    },
    {
        "question": "12031064÷14435=？",
        "answer": 2.9208872488400695
    },
    {
        "question": "22265÷659=？",
        "answer": 1.528737284873232
    },
    {
        "question": "8815006÷57626=？",
        "answer": 2.184604137345251
    },
    {
        "question": "28×1922481=？",
        "answer": 7.731020087677362
    },
    {
        "question": "59409×2351=？",
        "answer": 8.14510487131585
    },
    {
        "question": "27121254÷1108=？",
        "answer": 4.388770005654005
    },
    {
        "question": "28027678÷555582=？",
        "answer": 1.702838952573688
    },
    {
        "question": "51×445452=？",
        "answer": 7.3563710892783805
    },
    {
        "question": "1209÷523=？",
        "answer": 0.3639246119934976
    },
    {
        "question": "2140972÷595659=？",
        "answer": 0.5556132794919999
    },
    {
        "question": "657942803÷9722=？",
        "answer": 4.830432523955715
    },
    {
        "question": "17810079÷14447282=？",
        "answer": 0.09087969589420017
    },
    {
        "question": "6761696÷46719=？",
        "answer": 2.1605621030464577
    },
    {
        "question": "26152÷9992=？",
        "answer": 0.41785248220623344
    },
    {
        "question": "217503936÷52756640=？",
        "answer": 0.6151899923330109
    },
    {
        "question": "139901896÷1080193=？",
        "answer": 2.1123222416586183
    },
    {
        "question": "597747475÷731146=？",
        "answer": 2.912513641877252
    },
    {
        "question": "1260570÷1239=？",
        "answer": 3.0074956608673715
    },
    {
        "question": "9076246÷12609=？",
        "answer": 2.857225613641909
    },
    {
        "question": "55810599÷10601130=？",
        "answer": 0.7213645234785637
    },
    {
        "question": "6866750÷58072=？",
        "answer": 2.072784452786369
    },
    {
        "question": "54×14316282=？",
        "answer": 8.888224004293498
    },
    {
        "question": "143434570÷35131=？",
        "answer": 3.6109633236747394
    },
    {
        "question": "1081×9791=？",
        "answer": 7.02465274452079
    },
    {
        "question": "2×16472871=？",
        "answer": 7.517799293121277
    },
    {
        "question": "11×2809047=？",
        "answer": 7.489951690885217
    },
    {
        "question": "5×6831054=？",
        "answer": 7.533457722815214
    },
    {
        "question": "34×161967=？",
        "answer": 6.740905455178632
    },
    {
        "question": "2×102073797=？",
        "answer": 8.309944265872138
    },
    {
        "question": "10875477÷534995=？",
        "answer": 1.30809859108811
    },
    {
        "question": "167875860÷2419=？",
        "answer": 4.841352382138706
    },
    {
        "question": "16529415÷346855=？",
        "answer": 1.6781095241887776
    },
    {
        "question": "92064506÷151792=？",
        "answer": 2.782843343926223
    },
    {
        "question": "439048÷2197=？",
        "answer": 2.30068194622722
    },
    {
        "question": "287997÷1042=？",
        "answer": 2.44152024487131
    },
    {
        "question": "113468÷816=？",
        "answer": 2.143183241251956
    },
    {
        "question": "243×3103726=？",
        "answer": 8.87748964793045
    },
    {
        "question": "2136550÷334=？",
        "answer": 3.8059665939129155
    },
    {
        "question": "152230663÷199174=？",
        "answer": 2.883269493471662
    },
    {
        "question": "282×8961=？",
        "answer": 6.402605585643152
    },
    {
        "question": "2×2559=？",
        "answer": 3.7091002815511667
    },
    {
        "question": "9102981÷755084=？",
        "answer": 1.0811883684626673
    },
    {
        "question": "735347235÷44942435=？",
        "answer": 1.21383586477833
    },
    {
        "question": "3×74195408=？",
        "answer": 8.347498282074522
    },
    {
        "question": "10×235322=？",
        "answer": 6.371662530796799
    },
    {
        "question": "194318063÷59297763=？",
        "answer": 0.5154748627139839
    },
    {
        "question": "10×3664=？",
        "answer": 4.5639554649958125
    },
    {
        "question": "6×46360=？",
        "answer": 5.444294677675202
    },
    {
        "question": "2×1845=？",
        "answer": 3.56702636615906
    },
    {
        "question": "13786÷706=？",
        "answer": 1.2906335731063643
    },
    {
        "question": "380313346÷127392215=？",
        "answer": 0.47499867712731064
    },
    {
        "question": "32×360=？",
        "answer": 4.061452479087193
    },
    {
        "question": "30724247÷2459=？",
        "answer": 4.096722719117505
    },
    {
        "question": "4326×8706=？",
        "answer": 7.575905177924453
    },
    {
        "question": "169153709÷28752=？",
        "answer": 3.7696134651529136
    },
    {
        "question": "689218907÷3256451=？",
        "answer": 2.325612635018301
    },
    {
        "question": "720×98669=？",
        "answer": 7.851513223126718
    },
    {
        "question": "363864597÷4877827=？",
        "answer": 1.8727134087156787
    },
    {
        "question": "205343÷2396=？",
        "answer": 1.9329930889280122
    },
    {
        "question": "2764×658=？",
        "answer": 6.259763932316116
    },
    {
        "question": "12572797÷118050=？",
        "answer": 2.027365912089803
    },
    {
        "question": "17968÷2896=？",
        "answer": 0.7927011813922733
    },
    {
        "question": "29539249÷17735=？",
        "answer": 3.2215682568916684
    },
    {
        "question": "2×454658=？",
        "answer": 5.958714832845315
    },
    {
        "question": "1402×103001=？",
        "answer": 8.159589454766625
    },
    {
        "question": "332500983÷361218=？",
        "answer": 2.9640235498971395
    },
    {
        "question": "54937020÷8581=？",
        "answer": 3.8063271959112255
    },
    {
        "question": "3001526×261=？",
        "answer": 8.893982617018388
    },
    {
        "question": "18591÷12575=？",
        "answer": 0.16979475714137626
    },
    {
        "question": "20×8994=？",
        "answer": 5.2549828788959045
    },
    {
        "question": "3737162÷3139=？",
        "answer": 3.07575060852935
    },
    {
        "question": "2611473÷876552=？",
        "answer": 0.4741078550317384
    },
    {
        "question": "82366386÷3282=？",
        "answer": 4.3996114340925105
    },
    {
        "question": "14448÷964=？",
        "answer": 1.1757306990665999
    },
    {
        "question": "1583÷266=？",
        "answer": 0.7745992782312889
    },
    {
        "question": "2313516÷494995=？",
        "answer": 0.6696716952765404
    },
    {
        "question": "516093794÷3556217=？",
        "answer": 2.161740383021762
    },
    {
        "question": "2764×136400=？",
        "answer": 8.57635240902262
    },
    {
        "question": "53313×2597=？",
        "answer": 8.141305071223623
    },
    {
        "question": "30733÷653=？",
        "answer": 1.6726917746810503
    },
    {
        "question": "2×668239=？",
        "answer": 6.1259618141533565
    },
    {
        "question": "177183639÷164253=？",
        "answer": 3.0329103065076426
    },
    {
        "question": "54×1018111=？",
        "answer": 7.740188889552115
    },
    {
        "question": "7187819÷1674=？",
        "answer": 3.6328416787347675
    },
    {
        "question": "4×4860=？",
        "answer": 4.288696260590256
    },
    {
        "question": "30557÷20888=？",
        "answer": 0.16521385537540284
    },
    {
        "question": "605×66343=？",
        "answer": 7.603550480877044
    },
    {
        "question": "42024754÷5830=？",
        "answer": 3.8578366251334524
    },
    {
        "question": "5830410÷46207=？",
        "answer": 2.1009913230697985
    },
    {
        "question": "188440÷28185=？",
        "answer": 0.8251550564099892
    },
    {
        "question": "1343613÷267266=？",
        "answer": 0.7013304832702696
    },
    {
        "question": "73×274698=？",
        "answer": 7.302178357574779
    },
    {
        "question": "217799000÷183454594=？",
        "answer": 0.0745272897443156
    },
    {
        "question": "695052027÷17027261=？",
        "answer": 1.6108725211175552
    },
    {
        "question": "18×105738=？",
        "answer": 6.2795035967107165
    },
    {
        "question": "53670÷684=？",
        "answer": 1.8946754935669192
    },
    {
        "question": "19192177÷35218=？",
        "answer": 2.736359551141877
    },
    {
        "question": "87856525÷48578045=？",
        "answer": 0.25733398871688784
    },
    {
        "question": "36×1526191=？",
        "answer": 7.739911388944007
    },
    {
        "question": "101782761÷79761811=？",
        "answer": 0.10587922142761834
    },
    {
        "question": "6377510÷2386807=？",
        "answer": 0.42683384539272096
    },
    {
        "question": "450963728÷331934=？",
        "answer": 3.1330898725553173
    },
    {
        "question": "25075709÷2435485=？",
        "answer": 1.0126677621476663
    },
    {
        "question": "768080÷305802=？",
        "answer": 0.3999661352345112
    },
    {
        "question": "1378×263=？",
        "answer": 5.5592049660613645
    },
    {
        "question": "341405860÷13892=？",
        "answer": 4.390506196574151
    },
    {
        "question": "289×51305=？",
        "answer": 7.171057534702558
    },
    {
        "question": "2398×337=？",
        "answer": 5.907479079634168
    },
    {
        "question": "15101×23452=？",
        "answer": 8.54918559307758
    },
    {
        "question": "97821÷26666=？",
        "answer": 0.5644742234190099
    },
    {
        "question": "2×2490086=？",
        "answer": 6.697244342229786
    },
    {
        "question": "38595799÷4636=？",
        "answer": 3.920396608716774
    },
    {
        "question": "5×809082=？",
        "answer": 6.606962543677364
    },
    {
        "question": "300885÷543=？",
        "answer": 2.743600707836819
    },
    {
        "question": "43×2359546=？",
        "answer": 8.006296904031784
    },
    {
        "question": "201×3799917=？",
        "answer": 8.882970168027912
    },
    {
        "question": "3×16979=？",
        "answer": 4.70703336304981
    },
    {
        "question": "1611312×241=？",
        "answer": 8.589196684023891
    },
    {
        "question": "370140÷585=？",
        "answer": 2.8012101545454424
    },
    {
        "question": "45434÷2759=？",
        "answer": 1.2166292732153652
    },
    {
        "question": "7×225=？",
        "answer": 3.197280558125619
    },
    {
        "question": "43856980÷25278265=？",
        "answer": 0.2392914603903674
    },
    {
        "question": "1420×1363=？",
        "answer": 6.28678420021773
    },
    {
        "question": "236×2141=？",
        "answer": 5.703528670264545
    },
    {
        "question": "133×862041=？",
        "answer": 8.059379562998654
    },
    {
        "question": "147961464÷956=？",
        "answer": 5.189690727501455
    },
    {
        "question": "1202×357452=？",
        "answer": 8.633122199021393
    },
    {
        "question": "142281483÷7145495=？",
        "answer": 1.2991160635228953
    },
    {
        "question": "213252×341=？",
        "answer": 7.861647491914781
    },
    {
        "question": "22124065÷177486=？",
        "answer": 2.0957008239188024
    },
    {
        "question": "640807÷26836=？",
        "answer": 1.378009464012126
    },
    {
        "question": "15861×8240=？",
        "answer": 8.11625777682189
    },
    {
        "question": "14152343÷9364=？",
        "answer": 3.17936694068277
    },
    {
        "question": "1×152350453=？",
        "answer": 8.18284374989514
    },
    {
        "question": "2×947879=？",
        "answer": 6.277782897362556
    },
    {
        "question": "142805÷13371=？",
        "answer": 1.0285795247575271
    },
    {
        "question": "228981219÷52638=？",
        "answer": 3.6385004833000734
    },
    {
        "question": "3×6027=？",
        "answer": 4.257222446187574
    },
    {
        "question": "5338×77763=？",
        "answer": 8.618151576234851
    },
    {
        "question": "8380÷4375=？",
        "answer": 0.2822659612719445
    },
    {
        "question": "352232÷676=？",
        "answer": 2.716882112793872
    },
    {
        "question": "1×552019=？",
        "answer": 5.741954026013888
    },
    {
        "question": "64270×4618=？",
        "answer": 8.472462228491558
    },
    {
        "question": "337458536÷28465=？",
        "answer": 4.073909229930112
    },
    {
        "question": "117435317÷35659=？",
        "answer": 3.517629564527034
    },
    {
        "question": "30×285581=？",
        "answer": 6.932850564722806
    },
    {
        "question": "24052772÷975479=？",
        "answer": 1.391947210163726
    },
    {
        "question": "459752607÷58571=？",
        "answer": 3.894841561628952
    },
    {
        "question": "7978455÷490=？",
        "answer": 4.211722719851377
    },
    {
        "question": "52870138÷30814=？",
        "answer": 3.2344623657570377
    },
    {
        "question": "151185783÷1609285=？",
        "answer": 1.9728779902173885
    },
    {
        "question": "835×465=？",
        "answer": 5.589139428373556
    },
    {
        "question": "1587÷841=？",
        "answer": 0.275780930956936
    },
    {
        "question": "6135790÷532=？",
        "answer": 4.061958854988462
    },
    {
        "question": "580×6945=？",
        "answer": 6.6051002436365716
    },
    {
        "question": "1607098÷998=？",
        "answer": 3.2069118193350468
    },
    {
        "question": "2467803÷50108=？",
        "answer": 1.6924034190946171
    },
    {
        "question": "32168906÷16649039=？",
        "answer": 0.28604712103585195
    },
    {
        "question": "946945903÷46686=？",
        "answer": 4.307138503695389
    },
    {
        "question": "36×37260=？",
        "answer": 6.127545351327511
    },
    {
        "question": "9160585÷7570375=？",
        "answer": 0.08280581594344263
    },
    {
        "question": "345×1041=？",
        "answer": 5.55526982458381
    },
    {
        "question": "142605564÷921515=？",
        "answer": 2.189634061728758
    },
    {
        "question": "4×1407035=？",
        "answer": 6.750364891973661
    },
    {
        "question": "5×1535797=？",
        "answer": 6.8853038192462686
    },
    {
        "question": "503774623÷219829908=？",
        "answer": 0.3601495085359762
    },
    {
        "question": "435619129÷89958=？",
        "answer": 3.685067150957743
    },
    {
        "question": "126728075÷45738=？",
        "answer": 3.4425956678307723
    },
    {
        "question": "23×75515=？",
        "answer": 6.239761062748592
    },
    {
        "question": "78288055÷724664=？",
        "answer": 2.0335588166345913
    },
    {
        "question": "956369÷244=？",
        "answer": 3.593235663995916
    },
    {
        "question": "224360×1507=？",
        "answer": 8.52905868365211
    },
    {
        "question": "381×10002=？",
        "answer": 6.581011825887268
    },
    {
        "question": "393201×334=？",
        "answer": 8.118361080483183
    },
    {
        "question": "11×60126=？",
        "answer": 5.820454997673092
    },
    {
        "question": "4342096÷3838=？",
        "answer": 3.0535944507017603
    },
    {
        "question": "302816037÷440=？",
        "answer": 5.837726194989725
    },
    {
        "question": "2×2898747=？",
        "answer": 6.763240307845904
    },
    {
        "question": "70366÷42543=？",
        "answer": 0.21853475224093083
    },
    {
        "question": "2×34295930=？",
        "answer": 7.836272579747011
    },
    {
        "question": "23502031÷44704=？",
        "answer": 2.720759010347394
    },
    {
        "question": "7341880÷235=？",
        "answer": 4.494739419590085
    },
    {
        "question": "1675852÷23938=？",
        "answer": 1.8451477993709988
    },
    {
        "question": "46862×2879=？",
        "answer": 8.13006248457284
    },
    {
        "question": "379024460÷179750408=？",
        "answer": 0.32399735284947123
    },
    {
        "question": "2970×513=？",
        "answer": 6.182873814429029
    },
    {
        "question": "6396×38373=？",
        "answer": 8.389934208729503
    },
    {
        "question": "4892×43547=？",
        "answer": 8.328444689721174
    },
    {
        "question": "72×7229324=？",
        "answer": 8.716430185593637
    },
    {
        "question": "14601314÷12167=？",
        "answer": 3.0792084324762428
    },
    {
        "question": "177×81018=？",
        "answer": 7.156554784403592
    },
    {
        "question": "1208×1057=？",
        "answer": 6.106141921592539
    },
    {
        "question": "95×2877894=？",
        "answer": 8.436798399037153
    },
    {
        "question": "5097×31473=？",
        "answer": 8.205252775337277
    },
    {
        "question": "7865728÷485962=？",
        "answer": 1.2091366135046515
    },
    {
        "question": "63×2878=？",
        "answer": 5.258431339054168
    },
    {
        "question": "1521×15441=？",
        "answer": 7.370804637022831
    },
    {
        "question": "339134÷7368=？",
        "answer": 1.6630217151200342
    },
    {
        "question": "12908÷1177=？",
        "answer": 1.0400824938884328
    },
    {
        "question": "3835×207=？",
        "answer": 5.899735713741918
    },
    {
        "question": "371064774÷17977980=？",
        "answer": 1.3147088348182072
    },
    {
        "question": "34×254506=？",
        "answer": 6.937176942364053
    },
    {
        "question": "88×7760=？",
        "answer": 5.834344393408357
    },
    {
        "question": "1053850×298=？",
        "answer": 8.49699506393929
    },
    {
        "question": "4345418÷11910=？",
        "answer": 2.5621197975209937
    },
    {
        "question": "597274333÷5912=？",
        "answer": 5.004439426584516
    },
    {
        "question": "1414490÷896524=？",
        "answer": 0.19803796133574791
    },
    {
        "question": "546×191130=？",
        "answer": 8.018521502506442
    },
    {
        "question": "65462756÷11508080=？",
        "answer": 0.7549914129872258
    },
    {
        "question": "673150981÷1778=？",
        "answer": 5.578180726402936
    },
    {
        "question": "236076086÷572=？",
        "answer": 5.615655967416377
    },
    {
        "question": "79763777÷4799369=？",
        "answer": 1.2206215686484696
    },
    {
        "question": "78×8816491=？",
        "answer": 8.837390371205082
    },
    {
        "question": "20139×1775=？",
        "answer": 7.553236259295696
    },
    {
        "question": "12185082÷2167=？",
        "answer": 3.7499695448129637
    },
    {
        "question": "5×281=？",
        "answer": 3.1476763242410986
    },
    {
        "question": "3×760=？",
        "answer": 3.357934847000454
    },
    {
        "question": "272626511÷14678685=？",
        "answer": 1.2688809348633923
    },
    {
        "question": "646965÷1144=？",
        "answer": 2.752454762057108
    },
    {
        "question": "35734019÷10707669=？",
        "answer": 0.5233869263602381
    },
    {
        "question": "606642÷60701=？",
        "answer": 0.9997366289937505
    },
    {
        "question": "51743385÷127279=？",
        "answer": 2.6090980819100524
    },
    {
        "question": "624÷514=？",
        "answer": 0.08422147068714822
    },
    {
        "question": "223998941÷125204=？",
        "answer": 3.252627761248763
    },
    {
        "question": "3500686÷224=？",
        "answer": 4.193905139393728
    },
    {
        "question": "1610113÷38356=？",
        "answer": 1.6230230465446673
    },
    {
        "question": "131×7545=？",
        "answer": 5.994930539767373
    },
    {
        "question": "4141×5916=？",
        "answer": 7.3891333958272325
    },
    {
        "question": "38×2958=？",
        "answer": 5.050781766277684
    },
    {
        "question": "892164÷364=？",
        "answer": 3.389343311252078
    },
    {
        "question": "398162370÷62216992=？",
        "answer": 0.8061512023352689
    },
    {
        "question": "4312960÷89255=？",
        "answer": 1.6841428760297763
    },
    {
        "question": "34209÷9074=？",
        "answer": 0.5763416041124308
    },
    {
        "question": "83285535÷762726=？",
        "answer": 2.038201028872961
    },
    {
        "question": "8693095÷1339668=？",
        "answer": 0.812177242000531
    },
    {
        "question": "28003310÷411=？",
        "answer": 4.8333675462438075
    },
    {
        "question": "1256×3283=？",
        "answer": 6.615260522130518
    },
    {
        "question": "1526÷718=？",
        "answer": 0.3274300893765613
    },
    {
        "question": "63885539÷2051054=？",
        "answer": 1.4934254686795405
    },
    {
        "question": "3630÷519=？",
        "answer": 0.8447392671876547
    },
    {
        "question": "984÷231=？",
        "answer": 0.6293831185391972
    },
    {
        "question": "102321735÷2220=？",
        "answer": 4.663614921118256
    },
    {
        "question": "12431145÷10310=？",
        "answer": 3.0812524669204846
    },
    {
        "question": "124705374÷1061=？",
        "answer": 5.070169785280947
    },
    {
        "question": "341757×529=？",
        "answer": 8.257173090754897
    },
    {
        "question": "2×121387=？",
        "answer": 5.385202173914132
    },
    {
        "question": "20631×5726=？",
        "answer": 8.072371622747264
    },
    {
        "question": "115817×2021=？",
        "answer": 8.369338624757454
    },
    {
        "question": "31×911633=？",
        "answer": 7.4511817315564155
    },
    {
        "question": "54508×6423=？",
        "answer": 8.544198169261048
    },
    {
        "question": "3×1159082=？",
        "answer": 6.541235416211976
    },
    {
        "question": "918272573÷12666=？",
        "answer": 4.860332129295371
    },
    {
        "question": "9770×42430=？",
        "answer": 8.617567595485388
    },
    {
        "question": "6886398÷660743=？",
        "answer": 1.0179595483290695
    },
    {
        "question": "2717980÷295=？",
        "answer": 3.964424240715003
    },
    {
        "question": "3416262÷1055=？",
        "answer": 3.5102987105773256
    },
    {
        "question": "558835×1442=？",
        "answer": 8.906248858668176
    },
    {
        "question": "121×5551=？",
        "answer": 5.827156597648311
    },
    {
        "question": "10879430÷111034=？",
        "answer": 1.991150156650075
    },
    {
        "question": "49×2397188=？",
        "answer": 8.069898175038766
    },
    {
        "question": "10×18909=？",
        "answer": 5.276668561845278
    },
    {
        "question": "1×7945=？",
        "answer": 3.900093901543398
    },
    {
        "question": "2×289359=？",
        "answer": 5.762466990535486
    },
    {
        "question": "958×307=？",
        "answer": 5.468503884555731
    },
    {
        "question": "60×591=？",
        "answer": 4.549738731264899
    },
    {
        "question": "8407010÷460=？",
        "answer": 4.261883732322033
    },
    {
        "question": "6823×23130=？",
        "answer": 8.198151004050526
    },
    {
        "question": "1932231÷278187=？",
        "answer": 0.8417222144423776
    },
    {
        "question": "1500×1505=？",
        "answer": 6.353627758985543
    },
    {
        "question": "4×45719=？",
        "answer": 5.262156713942907
    },
    {
        "question": "118012166÷1002427=？",
        "answer": 2.0708740257905323
    },
    {
        "question": "271551÷19598=？",
        "answer": 1.1416396531106652
    },
    {
        "question": "3×21098350=？",
        "answer": 7.801369747272579
    },
    {
        "question": "7898×405=？",
        "answer": 6.504972152615194
    },
    {
        "question": "9×8031588=？",
        "answer": 7.859043931611313
    },
    {
        "question": "15662712÷1071=？",
        "answer": 4.16507749152994
    },
    {
        "question": "1433×650=？",
        "answer": 5.9691595470402
    },
    {
        "question": "408787÷2801=？",
        "answer": 2.164183967348987
    },
    {
        "question": "49659÷36340=？",
        "answer": 0.13561304680040354
    },
    {
        "question": "7×3574=？",
        "answer": 4.398252588183882
    },
    {
        "question": "684277907÷40363=？",
        "answer": 4.229249080417589
    },
    {
        "question": "1×740449=？",
        "answer": 5.8694951509310425
    },
    {
        "question": "539826÷208=？",
        "answer": 3.4141904629765234
    },
    {
        "question": "3650456÷217=？",
        "answer": 4.22588738428306
    },
    {
        "question": "551344606÷58935606=？",
        "answer": 0.9710453765901443
    },
    {
        "question": "1451594÷4549=？",
        "answer": 2.5039292275950387
    },
    {
        "question": "44×1150089=？",
        "answer": 7.704184126155707
    },
    {
        "question": "20942×7656=？",
        "answer": 8.205020080024054
    },
    {
        "question": "34×109256=？",
        "answer": 6.569924213442974
    },
    {
        "question": "7256×498=？",
        "answer": 6.5579266168117565
    },
    {
        "question": "102287÷203=？",
        "answer": 2.7023244033549276
    },
    {
        "question": "2580÷410=？",
        "answer": 0.7988358492434947
    },
    {
        "question": "3363419÷26453=？",
        "answer": 2.1043060412569807
    },
    {
        "question": "7888×2742=？",
        "answer": 7.335034352386649
    },
    {
        "question": "20×224598=？",
        "answer": 6.65243588030166
    },
    {
        "question": "79900282÷29961=？",
        "answer": 3.4259920075193477
    },
    {
        "question": "186×2466=？",
        "answer": 5.661506016477629
    },
    {
        "question": "242×28079=？",
        "answer": 6.832197002835092
    },
    {
        "question": "32177310÷24057134=？",
        "answer": 0.12630584731913966
    },
    {
        "question": "327×1066621=？",
        "answer": 8.54255788263
    },
    {
        "question": "2791×11155=？",
        "answer": 7.493229411108487
    },
    {
        "question": "1963÷1718=？",
        "answer": 0.057897140104782675
    },
    {
        "question": "620744÷479=？",
        "answer": 3.112577017019876
    },
    {
        "question": "5117÷468=？",
        "answer": 1.0387695638979932
    },
    {
        "question": "3743130÷17247=？",
        "answer": 2.336521347185127
    },
    {
        "question": "4968645÷3321973=？",
        "answer": 0.17484187004535195
    },
    {
        "question": "467556913÷771=？",
        "answer": 5.782780104531823
    },
    {
        "question": "87×230=？",
        "answer": 4.301247088636211
    },
    {
        "question": "9019×304=？",
        "answer": 6.4380319705345475
    },
    {
        "question": "85061×4264=？",
        "answer": 8.5595476801093
    },
    {
        "question": "7×501=？",
        "answer": 3.5449357658815024
    },
    {
        "question": "8×51513=？",
        "answer": 5.615006829932248
    },
    {
        "question": "8825035÷29484=？",
        "answer": 2.476130033943115
    },
    {
        "question": "336675470÷257062=？",
        "answer": 3.11717359294326
    },
    {
        "question": "2789×1400=？",
        "answer": 6.591576549944288
    },
    {
        "question": "4074939÷2460=？",
        "answer": 3.2191860048286456
    },
    {
        "question": "16×464860=？",
        "answer": 6.871442160530444
    },
    {
        "question": "455510711÷496=？",
        "answer": 5.9630169170548335
    },
    {
        "question": "818638674÷514=？",
        "answer": 6.202129138670501
    },
    {
        "question": "209081÷2766=？",
        "answer": 1.8784623928163935
    },
    {
        "question": "10618510÷3681=？",
        "answer": 3.4600977629356304
    },
    {
        "question": "3906028÷445474=？",
        "answer": 0.9429129905598889
    },
    {
        "question": "15130÷299=？",
        "answer": 1.7041677396987571
    },
    {
        "question": "19441286÷4141636=？",
        "answer": 0.6715530622307782
    },
    {
        "question": "2×495=？",
        "answer": 2.99563519459755
    },
    {
        "question": "1187×6723=？",
        "answer": 6.902013830209315
    },
    {
        "question": "38303109÷4521326=？",
        "answer": 0.9279682043780209
    },
    {
        "question": "6×2715689=？",
        "answer": 7.212031283548288
    },
    {
        "question": "41881÷1138=？",
        "answer": 1.5658747807972508
    },
    {
        "question": "6025÷1754=？",
        "answer": 0.5359274622168843
    },
    {
        "question": "4192×21904=？",
        "answer": 7.962944704765585
    },
    {
        "question": "3858×69095=？",
        "answer": 8.425808844474018
    },
    {
        "question": "484820×1468=？",
        "answer": 8.852306582807751
    },
    {
        "question": "1×878084=？",
        "answer": 5.943536063732411
    },
    {
        "question": "180898509÷267=？",
        "answer": 5.83092372597207
    },
    {
        "question": "292463÷299=？",
        "answer": 2.9903997422228654
    },
    {
        "question": "542×12008=？",
        "answer": 6.813469965773601
    },
    {
        "question": "14133÷691=？",
        "answer": 1.3107563115836978
    },
    {
        "question": "13×12639316=？",
        "answer": 8.215666924238695
    },
    {
        "question": "16471717÷270389=？",
        "answer": 1.7847498524704777
    },
    {
        "question": "53026×305=？",
        "answer": 7.20878870683028
    },
    {
        "question": "1×3848=？",
        "answer": 3.5852350633657752
    },
    {
        "question": "129062612÷111342=？",
        "answer": 3.0641414320846168
    },
    {
        "question": "1×485994390=？",
        "answer": 8.686631256081006
    },
    {
        "question": "495×484846=？",
        "answer": 8.380209015946683
    },
    {
        "question": "1×255=？",
        "answer": 2.406540180433955
    },
    {
        "question": "1351÷236=？",
        "answer": 0.757743346051924
    },
    {
        "question": "26831×33906=？",
        "answer": 8.958913416950152
    },
    {
        "question": "3404822÷1394299=？",
        "answer": 0.387738496559405
    },
    {
        "question": "286579÷249=？",
        "answer": 3.0610450158034563
    },
    {
        "question": "1×2636827=？",
        "answer": 6.421081637032714
    },
    {
        "question": "502901094÷8085589=？",
        "answer": 1.793770918517312
    },
    {
        "question": "22172315÷815=？",
        "answer": 4.434653431205255
    },
    {
        "question": "5×1808938=？",
        "answer": 6.956393686331647
    },
    {
        "question": "29×33052460=？",
        "answer": 8.981601786218855
    },
    {
        "question": "22701×1621=？",
        "answer": 7.565828003535745
    },
    {
        "question": "1547067÷14498=？",
        "answer": 2.0282010270098483
    },
    {
        "question": "3×222=？",
        "answer": 2.823474229170301
    },
    {
        "question": "1675013÷1106=？",
        "answer": 3.1802630550348447
    },
    {
        "question": "2036×144160=？",
        "answer": 8.467622547299708
    },
    {
        "question": "7×9154=？",
        "answer": 4.806708948105538
    },
    {
        "question": "4×1167=？",
        "answer": 3.6691308473733324
    },
    {
        "question": "4×71389=？",
        "answer": 5.455691289836163
    },
    {
        "question": "48236933÷39812734=？",
        "answer": 0.08335768444433257
    },
    {
        "question": "7191×127419=？",
        "answer": 8.962023481116148
    },
    {
        "question": "245650÷115740=？",
        "answer": 0.3268332904433124
    },
    {
        "question": "19315655÷758724=？",
        "answer": 1.4058256178857682
    },
    {
        "question": "824190509÷209950=？",
        "answer": 3.593911730107282
    },
    {
        "question": "60×69084=？",
        "answer": 6.617528725886403
    },
    {
        "question": "281184×404=？",
        "answer": 8.055371969831771
    },
    {
        "question": "3493027÷16688=？",
        "answer": 2.3207976515279056
    },
    {
        "question": "308673782÷21181577=？",
        "answer": 1.1635414522848861
    },
    {
        "question": "5688177÷1014=？",
        "answer": 3.7489351469521166
    },
    {
        "question": "143587516÷6956=？",
        "answer": 4.314757109138299
    },
    {
        "question": "438265594÷4065=？",
        "answer": 5.032676827813874
    },
    {
        "question": "240313520÷22696=？",
        "answer": 4.024828882041168
    },
    {
        "question": "4×119885=？",
        "answer": 5.680824838940963
    },
    {
        "question": "1916×864=？",
        "answer": 6.2189092472214185
    },
    {
        "question": "137226÷276=？",
        "answer": 2.6965273222118964
    },
    {
        "question": "280812754÷13316=？",
        "answer": 4.32404304227953
    },
    {
        "question": "535961÷467=？",
        "answer": 3.059816308191919
    },
    {
        "question": "11568016÷6789=？",
        "answer": 3.2314530719595798
    },
    {
        "question": "1330×469017=？",
        "answer": 8.79504022541434
    },
    {
        "question": "890468÷45051=？",
        "answer": 1.2959138817187916
    },
    {
        "question": "301863530÷563835=？",
        "answer": 2.7286586152321672
    },
    {
        "question": "25095×978=？",
        "answer": 7.389926054805677
    },
    {
        "question": "103×1318678=？",
        "answer": 8.132975985455882
    },
    {
        "question": "1915784÷601=？",
        "answer": 3.503472069850338
    },
    {
        "question": "66995443÷3332063=？",
        "answer": 1.303332059082065
    },
    {
        "question": "18838×2913=？",
        "answer": 7.739375277189063
    },
    {
        "question": "1228÷298=？",
        "answer": 0.6149821027288936
    },
    {
        "question": "6177×236=？",
        "answer": 6.1636896043078
    },
    {
        "question": "18×359834=？",
        "answer": 6.811374701674699
    },
    {
        "question": "3×19435=？",
        "answer": 4.765705799686947
    },
    {
        "question": "2224×5937=？",
        "answer": 7.120701831836079
    },
    {
        "question": "16067934÷105645=？",
        "answer": 2.1821110917247237
    },
    {
        "question": "743×44969=？",
        "answer": 7.523902043794368
    },
    {
        "question": "81218391÷10991313=？",
        "answer": 0.8686048060629823
    },
    {
        "question": "33×7434=？",
        "answer": 5.389736496637594
    },
    {
        "question": "72×929158=？",
        "answer": 7.825422066930446
    },
    {
        "question": "320850609÷650=？",
        "answer": 5.693389511310638
    },
    {
        "question": "158×26597=？",
        "answer": 6.623489740242554
    },
    {
        "question": "20702×370=？",
        "answer": 6.884214028316459
    },
    {
        "question": "45019÷2725=？",
        "answer": 1.2180293372436364
    },
    {
        "question": "1699×1221=？",
        "answer": 6.316909042813928
    },
    {
        "question": "317208593÷228583813=？",
        "answer": 0.14229947070137147
    },
    {
        "question": "39501×22824=？",
        "answer": 8.954999848933317
    },
    {
        "question": "3774021÷4189=？",
        "answer": 2.9546939520439373
    },
    {
        "question": "345÷296=？",
        "answer": 0.06652738401433556
    },
    {
        "question": "1393÷671=？",
        "answer": 0.3172285962549714
    },
    {
        "question": "919092152÷6542=？",
        "answer": 5.147648517950454
    },
    {
        "question": "86756÷19891=？",
        "answer": 0.6396429026917381
    },
    {
        "question": "11×6446=？",
        "answer": 4.850682986334541
    },
    {
        "question": "447992009÷500548=？",
        "answer": 2.9518245369572402
    },
    {
        "question": "4967÷2706=？",
        "answer": 0.26376636773361917
    },
    {
        "question": "127685685÷1256601=？",
        "answer": 2.0069448097107023
    },
    {
        "question": "224×17543=？",
        "answer": 6.59435188171067
    },
    {
        "question": "357508×390=？",
        "answer": 8.144350371532779
    },
    {
        "question": "520075×1752=？",
        "answer": 8.959600079577283
    },
    {
        "question": "37×503492=？",
        "answer": 7.270194298492963
    },
    {
        "question": "11366355÷127569=？",
        "answer": 1.9498760648835918
    },
    {
        "question": "532487417÷81917887=？",
        "answer": 0.8129306080592996
    },
    {
        "question": "92936252÷184739=？",
        "answer": 2.7016265655169938
    },
    {
        "question": "272376392÷260340928=？",
        "answer": 0.019627014171616757
    },
    {
        "question": "882954÷14563=？",
        "answer": 1.7826872288480047
    },
    {
        "question": "33247609÷1018860=？",
        "answer": 1.5136459061348924
    },
    {
        "question": "30×22589941=？",
        "answer": 8.831036351359021
    },
    {
        "question": "117906÷548=？",
        "answer": 2.3327553475487113
    },
    {
        "question": "1×71480514=？",
        "answer": 7.854187666756958
    },
    {
        "question": "39×824118=？",
        "answer": 7.507054006927314
    },
    {
        "question": "93159÷5018=？",
        "answer": 1.268694161046215
    },
    {
        "question": "37883420÷8283978=？",
        "answer": 0.6602102420322113
    },
    {
        "question": "7721÷591=？",
        "answer": 1.116086071573192
    },
    {
        "question": "27×180994=？",
        "answer": 6.689027942287388
    },
    {
        "question": "7×84937=？",
        "answer": 5.77419495753006
    },
    {
        "question": "7×10867509=？",
        "answer": 7.88122804854115
    },
    {
        "question": "4×6138=？",
        "answer": 4.3900868754237665
    },
    {
        "question": "87915÷4557=？",
        "answer": 1.2853839518548513
    },
    {
        "question": "55439767÷16338=？",
        "answer": 3.5306225046487762
    },
    {
        "question": "1×164376=？",
        "answer": 5.215838407921503
    },
    {
        "question": "224964274÷66572=？",
        "answer": 3.5288219498838016
    },
    {
        "question": "192683÷113785=？",
        "answer": 0.22875838564622744
    },
    {
        "question": "31028×11292=？",
        "answer": 8.544524652247029
    },
    {
        "question": "2259×1318=？",
        "answer": 6.473831641178354
    },
    {
        "question": "477987÷10035=？",
        "answer": 1.6778987082717944
    },
    {
        "question": "16×36765=？",
        "answer": 5.769554552963684
    },
    {
        "question": "2×2631186=？",
        "answer": 6.721181545353036
    },
    {
        "question": "134×579=？",
        "answer": 4.889783362092244
    },
    {
        "question": "2749707÷1113334=？",
        "answer": 0.3926609471136653
    },
    {
        "question": "943×588=？",
        "answer": 5.743889018813467
    },
    {
        "question": "1×65111980=？",
        "answer": 7.813660902073967
    },
    {
        "question": "13843231÷1693430=？",
        "answer": 0.9124702167083033
    },
    {
        "question": "123942×658=？",
        "answer": 7.9114443935118155
    },
    {
        "question": "254517372÷10430855=？",
        "answer": 1.3873975220235144
    },
    {
        "question": "1×2874=？",
        "answer": 3.4584867637982066
    },
    {
        "question": "29938÷215=？",
        "answer": 2.143784324134979
    },
    {
        "question": "392÷274=？",
        "answer": 0.15553550420006929
    },
    {
        "question": "712534÷562=？",
        "answer": 3.103069276844938
    },
    {
        "question": "68062160÷48932=？",
        "answer": 3.1433127605539717
    },
    {
        "question": "9388÷271=？",
        "answer": 1.5396037900521493
    },
    {
        "question": "24807619÷15163=？",
        "answer": 3.213799948332088
    },
    {
        "question": "24529×25405=？",
        "answer": 8.794599042465563
    },
    {
        "question": "934261÷235194=？",
        "answer": 0.5990419816181942
    },
    {
        "question": "1159212÷599=？",
        "answer": 3.286736045852627
    },
    {
        "question": "19657÷2507=？",
        "answer": 0.8943629037056527
    },
    {
        "question": "540979551÷76218702=？",
        "answer": 0.8511193006174007
    },
    {
        "question": "336390215÷10786709=？",
        "answer": 1.493954391797991
    },
    {
        "question": "19981956÷57818=？",
        "answer": 2.538574933543684
    },
    {
        "question": "3118384÷1533901=？",
        "answer": 0.30813226289692214
    },
    {
        "question": "115418688÷403=？",
        "answer": 5.4569710870996095
    },
    {
        "question": "104845260÷14204600=？",
        "answer": 0.8681197924706814
    },
    {
        "question": "9779644÷6816437=？",
        "answer": 0.1567656206682316
    },
    {
        "question": "1871079÷287071=？",
        "answer": 0.8141028023555222
    },
    {
        "question": "11456×6126=？",
        "answer": 7.846209997434334
    },
    {
        "question": "81675379÷7795848=？",
        "answer": 1.0202277955718801
    },
    {
        "question": "20×397=？",
        "answer": 3.8998205024270964
    },
    {
        "question": "156×249748=？",
        "answer": 7.590626617404867
    },
    {
        "question": "286×1533530=？",
        "answer": 8.642058309506899
    },
    {
        "question": "6634÷4615=？",
        "answer": 0.15760376182153263
    },
    {
        "question": "1576993×455=？",
        "answer": 8.855841162231975
    },
    {
        "question": "124×442859=？",
        "answer": 7.739687160213356
    },
    {
        "question": "4872×6857=？",
        "answer": 7.523841429090194
    },
    {
        "question": "2040138÷897807=？",
        "answer": 0.35647655800102085
    },
    {
        "question": "172×7090=？",
        "answer": 6.086174682090616
    },
    {
        "question": "1×29213=？",
        "answer": 4.465576158703925
    },
    {
        "question": "291×128044=？",
        "answer": 7.571252221708808
    },
    {
        "question": "1452158÷5962=？",
        "answer": 2.386621900035944
    },
    {
        "question": "26×1035709=？",
        "answer": 7.4302110981224745
    },
    {
        "question": "10×402=？",
        "answer": 3.60422605308447
    },
    {
        "question": "4332786÷4082=？",
        "answer": 3.0258942390087524
    },
    {
        "question": "8368÷4174=？",
        "answer": 0.3020692267937638
    },
    {
        "question": "598547235÷236267=？",
        "answer": 3.4036953620349935
    },
    {
        "question": "46775÷14062=？",
        "answer": 0.5219667025727122
    },
    {
        "question": "5363÷838=？",
        "answer": 0.8061637783327916
    },
    {
        "question": "97×430=？",
        "answer": 4.620240189845831
    },
    {
        "question": "15×6378=？",
        "answer": 4.9807757739626215
    },
    {
        "question": "3×68996753=？",
        "answer": 8.315949907958899
    },
    {
        "question": "293986799÷1575155=？",
        "answer": 2.271004533446689
    },
    {
        "question": "75×12912489=？",
        "answer": 8.98607122794909
    },
    {
        "question": "1×158267=？",
        "answer": 5.1993903702512325
    },
    {
        "question": "676×1399288=？",
        "answer": 8.975853805671717
    },
    {
        "question": "8165÷7692=？",
        "answer": 0.025916913506244706
    },
    {
        "question": "318458406÷270523856=？",
        "answer": 0.07084714781637674
    },
    {
        "question": "772002464÷2584=？",
        "answer": 5.475326177152451
    },
    {
        "question": "866395÷307773=？",
        "answer": 0.44948541947646964
    },
    {
        "question": "1545×72640=？",
        "answer": 8.050104319273881
    },
    {
        "question": "7061÷1916=？",
        "answer": 0.5664707067522537
    },
    {
        "question": "48587079÷6046=？",
        "answer": 3.9050526477150647
    },
    {
        "question": "300558261÷90479906=？",
        "answer": 0.521376528551163
    },
    {
        "question": "338706÷212=？",
        "answer": 3.203487029084085
    },
    {
        "question": "171728÷201=？",
        "answer": 2.931645054595898
    },
    {
        "question": "5×3467=？",
        "answer": 4.2389238459924155
    },
    {
        "question": "127534250÷4467343=？",
        "answer": 1.455577533892931
    },
    {
        "question": "10013507÷1104=？",
        "answer": 3.9576171323585343
    },
    {
        "question": "34940×673=？",
        "answer": 7.3713379648708885
    },
    {
        "question": "197772×332=？",
        "answer": 7.817302889133755
    },
    {
        "question": "59×405191=？",
        "answer": 7.378511801998339
    },
    {
        "question": "13310÷3254=？",
        "answer": 0.6117605068738351
    },
    {
        "question": "1479×953=？",
        "answer": 6.149061074635219
    },
    {
        "question": "80660633÷3865=？",
        "answer": 4.319512127641015
    },
    {
        "question": "188×2877=？",
        "answer": 5.733097711154006
    },
    {
        "question": "105×192840=？",
        "answer": 7.306386421880908
    },
    {
        "question": "1×234=？",
        "answer": 2.369215857410143
    },
    {
        "question": "5627÷307=？",
        "answer": 1.2631385396768062
    },
    {
        "question": "901765630÷3515017=？",
        "answer": 2.4091662487563776
    },
    {
        "question": "884488÷563635=？",
        "answer": 0.19569399151188174
    },
    {
        "question": "7712586÷2242923=？",
        "answer": 0.5363856552929915
    },
    {
        "question": "2×7000740=？",
        "answer": 7.146173944382622
    },
    {
        "question": "22×21148=？",
        "answer": 5.66769198255528
    },
    {
        "question": "9×18756583=？",
        "answer": 8.22739623263964
    },
    {
        "question": "648746648÷1760=？",
        "answer": 5.566562459098065
    },
    {
        "question": "40363183÷48483=？",
        "answer": 2.9203959219559246
    },
    {
        "question": "794494977÷4721=？",
        "answer": 5.226057155400277
    },
    {
        "question": "707957÷47298=？",
        "answer": 1.175164103299961
    },
    {
        "question": "23311759÷8650=？",
        "answer": 3.4305589371914045
    },
    {
        "question": "664395949÷2561695=？",
        "answer": 2.413899555170783
    },
    {
        "question": "797288÷7720=？",
        "answer": 2.01399792723059
    },
    {
        "question": "5326÷1333=？",
        "answer": 0.6015710126890632
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1441=？",
        "answer": 3.1586639808139894
    },
    {
        "question": "1×8547135=？",
        "answer": 6.931820563593167
    },
    {
        "question": "256008÷5346=？",
        "answer": 1.6802245823818371
    },
    {
        "question": "12×4516=？",
        "answer": 4.7339351793005555
    },
    {
        "question": "174419×4160=？",
        "answer": 8.860687122838566
    },
    {
        "question": "8×44676=？",
        "answer": 5.553164269257961
    },
    {
        "question": "52×88556=？",
        "answer": 6.663221335232199
    },
    {
        "question": "519755×353=？",
        "answer": 8.263573381288328
    },
    {
        "question": "24984886÷11666=？",
        "answer": 3.3307554001083077
    },
    {
        "question": "23×1447032=？",
        "answer": 7.5222059713313465
    },
    {
        "question": "6224×9746=？",
        "answer": 7.782895991026908
    },
    {
        "question": "452621÷1178=？",
        "answer": 2.5845894093500057
    },
    {
        "question": "16×252427=？",
        "answer": 6.60625578855241
    },
    {
        "question": "981868681÷5609=？",
        "answer": 5.243167967399955
    },
    {
        "question": "5×33514=？",
        "answer": 5.22419626966024
    },
    {
        "question": "120822084÷5362504=？",
        "answer": 1.3527786932455206
    },
    {
        "question": "2×199477743=？",
        "answer": 8.600924441393428
    },
    {
        "question": "663335697÷12892=？",
        "answer": 4.711413072375719
    },
    {
        "question": "23842100÷6869689=？",
        "answer": 0.5404074287761474
    },
    {
        "question": "184608663÷11263357=？",
        "answer": 1.2145842273980445
    },
    {
        "question": "47×24504=？",
        "answer": 6.061334841734234
    },
    {
        "question": "409×369=？",
        "answer": 5.1787496741664025
    },
    {
        "question": "11×23129=？",
        "answer": 5.405549541280756
    },
    {
        "question": "1818÷1016=？",
        "answer": 0.2527001709380482
    },
    {
        "question": "15340×2229=？",
        "answer": 7.5339354280932
    },
    {
        "question": "90518931÷296240=？",
        "answer": 2.485095717390857
    },
    {
        "question": "1146÷687=？",
        "answer": 0.22222788057182072
    },
    {
        "question": "3186873÷2521=？",
        "answer": 3.1017919110830774
    },
    {
        "question": "17×47172278=？",
        "answer": 8.904135770677646
    },
    {
        "question": "2869047÷54601=？",
        "answer": 1.720537066062995
    },
    {
        "question": "54388313÷27923=？",
        "answer": 3.2895435118870395
    },
    {
        "question": "1132÷718=？",
        "answer": 0.19772198260995227
    },
    {
        "question": "2×16705749=？",
        "answer": 7.523895947609083
    },
    {
        "question": "6688624÷1093=？",
        "answer": 3.7867166208896244
    },
    {
        "question": "48603870÷38159=？",
        "answer": 3.105073865593922
    },
    {
        "question": "107×16298=？",
        "answer": 6.241518091153226
    },
    {
        "question": "905244259÷1195474=？",
        "answer": 2.879225644014466
    },
    {
        "question": "751169÷13986=？",
        "answer": 1.7300441328209
    },
    {
        "question": "641433495÷1458=？",
        "answer": 5.643394110615545
    },
    {
        "question": "1767÷704=？",
        "answer": 0.39966389036465183
    },
    {
        "question": "1970×5899=？",
        "answer": 7.065244622330741
    },
    {
        "question": "347253865÷540670=？",
        "answer": 2.8077148155430125
    },
    {
        "question": "7181789÷737956=？",
        "answer": 0.9882021733085152
    },
    {
        "question": "40640506÷6239689=？",
        "answer": 0.8137961625330725
    },
    {
        "question": "23921×28131=？",
        "answer": 8.827964501788376
    },
    {
        "question": "27×1300404=？",
        "answer": 7.545442060860696
    },
    {
        "question": "18896953÷17036=？",
        "answer": 3.0450241515034575
    },
    {
        "question": "35017244÷58028=？",
        "answer": 2.7806443599676256
    },
    {
        "question": "152240×209=？",
        "answer": 7.502675061390018
    },
    {
        "question": "678×671933=？",
        "answer": 8.658555664568299
    },
    {
        "question": "2×1233=？",
        "answer": 3.3919930722597127
    },
    {
        "question": "910556585÷53100=？",
        "answer": 4.234212418384638
    },
    {
        "question": "87327007÷14249=？",
        "answer": 3.7873641891630623
    },
    {
        "question": "50577÷490=？",
        "answer": 2.0137569853498696
    },
    {
        "question": "379620314÷897951=？",
        "answer": 2.6260968056286003
    },
    {
        "question": "84040÷75356=？",
        "answer": 0.04736820628498431
    },
    {
        "question": "2859514÷5451=？",
        "answer": 2.7198160451385625
    },
    {
        "question": "336978×602=？",
        "answer": 8.30719803963515
    },
    {
        "question": "84×32951=？",
        "answer": 6.442147885201071
    },
    {
        "question": "803÷648=？",
        "answer": 0.09314053940808763
    },
    {
        "question": "12×4930=？",
        "answer": 4.772028165324855
    },
    {
        "question": "2399178÷494190=？",
        "answer": 0.6861685172243062
    },
    {
        "question": "170295÷37557=？",
        "answer": 0.6565110027587939
    },
    {
        "question": "9931274÷1463174=？",
        "answer": 0.8317089887697485
    },
    {
        "question": "16760923÷202=？",
        "answer": 4.918946561480651
    },
    {
        "question": "20405×910=？",
        "answer": 7.268777991430383
    },
    {
        "question": "308×18596=？",
        "answer": 6.757970254011494
    },
    {
        "question": "69890÷56994=？",
        "answer": 0.08858590241618693
    },
    {
        "question": "3567933÷40191=？",
        "answer": 1.9482878783430597
    },
    {
        "question": "12×8673169=？",
        "answer": 8.017359054913717
    },
    {
        "question": "1×7175967=？",
        "answer": 6.8558804328578224
    },
    {
        "question": "2767÷864=？",
        "answer": 0.5054954166620587
    },
    {
        "question": "21497567÷105123=？",
        "answer": 2.3106915648713278
    },
    {
        "question": "5024333÷133270=？",
        "answer": 1.5763460178956237
    },
    {
        "question": "917210÷13599=？",
        "answer": 1.8289618072568126
    },
    {
        "question": "2857×91674=？",
        "answer": 8.418156421662227
    },
    {
        "question": "156×422=？",
        "answer": 4.8184370493161355
    },
    {
        "question": "34×20928541=？",
        "answer": 8.8522178702861
    },
    {
        "question": "4631÷897=？",
        "answer": 0.7128823379498013
    },
    {
        "question": "137233268÷6482=？",
        "answer": 4.325750378824919
    },
    {
        "question": "388×904452=？",
        "answer": 8.545217249041801
    },
    {
        "question": "4031833÷2233108=？",
        "answer": 0.25659280777159915
    },
    {
        "question": "1×69979=？",
        "answer": 4.844967732122525
    },
    {
        "question": "112×13234=？",
        "answer": 6.170909152977758
    },
    {
        "question": "269749×439=？",
        "answer": 8.073424363605273
    },
    {
        "question": "1×946=？",
        "answer": 2.975891136401793
    },
    {
        "question": "1136814÷27946=？",
        "answer": 1.6093697586225626
    },
    {
        "question": "786273765÷60374739=？",
        "answer": 1.1147185188250672
    },
    {
        "question": "732467×476=？",
        "answer": 8.542395015820711
    },
    {
        "question": "3×788=？",
        "answer": 3.3736474722092176
    },
    {
        "question": "44×151587=？",
        "answer": 6.824114634574115
    },
    {
        "question": "2664932÷288=？",
        "answer": 3.9662936440267957
    },
    {
        "question": "2098326÷529=？",
        "answer": 3.5984172898978817
    },
    {
        "question": "94669300÷9969=？",
        "answer": 3.977557569887766
    },
    {
        "question": "1774×34203=？",
        "answer": 7.783017815888248
    },
    {
        "question": "2×429225=？",
        "answer": 5.93371500496407
    },
    {
        "question": "252×43307=？",
        "answer": 7.0379586407299985
    },
    {
        "question": "5×2730904=？",
        "answer": 7.135276437905609
    },
    {
        "question": "214×463639=？",
        "answer": 7.996593733799523
    },
    {
        "question": "610753÷270=？",
        "answer": 3.3545018447328987
    },
    {
        "question": "289174464÷135950=？",
        "answer": 3.3277807273437126
    },
    {
        "question": "3×5470746=？",
        "answer": 7.21516780620721
    },
    {
        "question": "2×10656=？",
        "answer": 4.328624207490207
    },
    {
        "question": "1×31140=？",
        "answer": 4.4933186082321015
    },
    {
        "question": "54980531÷8079049=？",
        "answer": 0.8328486877625455
    },
    {
        "question": "6490×2651=？",
        "answer": 7.235654424533463
    },
    {
        "question": "690987850÷165173071=？",
        "answer": 0.621531167482058
    },
    {
        "question": "329563679÷11237539=？",
        "answer": 1.467268130380725
    },
    {
        "question": "49×47164=？",
        "answer": 6.363806710723408
    },
    {
        "question": "243270÷528=？",
        "answer": 2.663454632604238
    },
    {
        "question": "1×8944=？",
        "answer": 3.951531790542348
    },
    {
        "question": "61479÷1575=？",
        "answer": 1.5914462366485107
    },
    {
        "question": "182×445252=？",
        "answer": 7.908677266905338
    },
    {
        "question": "2×567=？",
        "answer": 3.0546130545568877
    },
    {
        "question": "106×38043=？",
        "answer": 6.605580622533114
    },
    {
        "question": "2815÷648=？",
        "answer": 0.6379033933167717
    },
    {
        "question": "646458669÷4730=？",
        "answer": 5.135679622973535
    },
    {
        "question": "82928÷33946=？",
        "answer": 0.3879125846101015
    },
    {
        "question": "1821÷1402=？",
        "answer": 0.11356193216428019
    },
    {
        "question": "219×11395=？",
        "answer": 6.397158444356513
    },
    {
        "question": "47×1039=？",
        "answer": 4.688713405492895
    },
    {
        "question": "44389167÷62336=？",
        "answer": 2.8525380643386278
    },
    {
        "question": "39201÷1449=？",
        "answer": 1.4322287603488368
    },
    {
        "question": "154×589=？",
        "answer": 4.957636015623565
    },
    {
        "question": "19949325÷64443=？",
        "answer": 2.490752455772119
    },
    {
        "question": "62×2073288=？",
        "answer": 8.109051323537695
    },
    {
        "question": "159948×5768=？",
        "answer": 8.965004065719532
    },
    {
        "question": "195989961÷9737=？",
        "answer": 4.303808656483016
    },
    {
        "question": "33×6992=？",
        "answer": 5.363115359504234
    },
    {
        "question": "29079÷1183=？",
        "answer": 1.3905947228290385
    },
    {
        "question": "1160×332=？",
        "answer": 5.585596072930954
    },
    {
        "question": "2153947÷33296=？",
        "answer": 1.8108429499798688
    },
    {
        "question": "31803674÷6443=？",
        "answer": 3.6933891617752006
    },
    {
        "question": "632222÷2795=？",
        "answer": 2.3544877920814384
    },
    {
        "question": "117502÷70526=？",
        "answer": 0.22169600598587622
    },
    {
        "question": "18×1009=？",
        "answer": 4.259163671340216
    },
    {
        "question": "650274÷1285=？",
        "answer": 2.7041932622282303
    },
    {
        "question": "49×181026=？",
        "answer": 6.947937035260153
    },
    {
        "question": "345337938÷5133=？",
        "answer": 4.827873027262743
    },
    {
        "question": "4×1425=？",
        "answer": 3.7558748556724915
    },
    {
        "question": "217×883=？",
        "answer": 5.282420437426098
    },
    {
        "question": "1×503565=？",
        "answer": 5.702055537092897
    },
    {
        "question": "2×60291=？",
        "answer": 5.081282482894406
    },
    {
        "question": "273÷260=？",
        "answer": 0.021189299069938092
    },
    {
        "question": "15472÷13168=？",
        "answer": 0.0700266388707318
    },
    {
        "question": "98073×2071=？",
        "answer": 8.30772955922987
    },
    {
        "question": "7397×26234=？",
        "answer": 8.287920132909637
    },
    {
        "question": "415686÷1220=？",
        "answer": 2.5324055673577295
    },
    {
        "question": "18×627317=？",
        "answer": 7.052759561979319
    },
    {
        "question": "20870553÷555742=？",
        "answer": 1.5746607368986723
    },
    {
        "question": "98534÷35031=？",
        "answer": 0.4491335784583314
    },
    {
        "question": "207135125÷214029=？",
        "answer": 2.9857811284010496
    },
    {
        "question": "434507851÷2539=？",
        "answer": 5.233334927126552
    },
    {
        "question": "2×15329=？",
        "answer": 4.486543819882519
    },
    {
        "question": "4406÷317=？",
        "answer": 1.1429852305969974
    },
    {
        "question": "2124470÷350=？",
        "answer": 3.783182558372764
    },
    {
        "question": "55497÷54289=？",
        "answer": 0.009557665058745548
    },
    {
        "question": "84710×11338=？",
        "answer": 8.98247113439613
    },
    {
        "question": "68×6914=？",
        "answer": 5.6722382879126245
    },
    {
        "question": "1×17969=？",
        "answer": 4.2545239086857
    },
    {
        "question": "90411÷21075=？",
        "answer": 0.6324536895311706
    },
    {
        "question": "82359221÷181557=？",
        "answer": 2.656699232200489
    },
    {
        "question": "58125×3125=？",
        "answer": 8.259212987578104
    },
    {
        "question": "30×87774=？",
        "answer": 6.420487145013635
    },
    {
        "question": "1497061×257=？",
        "answer": 8.585172620016138
    },
    {
        "question": "503796÷136232=？",
        "answer": 0.5679755825238787
    },
    {
        "question": "118070820÷43361013=？",
        "answer": 0.43504315978192765
    },
    {
        "question": "150799753÷766=？",
        "answer": 5.294171860556158
    },
    {
        "question": "584001851÷37037=？",
        "answer": 4.197778422069189
    },
    {
        "question": "100493÷64103=？",
        "answer": 0.19525745649812498
    },
    {
        "question": "40150556÷94889=？",
        "answer": 2.6264756939224
    },
    {
        "question": "13×20419=？",
        "answer": 5.4239778214428265
    },
    {
        "question": "990÷383=？",
        "answer": 0.41243642062892716
    },
    {
        "question": "245999478÷81996=？",
        "answer": 3.477141518780384
    },
    {
        "question": "287788315÷40191=？",
        "answer": 3.854944344312781
    },
    {
        "question": "780596546÷59837=？",
        "answer": 4.1154568137483745
    },
    {
        "question": "1×457243=？",
        "answer": 5.660147065521569
    },
    {
        "question": "116774÷14149=？",
        "answer": 0.9166204102869938
    },
    {
        "question": "6452943÷45541=？",
        "answer": 2.151355266198902
    },
    {
        "question": "37506×1556=？",
        "answer": 7.766110341940117
    },
    {
        "question": "302134659÷65506771=？",
        "answer": 0.6639143552308623
    },
    {
        "question": "182334771÷695=？",
        "answer": 5.418884691346718
    },
    {
        "question": "7×70150=？",
        "answer": 5.691125715378636
    },
    {
        "question": "44×9827=？",
        "answer": 5.635873632538211
    },
    {
        "question": "11163839÷1630=？",
        "answer": 3.8356259602528566
    },
    {
        "question": "299×2277221=？",
        "answer": 8.833076368444647
    },
    {
        "question": "77569468÷565=？",
        "answer": 5.137642365083344
    },
    {
        "question": "20154650÷57701=？",
        "answer": 2.5431919208604095
    },
    {
        "question": "4617×1402=？",
        "answer": 6.811107888181781
    },
    {
        "question": "5815079÷10474=？",
        "answer": 2.7444430495903185
    },
    {
        "question": "131202127÷20213578=？",
        "answer": 0.81229768104786
    },
    {
        "question": "1072÷583=？",
        "answer": 0.26452623059773717
    },
    {
        "question": "75442×300=？",
        "answer": 7.354734447935816
    },
    {
        "question": "3038×361=？",
        "answer": 6.040094971432425
    },
    {
        "question": "171033÷106521=？",
        "answer": 0.20564467865738345
    },
    {
        "question": "6876×3217=？",
        "answer": 7.344786928916984
    },
    {
        "question": "2×245=？",
        "answer": 2.690196080028514
    },
    {
        "question": "8106830÷7554=？",
        "answer": 3.0306740854780307
    },
    {
        "question": "11×40059174=？",
        "answer": 8.644094675274534
    },
    {
        "question": "1×417=？",
        "answer": 2.6201360549737576
    },
    {
        "question": "2111409÷19722=？",
        "answer": 2.0296214139622473
    },
    {
        "question": "3×1216=？",
        "answer": 3.5620548296563785
    },
    {
        "question": "57001383÷40099651=？",
        "answer": 0.15274480006644162
    },
    {
        "question": "1×55661=？",
        "answer": 4.74555100455966
    },
    {
        "question": "9×15428=？",
        "answer": 5.142552139633329
    },
    {
        "question": "84356603÷5476=？",
        "answer": 4.187655643126841
    },
    {
        "question": "72851×13183=？",
        "answer": 8.982449769632273
    },
    {
        "question": "382÷229=？",
        "answer": 0.22222788057182072
    },
    {
        "question": "4×762457=？",
        "answer": 6.484275347295237
    },
    {
        "question": "6166643÷482843=？",
        "answer": 1.106242867310931
    },
    {
        "question": "4166032÷1103393=？",
        "answer": 0.5769923770774595
    },
    {
        "question": "16426÷2072=？",
        "answer": 0.8991420674180999
    },
    {
        "question": "213617177÷3847631=？",
        "answer": 1.744442756320494
    },
    {
        "question": "506746÷92081=？",
        "answer": 0.7406203021876755
    },
    {
        "question": "348829138÷1256=？",
        "answer": 5.443623115368754
    },
    {
        "question": "801289822÷594500332=？",
        "answer": 0.1296375248710461
    },
    {
        "question": "76726521÷1112=？",
        "answer": 4.838840719246672
    },
    {
        "question": "1×460841=？",
        "answer": 5.663551110349294
    },
    {
        "question": "605826÷596670=？",
        "answer": 0.006613705365405442
    },
    {
        "question": "4478×84608=？",
        "answer": 8.57849551837652
    },
    {
        "question": "15100274÷2587094=？",
        "answer": 0.7661726190497092
    },
    {
        "question": "53598024÷51393=？",
        "answer": 3.0182448090352665
    },
    {
        "question": "358573389÷1444=？",
        "answer": 5.395010862658214
    },
    {
        "question": "1×31752=？",
        "answer": 4.501771085899107
    },
    {
        "question": "66594137÷14867223=？",
        "answer": 0.6512061395768136
    },
    {
        "question": "5288407÷35056=？",
        "answer": 2.1785625111951914
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1383=？",
        "answer": 3.1408221801093106
    },
    {
        "question": "3×2256170=？",
        "answer": 6.830493074889277
    },
    {
        "question": "2×194410=？",
        "answer": 5.589748595930788
    },
    {
        "question": "1317459÷6213=？",
        "answer": 2.326435755014678
    },
    {
        "question": "110055÷35110=？",
        "answer": 0.49617894866510404
    },
    {
        "question": "1106÷653=？",
        "answer": 0.22884194569360553
    },
    {
        "question": "3944047÷166953=？",
        "answer": 1.3733478543002327
    },
    {
        "question": "2×6206=？",
        "answer": 4.093841766912128
    },
    {
        "question": "276×341668=？",
        "answer": 7.974513387541756
    },
    {
        "question": "100961÷442=？",
        "answer": 2.358731374178652
    },
    {
        "question": "3749÷790=？",
        "answer": 0.6762883491311092
    },
    {
        "question": "8×89805959=？",
        "answer": 8.856395141865871
    },
    {
        "question": "461×56508=？",
        "answer": 7.415810861879995
    },
    {
        "question": "169520×300=？",
        "answer": 7.7063421984224005
    },
    {
        "question": "229370639÷11356=？",
        "answer": 4.3053124406252214
    },
    {
        "question": "356419×492=？",
        "answer": 8.243925950138971
    },
    {
        "question": "31×90925=？",
        "answer": 6.450045003561022
    },
    {
        "question": "790094÷164566=？",
        "answer": 0.6813386506116434
    },
    {
        "question": "847×3576=？",
        "answer": 6.481280920454587
    },
    {
        "question": "828÷633=？",
        "answer": 0.11662662676752503
    },
    {
        "question": "1×10706270=？",
        "answer": 7.02963819160033
    },
    {
        "question": "3×193666697=？",
        "answer": 8.764176200412352
    },
    {
        "question": "8×79595791=？",
        "answer": 8.80398008998333
    },
    {
        "question": "190×342=？",
        "answer": 4.812779707008964
    },
    {
        "question": "5×2821469=？",
        "answer": 7.149445287294764
    },
    {
        "question": "50×288=？",
        "answer": 4.158362492095249
    },
    {
        "question": "579466÷230007=？",
        "answer": 0.40128690546940815
    },
    {
        "question": "730471÷1569=？",
        "answer": 2.667980035355554
    },
    {
        "question": "513×534730=？",
        "answer": 8.438251915153753
    },
    {
        "question": "18×31440368=？",
        "answer": 8.752760125786008
    },
    {
        "question": "285330642÷5625=？",
        "answer": 4.705225886783689
    },
    {
        "question": "1449×50493=？",
        "answer": 7.864299560182111
    },
    {
        "question": "173187÷1379=？",
        "answer": 2.0989510231212005
    },
    {
        "question": "141×278811=？",
        "answer": 7.594529016747997
    },
    {
        "question": "8514733÷2396509=？",
        "answer": 0.5505919698530954
    },
    {
        "question": "39275503÷533=？",
        "answer": 4.86739454671537
    },
    {
        "question": "4583×7230=？",
        "answer": 7.520288154539317
    },
    {
        "question": "15401409÷1345272=？",
        "answer": 1.0587503511019472
    },
    {
        "question": "124×4094531=？",
        "answer": 8.705625848700219
    },
    {
        "question": "5×4757=？",
        "answer": 4.37630315575592
    },
    {
        "question": "21×6293077=？",
        "answer": 8.12108234039695
    },
    {
        "question": "72335÷836=？",
        "answer": 1.9371422083598642
    },
    {
        "question": "1893÷250=？",
        "answer": 0.8792106052917591
    },
    {
        "question": "191×922=？",
        "answer": 5.245764288301356
    },
    {
        "question": "560×266=？",
        "answer": 5.173069663637268
    },
    {
        "question": "284997÷262630=？",
        "answer": 0.03549595478974416
    },
    {
        "question": "2×35172995=？",
        "answer": 7.847239345971073
    },
    {
        "question": "14802÷3877=？",
        "answer": 0.5818245988661697
    },
    {
        "question": "33×669=？",
        "answer": 4.34394005764571
    },
    {
        "question": "79075780÷24771176=？",
        "answer": 0.5040968594677089
    },
    {
        "question": "36698001÷154121=？",
        "answer": 2.37678058993715
    },
    {
        "question": "232619082÷131378108=？",
        "answer": 0.24812233428628114
    },
    {
        "question": "1305044÷235189=？",
        "answer": 0.7442081487690039
    },
    {
        "question": "20186735÷656175=？",
        "answer": 1.4880464019657271
    },
    {
        "question": "217201266÷292177=？",
        "answer": 2.8712163267543946
    },
    {
        "question": "4×20867029=？",
        "answer": 7.921520610936993
    },
    {
        "question": "736×303951=？",
        "answer": 8.349681390890883
    },
    {
        "question": "9×586=？",
        "answer": 3.7221401254574156
    },
    {
        "question": "393580164÷333056=？",
        "answer": 3.072515940481335
    },
    {
        "question": "2035÷1799=？",
        "answer": 0.053533250215687465
    },
    {
        "question": "395532610÷27486442=？",
        "answer": 1.1580637691073372
    },
    {
        "question": "2×60233341=？",
        "answer": 8.08086694878346
    },
    {
        "question": "18099443÷2354=？",
        "answer": 3.8858587514032834
    },
    {
        "question": "3282616÷26584=？",
        "answer": 2.091599753716991
    },
    {
        "question": "273631371÷152813=？",
        "answer": 3.2530055846310377
    },
    {
        "question": "70669×299=？",
        "answer": 7.324900134208918
    },
    {
        "question": "1330×411048=？",
        "answer": 8.737744180405038
    },
    {
        "question": "18×827=？",
        "answer": 4.172778014655853
    },
    {
        "question": "184706732÷10722=？",
        "answer": 4.2362069215556755
    },
    {
        "question": "1501÷574=？",
        "answer": 0.4174687998452969
    },
    {
        "question": "363956879÷21686285=？",
        "answer": 1.2248647712659795
    },
    {
        "question": "769×34385=？",
        "answer": 7.422295368479473
    },
    {
        "question": "136044654÷28878188=？",
        "answer": 0.6731115410770113
    },
    {
        "question": "13×4978662=？",
        "answer": 7.811055995449621
    },
    {
        "question": "23137÷902=？",
        "answer": 1.4091005090396669
    },
    {
        "question": "6×6002=？",
        "answer": 4.556447241472477
    },
    {
        "question": "27900÷3763=？",
        "answer": 0.8700699849537332
    },
    {
        "question": "872785541÷26585683=？",
        "answer": 1.516259720856924
    },
    {
        "question": "197380÷2897=？",
        "answer": 1.8333546494333897
    },
    {
        "question": "2965895÷262936=？",
        "answer": 1.0523057200679242
    },
    {
        "question": "486156499÷1808=？",
        "answer": 5.429577669689516
    },
    {
        "question": "76193÷244=？",
        "answer": 2.4945252473497264
    },
    {
        "question": "1003÷224=？",
        "answer": 0.6510529146862553
    },
    {
        "question": "1451×7823=？",
        "answer": 7.055040742683761
    },
    {
        "question": "58×6558809=？",
        "answer": 8.580252977498386
    },
    {
        "question": "9×62477=？",
        "answer": 5.749962676999895
    },
    {
        "question": "61190÷5333=？",
        "answer": 1.0597088695137722
    },
    {
        "question": "4799313÷3185898=？",
        "answer": 0.17794720725315416
    },
    {
        "question": "61×554994=？",
        "answer": 7.529618123032584
    },
    {
        "question": "305×8805=？",
        "answer": 6.429029199650081
    },
    {
        "question": "49836063÷11618=？",
        "answer": 3.632412354028752
    },
    {
        "question": "1×2612=？",
        "answer": 3.4169731726030363
    },
    {
        "question": "24717990÷359=？",
        "answer": 4.837918703623253
    },
    {
        "question": "4150÷681=？",
        "answer": 0.7849009847993076
    },
    {
        "question": "460544603÷893=？",
        "answer": 5.712420238399433
    },
    {
        "question": "335174521÷698=？",
        "answer": 5.681415574776387
    },
    {
        "question": "73×26297=？",
        "answer": 6.28322906649005
    },
    {
        "question": "2×26201371=？",
        "answer": 7.719354012256881
    },
    {
        "question": "8×82263560=？",
        "answer": 8.8182974869001
    },
    {
        "question": "15×1560456=？",
        "answer": 7.369342786477662
    },
    {
        "question": "154529707÷847=？",
        "answer": 5.261128570815164
    },
    {
        "question": "622734634÷28771710=？",
        "answer": 1.3353373458616744
    },
    {
        "question": "92×14484=？",
        "answer": 6.124676343490529
    },
    {
        "question": "3121×105972=？",
        "answer": 8.519484899478723
    },
    {
        "question": "89×814768=？",
        "answer": 7.8604239703992445
    },
    {
        "question": "30×14037=？",
        "answer": 5.624395554631505
    },
    {
        "question": "4×158430134=？",
        "answer": 8.80189778086198
    },
    {
        "question": "23519÷15543=？",
        "answer": 0.1798840051033285
    },
    {
        "question": "30781÷15143=？",
        "answer": 0.3080708025496128
    },
    {
        "question": "84643507÷49047=？",
        "answer": 3.2369812004605283
    },
    {
        "question": "54×6398051=？",
        "answer": 8.538441457423245
    },
    {
        "question": "405450855÷106209706=？",
        "answer": 0.5817740139131342
    },
    {
        "question": "2×44994=？",
        "answer": 4.954184599647665
    },
    {
        "question": "27×1891564=？",
        "answer": 7.70818480414494
    },
    {
        "question": "759992587÷1119=？",
        "answer": 5.831979269646263
    },
    {
        "question": "528202100÷99013728=？",
        "answer": 0.7271047109303465
    },
    {
        "question": "1296×29542=？",
        "answer": 7.583044895339256
    },
    {
        "question": "5×129040638=？",
        "answer": 8.809696505951846
    },
    {
        "question": "1174×3380=？",
        "answer": 6.59858479718925
    },
    {
        "question": "126×6800=？",
        "answer": 5.932879457823799
    },
    {
        "question": "393034520÷209570105=？",
        "answer": 0.27310136490400777
    },
    {
        "question": "15095228÷82628=？",
        "answer": 2.261712436198559
    },
    {
        "question": "45066÷8410=？",
        "answer": 0.7290530165659393
    },
    {
        "question": "673760099÷56663=？",
        "answer": 4.075205723548181
    },
    {
        "question": "511517435÷7641286=？",
        "answer": 1.8256939862948989
    },
    {
        "question": "5552573÷702=？",
        "answer": 3.898157164823038
    },
    {
        "question": "55689581÷735=？",
        "answer": 4.87948661125174
    },
    {
        "question": "17695×305=？",
        "answer": 6.7321504063203195
    },
    {
        "question": "1×10974536=？",
        "answer": 7.040386167465458
    },
    {
        "question": "1071×47451=？",
        "answer": 7.706034840174843
    },
    {
        "question": "3199×6751=？",
        "answer": 7.3343823480729275
    },
    {
        "question": "4347603÷18384=？",
        "answer": 2.373809868416624
    },
    {
        "question": "372848×966=？",
        "answer": 8.556508944242342
    },
    {
        "question": "325579392÷1633=？",
        "answer": 5.299670723077773
    },
    {
        "question": "1003×1607=？",
        "answer": 6.207316809783762
    },
    {
        "question": "2×838507=？",
        "answer": 6.224536688185911
    },
    {
        "question": "120×6348108=？",
        "answer": 8.881825552820583
    },
    {
        "question": "671×745979=？",
        "answer": 8.699449122021703
    },
    {
        "question": "17391×1294=？",
        "answer": 7.352258831423116
    },
    {
        "question": "13456124÷3092666=？",
        "answer": 0.6385869607096387
    },
    {
        "question": "68246×2296=？",
        "answer": 8.195049085536372
    },
    {
        "question": "69×11079805=？",
        "answer": 8.883381207793096
    },
    {
        "question": "11×243881=？",
        "answer": 6.428570652275663
    },
    {
        "question": "17×26876=？",
        "answer": 5.6598135537959715
    },
    {
        "question": "494631435÷285=？",
        "answer": 6.2394368533374704
    },
    {
        "question": "330×72357=？",
        "answer": 7.377994492116868
    },
    {
        "question": "5280×36393=？",
        "answer": 8.283651779981648
    },
    {
        "question": "5215590÷423=？",
        "answer": 4.090963076595732
    },
    {
        "question": "93847524÷23613=？",
        "answer": 3.599271651905171
    },
    {
        "question": "6866÷5498=？",
        "answer": 0.09649906358228166
    },
    {
        "question": "1082795÷56611=？",
        "answer": 1.2816454151616867
    },
    {
        "question": "1050952÷16405=？",
        "answer": 1.8066066462812704
    },
    {
        "question": "44×438=？",
        "answer": 4.284926786990287
    },
    {
        "question": "19×21662=？",
        "answer": 5.614452152451051
    },
    {
        "question": "1×3221=？",
        "answer": 3.5079907248196913
    },
    {
        "question": "13782×31470=？",
        "answer": 8.63720898849189
    },
    {
        "question": "45544÷35947=？",
        "answer": 0.10276851913913902
    },
    {
        "question": "6812183÷5481=？",
        "answer": 3.0944265041036645
    },
    {
        "question": "348999÷274=？",
        "answer": 3.105073619740213
    },
    {
        "question": "1218471÷771=？",
        "answer": 3.1987608192450416
    },
    {
        "question": "1368514÷88315=？",
        "answer": 1.1902147713622473
    },
    {
        "question": "4238770÷12342=？",
        "answer": 2.5358543098659343
    },
    {
        "question": "32812324÷1634239=？",
        "answer": 1.3027214208426057
    },
    {
        "question": "427467÷5161=？",
        "answer": 1.918168734213923
    },
    {
        "question": "932×23105=？",
        "answer": 7.333121885208705
    },
    {
        "question": "59×6253773=？",
        "answer": 8.566994124776018
    },
    {
        "question": "121488÷29481=？",
        "answer": 0.6149911717621548
    },
    {
        "question": "9834771÷7013602=？",
        "answer": 0.14682313455298523
    },
    {
        "question": "127701047÷4796692=？",
        "answer": 1.425252625073944
    },
    {
        "question": "11475÷2709=？",
        "answer": 0.6269436891761306
    },
    {
        "question": "705703572÷86363=？",
        "answer": 3.912294595617064
    },
    {
        "question": "2×209548=？",
        "answer": 5.622313515793955
    },
    {
        "question": "146×231=？",
        "answer": 4.527964835676581
    },
    {
        "question": "362×134602=？",
        "answer": 7.6877600834858395
    },
    {
        "question": "3209488÷5066=？",
        "answer": 2.801770570779033
    },
    {
        "question": "29563871÷1051=？",
        "answer": 4.449158582567081
    },
    {
        "question": "7×209=？",
        "answer": 3.1652443261253107
    },
    {
        "question": "97149÷52032=？",
        "answer": 0.2711678149850504
    },
    {
        "question": "4×11785=？",
        "answer": 4.673389578188305
    },
    {
        "question": "149239×243=？",
        "answer": 7.559488603916601
    },
    {
        "question": "904389795÷701870406=？",
        "answer": 0.11009872218890807
    },
    {
        "question": "6453÷322=？",
        "answer": 1.301905793411294
    },
    {
        "question": "406983695÷1028007=？",
        "answer": 2.597580938513532
    },
    {
        "question": "7094×120368=？",
        "answer": 8.931402228611036
    },
    {
        "question": "15×5698=？",
        "answer": 4.931813703959139
    },
    {
        "question": "3×559157=？",
        "answer": 6.224655020853643
    },
    {
        "question": "12×9918386=？",
        "answer": 8.075622252040217
    },
    {
        "question": "985672÷741=？",
        "answer": 3.1239142117401846
    },
    {
        "question": "17027×4155=？",
        "answer": 7.849709164149849
    },
    {
        "question": "574614961÷205=？",
        "answer": 6.447623068284053
    },
    {
        "question": "1952570÷1044463=？",
        "answer": 0.2717135526177801
    },
    {
        "question": "11107707÷12986=？",
        "answer": 2.9321490168373536
    },
    {
        "question": "240678×450=？",
        "answer": 8.034648907684488
    },
    {
        "question": "5×17746=？",
        "answer": 4.948070481518941
    },
    {
        "question": "2355×938=？",
        "answer": 6.3441937498439795
    },
    {
        "question": "4×12413=？",
        "answer": 4.695936746718007
    },
    {
        "question": "429495÷8955=？",
        "answer": 1.6808925221380917
    },
    {
        "question": "457924÷280=？",
        "answer": 3.2136353743484443
    },
    {
        "question": "14983741÷2411=？",
        "answer": 3.793423047099514
    },
    {
        "question": "10758×999=？",
        "answer": 7.031297028171808
    },
    {
        "question": "3435374÷4917=？",
        "answer": 2.844273816160564
    },
    {
        "question": "83×721=？",
        "answer": 4.777013357095503
    },
    {
        "question": "15287×6689=？",
        "answer": 8.009683461529791
    },
    {
        "question": "19×6388=？",
        "answer": 5.084118508419274
    },
    {
        "question": "1×74319581=？",
        "answer": 7.871103252520826
    },
    {
        "question": "23222068÷603297=？",
        "answer": 1.5853697267316849
    },
    {
        "question": "184×23310=？",
        "answer": 6.632360096530113
    },
    {
        "question": "9×4432=？",
        "answer": 4.600842261159698
    },
    {
        "question": "3643×280=？",
        "answer": 6.008617202584135
    },
    {
        "question": "169312030÷11429169=？",
        "answer": 1.1706731622468334
    },
    {
        "question": "1552×338579=？",
        "answer": 8.720551734880116
    },
    {
        "question": "71×781=？",
        "answer": 4.743909382596375
    },
    {
        "question": "26276×605=？",
        "answer": 7.201314627848189
    },
    {
        "question": "514580923÷164548=？",
        "answer": 3.495161073596191
    },
    {
        "question": "640×46070=？",
        "answer": 7.469598186236567
    },
    {
        "question": "1299×4604=？",
        "answer": 6.776744466030782
    },
    {
        "question": "328080084÷2552610=？",
        "answer": 2.1089954011955485
    },
    {
        "question": "575÷330=？",
        "answer": 0.241153904811743
    },
    {
        "question": "11376×38327=？",
        "answer": 8.639494410090208
    },
    {
        "question": "12×1475=？",
        "answer": 4.247973266361806
    },
    {
        "question": "92645361÷1510623=？",
        "answer": 1.7876675851529715
    },
    {
        "question": "47480649÷3296=？",
        "answer": 4.158529443550492
    },
    {
        "question": "168×256711=？",
        "answer": 7.634753760202322
    },
    {
        "question": "34×229=？",
        "answer": 3.8913143993821433
    },
    {
        "question": "8×54428557=？",
        "answer": 8.638916807525357
    },
    {
        "question": "22×387=？",
        "answer": 3.9301336458411176
    },
    {
        "question": "12×71865=？",
        "answer": 5.935698675961452
    },
    {
        "question": "209×1845=？",
        "answer": 5.586142656606133
    },
    {
        "question": "1343704÷2524=？",
        "answer": 2.726214259422009
    },
    {
        "question": "263550890÷7098=？",
        "answer": 4.569728492135631
    },
    {
        "question": "19250÷571=？",
        "answer": 1.5277946255986714
    },
    {
        "question": "30400÷1891=？",
        "answer": 1.206182054763714
    },
    {
        "question": "645658÷328211=？",
        "answer": 0.2938494041526092
    },
    {
        "question": "5×3923871=？",
        "answer": 7.2926847255441665
    },
    {
        "question": "3×750=？",
        "answer": 3.3521825181113627
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1230219=？",
        "answer": 6.089982430159226
    },
    {
        "question": "399764×715=？",
        "answer": 8.456109723766021
    },
    {
        "question": "1230600×700=？",
        "answer": 8.935214950766266
    },
    {
        "question": "2900282÷774=？",
        "answer": 3.573699266557324
    },
    {
        "question": "49588917÷861=？",
        "answer": 4.760381472141753
    },
    {
        "question": "3636×40687=？",
        "answer": 8.170079543477247
    },
    {
        "question": "8×32340=？",
        "answer": 5.412830002562326
    },
    {
        "question": "22×5717243=？",
        "answer": 8.09960933224871
    },
    {
        "question": "148260973÷3368218=？",
        "answer": 1.6436266535343504
    },
    {
        "question": "7×17084=？",
        "answer": 5.077687602769044
    },
    {
        "question": "96808995÷309324=？",
        "answer": 2.4955020940314143
    },
    {
        "question": "249462456÷52245819=？",
        "answer": 0.6789536522090448
    },
    {
        "question": "94553109÷11666615=？",
        "answer": 0.9087309471269047
    },
    {
        "question": "395337690÷97968=？",
        "answer": 3.6058839782182743
    },
    {
        "question": "25414749÷3725339=？",
        "answer": 0.8339200259017501
    },
    {
        "question": "35×26207=？",
        "answer": 5.9624853530490505
    },
    {
        "question": "166×3133=？",
        "answer": 5.71606848292176
    },
    {
        "question": "11295260÷707854=？",
        "answer": 1.2029525416284026
    },
    {
        "question": "17944463÷1629124=？",
        "answer": 1.0419763246273093
    },
    {
        "question": "734×256008=？",
        "answer": 8.273949596718426
    },
    {
        "question": "428098÷341=？",
        "answer": 3.0987888198976568
    },
    {
        "question": "2×395554=？",
        "answer": 5.898235776294525
    },
    {
        "question": "16×4083808=？",
        "answer": 7.815185298220491
    },
    {
        "question": "220947363÷607=？",
        "answer": 5.561100131562665
    },
    {
        "question": "27×47127=？",
        "answer": 6.104633558577775
    },
    {
        "question": "9×84120=？",
        "answer": 5.879141773453608
    },
    {
        "question": "30462×9940=？",
        "answer": 8.481144798185563
    },
    {
        "question": "516×525277=？",
        "answer": 8.433038086645498
    },
    {
        "question": "185×3064631=？",
        "answer": 8.75354991873828
    },
    {
        "question": "340370357÷4661=？",
        "answer": 4.863472627234657
    },
    {
        "question": "1659104÷2262=？",
        "answer": 2.865381009793252
    },
    {
        "question": "119×7501334=？",
        "answer": 8.950685464427103
    },
    {
        "question": "7×2404249=？",
        "answer": 7.226077484096201
    },
    {
        "question": "15774013÷6428=？",
        "answer": 3.3898663263184368
    },
    {
        "question": "434799736÷6463=？",
        "answer": 4.827855115798442
    },
    {
        "question": "6×67264=？",
        "answer": 5.605933940395773
    },
    {
        "question": "24×47048=？",
        "answer": 6.0527524081055875
    },
    {
        "question": "2358439÷657=？",
        "answer": 3.555059278329129
    },
    {
        "question": "3179÷2070=？",
        "answer": 0.18632018245785512
    },
    {
        "question": "53124÷2517=？",
        "answer": 1.32440755247811
    },
    {
        "question": "9538×3227=？",
        "answer": 7.488256283501753
    },
    {
        "question": "9×712836=？",
        "answer": 6.807232133979014
    },
    {
        "question": "1×27568310=？",
        "answer": 7.440410143683917
    },
    {
        "question": "11703÷1472=？",
        "answer": 0.9003893950299737
    },
    {
        "question": "122137554÷12240472=？",
        "answer": 0.9990510535146517
    },
    {
        "question": "200085÷59585=？",
        "answer": 0.5260775879267278
    },
    {
        "question": "1×312566=？",
        "answer": 5.494941734990087
    },
    {
        "question": "32×1881=？",
        "answer": 4.779538773870285
    },
    {
        "question": "1×883=？",
        "answer": 2.9459607035775686
    },
    {
        "question": "219419×724=？",
        "answer": 8.201012797630385
    },
    {
        "question": "55×9031=？",
        "answer": 5.696098531771909
    },
    {
        "question": "62534÷313=？",
        "answer": 2.300571871757392
    },
    {
        "question": "143×256=？",
        "answer": 4.5635760027769114
    },
    {
        "question": "5×1012=？",
        "answer": 3.7041505168397992
    },
    {
        "question": "35855061÷6114=？",
        "answer": 3.7682250313108896
    },
    {
        "question": "69×17554=？",
        "answer": 6.083225184757827
    },
    {
        "question": "2×10621231=？",
        "answer": 7.3272048500294895
    },
    {
        "question": "1144043÷150800=？",
        "answer": 0.880041006622345
    },
    {
        "question": "334800÷81528=？",
        "answer": 0.6134786607395883
    },
    {
        "question": "1×23917908=？",
        "answer": 7.378723191044289
    },
    {
        "question": "12158366÷4601344=？",
        "answer": 0.42199051002793814
    },
    {
        "question": "15×69388=？",
        "answer": 6.017375628870772
    },
    {
        "question": "3×119234976=？",
        "answer": 8.553524923342888
    },
    {
        "question": "393×22624=？",
        "answer": 6.948961942492232
    },
    {
        "question": "26009698÷176352=？",
        "answer": 2.1687549202632233
    },
    {
        "question": "1087628÷6775=？",
        "answer": 2.2055710800319144
    },
    {
        "question": "8124793÷1574244=？",
        "answer": 0.7127402582952911
    },
    {
        "question": "39496375÷11988353=？",
        "answer": 0.5177977152887226
    },
    {
        "question": "5583117÷160617=？",
        "answer": 1.541085219130829
    },
    {
        "question": "433613÷8369=？",
        "answer": 1.7144287262982318
    },
    {
        "question": "23×31780=？",
        "answer": 5.863881728888954
    },
    {
        "question": "112745340÷3323065=？",
        "answer": 1.530559764351653
    },
    {
        "question": "2479×183491=？",
        "answer": 8.65789129428676
    },
    {
        "question": "51238280÷917079=？",
        "answer": 1.747187793895722
    },
    {
        "question": "17303454÷5444421=？",
        "answer": 0.5021811022882288
    },
    {
        "question": "6076005÷6523=？",
        "answer": 2.969170744053303
    },
    {
        "question": "168546÷30859=？",
        "answer": 0.7373366016877784
    },
    {
        "question": "23120÷2067=？",
        "answer": 1.0486473531212033
    },
    {
        "question": "140×802550=？",
        "answer": 8.050600134758453
    },
    {
        "question": "87731761÷280=？",
        "answer": 5.49599881550075
    },
    {
        "question": "8677176÷11617=？",
        "answer": 2.8732844170209684
    },
    {
        "question": "147393130÷38956053=？",
        "answer": 0.5779022934877633
    },
    {
        "question": "3122×6638=？",
        "answer": 7.316470146798983
    },
    {
        "question": "25×2323=？",
        "answer": 4.763989218472273
    },
    {
        "question": "68×276431=？",
        "answer": 7.2740956575372255
    },
    {
        "question": "6408×97367=？",
        "answer": 8.795134292128214
    },
    {
        "question": "151305÷488=？",
        "answer": 2.4914334578812167
    },
    {
        "question": "399408136÷42359=？",
        "answer": 3.974471208416663
    },
    {
        "question": "2702592÷9641=？",
        "answer": 2.4476584040055935
    },
    {
        "question": "45278022÷46663=？",
        "answer": 2.9869147896760824
    },
    {
        "question": "17546×313=？",
        "answer": 6.739722462568992
    },
    {
        "question": "5774455÷12881=？",
        "answer": 2.65156142103284
    },
    {
        "question": "22313122÷18409=？",
        "answer": 3.0835301422834673
    },
    {
        "question": "34×74957=？",
        "answer": 6.4062911135249925
    },
    {
        "question": "1410581÷6066=？",
        "answer": 2.3664956237886323
    },
    {
        "question": "1554×3226=？",
        "answer": 6.700115377517839
    },
    {
        "question": "4449813÷597=？",
        "answer": 3.8723674293404273
    },
    {
        "question": "3772683÷4665=？",
        "answer": 2.9077986670218627
    },
    {
        "question": "196×4190783=？",
        "answer": 8.914551244874055
    },
    {
        "question": "1516×180533=？",
        "answer": 8.4372558003796
    },
    {
        "question": "3×37514=？",
        "answer": 5.051314628795989
    },
    {
        "question": "1527640÷7963=？",
        "answer": 2.2829443057685848
    },
    {
        "question": "1219246×681=？",
        "answer": 8.91923845138182
    },
    {
        "question": "37×1131374=？",
        "answer": 7.621807918105224
    },
    {
        "question": "54071333÷553=？",
        "answer": 4.990241944899527
    },
    {
        "question": "194×9954=？",
        "answer": 6.285799366338231
    },
    {
        "question": "933×11606=？",
        "answer": 7.034564209975011
    },
    {
        "question": "45×27958=？",
        "answer": 6.099718614324284
    },
    {
        "question": "1121092÷5443=？",
        "answer": 2.313802919181446
    },
    {
        "question": "69435÷6254=？",
        "answer": 1.0454205629315776
    },
    {
        "question": "19×10330=？",
        "answer": 5.29285392247245
    },
    {
        "question": "166583583÷4696=？",
        "answer": 4.549904110729029
    },
    {
        "question": "112918762÷99813=？",
        "answer": 3.053578999026474
    },
    {
        "question": "35450701÷42374=？",
        "answer": 2.922525365063722
    },
    {
        "question": "227363÷7936=？",
        "answer": 1.4571181318861202
    },
    {
        "question": "75334380÷653677=？",
        "answer": 2.0616300140543826
    },
    {
        "question": "2×306652=？",
        "answer": 5.7876757971875135
    },
    {
        "question": "265×546713=？",
        "answer": 8.161005274810512
    },
    {
        "question": "480761054÷54717582=？",
        "answer": 0.9438023812084321
    },
    {
        "question": "88183324÷1223=？",
        "answer": 4.857960008146351
    },
    {
        "question": "11×459120=？",
        "answer": 6.703318896897127
    },
    {
        "question": "710921÷7823=？",
        "answer": 1.958448012860279
    },
    {
        "question": "155×1116650=？",
        "answer": 8.238248768431909
    },
    {
        "question": "579758700÷208558=？",
        "answer": 3.4440204210430365
    },
    {
        "question": "855115139÷1575=？",
        "answer": 5.734744037147268
    },
    {
        "question": "37731502÷2448702=？",
        "answer": 1.1877681578104988
    },
    {
        "question": "3492×32544=？",
        "answer": 8.055545166276183
    },
    {
        "question": "19×226=？",
        "answer": 3.63286204010023
    },
    {
        "question": "17526430÷38510=？",
        "answer": 2.658119944008703
    },
    {
        "question": "768×4633=？",
        "answer": 6.551223520234667
    },
    {
        "question": "39×454577=？",
        "answer": 7.248672065195526
    },
    {
        "question": "1723441÷1398=？",
        "answer": 3.0908892490218465
    },
    {
        "question": "8936×2483=？",
        "answer": 7.346119879662117
    },
    {
        "question": "733×6768=？",
        "answer": 6.6955643246720955
    },
    {
        "question": "5075320÷25466=？",
        "answer": 2.299502695065783
    },
    {
        "question": "772912169÷325685=？",
        "answer": 3.3753323882129647
    },
    {
        "question": "299653÷244475=？",
        "answer": 0.08838417522776815
    },
    {
        "question": "5×536=？",
        "answer": 3.428134794028789
    },
    {
        "question": "1×411=？",
        "answer": 2.6138418218760693
    },
    {
        "question": "1×2871846=？",
        "answer": 6.458161147567684
    },
    {
        "question": "444704498÷980877=？",
        "answer": 2.6564569710371853
    },
    {
        "question": "474×169585=？",
        "answer": 7.905165777417161
    },
    {
        "question": "48×725=？",
        "answer": 4.541579243946581
    },
    {
        "question": "9208×74414=？",
        "answer": 8.8358199605596
    },
    {
        "question": "4944812÷147398=？",
        "answer": 1.5256581937755265
    },
    {
        "question": "71191585÷726856=？",
        "answer": 1.99098028234674
    },
    {
        "question": "15274×17636=？",
        "answer": 8.430352876420866
    },
    {
        "question": "236×14570=？",
        "answer": 6.5363715547400965
    },
    {
        "question": "509578907÷27942=？",
        "answer": 4.260953954631217
    },
    {
        "question": "58243553÷942=？",
        "answer": 4.791196957351876
    },
    {
        "question": "423052÷351829=？",
        "answer": 0.08006211861056035
    },
    {
        "question": "11788÷2018=？",
        "answer": 0.7665189652769958
    },
    {
        "question": "39075053÷1765=？",
        "answer": 4.345154866029237
    },
    {
        "question": "24×54539=？",
        "answer": 6.116918412382428
    },
    {
        "question": "11×4227=？",
        "answer": 4.6674249329872435
    },
    {
        "question": "722×2344=？",
        "answer": 6.228494804915692
    },
    {
        "question": "1093×379=？",
        "answer": 5.6172593719177755
    },
    {
        "question": "687022019÷1140063=？",
        "answer": 2.780041805227685
    },
    {
        "question": "16748533÷28953=？",
        "answer": 2.7622832029476116
    },
    {
        "question": "52759×4457=？",
        "answer": 8.371339189372224
    },
    {
        "question": "232713788÷47535540=？",
        "answer": 0.6898036836270673
    },
    {
        "question": "14×34979=？",
        "answer": 5.689935425135082
    },
    {
        "question": "144596976÷51946=？",
        "answer": 3.444607099337877
    },
    {
        "question": "17×8774687=？",
        "answer": 8.173680555166023
    },
    {
        "question": "4686074÷408229=？",
        "answer": 1.0599052893334433
    },
    {
        "question": "17×19603838=？",
        "answer": 8.522790026359614
    },
    {
        "question": "25905694÷22142=？",
        "answer": 3.068178384869781
    },
    {
        "question": "36×50656=？",
        "answer": 6.260933393949549
    },
    {
        "question": "12567211÷7126332=？",
        "answer": 0.2463728555235811
    },
    {
        "question": "12290445÷152965=？",
        "answer": 1.9049755366248216
    },
    {
        "question": "1×3617=？",
        "answer": 3.5583485087616196
    },
    {
        "question": "19×812=？",
        "answer": 4.188309630194004
    },
    {
        "question": "677933561÷7474841=？",
        "answer": 1.957585175062879
    },
    {
        "question": "893÷526=？",
        "answer": 0.22986571473480735
    },
    {
        "question": "19×259954=？",
        "answer": 6.693650105409722
    },
    {
        "question": "193082×1546=？",
        "answer": 8.47495127830191
    },
    {
        "question": "11×87800968=？",
        "answer": 8.984891989159328
    },
    {
        "question": "9×2505=？",
        "answer": 4.353050239642589
    },
    {
        "question": "3867×1806=？",
        "answer": 6.844091918050553
    },
    {
        "question": "153261÷61738=？",
        "answer": 0.39487909850012387
    },
    {
        "question": "4×762=？",
        "answer": 3.4840149626675627
    },
    {
        "question": "67837107÷609=？",
        "answer": 5.046850025968281
    },
    {
        "question": "21×2344=？",
        "answer": 4.692176902079972
    },
    {
        "question": "3×296983=？",
        "answer": 5.949852844718698
    },
    {
        "question": "5965621÷4199=？",
        "answer": 3.152509784237747
    },
    {
        "question": "5×655058=？",
        "answer": 6.5152497592358545
    },
    {
        "question": "30572749÷2217046=？",
        "answer": 1.1395597867057292
    },
    {
        "question": "16×2210603=？",
        "answer": 7.548630737722065
    },
    {
        "question": "1×12265=？",
        "answer": 4.088667552542405
    },
    {
        "question": "2402440÷410=？",
        "answer": 3.7678686934213466
    },
    {
        "question": "60×1983384=？",
        "answer": 8.075558055832543
    },
    {
        "question": "67102220÷2878=？",
        "answer": 4.367646098940999
    },
    {
        "question": "130027÷568=？",
        "answer": 2.359685206853395
    },
    {
        "question": "156057899÷10651=？",
        "answer": 4.16589537104815
    },
    {
        "question": "594250552÷32784091=？",
        "answer": 1.2583064472711691
    },
    {
        "question": "100145824÷9937=？",
        "answer": 4.003377554457829
    },
    {
        "question": "10×53073272=？",
        "answer": 8.724875862977807
    },
    {
        "question": "22×126882=？",
        "answer": 6.445822696493387
    },
    {
        "question": "4×895=？",
        "answer": 3.5538830266438746
    },
    {
        "question": "102×64937=？",
        "answer": 6.8210923927081835
    },
    {
        "question": "84895268÷1864221=？",
        "answer": 1.6583860877737633
    },
    {
        "question": "1022721÷45221=？",
        "answer": 1.3544170116695904
    },
    {
        "question": "4408640÷71281=？",
        "answer": 1.791330852944968
    },
    {
        "question": "4518716÷41875=？",
        "answer": 2.0330602268608278
    },
    {
        "question": "295089787÷421=？",
        "answer": 5.84567208307704
    },
    {
        "question": "114646957÷9840=？",
        "answer": 4.06636743359016
    },
    {
        "question": "973×6679=？",
        "answer": 6.812824283733086
    },
    {
        "question": "123855×2533=？",
        "answer": 8.496548733442141
    },
    {
        "question": "79×40295=？",
        "answer": 6.502878251398613
    },
    {
        "question": "29583×13632=？",
        "answer": 8.605601790943574
    },
    {
        "question": "583×337=？",
        "answer": 5.293298455630353
    },
    {
        "question": "951101÷9086=？",
        "answer": 2.0198539058190432
    },
    {
        "question": "7765×87796=？",
        "answer": 8.83361618989437
    },
    {
        "question": "3×2954=？",
        "answer": 3.947531745695593
    },
    {
        "question": "158×24474=？",
        "answer": 6.587362042655161
    },
    {
        "question": "4959×682=？",
        "answer": 6.5291784829475885
    },
    {
        "question": "946×939=？",
        "answer": 5.948556728667904
    },
    {
        "question": "1×2739153=？",
        "answer": 6.4376162911805555
    },
    {
        "question": "246823÷633=？",
        "answer": 2.590981916606699
    },
    {
        "question": "1×2803=？",
        "answer": 3.447623097760286
    },
    {
        "question": "2217870÷595644=？",
        "answer": 0.570949315039815
    },
    {
        "question": "25194686÷1509454=？",
        "answer": 1.2224890675248956
    },
    {
        "question": "186689788÷340283=？",
        "answer": 2.7392803095581075
    },
    {
        "question": "1818957÷71614=？",
        "answer": 1.4048245005751758
    },
    {
        "question": "1581307÷8145=？",
        "answer": 2.288125104793503
    },
    {
        "question": "3×20509=？",
        "answer": 4.789065739804283
    },
    {
        "question": "310×1178=？",
        "answer": 5.562506984285355
    },
    {
        "question": "140230÷1502=？",
        "answer": 1.9701710013669178
    },
    {
        "question": "17×41034916=？",
        "answer": 8.843602470121484
    },
    {
        "question": "627034711÷1085=？",
        "answer": 5.761861844717146
    },
    {
        "question": "136110÷44185=？",
        "answer": 0.48861517465618537
    },
    {
        "question": "23236752÷12599344=？",
        "answer": 0.26582748925662675
    },
    {
        "question": "16502373÷14930=？",
        "answer": 3.043486591440671
    },
    {
        "question": "22586÷18971=？",
        "answer": 0.07574909976693803
    },
    {
        "question": "2×11884906=？",
        "answer": 7.376025746823449
    },
    {
        "question": "1517635÷746=？",
        "answer": 3.30842850630909
    },
    {
        "question": "1450391÷346481=？",
        "answer": 0.6218056720341292
    },
    {
        "question": "7970239÷782=？",
        "answer": 4.008264591526341
    },
    {
        "question": "293×472=？",
        "answer": 5.1408096189881975
    },
    {
        "question": "132628928÷376=？",
        "answer": 5.547450414439517
    },
    {
        "question": "1464182÷25181=？",
        "answer": 1.7645220905017593
    },
    {
        "question": "429809491÷80049=？",
        "answer": 3.7299200903671093
    },
    {
        "question": "192127÷25193=？",
        "answer": 0.8823085147746238
    },
    {
        "question": "160834÷1524=？",
        "answer": 2.023392896137217
    },
    {
        "question": "2603610÷53567=？",
        "answer": 1.6866786063681476
    },
    {
        "question": "6239×1646=？",
        "answer": 7.011544816506614
    },
    {
        "question": "11567÷2409=？",
        "answer": 0.6813839355836511
    },
    {
        "question": "653÷422=？",
        "answer": 0.18960073031340008
    },
    {
        "question": "5326÷4114=？",
        "answer": 0.1121368747442172
    },
    {
        "question": "1×267=？",
        "answer": 2.4265112613645754
    },
    {
        "question": "577908÷4011=？",
        "answer": 2.1586060444795576
    },
    {
        "question": "91×737058=？",
        "answer": 7.8265430566914675
    },
    {
        "question": "5×6229=？",
        "answer": 4.49338833521016
    },
    {
        "question": "62730856÷36795=？",
        "answer": 3.2316924065233157
    },
    {
        "question": "896044÷573=？",
        "answer": 3.1941747141322643
    },
    {
        "question": "24346÷4249=？",
        "answer": 0.7581408865914361
    },
    {
        "question": "1031×812598=？",
        "answer": 8.92313441437158
    },
    {
        "question": "1310×525152=？",
        "answer": 8.837556319455931
    },
    {
        "question": "1396245÷4770=？",
        "answer": 2.466443251863285
    },
    {
        "question": "9553×4153=？",
        "answer": 7.598501708855633
    },
    {
        "question": "16635377÷438086=？",
        "answer": 1.5794732729689127
    },
    {
        "question": "129×177008=？",
        "answer": 7.358582605346599
    },
    {
        "question": "45×1717987=？",
        "answer": 7.888232386978585
    },
    {
        "question": "43322×7490=？",
        "answer": 8.511190315720013
    },
    {
        "question": "5×305=？",
        "answer": 3.1832698436828046
    },
    {
        "question": "1×10082=？",
        "answer": 4.003546693102132
    },
    {
        "question": "732449406÷1390=？",
        "answer": 5.721762830882792
    },
    {
        "question": "80123×227=？",
        "answer": 7.2597830591608155
    },
    {
        "question": "10040218÷67353=？",
        "answer": 2.1733861980127727
    },
    {
        "question": "19×9779160=？",
        "answer": 8.269055152771896
    },
    {
        "question": "24188×320=？",
        "answer": 6.88874993825381
    },
    {
        "question": "99102527÷8797093=？",
        "answer": 1.0517455454194868
    },
    {
        "question": "1×71234958=？",
        "answer": 7.852693172578548
    },
    {
        "question": "22×4317=？",
        "answer": 4.9776047294784735
    },
    {
        "question": "2×20884506=？",
        "answer": 7.620854202628712
    },
    {
        "question": "10187022÷90235=？",
        "answer": 2.0526722213961155
    },
    {
        "question": "727798955÷73972=？",
        "answer": 3.99294406668266
    },
    {
        "question": "3759283÷21507=？",
        "answer": 2.242525185663205
    },
    {
        "question": "12×356=？",
        "answer": 3.6306312440205
    },
    {
        "question": "12×6808584=？",
        "answer": 7.912238045929645
    },
    {
        "question": "20×318115=？",
        "answer": 6.803614143437298
    },
    {
        "question": "30×2466=？",
        "answer": 4.869114326979375
    },
    {
        "question": "87867×5551=？",
        "answer": 8.688197026082191
    },
    {
        "question": "6701×2731=？",
        "answer": 7.262461318075648
    },
    {
        "question": "545629÷61273=？",
        "answer": 0.9496283004349431
    },
    {
        "question": "16831×4378=？",
        "answer": 7.8673856772231865
    },
    {
        "question": "37025×269=？",
        "answer": 6.998247347195654
    },
    {
        "question": "492850905÷1566776=？",
        "answer": 2.4977086479974884
    },
    {
        "question": "48×2091886=？",
        "answer": 8.001779250783082
    },
    {
        "question": "23407÷2361=？",
        "answer": 0.9962497680559437
    },
    {
        "question": "1259909÷55070=？",
        "answer": 1.3594241017909932
    },
    {
        "question": "1541×1722=？",
        "answer": 6.423835785836055
    },
    {
        "question": "1×55232073=？",
        "answer": 7.742191343704677
    },
    {
        "question": "388738÷6488=？",
        "answer": 1.7775461547502
    },
    {
        "question": "284696739÷700227=？",
        "answer": 2.6091436399589973
    },
    {
        "question": "249311797÷51874477=？",
        "answer": 0.6817890978759396
    },
    {
        "question": "99789÷44958=？",
        "answer": 0.34627568753814153
    },
    {
        "question": "4×11219701=？",
        "answer": 7.652041274649143
    },
    {
        "question": "4487×603=？",
        "answer": 6.432273381673226
    },
    {
        "question": "10820673÷10099477=？",
        "answer": 0.029955388400605198
    },
    {
        "question": "16824110÷22309=？",
        "answer": 2.877451995719331
    },
    {
        "question": "1185353÷125358=？",
        "answer": 0.9756956485437155
    },
    {
        "question": "42×8236=？",
        "answer": 5.538965628343894
    },
    {
        "question": "75×54073=？",
        "answer": 6.608041728534232
    },
    {
        "question": "11×196537=？",
        "answer": 6.3348370077229665
    },
    {
        "question": "9387÷217=？",
        "answer": 1.6360670840173261
    },
    {
        "question": "743801361÷105196=？",
        "answer": 3.8494577422856064
    },
    {
        "question": "9745×1340=？",
        "answer": 7.115886641818448
    },
    {
        "question": "64537×6243=？",
        "answer": 8.605202108305846
    },
    {
        "question": "158404×1094=？",
        "answer": 8.238783466144788
    },
    {
        "question": "44738×11927=？",
        "answer": 8.727207784432872
    },
    {
        "question": "104375374÷207=？",
        "answer": 5.702627699210503
    },
    {
        "question": "214528÷4596=？",
        "answer": 1.6691039639258785
    },
    {
        "question": "37291×1112=？",
        "answer": 7.617708816857247
    },
    {
        "question": "118×88175=？",
        "answer": 7.017227475645653
    },
    {
        "question": "10×4335=？",
        "answer": 4.636989101812229
    },
    {
        "question": "1451266÷977048=？",
        "answer": 0.17183112072944687
    },
    {
        "question": "123×521044=？",
        "answer": 7.8067795106512925
    },
    {
        "question": "70×723=？",
        "answer": 4.704236337308788
    },
    {
        "question": "2×21532643=？",
        "answer": 7.634127335746066
    },
    {
        "question": "50×6136=？",
        "answer": 5.486855355276943
    },
    {
        "question": "5833356÷40038=？",
        "answer": 2.163446106273211
    },
    {
        "question": "1851688÷237846=？",
        "answer": 0.8912719600767599
    },
    {
        "question": "1×541044=？",
        "answer": 5.7332325852177926
    },
    {
        "question": "4×1334=？",
        "answer": 3.7272158209084925
    },
    {
        "question": "19110×428=？",
        "answer": 6.912704456068185
    },
    {
        "question": "1260×719=？",
        "answer": 5.957099435500446
    },
    {
        "question": "207037÷1433=？",
        "answer": 2.159801775638764
    },
    {
        "question": "110972÷6077=？",
        "answer": 1.2615241768584768
    },
    {
        "question": "100185282÷548101=？",
        "answer": 2.2619433305325396
    },
    {
        "question": "45×206=？",
        "answer": 3.967079734144497
    },
    {
        "question": "6937÷5823=？",
        "answer": 0.07602490439150693
    },
    {
        "question": "490962÷355144=？",
        "answer": 0.14064339757884495
    },
    {
        "question": "39968×14734=？",
        "answer": 8.770033082212906
    },
    {
        "question": "916×2254=？",
        "answer": 6.314849385377938
    },
    {
        "question": "58×599726=？",
        "answer": 7.541380870834536
    },
    {
        "question": "15×6617=？",
        "answer": 4.996752393699277
    },
    {
        "question": "83051342÷34593760=？",
        "answer": 0.38034888636924996
    },
    {
        "question": "10×75928=？",
        "answer": 5.88040196038887
    },
    {
        "question": "3×90546913=？",
        "answer": 8.433994903296643
    },
    {
        "question": "5217899÷317=？",
        "answer": 4.216436406228476
    },
    {
        "question": "4×5166560=？",
        "answer": 7.315261468606411
    },
    {
        "question": "7965299÷7385=？",
        "answer": 3.032851583265433
    },
    {
        "question": "309728232÷228438=？",
        "answer": 3.132212444270921
    },
    {
        "question": "1×31422=？",
        "answer": 4.4972338242851295
    },
    {
        "question": "16008÷4012=？",
        "answer": 0.6009761512797744
    },
    {
        "question": "77×2098553=？",
        "answer": 8.20841066718169
    },
    {
        "question": "27100×762=？",
        "answer": 7.3149242622140065
    },
    {
        "question": "1343689÷64852=？",
        "answer": 1.31637538783317
    },
    {
        "question": "256×926=？",
        "answer": 5.374850951993784
    },
    {
        "question": "17563×416=？",
        "answer": 6.86369203195561
    },
    {
        "question": "59×1636=？",
        "answer": 4.984635310977448
    },
    {
        "question": "355584038÷2427=？",
        "answer": 5.165872481129037
    },
    {
        "question": "616789×357=？",
        "answer": 8.342804835886124
    },
    {
        "question": "18858228÷889057=？",
        "answer": 1.326571276415402
    },
    {
        "question": "51886663÷3404=？",
        "answer": 4.1830661892903205
    },
    {
        "question": "5583×93348=？",
        "answer": 8.716972645387068
    },
    {
        "question": "22186×44027=？",
        "answer": 8.989798102292482
    },
    {
        "question": "7664649÷5064364=？",
        "answer": 0.17996735833001926
    },
    {
        "question": "78306395÷363=？",
        "answer": 5.333890605729393
    },
    {
        "question": "497150817÷1791=？",
        "answer": 5.443392571606429
    },
    {
        "question": "1×63024=？",
        "answer": 4.799505963465067
    },
    {
        "question": "14121÷758=？",
        "answer": 1.270196247394208
    },
    {
        "question": "4×2175=？",
        "answer": 3.9395192526186187
    },
    {
        "question": "3×21697=？",
        "answer": 4.813520943705746
    },
    {
        "question": "1×207=？",
        "answer": 2.315970345456918
    },
    {
        "question": "443×9400=？",
        "answer": 6.619531579822768
    },
    {
        "question": "141×1072=？",
        "answer": 5.179413898012131
    },
    {
        "question": "22707381÷1895=？",
        "answer": 4.0785578326043845
    },
    {
        "question": "3×1353=？",
        "answer": 3.6084190513172856
    },
    {
        "question": "10×223=？",
        "answer": 3.3483048630481607
    },
    {
        "question": "19728×48252=？",
        "answer": 8.978598378402193
    },
    {
        "question": "6261321÷508=？",
        "answer": 4.090802257106547
    },
    {
        "question": "99383493÷1983=？",
        "answer": 4.6999915424824
    },
    {
        "question": "55772877÷61739=？",
        "answer": 2.9558634569677715
    },
    {
        "question": "39521÷779=？",
        "answer": 1.7052904673368363
    },
    {
        "question": "93298÷237=？",
        "answer": 2.5951239880014167
    },
    {
        "question": "275346758÷2131=？",
        "answer": 5.1112965176438685
    },
    {
        "question": "1×87128=？",
        "answer": 4.940157745034502
    },
    {
        "question": "32391÷8533=？",
        "answer": 0.5793226104595973
    },
    {
        "question": "91923÷698=？",
        "answer": 2.119568766927662
    },
    {
        "question": "139218622÷7275=？",
        "answer": 4.2818643330973964
    },
    {
        "question": "19760160÷4686=？",
        "answer": 3.6249881725309376
    },
    {
        "question": "802×137067=？",
        "answer": 8.04110727571406
    },
    {
        "question": "24×34154=？",
        "answer": 5.913652815796433
    },
    {
        "question": "106×15768=？",
        "answer": 6.223082476536157
    },
    {
        "question": "1040×660=？",
        "answer": 5.836577274840649
    },
    {
        "question": "4×1298725=？",
        "answer": 6.715577191957452
    },
    {
        "question": "279377×2495=？",
        "answer": 8.843261199467563
    },
    {
        "question": "4×5490369=？",
        "answer": 7.341661525081962
    },
    {
        "question": "19×540=？",
        "answer": 4.011147360775797
    },
    {
        "question": "18804446÷1531438=？",
        "answer": 1.0891611239837389
    },
    {
        "question": "23748313÷1213=？",
        "answer": 4.2917719633758695
    },
    {
        "question": "4891199÷2298=？",
        "answer": 3.32806530823875
    },
    {
        "question": "366735÷217=？",
        "answer": 3.227892625748041
    },
    {
        "question": "302×1926836=？",
        "answer": 8.764851694807193
    },
    {
        "question": "1×15243724=？",
        "answer": 7.183091076917099
    },
    {
        "question": "1×290631608=？",
        "answer": 8.463342844764131
    },
    {
        "question": "2563214÷3092=？",
        "answer": 2.918545381234223
    },
    {
        "question": "1×6715=？",
        "answer": 3.8270460170047342
    },
    {
        "question": "7868836÷2068=？",
        "answer": 3.580359959542674
    },
    {
        "question": "114408730÷30102640=？",
        "answer": 0.5798545798526434
    },
    {
        "question": "200×1435=？",
        "answer": 5.457881896733992
    },
    {
        "question": "1111×146527=？",
        "answer": 8.211631716877383
    },
    {
        "question": "133525×824=？",
        "answer": 8.04148979833829
    },
    {
        "question": "2×1804=？",
        "answer": 3.557266528869904
    },
    {
        "question": "127504765÷191908=？",
        "answer": 2.8224333357672897
    },
    {
        "question": "538609÷3028=？",
        "answer": 2.250117735242779
    },
    {
        "question": "23955×1574=？",
        "answer": 7.57640090321721
    },
    {
        "question": "634÷353=？",
        "answer": 0.2543145524939101
    },
    {
        "question": "6×61499=？",
        "answer": 5.567019304402755
    },
    {
        "question": "491423899÷1044348=？",
        "answer": 2.672611033959925
    },
    {
        "question": "3×5594402=？",
        "answer": 7.22487492521225
    },
    {
        "question": "444096÷20830=？",
        "answer": 1.3287875915264231
    },
    {
        "question": "63×268=？",
        "answer": 4.227475343482371
    },
    {
        "question": "634867029÷61793547=？",
        "answer": 1.0117396483488725
    },
    {
        "question": "1×480037280=？",
        "answer": 8.68127496627056
    },
    {
        "question": "909407÷55972=？",
        "answer": 1.2107874673268015
    },
    {
        "question": "4029÷260=？",
        "answer": 1.19022391941756
    },
    {
        "question": "154403÷23068=？",
        "answer": 0.8256457915431654
    },
    {
        "question": "12992962÷10867=？",
        "answer": 3.0775985012269573
    },
    {
        "question": "309845708÷2306=？",
        "answer": 5.128286181697337
    },
    {
        "question": "106604÷969=？",
        "answer": 2.0414497235622644
    },
    {
        "question": "189593÷9588=？",
        "answer": 1.296094273265463
    },
    {
        "question": "11216977÷35459=？",
        "answer": 2.5001493457250024
    },
    {
        "question": "96437322÷4535709=？",
        "answer": 1.327599958298775
    },
    {
        "question": "1×268=？",
        "answer": 2.428134794028789
    },
    {
        "question": "7436510÷963376=？",
        "answer": 0.8875733434797519
    },
    {
        "question": "177917244÷2491497=？",
        "answer": 1.8537576740060528
    },
    {
        "question": "4×7506086=？",
        "answer": 7.477473527305836
    },
    {
        "question": "700837011÷18445931=？",
        "answer": 1.5797164489759445
    },
    {
        "question": "4070×231697=？",
        "answer": 8.974514819830558
    },
    {
        "question": "63788906÷601253=？",
        "answer": 2.025687897591619
    },
    {
        "question": "23×3032021=？",
        "answer": 7.8434600409434845
    },
    {
        "question": "54×1246439=？",
        "answer": 7.828064789063373
    },
    {
        "question": "1012891÷129732=？",
        "answer": 0.892515598849723
    },
    {
        "question": "57110654÷8589469=？",
        "answer": 0.8227508168708892
    },
    {
        "question": "506×813=？",
        "answer": 5.614241062433868
    },
    {
        "question": "1202209÷807639=？",
        "answer": 0.1727626924870604
    },
    {
        "question": "9005×1386=？",
        "answer": 7.09624694743134
    },
    {
        "question": "34×47535=？",
        "answer": 6.208492415288237
    },
    {
        "question": "100754÷27204=？",
        "answer": 0.5686295307575517
    },
    {
        "question": "44315×2692=？",
        "answer": 8.076625809192281
    },
    {
        "question": "61×1370=？",
        "answer": 4.922050402167174
    },
    {
        "question": "195863÷5036=？",
        "answer": 1.589866680799326
    },
    {
        "question": "407141619÷19434=？",
        "answer": 4.321183300886047
    },
    {
        "question": "5×1344933=？",
        "answer": 6.827670654135375
    },
    {
        "question": "109538398÷319=？",
        "answer": 5.535775702021549
    },
    {
        "question": "1×30568=？",
        "answer": 4.485267024680352
    },
    {
        "question": "48056×4912=？",
        "answer": 8.37300597707241
    },
    {
        "question": "979442÷8502=？",
        "answer": 2.061457622674892
    },
    {
        "question": "16×57651=？",
        "answer": 5.964926827516743
    },
    {
        "question": "7177÷827=？",
        "answer": 0.9384374366797694
    },
    {
        "question": "58953×353=？",
        "answer": 7.318280615756922
    },
    {
        "question": "44515÷299=？",
        "answer": 2.172835189387732
    },
    {
        "question": "103162×5305=？",
        "answer": 8.738205141444865
    },
    {
        "question": "1×10912=？",
        "answer": 4.037904357312404
    },
    {
        "question": "2240901÷344652=？",
        "answer": 0.8130418673824702
    },
    {
        "question": "6960÷1276=？",
        "answer": 0.7367585652254186
    },
    {
        "question": "14×34786=？",
        "answer": 5.687532528300452
    },
    {
        "question": "16×620=？",
        "answer": 3.9965116721541785
    },
    {
        "question": "23182÷4930=？",
        "answer": 0.672303982216373
    },
    {
        "question": "186888145÷1382=？",
        "answer": 5.131073710323662
    },
    {
        "question": "146633860÷123113358=？",
        "answer": 0.07592908997390405
    },
    {
        "question": "7666711÷11690=？",
        "answer": 2.816794581483877
    },
    {
        "question": "23×1424=？",
        "answer": 4.51523782531843
    },
    {
        "question": "50722÷319=？",
        "answer": 2.2014056866555936
    },
    {
        "question": "830469052÷510213660=？",
        "answer": 0.21157137096873124
    },
    {
        "question": "6×819356=？",
        "answer": 6.691623888704359
    },
    {
        "question": "682×946=？",
        "answer": 5.809675511058272
    },
    {
        "question": "159×4747896=？",
        "answer": 8.87789832173005
    },
    {
        "question": "868892942÷18853=？",
        "answer": 4.6635858019443885
    },
    {
        "question": "177×171612=？",
        "answer": 7.482520919056136
    },
    {
        "question": "33×4180323=？",
        "answer": 8.139723779475442
    },
    {
        "question": "14×6295=？",
        "answer": 4.94512377012212
    },
    {
        "question": "916×42844=？",
        "answer": 7.593785484306471
    },
    {
        "question": "589×685=？",
        "answer": 5.605805866279527
    },
    {
        "question": "3179000÷41461=？",
        "answer": 1.8846507552595726
    },
    {
        "question": "313475907÷51658473=？",
        "answer": 0.78306260313814
    },
    {
        "question": "20516516÷10919333=？",
        "answer": 0.2739075026439273
    },
    {
        "question": "781389×1078=？",
        "answer": 8.925486054003978
    },
    {
        "question": "1808÷727=？",
        "answer": 0.39566401528030665
    },
    {
        "question": "374705÷3702=？",
        "answer": 2.0052530738675225
    },
    {
        "question": "7×2138=？",
        "answer": 4.175105740887016
    },
    {
        "question": "200×904576=？",
        "answer": 8.257475056626571
    },
    {
        "question": "2502÷2410=？",
        "answer": 0.016270262782532803
    },
    {
        "question": "7731405÷2525=？",
        "answer": 3.4859970413860877
    },
    {
        "question": "10704×2572=？",
        "answer": 7.439817064675933
    },
    {
        "question": "2297×2913=？",
        "answer": 6.825501479822694
    },
    {
        "question": "2×1627218=？",
        "answer": 6.512475735358578
    },
    {
        "question": "30689÷376=？",
        "answer": 1.9117948922640977
    },
    {
        "question": "31835656÷3688457=？",
        "answer": 0.9360690784661778
    },
    {
        "question": "1000498÷471612=？",
        "answer": 0.3266313777838413
    },
    {
        "question": "3×4830370=？",
        "answer": 7.16110165313243
    },
    {
        "question": "133321÷17132=？",
        "answer": 0.8910904967861115
    },
    {
        "question": "19970441÷74668=？",
        "answer": 2.427253136540141
    },
    {
        "question": "7281726÷2158172=？",
        "answer": 0.5281482793539632
    },
    {
        "question": "1×73910=？",
        "answer": 4.868703202278537
    },
    {
        "question": "131×6574893=？",
        "answer": 8.935159985154034
    },
    {
        "question": "2686150÷2924=？",
        "answer": 2.9631528925983854
    },
    {
        "question": "3896×46895=？",
        "answer": 8.26174548840209
    },
    {
        "question": "2401÷2122=？",
        "answer": 0.05364678049170543
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1481297=？",
        "answer": 6.170642143281148
    },
    {
        "question": "6106808÷213025=？",
        "answer": 1.4573836918745535
    },
    {
        "question": "33516561÷3595446=？",
        "answer": 0.9695066805580265
    },
    {
        "question": "729×550=？",
        "answer": 5.603090217812219
    },
    {
        "question": "184×25525=？",
        "answer": 6.671783573768485
    },
    {
        "question": "846491160÷323=？",
        "answer": 6.418419904752639
    },
    {
        "question": "148329058÷61634546=？",
        "answer": 0.3814020373237239
    },
    {
        "question": "35198×7177=？",
        "answer": 8.402460933186568
    },
    {
        "question": "369030×706=？",
        "answer": 8.4158663742701
    },
    {
        "question": "100334915÷1405451=？",
        "answer": 1.8536363782359018
    },
    {
        "question": "52564589÷461=？",
        "answer": 5.056992347645702
    },
    {
        "question": "687×1578=？",
        "answer": 6.035063735932952
    },
    {
        "question": "27303÷2369=？",
        "answer": 1.0616453083642896
    },
    {
        "question": "1548×492570=？",
        "answer": 8.882238913928704
    },
    {
        "question": "499758281÷9787=？",
        "answer": 4.708110410795078
    },
    {
        "question": "1×51844=？",
        "answer": 4.7146985019464545
    },
    {
        "question": "557955÷7260=？",
        "answer": 1.8856625530766207
    },
    {
        "question": "72646÷1506=？",
        "answer": 1.6833867345084834
    },
    {
        "question": "676704÷4024=？",
        "answer": 2.2257407715595723
    },
    {
        "question": "35374÷22106=？",
        "answer": 0.20417400579647282
    },
    {
        "question": "21146×1256=？",
        "answer": 7.424217867272027
    },
    {
        "question": "3×18545=？",
        "answer": 4.745348092384291
    },
    {
        "question": "237250123÷69537=？",
        "answer": 3.5329904960532508
    },
    {
        "question": "131319621÷113622612=？",
        "answer": 0.06286485186354565
    },
    {
        "question": "52×44139=？",
        "answer": 6.36082583332583
    },
    {
        "question": "743167÷365=？",
        "answer": 3.3087935523040097
    },
    {
        "question": "740581905÷2971=？",
        "answer": 5.396670444709847
    },
    {
        "question": "752659999÷315910=？",
        "answer": 3.3770354620226604
    },
    {
        "question": "207×138997=？",
        "answer": 7.458975772347662
    },
    {
        "question": "81057÷42035=？",
        "answer": 0.2851794742802261
    },
    {
        "question": "165815478÷449952=？",
        "answer": 2.566458880645122
    },
    {
        "question": "3824948÷589=？",
        "answer": 3.8125102405282685
    },
    {
        "question": "314×13455=？",
        "answer": 6.625813350172988
    },
    {
        "question": "6×30682025=？",
        "answer": 8.265035269849104
    },
    {
        "question": "1×284696=？",
        "answer": 5.4543813653200095
    },
    {
        "question": "70394093÷1503115=？",
        "answer": 1.6705440088247854
    },
    {
        "question": "54×605=？",
        "answer": 4.514149134475438
    },
    {
        "question": "25×3240=？",
        "answer": 4.9084850188786495
    },
    {
        "question": "3×62382816=？",
        "answer": 8.272186229912473
    },
    {
        "question": "153537÷300=？",
        "answer": 2.709091795839467
    },
    {
        "question": "4×1555=？",
        "answer": 3.7937903846908188
    },
    {
        "question": "12×5676088=？",
        "answer": 7.833230366028648
    },
    {
        "question": "19453455÷5861627=？",
        "answer": 0.5209785656985116
    },
    {
        "question": "225×3114591=？",
        "answer": 8.845583542427478
    },
    {
        "question": "25801÷2338=？",
        "answer": 1.0427920319306476
    },
    {
        "question": "261979÷41689=？",
        "answer": 0.798245002294122
    },
    {
        "question": "4×178138=？",
        "answer": 5.85281656340196
    },
    {
        "question": "3849×91972=？",
        "answer": 8.549003541740788
    },
    {
        "question": "274099504÷14640208=？",
        "answer": 1.2723610026748369
    },
    {
        "question": "175047313÷6965433=？",
        "answer": 1.4002073295403643
    },
    {
        "question": "548938×451=？",
        "answer": 8.393699837551333
    },
    {
        "question": "43519÷10410=？",
        "answer": 0.6212281778718765
    },
    {
        "question": "252×58631=？",
        "answer": 7.169527842279632
    },
    {
        "question": "142×78006=？",
        "answer": 7.044416353056547
    },
    {
        "question": "83327521÷79079=？",
        "answer": 3.022727292954668
    },
    {
        "question": "584367558÷24722390=？",
        "answer": 1.3735956442383155
    },
    {
        "question": "3330×868=？",
        "answer": 6.460963958682812
    },
    {
        "question": "1×863298=？",
        "answer": 5.936160734783543
    },
    {
        "question": "346×747915=？",
        "answer": 8.412928342207284
    },
    {
        "question": "208127452÷1396=？",
        "answer": 5.173443949122036
    },
    {
        "question": "210009358÷10384794=？",
        "answer": 1.3058407613030523
    },
    {
        "question": "319862÷172603=？",
        "answer": 0.2679143085435558
    },
    {
        "question": "274389915÷24910233=？",
        "answer": 1.0419903553868402
    },
    {
        "question": "17216739÷2229=？",
        "answer": 3.8878408272773193
    },
    {
        "question": "101180÷9230=？",
        "answer": 1.0398929740466365
    },
    {
        "question": "115369206÷3177=？",
        "answer": 4.560072688889047
    },
    {
        "question": "591×34660=？",
        "answer": 7.311416039259154
    },
    {
        "question": "5097÷1560=？",
        "answer": 0.5141900352342464
    },
    {
        "question": "323751861÷147110138=？",
        "answer": 0.342569670638697
    },
    {
        "question": "62×2795=？",
        "answer": 5.238773501720696
    },
    {
        "question": "23158618÷227089=？",
        "answer": 2.0085165412577464
    },
    {
        "question": "144291÷702=？",
        "answer": 2.312902131145022
    },
    {
        "question": "658127485÷275229086=？",
        "answer": 0.37861570047108806
    },
    {
        "question": "209888646÷8642054=？",
        "answer": 1.3853719702262612
    },
    {
        "question": "18267437÷380=？",
        "answer": 4.681894021625733
    },
    {
        "question": "5554×44439=？",
        "answer": 8.392370152970011
    },
    {
        "question": "9818÷9056=？",
        "answer": 0.03508661391965438
    },
    {
        "question": "248649720÷48161680=？",
        "answer": 0.7128863467242332
    },
    {
        "question": "76825×226=？",
        "answer": 7.2396110080758165
    },
    {
        "question": "1580573×257=？",
        "answer": 8.608747682200372
    },
    {
        "question": "31952234÷17687=？",
        "answer": 3.25684705224518
    },
    {
        "question": "10×96716=？",
        "answer": 5.985498326584618
    },
    {
        "question": "18583810÷21919=？",
        "answer": 2.9283140199525866
    },
    {
        "question": "2×1056=？",
        "answer": 3.3246939138617746
    },
    {
        "question": "16×19309530=？",
        "answer": 8.489891685700435
    },
    {
        "question": "7065÷350=？",
        "answer": 1.3050441218343019
    },
    {
        "question": "19914×8084=？",
        "answer": 8.206784807635515
    },
    {
        "question": "3564837÷1175957=？",
        "answer": 0.48164823515671396
    },
    {
        "question": "188944×2387=？",
        "answer": 8.654185524266062
    },
    {
        "question": "799×174468=？",
        "answer": 8.144262561910972
    },
    {
        "question": "2264504÷33898=？",
        "answer": 1.8247990167997057
    },
    {
        "question": "112×6389027=？",
        "answer": 8.85465274613277
    },
    {
        "question": "36308×206=？",
        "answer": 6.873869547142521
    },
    {
        "question": "551÷415=？",
        "answer": 0.1231035021396923
    },
    {
        "question": "61229694÷40356=？",
        "answer": 3.1810539756595655
    },
    {
        "question": "15643×2827=？",
        "answer": 7.645645853792942
    },
    {
        "question": "22443×389=？",
        "answer": 6.941030510788723
    },
    {
        "question": "30×445=？",
        "answer": 4.125481265700594
    },
    {
        "question": "548×23328=？",
        "answer": 7.10665806512225
    },
    {
        "question": "58822÷22045=？",
        "answer": 0.4262296836560611
    },
    {
        "question": "17855629÷4260747=？",
        "answer": 0.6222894068025805
    },
    {
        "question": "423×2240=？",
        "answer": 5.9765883857092055
    },
    {
        "question": "57403185÷5366=？",
        "answer": 4.029285321440976
    },
    {
        "question": "24990×1146=？",
        "answer": 7.456950873757822
    },
    {
        "question": "473458456÷775581=？",
        "answer": 2.7856547161926373
    },
    {
        "question": "38275907÷334=？",
        "answer": 5.059179023882783
    },
    {
        "question": "903021421÷12324677=？",
        "answer": 1.8649225062517956
    },
    {
        "question": "2441626÷1841486=？",
        "answer": 0.12251071949019492
    },
    {
        "question": "3×731=？",
        "answer": 3.341038631677523
    },
    {
        "question": "128373381÷7452=？",
        "answer": 4.236202133246174
    },
    {
        "question": "367×193962=？",
        "answer": 7.852382717858525
    },
    {
        "question": "3275194÷1826272=？",
        "answer": 0.2536715690540823
    },
    {
        "question": "1773261÷243=？",
        "answer": 3.8631663889724375
    },
    {
        "question": "7×2321735=？",
        "answer": 7.210910688403263
    },
    {
        "question": "38×187666=？",
        "answer": 6.853169193958962
    },
    {
        "question": "1×972=？",
        "answer": 2.9876662649262746
    },
    {
        "question": "12823×23530=？",
        "answer": 8.479611569443533
    },
    {
        "question": "2251×241=？",
        "answer": 5.734392537575388
    },
    {
        "question": "3×3248773=？",
        "answer": 6.9888406218690475
    },
    {
        "question": "10×19849=？",
        "answer": 5.297738631732803
    },
    {
        "question": "255×12165=？",
        "answer": 6.491652293700793
    },
    {
        "question": "12687÷2366=？",
        "answer": 0.7293441995746512
    },
    {
        "question": "1360×598=？",
        "answer": 5.910240092358628
    },
    {
        "question": "392×606=？",
        "answer": 5.375758691186744
    },
    {
        "question": "25×14187630=？",
        "answer": 8.549849862629427
    },
    {
        "question": "4699721÷3449589=？",
        "answer": 0.13430472241002103
    },
    {
        "question": "6307482÷53133=？",
        "answer": 2.0744916820476207
    },
    {
        "question": "51344×2195=？",
        "answer": 8.05192422432957
    },
    {
        "question": "14×2612205=？",
        "answer": 7.563135292077311
    },
    {
        "question": "95428618÷309809=？",
        "answer": 2.4885846044781452
    },
    {
        "question": "565735591÷221=？",
        "answer": 6.408221227821231
    },
    {
        "question": "2×17735=？",
        "answer": 4.549861188471943
    },
    {
        "question": "1×46972=？",
        "answer": 4.671839052209476
    },
    {
        "question": "14×618632=？",
        "answer": 6.937560416692922
    },
    {
        "question": "1×335=？",
        "answer": 2.525044807036845
    },
    {
        "question": "10×166489=？",
        "answer": 6.221385544766576
    },
    {
        "question": "4791×481=？",
        "answer": 6.362571247231977
    },
    {
        "question": "58×590209=？",
        "answer": 7.53443382126252
    },
    {
        "question": "5×15774465=？",
        "answer": 7.896924643156288
    },
    {
        "question": "122816066÷16976=？",
        "answer": 3.859419815547223
    },
    {
        "question": "1×3193773=？",
        "answer": 6.504304045067709
    },
    {
        "question": "1186×83651=？",
        "answer": 7.996555826100549
    },
    {
        "question": "8578782÷546=？",
        "answer": 4.1962329891733
    },
    {
        "question": "134865÷8202=？",
        "answer": 1.2159794917695226
    },
    {
        "question": "849488835÷235675=？",
        "answer": 3.5568441594707263
    },
    {
        "question": "224×1076=？",
        "answer": 5.382060289664533
    },
    {
        "question": "309676÷200=？",
        "answer": 3.1898775530203776
    },
    {
        "question": "139×73271=？",
        "answer": 7.007946919069179
    },
    {
        "question": "157997707÷31108=？",
        "answer": 3.7057786938582145
    },
    {
        "question": "167×243729=？",
        "answer": 7.609623677766313
    },
    {
        "question": "439642427÷74251085=？",
        "answer": 0.7723967924798896
    },
    {
        "question": "53254876÷34638211=？",
        "answer": 0.18680392438797042
    },
    {
        "question": "182123÷135046=？",
        "answer": 0.12988307044809233
    },
    {
        "question": "1696800÷5936=？",
        "answer": 2.456136763237535
    },
    {
        "question": "13924905÷1548255=？",
        "answer": 0.9539497497520762
    },
    {
        "question": "384×91598=？",
        "answer": 7.546217215519591
    },
    {
        "question": "245103÷255=？",
        "answer": 2.9828084465075237
    },
    {
        "question": "4566474÷40559=？",
        "answer": 2.051493750525484
    },
    {
        "question": "37969789÷5383=？",
        "answer": 3.848413803934847
    },
    {
        "question": "37294÷15269=？",
        "answer": 0.3878283713890249
    },
    {
        "question": "115287959÷20786=？",
        "answer": 3.744013027770906
    },
    {
        "question": "2280÷360=？",
        "answer": 0.8016323462331665
    },
    {
        "question": "223209362÷27334=？",
        "answer": 3.9120092160410675
    },
    {
        "question": "4×19780752=？",
        "answer": 7.898302789369829
    },
    {
        "question": "6×29278545=？",
        "answer": 8.244700741001827
    },
    {
        "question": "263319÷212=？",
        "answer": 3.0941463361850974
    },
    {
        "question": "601×796=？",
        "answer": 5.679787539740409
    },
    {
        "question": "30×8310040=？",
        "answer": 8.396724368965563
    },
    {
        "question": "521877706÷130092=？",
        "answer": 3.6033181542350126
    },
    {
        "question": "1729×32711=？",
        "answer": 7.752488814312493
    },
    {
        "question": "493905÷146813=？",
        "answer": 0.5268789095245695
    },
    {
        "question": "3×1838=？",
        "answer": 3.741466761769755
    },
    {
        "question": "361917÷405=？",
        "answer": 2.9511539600946692
    },
    {
        "question": "383922132÷862=？",
        "answer": 5.648735882834557
    },
    {
        "question": "41982517÷2160003=？",
        "answer": 1.2886141181759334
    },
    {
        "question": "70779×404=？",
        "answer": 7.456285787532617
    },
    {
        "question": "504×5920=？",
        "answer": 6.474752243168445
    },
    {
        "question": "429973892÷1521312=？",
        "answer": 2.4512237950692994
    },
    {
        "question": "2625606÷360=？",
        "answer": 3.8629270553868533
    },
    {
        "question": "216×21798=？",
        "answer": 6.672870399397289
    },
    {
        "question": "1288963÷561511=？",
        "answer": 0.36088218249305415
    },
    {
        "question": "1×403=？",
        "answer": 2.6053050461411096
    },
    {
        "question": "6×557=？",
        "answer": 3.5240064455573727
    },
    {
        "question": "112566÷68153=？",
        "answer": 0.2179222562065985
    },
    {
        "question": "265×1819796=？",
        "answer": 8.683268580031799
    },
    {
        "question": "77446481÷17399=？",
        "answer": 3.648477401032542
    },
    {
        "question": "15×207979=？",
        "answer": 6.494110744765823
    },
    {
        "question": "1087157÷164783=？",
        "answer": 0.819379861287243
    },
    {
        "question": "2429462÷205=？",
        "answer": 4.0737562494561015
    },
    {
        "question": "594342833÷1043=？",
        "answer": 5.755752721621716
    },
    {
        "question": "7146139÷100362=？",
        "answer": 1.852502152148975
    },
    {
        "question": "94982×3292=？",
        "answer": 8.495101136656931
    },
    {
        "question": "5897×1498=？",
        "answer": 6.946142941141254
    },
    {
        "question": "402×201=？",
        "answer": 4.907422110504959
    },
    {
        "question": "173974819÷652357=？",
        "answer": 2.4260010664705924
    },
    {
        "question": "1986×49519=？",
        "answer": 7.992751110000443
    },
    {
        "question": "31459672÷7918=？",
        "answer": 3.599138692920267
    },
    {
        "question": "27626128÷36258=？",
        "answer": 2.8819161750628495
    },
    {
        "question": "150509÷303=？",
        "answer": 2.696119841749629
    },
    {
        "question": "41107×9483=？",
        "answer": 8.590861533567105
    },
    {
        "question": "197881213÷784815=？",
        "answer": 2.4016372688714243
    },
    {
        "question": "41×112905=？",
        "answer": 6.665497031809689
    },
    {
        "question": "10×90800758=？",
        "answer": 8.95808947400394
    },
    {
        "question": "2×469=？",
        "answer": 2.9722028383790646
    },
    {
        "question": "260028460÷2151805=？",
        "answer": 2.0822179715922067
    },
    {
        "question": "220997555÷28434630=？",
        "answer": 0.8905398874534753
    },
    {
        "question": "153772÷659=？",
        "answer": 2.367991848358125
    },
    {
        "question": "34×10280=？",
        "answer": 5.543472031701512
    },
    {
        "question": "7889458÷115324=？",
        "answer": 1.8351274710878511
    },
    {
        "question": "3614×4392=？",
        "answer": 7.200650479666948
    },
    {
        "question": "301088858÷41274=？",
        "answer": 3.863018124611265
    },
    {
        "question": "21673×428=？",
        "answer": 6.967362800003884
    },
    {
        "question": "11011×9394=？",
        "answer": 8.014677318484773
    },
    {
        "question": "16707÷1954=？",
        "answer": 0.9319739132266672
    },
    {
        "question": "489560÷924=？",
        "answer": 2.7241339548925896
    },
    {
        "question": "266994202÷456320=？",
        "answer": 2.767232326567225
    },
    {
        "question": "476840÷57200=？",
        "answer": 0.920976650511796
    },
    {
        "question": "927×1315=？",
        "answer": 6.086005486970274
    },
    {
        "question": "9×230929=？",
        "answer": 6.317720984362273
    },
    {
        "question": "1408328÷1464=？",
        "answer": 2.9831627371750677
    },
    {
        "question": "1469×456626=？",
        "answer": 8.82658243210578
    },
    {
        "question": "1359×3582=？",
        "answer": 6.687345038245507
    },
    {
        "question": "357351176÷303=？",
        "answer": 6.071652587148454
    },
    {
        "question": "50553×8714=？",
        "answer": 8.643964488915202
    },
    {
        "question": "52×5658330=？",
        "answer": 8.468691616024017
    },
    {
        "question": "4×804=？",
        "answer": 3.5073160400764136
    },
    {
        "question": "2336÷2140=？",
        "answer": 0.03805906509117104
    },
    {
        "question": "83856×8962=？",
        "answer": 8.875939081935543
    },
    {
        "question": "901965÷11906=？",
        "answer": 1.879423807217803
    },
    {
        "question": "1376×59379=？",
        "answer": 7.9122513132804535
    },
    {
        "question": "1109×43165=？",
        "answer": 7.680063291396337
    },
    {
        "question": "5×20888085=？",
        "answer": 8.018868630431443
    },
    {
        "question": "2×1329325=？",
        "answer": 6.4246611680673675
    },
    {
        "question": "88×1256=？",
        "answer": 5.043472311551346
    },
    {
        "question": "6×972615=？",
        "answer": 6.76609221350496
    },
    {
        "question": "1×15542481=？",
        "answer": 7.191520345134599
    },
    {
        "question": "57296×388=？",
        "answer": 7.346956029262035
    },
    {
        "question": "7×34594=？",
        "answer": 5.384098821094574
    },
    {
        "question": "8495×6028=？",
        "answer": 7.709336626847659
    },
    {
        "question": "4367171÷837=？",
        "answer": 3.717474739401505
    },
    {
        "question": "515÷253=？",
        "answer": 0.30868670786537306
    },
    {
        "question": "340020×776=？",
        "answer": 8.421366184283329
    },
    {
        "question": "3750712÷55678=？",
        "answer": 1.8284300912821048
    },
    {
        "question": "19737403÷3152510=？",
        "answer": 0.7966335358074104
    },
    {
        "question": "32×206=？",
        "answer": 3.8190171986890595
    },
    {
        "question": "133395788÷55652=？",
        "answer": 3.3796613403997156
    },
    {
        "question": "469835621÷88280544=？",
        "answer": 0.7260809394114973
    },
    {
        "question": "497029÷78464=？",
        "answer": 0.8017112849544595
    },
    {
        "question": "271029÷1313=？",
        "answer": 2.3147510366157222
    },
    {
        "question": "947581355÷81246076=？",
        "answer": 1.0668141120527945
    },
    {
        "question": "82548×1305=？",
        "answer": 8.032317067171526
    },
    {
        "question": "24079117÷1508=？",
        "answer": 4.203239215426669
    },
    {
        "question": "19506×1504=？",
        "answer": 7.467416056135394
    },
    {
        "question": "47×2078=？",
        "answer": 4.989743401156876
    },
    {
        "question": "504837÷405913=？",
        "answer": 0.0947182167706017
    },
    {
        "question": "208380515÷30460460=？",
        "answer": 0.8351206494615095
    },
    {
        "question": "1999×879=？",
        "answer": 6.244801669191888
    },
    {
        "question": "372085÷5538=？",
        "answer": 1.8272892110910544
    },
    {
        "question": "218160685÷29137=？",
        "answer": 3.8743316546075857
    },
    {
        "question": "299×1156=？",
        "answer": 5.53862902240894
    },
    {
        "question": "164343481÷1041=？",
        "answer": 5.198301752123544
    },
    {
        "question": "395×2513206=？",
        "answer": 8.996825183501405
    },
    {
        "question": "553×361926=？",
        "answer": 8.301344914332587
    },
    {
        "question": "87707385÷2290=？",
        "answer": 4.583200680350195
    },
    {
        "question": "11534315÷5294664=？",
        "answer": 0.33815340279938816
    },
    {
        "question": "20×33152=？",
        "answer": 5.821539729393101
    },
    {
        "question": "1271430÷1196=？",
        "answer": 3.0265612749493176
    },
    {
        "question": "1412169×379=？",
        "answer": 8.728525883578675
    },
    {
        "question": "1×253960=？",
        "answer": 5.4047653184023146
    },
    {
        "question": "1448716÷795=？",
        "answer": 3.2606161279523485
    },
    {
        "question": "832×2885=？",
        "answer": 6.380269143782474
    },
    {
        "question": "524799151÷3001=？",
        "answer": 5.242727128358313
    },
    {
        "question": "43615×1825=？",
        "answer": 7.900898745604342
    },
    {
        "question": "35485923÷338052=？",
        "answer": 2.021072596173382
    },
    {
        "question": "242×125088=？",
        "answer": 7.481031014732585
    },
    {
        "question": "1×807=？",
        "answer": 2.90687353472207
    },
    {
        "question": "537×452809=？",
        "answer": 8.38588933597229
    },
    {
        "question": "1×74987793=？",
        "answer": 7.874990571868794
    },
    {
        "question": "1026272÷4936=？",
        "answer": 2.3178873290912936
    },
    {
        "question": "8×6456044=？",
        "answer": 7.713056468571523
    },
    {
        "question": "659×286029=？",
        "answer": 8.275295482343626
    },
    {
        "question": "13824×1297=？",
        "answer": 7.253573701218898
    },
    {
        "question": "21090÷1030=？",
        "answer": 1.3112393550343142
    },
    {
        "question": "3033×223278=？",
        "answer": 8.830718343640513
    },
    {
        "question": "335786303÷111684929=？",
        "answer": 0.4780684044780178
    },
    {
        "question": "45177741÷126325=？",
        "answer": 2.5534352044070947
    },
    {
        "question": "46×7041418=？",
        "answer": 8.510417957807114
    },
    {
        "question": "21226×1187=？",
        "answer": 7.401318878848272
    },
    {
        "question": "8065597÷3178=？",
        "answer": 3.404482625686848
    },
    {
        "question": "1×6962042=？",
        "answer": 6.8427366389300595
    },
    {
        "question": "437186563÷962528=？",
        "answer": 2.657253433353305
    },
    {
        "question": "1999800×494=？",
        "answer": 8.99471351296782
    },
    {
        "question": "2192×67173=？",
        "answer": 8.168035294483682
    },
    {
        "question": "2×9933456=？",
        "answer": 7.298130368087102
    },
    {
        "question": "4×37218=？",
        "answer": 5.172813022876572
    },
    {
        "question": "34500307÷167415=？",
        "answer": 2.3140285924575705
    },
    {
        "question": "20×1087=？",
        "answer": 4.337259539750276
    },
    {
        "question": "521138÷93728=？",
        "answer": 0.745083391920991
    },
    {
        "question": "2×240017=？",
        "answer": 5.681271998811934
    },
    {
        "question": "775071233÷768765546=？",
        "answer": 0.0035477070304660778
    },
    {
        "question": "11×334837=？",
        "answer": 6.56622612733482
    },
    {
        "question": "1989×36497=？",
        "answer": 7.860891950677026
    },
    {
        "question": "622175÷9112=？",
        "answer": 1.8342988453959868
    },
    {
        "question": "53×217=？",
        "answer": 4.060735603449318
    },
    {
        "question": "352758763÷10317619=？",
        "answer": 1.5338983244297764
    },
    {
        "question": "258770884÷9141696=？",
        "answer": 1.4518886343729112
    },
    {
        "question": "12×266669=？",
        "answer": 6.505153778379998
    },
    {
        "question": "237902873÷6587=？",
        "answer": 4.557712023322581
    },
    {
        "question": "8×1897=？",
        "answer": 4.181157317880606
    },
    {
        "question": "10×10614575=？",
        "answer": 8.025902610009329
    },
    {
        "question": "385510792÷21854140=？",
        "answer": 1.2465028193218453
    },
    {
        "question": "9×492=？",
        "answer": 3.6462076122066853
    },
    {
        "question": "201570×2166=？",
        "answer": 8.640084348098698
    },
    {
        "question": "995280÷303=？",
        "answer": 3.516502648573319
    },
    {
        "question": "346454÷44542=？",
        "answer": 0.8908758662805142
    },
    {
        "question": "32×446458=？",
        "answer": 7.15493058773443
    },
    {
        "question": "75831346÷6300995=？",
        "answer": 1.0804396297538947
    },
    {
        "question": "269590÷63552=？",
        "answer": 0.627574556239484
    },
    {
        "question": "14134580÷21190=？",
        "answer": 2.8241519515238434
    },
    {
        "question": "1778146÷311=？",
        "answer": 3.7572070281198298
    },
    {
        "question": "979804772÷431278135=？",
        "answer": 0.3563821095141786
    },
    {
        "question": "2349×417497=？",
        "answer": 8.991536375907103
    },
    {
        "question": "19901065÷9597664=？",
        "answer": 0.3167107763248944
    },
    {
        "question": "2483403÷425=？",
        "answer": 3.766658271370743
    },
    {
        "question": "2279862÷10705=？",
        "answer": 2.3283218883295023
    },
    {
        "question": "196×448135=？",
        "answer": 7.943664935629412
    },
    {
        "question": "17×7137020=？",
        "answer": 8.083965835156006
    },
    {
        "question": "910047221÷1226=？",
        "answer": 5.870573457619643
    },
    {
        "question": "3×26007=？",
        "answer": 4.8922115123907775
    },
    {
        "question": "56×1873=？",
        "answer": 5.020725804381438
    },
    {
        "question": "79360÷522=？",
        "answer": 2.18193115614386
    },
    {
        "question": "1803110÷197077=？",
        "answer": 0.9613862793567747
    },
    {
        "question": "888579668÷519138=？",
        "answer": 3.233413552082585
    },
    {
        "question": "2×29999601=？",
        "answer": 7.778145474228623
    },
    {
        "question": "8×2183=？",
        "answer": 4.2421437227010825
    },
    {
        "question": "1094605÷14270=？",
        "answer": 1.884833454491812
    },
    {
        "question": "16×628=？",
        "answer": 4.002079626393121
    },
    {
        "question": "102998÷1286=？",
        "answer": 1.9035878231325338
    },
    {
        "question": "1213×67668=？",
        "answer": 7.914244141502551
    },
    {
        "question": "114717÷1601=？",
        "answer": 1.8552364491826536
    },
    {
        "question": "24×1670455=？",
        "answer": 7.603046022484967
    },
    {
        "question": "11370×2752=？",
        "answer": 7.4954088942512085
    },
    {
        "question": "1966020÷67664=？",
        "answer": 1.4632302637225174
    },
    {
        "question": "1×2349=？",
        "answer": 3.370883016777606
    },
    {
        "question": "114×96107=？",
        "answer": 7.0396598722064585
    },
    {
        "question": "8497254÷26276=？",
        "answer": 2.509719347186294
    },
    {
        "question": "411377342÷56202=？",
        "answer": 3.8644885971646468
    },
    {
        "question": "164096823÷127734808=？",
        "answer": 0.10879091342918681
    },
    {
        "question": "14532÷11302=？",
        "answer": 0.10917008622879762
    },
    {
        "question": "3518912÷30768=？",
        "answer": 2.0583091393575885
    },
    {
        "question": "12444980÷138268=？",
        "answer": 1.9542725220355686
    },
    {
        "question": "25×115263=？",
        "answer": 6.459629927634972
    },
    {
        "question": "63116÷20824=？",
        "answer": 0.48157531239781454
    },
    {
        "question": "23×640=？",
        "answer": 4.16790781000148
    },
    {
        "question": "13199÷2327=？",
        "answer": 0.7537446455756894
    },
    {
        "question": "10903787÷24492=？",
        "answer": 2.648553108421308
    },
    {
        "question": "2192459÷1328130=？",
        "answer": 0.21769089388749135
    },
    {
        "question": "4858736÷391699=？",
        "answer": 1.0935708394577643
    },
    {
        "question": "764081÷75314=？",
        "answer": 1.0062636864278598
    },
    {
        "question": "1033119÷493=？",
        "answer": 3.321303429412562
    },
    {
        "question": "4×146293=？",
        "answer": 5.767283537315854
    },
    {
        "question": "213551÷1087=？",
        "answer": 2.2932720653617045
    },
    {
        "question": "2×60507886=？",
        "answer": 8.082841975656851
    },
    {
        "question": "18×13289=？",
        "answer": 5.3787648065259575
    },
    {
        "question": "4366×222317=？",
        "answer": 8.987056404705964
    },
    {
        "question": "9×289=？",
        "answer": 3.4151403521958725
    },
    {
        "question": "18×453=？",
        "answer": 3.911370707116138
    },
    {
        "question": "3074×2683=？",
        "answer": 6.916324535835665
    },
    {
        "question": "207×6490=？",
        "answer": 6.128215042257287
    },
    {
        "question": "345515911÷245=？",
        "answer": 6.149301967057393
    },
    {
        "question": "23681÷15795=？",
        "answer": 0.17588040756106965
    },
    {
        "question": "12204666÷3188=？",
        "answer": 3.583007586035953
    },
    {
        "question": "8758×210=？",
        "answer": 6.264624235590026
    },
    {
        "question": "2×111097262=？",
        "answer": 8.346733351518044
    },
    {
        "question": "1384338÷1672=？",
        "answer": 2.918005867316233
    },
    {
        "question": "107×1264349=？",
        "answer": 8.131250747085208
    },
    {
        "question": "199327002÷2812=？",
        "answer": 4.850550818405249
    },
    {
        "question": "5×77272224=？",
        "answer": 8.586993416348461
    },
    {
        "question": "122027÷57947=？",
        "answer": 0.32342497756511185
    },
    {
        "question": "2×160079515=？",
        "answer": 8.505365755492893
    },
    {
        "question": "115804161÷24924=？",
        "answer": 3.667106421876682
    },
    {
        "question": "1×686058567=？",
        "answer": 8.836361191857215
    },
    {
        "question": "19535446÷50153=？",
        "answer": 2.5905264144361015
    },
    {
        "question": "511781295÷3614005=？",
        "answer": 2.1510956598178064
    },
    {
        "question": "19050766÷1510=？",
        "answer": 4.1009354953371036
    },
    {
        "question": "77616×1056=？",
        "answer": 7.913615175479782
    },
    {
        "question": "46686×1648=？",
        "answer": 7.8861438730600515
    },
    {
        "question": "727×50987=？",
        "answer": 7.568993870330437
    },
    {
        "question": "424159071÷29980281=？",
        "answer": 1.1506930600927523
    },
    {
        "question": "8×494301=？",
        "answer": 6.597081476056893
    },
    {
        "question": "545×521227=？",
        "answer": 8.45342340672183
    },
    {
        "question": "11×462=？",
        "answer": 3.7060346607143506
    },
    {
        "question": "233591÷21882=？",
        "answer": 1.0283690921845716
    },
    {
        "question": "42×11825532=？",
        "answer": 8.696069978029081
    },
    {
        "question": "24296×6738=？",
        "answer": 8.21406578555531
    },
    {
        "question": "8310828÷272479=？",
        "answer": 1.4843112575342081
    },
    {
        "question": "2×201645=？",
        "answer": 5.605617453352368
    },
    {
        "question": "33×1280=？",
        "answer": 4.625723909525756
    },
    {
        "question": "22442676÷1390244=？",
        "answer": 1.2079836102643582
    },
    {
        "question": "90152÷28740=？",
        "answer": 0.49648860208360845
    },
    {
        "question": "661841÷813=？",
        "answer": 2.910663121917312
    },
    {
        "question": "80×12165578=？",
        "answer": 8.988222734557777
    },
    {
        "question": "240×11007=？",
        "answer": 6.421880208187217
    },
    {
        "question": "740080÷94865=？",
        "answer": 0.8921726568965842
    },
    {
        "question": "2×4284=？",
        "answer": 3.932879457823799
    },
    {
        "question": "25×7990=？",
        "answer": 5.300486787986029
    },
    {
        "question": "1876×502=？",
        "answer": 5.973936551188065
    },
    {
        "question": "86842÷258=？",
        "answer": 2.527110110879974
    },
    {
        "question": "40140÷446=？",
        "answer": 1.954242509439325
    },
    {
        "question": "72013616÷5163=？",
        "answer": 4.144512493531208
    },
    {
        "question": "97×281806=？",
        "answer": 7.43672196980733
    },
    {
        "question": "678÷302=？",
        "answer": 0.35122275090991273
    },
    {
        "question": "3574÷1017=？",
        "answer": 0.5458335952468808
    },
    {
        "question": "4×916055=？",
        "answer": 6.563981540846714
    },
    {
        "question": "2665277÷487=？",
        "answer": 3.738213390354318
    },
    {
        "question": "9902142÷3958363=？",
        "answer": 0.3982135314791127
    },
    {
        "question": "317719122÷309=？",
        "answer": 6.012084874304332
    },
    {
        "question": "2×853690=？",
        "answer": 6.232330189853307
    },
    {
        "question": "1194×212=？",
        "answer": 5.403340187722102
    },
    {
        "question": "15×1097=？",
        "answer": 4.216297886630392
    },
    {
        "question": "36444×8517=？",
        "answer": 8.49191268521141
    },
    {
        "question": "7×33599478=？",
        "answer": 8.371430570276702
    },
    {
        "question": "11×4089=？",
        "answer": 4.653009795712561
    },
    {
        "question": "38×411900=？",
        "answer": 7.194575388573227
    },
    {
        "question": "462×8421=？",
        "answer": 6.590005642910227
    },
    {
        "question": "12623211÷640447=？",
        "answer": 1.2946866459542399
    },
    {
        "question": "13957895÷2090963=？",
        "answer": 0.8244735790082535
    },
    {
        "question": "7495922÷26703=？",
        "answer": 2.4482650030272595
    },
    {
        "question": "13×240=？",
        "answer": 3.494154594018443
    },
    {
        "question": "2×701176=？",
        "answer": 6.1468570382170205
    },
    {
        "question": "407×3639=？",
        "answer": 6.170576464811456
    },
    {
        "question": "405323÷199586=？",
        "answer": 0.30767117407763106
    },
    {
        "question": "625644001÷1530=？",
        "answer": 5.611635853862564
    },
    {
        "question": "208423÷278=？",
        "answer": 2.874900846837628
    },
    {
        "question": "3×569120=？",
        "answer": 6.232325102561368
    },
    {
        "question": "685303÷316=？",
        "answer": 3.3361955503818215
    },
    {
        "question": "49×4135=？",
        "answer": 5.306671593917079
    },
    {
        "question": "143×36656=？",
        "answer": 6.719481109310384
    },
    {
        "question": "510491200÷2699132=？",
        "answer": 2.2767641359107804
    },
    {
        "question": "35455÷2240=？",
        "answer": 1.1994294713763933
    },
    {
        "question": "59723856÷8064=？",
        "answer": 3.869597320565411
    },
    {
        "question": "16306340÷381=？",
        "answer": 4.631431517787949
    },
    {
        "question": "4559918÷551894=？",
        "answer": 0.9171013603206734
    },
    {
        "question": "15×6864255=？",
        "answer": 8.012684667788497
    },
    {
        "question": "61597×993=？",
        "answer": 7.786508809439469
    },
    {
        "question": "14×18704=？",
        "answer": 5.4180625294960025
    },
    {
        "question": "170900567÷1759=？",
        "answer": 4.987477664132572
    },
    {
        "question": "82×7601=？",
        "answer": 5.794684584916141
    },
    {
        "question": "468×40724=？",
        "answer": 7.280096281848065
    },
    {
        "question": "195462962÷325454=？",
        "answer": 2.77857486206393
    },
    {
        "question": "2599×18484=？",
        "answer": 7.68160223934768
    },
    {
        "question": "1×31006=？",
        "answer": 4.491445742697271
    },
    {
        "question": "281×227191=？",
        "answer": 7.805097443036688
    },
    {
        "question": "262167×1043=？",
        "answer": 8.436862332852069
    },
    {
        "question": "3×346=？",
        "answer": 3.016197353512439
    },
    {
        "question": "70655÷5388=？",
        "answer": 1.117715313678202
    },
    {
        "question": "1265646÷1940=？",
        "answer": 2.8145105209761567
    },
    {
        "question": "135585÷62696=？",
        "answer": 0.3349718116888351
    },
    {
        "question": "6×1168968=？",
        "answer": 6.84595387308215
    },
    {
        "question": "97981539÷34905549=？",
        "answer": 0.4482497836064093
    },
    {
        "question": "13605207÷255202=？",
        "answer": 1.726821080256098
    },
    {
        "question": "19040197÷398175=？",
        "answer": 1.6795974487804268
    },
    {
        "question": "11183×29737=？",
        "answer": 8.52185547774737
    },
    {
        "question": "128×4133=？",
        "answer": 5.723475374929577
    },
    {
        "question": "584260900÷391968158=？",
        "answer": 0.1733560353349068
    },
    {
        "question": "2402×8876=？",
        "answer": 7.328790296626858
    },
    {
        "question": "28792×3477=？",
        "answer": 8.000476524328112
    },
    {
        "question": "70903×5082=？",
        "answer": 8.556699271861902
    },
    {
        "question": "25256314÷10311064=？",
        "answer": 0.3890664858004461
    },
    {
        "question": "23172×34480=？",
        "answer": 8.902530776979695
    },
    {
        "question": "1529×246483=？",
        "answer": 8.576194456649137
    },
    {
        "question": "131218409÷115186=？",
        "answer": 3.056595070672827
    },
    {
        "question": "1×6241356=？",
        "answer": 6.795278954961289
    },
    {
        "question": "8586776÷8270190=？",
        "answer": 0.016314646586496912
    },
    {
        "question": "69899×618=？",
        "answer": 7.635459437707337
    },
    {
        "question": "15047×1047=？",
        "answer": 7.1973966026506675
    },
    {
        "question": "89854966÷52480=？",
        "answer": 3.233548257824176
    },
    {
        "question": "17×230925=？",
        "answer": 6.593919873673172
    },
    {
        "question": "9913×3354=？",
        "answer": 7.521768164448392
    },
    {
        "question": "98×17246=？",
        "answer": 6.227914457457111
    },
    {
        "question": "787×85329=？",
        "answer": 7.827071388374608
    },
    {
        "question": "152×115939=？",
        "answer": 7.246073138107912
    },
    {
        "question": "25×49187=？",
        "answer": 6.089790343669314
    },
    {
        "question": "10×37415=？",
        "answer": 5.5730457495590535
    },
    {
        "question": "14×1150214=？",
        "answer": 7.2069066850517025
    },
    {
        "question": "420845432÷274448=？",
        "answer": 3.185662547285812
    },
    {
        "question": "6×17627002=？",
        "answer": 8.024329704170555
    },
    {
        "question": "80×7457431=？",
        "answer": 8.77567923072797
    },
    {
        "question": "38×336071=？",
        "answer": 7.106214634872187
    },
    {
        "question": "155×909=？",
        "answer": 5.148895581392259
    },
    {
        "question": "1×85494=？",
        "answer": 4.931935636853013
    },
    {
        "question": "230233÷3269=？",
        "answer": 1.8477526519312548
    },
    {
        "question": "11415404÷43717=？",
        "answer": 2.4168409344893207
    },
    {
        "question": "42992642÷39214=？",
        "answer": 3.03995298986305
    },
    {
        "question": "485551006÷58531=？",
        "answer": 3.918848914179233
    },
    {
        "question": "3024508÷462=？",
        "answer": 3.816012762022989
    },
    {
        "question": "164773÷1625=？",
        "answer": 2.006032683601564
    },
    {
        "question": "22×333=？",
        "answer": 3.864866914328526
    },
    {
        "question": "1094÷746=？",
        "answer": 0.1662784945247432
    },
    {
        "question": "1656×27547=？",
        "answer": 7.659134641466492
    },
    {
        "question": "8×124957=？",
        "answer": 5.9998505769959944
    },
    {
        "question": "4300892÷217=？",
        "answer": 4.297098803243357
    },
    {
        "question": "3513401÷991=？",
        "answer": 3.5496540660862808
    },
    {
        "question": "2×167541=？",
        "answer": 5.525151098946473
    },
    {
        "question": "130×7255539=？",
        "answer": 8.97461303317855
    },
    {
        "question": "59629926÷970689=？",
        "answer": 1.7883841622331782
    },
    {
        "question": "3719×243=？",
        "answer": 5.9560324519572845
    },
    {
        "question": "8861÷8344=？",
        "answer": 0.02610844113844414
    },
    {
        "question": "37799×1083=？",
        "answer": 7.612108767038561
    },
    {
        "question": "187564144÷1190=？",
        "answer": 5.197602857984857
    },
    {
        "question": "197648009÷2648=？",
        "answer": 4.87297446308376
    },
    {
        "question": "121566÷262=？",
        "answer": 2.6665108356145284
    },
    {
        "question": "78366405÷635=？",
        "answer": 5.0913561989995735
    },
    {
        "question": "228424÷316=？",
        "answer": 2.859054649704891
    },
    {
        "question": "843528÷244=？",
        "answer": 3.5387096767614805
    },
    {
        "question": "2207819×263=？",
        "answer": 8.763919214954843
    },
    {
        "question": "16×4124=？",
        "answer": 4.819438639267403
    },
    {
        "question": "24172367÷11892960=？",
        "answer": 0.30802922114878634
    },
    {
        "question": "685×18323=？",
        "answer": 7.09868715309392
    },
    {
        "question": "126654800÷235688=？",
        "answer": 2.730284182371378
    },
    {
        "question": "1916÷353=？",
        "answer": 0.734620799354703
    },
    {
        "question": "6930651÷219=？",
        "answer": 4.50032991521599
    },
    {
        "question": "850920849÷28487537=？",
        "answer": 1.4752342624801236
    },
    {
        "question": "33×538715=？",
        "answer": 7.2498730081035045
    },
    {
        "question": "7×26059=？",
        "answer": 5.261055785895247
    },
    {
        "question": "987×6358=？",
        "answer": 6.7976376762483905
    },
    {
        "question": "18×355141=？",
        "answer": 6.805673318339556
    },
    {
        "question": "640181÷339953=？",
        "answer": 0.2748839024602888
    },
    {
        "question": "72385828÷12120=？",
        "answer": 3.7761509267002147
    },
    {
        "question": "2135394÷16076=？",
        "answer": 2.123300020594685
    },
    {
        "question": "223951÷28499=？",
        "answer": 0.8953233846856063
    },
    {
        "question": "960÷274=？",
        "answer": 0.5445206702191805
    },
    {
        "question": "8018÷1874=？",
        "answer": 0.6312964653627434
    },
    {
        "question": "759108350÷36923=？",
        "answer": 4.31300678829393
    },
    {
        "question": "1×319=？",
        "answer": 2.503790683057181
    },
    {
        "question": "897630÷664=？",
        "answer": 3.1309292794914105
    },
    {
        "question": "904503950÷43359166=？",
        "answer": 1.3193295476868725
    },
    {
        "question": "564664÷267=？",
        "answer": 3.325278838928125
    },
    {
        "question": "1×8348682=？",
        "answer": 6.921617919159416
    },
    {
        "question": "576539×1103=？",
        "answer": 8.803404202929388
    },
    {
        "question": "2708976÷277119=？",
        "answer": 0.9901388542827351
    },
    {
        "question": "3×8954=？",
        "answer": 4.429138344767089
    },
    {
        "question": "684677646÷15140817=？",
        "answer": 1.655336838473877
    },
    {
        "question": "2527598÷165492=？",
        "answer": 1.1839309985324373
    },
    {
        "question": "128206÷61561=？",
        "answer": 0.318602684583669
    },
    {
        "question": "1×33759=？",
        "answer": 4.528389573590047
    },
    {
        "question": "309×768=？",
        "answer": 5.375319699456346
    },
    {
        "question": "7×6227490=？",
        "answer": 7.639411078840496
    },
    {
        "question": "4532447÷16620=？",
        "answer": 2.4357017149428146
    },
    {
        "question": "9771×8597=？",
        "answer": 7.924285940022791
    },
    {
        "question": "525961874÷8022=？",
        "answer": 4.81667160644817
    },
    {
        "question": "46508504÷216222=？",
        "answer": 2.3326324900032565
    },
    {
        "question": "792×12654=？",
        "answer": 7.000953011712624
    },
    {
        "question": "98×858137=？",
        "answer": 7.924782703394775
    },
    {
        "question": "115380×6802=？",
        "answer": 8.894767162218827
    },
    {
        "question": "101×15866=？",
        "answer": 6.204788823732802
    },
    {
        "question": "21×32522512=？",
        "answer": 8.834403377338782
    },
    {
        "question": "33×8947=？",
        "answer": 5.470191377221188
    },
    {
        "question": "10467×49202=？",
        "answer": 8.71180498082355
    },
    {
        "question": "24×4780128=？",
        "answer": 8.059650767811046
    },
    {
        "question": "95×330626=？",
        "answer": 7.4970606082222115
    },
    {
        "question": "77452÷3432=？",
        "answer": 1.353485357608669
    },
    {
        "question": "272643576÷5127=？",
        "answer": 4.725731951900911
    },
    {
        "question": "251×625=？",
        "answer": 5.195553738825113
    },
    {
        "question": "15480÷1784=？",
        "answer": 0.9383761063067696
    },
    {
        "question": "211×953552=？",
        "answer": 8.303626836683158
    },
    {
        "question": "70284211÷3970898=？",
        "answer": 1.247969042336811
    },
    {
        "question": "482257735÷292346=？",
        "answer": 3.2173820460668123
    },
    {
        "question": "665÷662=？",
        "answer": 0.001963655863404623
    },
    {
        "question": "7359÷5377=？",
        "answer": 0.13627876644892892
    },
    {
        "question": "108034571÷5255=？",
        "answer": 4.312990031345308
    },
    {
        "question": "20349113÷3344=？",
        "answer": 3.7842792146910162
    },
    {
        "question": "24900864÷6419=？",
        "answer": 3.5887470406452935
    },
    {
        "question": "2×61772122=？",
        "answer": 8.09182251617055
    },
    {
        "question": "616851853÷12947645=？",
        "answer": 1.67799009031818
    },
    {
        "question": "1529127÷236945=？",
        "answer": 0.8097960080973398
    },
    {
        "question": "737505÷41870=？",
        "answer": 1.245862008118358
    },
    {
        "question": "37904÷319=？",
        "answer": 2.0748943603215086
    },
    {
        "question": "117893×5787=？",
        "answer": 8.833941501609402
    },
    {
        "question": "18424×250=？",
        "answer": 6.663323933628212
    },
    {
        "question": "291523049÷1827683=？",
        "answer": 2.2027720252318694
    },
    {
        "question": "5503855÷631641=？",
        "answer": 0.9401966713842224
    },
    {
        "question": "192431992÷55090=？",
        "answer": 3.543204503197807
    },
    {
        "question": "56824984÷476332=？",
        "answer": 2.076629563704584
    },
    {
        "question": "266831÷5180=？",
        "answer": 1.7119065240706661
    },
    {
        "question": "13481×8259=？",
        "answer": 8.046649574808871
    },
    {
        "question": "993308÷132240=？",
        "answer": 0.8757210926853096
    },
    {
        "question": "61391448÷225=？",
        "answer": 5.435925358810122
    },
    {
        "question": "117625234÷34490=？",
        "answer": 3.532807306040783
    },
    {
        "question": "6149961÷123494=？",
        "answer": 1.6972265039480385
    },
    {
        "question": "256648÷25359=？",
        "answer": 1.0052057605556735
    },
    {
        "question": "4572167÷1778656=？",
        "answer": 0.41003012305454695
    },
    {
        "question": "837×26018=？",
        "answer": 7.337999367346148
    },
    {
        "question": "50×5582=？",
        "answer": 5.445759836488631
    },
    {
        "question": "11×1018=？",
        "answer": 4.049140463158965
    },
    {
        "question": "21×17325=？",
        "answer": 5.560892538017764
    },
    {
        "question": "211560÷2852=？",
        "answer": 1.870284037167119
    },
    {
        "question": "10793÷1512=？",
        "answer": 0.8535903858954369
    },
    {
        "question": "1×422487318=？",
        "answer": 8.62581367706019
    },
    {
        "question": "480110÷20711=？",
        "answer": 1.3651396831257294
    },
    {
        "question": "373424674÷4320271=？",
        "answer": 1.9366920206312699
    },
    {
        "question": "31605×1758=？",
        "answer": 7.744774665401534
    },
    {
        "question": "15×630=？",
        "answer": 3.975431808509263
    },
    {
        "question": "120843×5889=？",
        "answer": 8.852263052675903
    },
    {
        "question": "57×1374=？",
        "answer": 4.893861588396023
    },
    {
        "question": "7×1001=？",
        "answer": 3.8455321174935753
    },
    {
        "question": "10×6250953=？",
        "answer": 7.795946233518483
    },
    {
        "question": "865×58902=？",
        "answer": 7.707146148843042
    },
    {
        "question": "23208342÷688015=？",
        "answer": 1.528046208878297
    },
    {
        "question": "125×2620884=？",
        "answer": 8.515357812560246
    },
    {
        "question": "52629672÷1030652=？",
        "answer": 1.708118613050244
    },
    {
        "question": "53363111÷510=？",
        "answer": 5.01967096435233
    },
    {
        "question": "13×764275=？",
        "answer": 6.997193006030733
    },
    {
        "question": "2×42239189=？",
        "answer": 7.926745566737889
    },
    {
        "question": "1211841÷214186=？",
        "answer": 0.7526545615087568
    },
    {
        "question": "101455132÷4764694=？",
        "answer": 1.3282390058060438
    },
    {
        "question": "4×420686=？",
        "answer": 6.226018050709077
    },
    {
        "question": "193904313÷10729=？",
        "answer": 4.257028223876609
    },
    {
        "question": "101471÷311=？",
        "answer": 2.513581551355025
    },
    {
        "question": "18579×9079=？",
        "answer": 8.227060350827571
    },
    {
        "question": "132007×965=？",
        "answer": 8.105124274706979
    },
    {
        "question": "505488×716=？",
        "answer": 8.558623872451212
    },
    {
        "question": "3879×1398=？",
        "answer": 6.7342269510097195
    },
    {
        "question": "94×365988=？",
        "answer": 7.536594699597334
    },
    {
        "question": "26×2613=？",
        "answer": 4.832112757698144
    },
    {
        "question": "231072÷19321=？",
        "answer": 1.0777177228064083
    },
    {
        "question": "1×2760306=？",
        "answer": 6.440957229436613
    },
    {
        "question": "27313×244=？",
        "answer": 6.823759231051519
    },
    {
        "question": "49×14541047=？",
        "answer": 8.852791758212607
    },
    {
        "question": "1941×891=？",
        "answer": 6.237903239425238
    },
    {
        "question": "26192287÷1076=？",
        "answer": 4.386361149512443
    },
    {
        "question": "5823÷267=？",
        "answer": 1.33863552874345
    },
    {
        "question": "886072×933=？",
        "answer": 8.917350656753454
    },
    {
        "question": "29×1264=？",
        "answer": 4.5641450718453225
    },
    {
        "question": "941929÷7919=？",
        "answer": 2.0753478251454887
    },
    {
        "question": "2311442÷2355=？",
        "answer": 2.9918920888850122
    },
    {
        "question": "32785×16937=？",
        "answer": 8.744511675530468
    },
    {
        "question": "411766937÷49032896=？",
        "answer": 0.9241639273497083
    },
    {
        "question": "83244×1060=？",
        "answer": 7.945658805811927
    },
    {
        "question": "163418883÷929=？",
        "answer": 5.245286523691645
    },
    {
        "question": "51×17519=？",
        "answer": 5.951079488724711
    },
    {
        "question": "36×2397=？",
        "answer": 4.9359705348009415
    },
    {
        "question": "369241627÷510=？",
        "answer": 5.8597404798456285
    },
    {
        "question": "99606÷512=？",
        "answer": 2.289015538978065
    },
    {
        "question": "340152025÷120660=？",
        "answer": 3.4501097397746987
    },
    {
        "question": "1200×336737=？",
        "answer": 8.606472084482013
    },
    {
        "question": "24200521÷413812=？",
        "answer": 1.7670216352962098
    },
    {
        "question": "7321539÷4191831=？",
        "answer": 0.24219861500560466
    },
    {
        "question": "3085×6339=？",
        "answer": 7.291275920141237
    },
    {
        "question": "1×427=？",
        "answer": 2.630427875025024
    },
    {
        "question": "13922976÷4138=？",
        "answer": 3.526941588186083
    },
    {
        "question": "881×839281=？",
        "answer": 8.868883299893369
    },
    {
        "question": "627822970÷288=？",
        "answer": 6.33844471331769
    },
    {
        "question": "25×6310521=？",
        "answer": 8.19800522498185
    },
    {
        "question": "2982078÷3649=？",
        "answer": 2.912345135419183
    },
    {
        "question": "220×8305=？",
        "answer": 6.2617623176096195
    },
    {
        "question": "1098079÷138207=？",
        "answer": 0.9001035460120858
    },
    {
        "question": "13×2502844=？",
        "answer": 7.512377133576854
    },
    {
        "question": "745902024÷817=？",
        "answer": 5.960459729076196
    },
    {
        "question": "249×605448=？",
        "answer": 8.178276196006953
    },
    {
        "question": "157×2162765=？",
        "answer": 8.530908985187308
    },
    {
        "question": "4182÷1472=？",
        "answer": 0.45347621848017305
    },
    {
        "question": "50262968÷3879=？",
        "answer": 4.112528350258661
    },
    {
        "question": "198×293270=？",
        "answer": 7.76393282944111
    },
    {
        "question": "21709×390=？",
        "answer": 6.927704425668188
    },
    {
        "question": "72894073÷2917736=？",
        "answer": 1.3976462234838403
    },
    {
        "question": "2892×1700=？",
        "answer": 6.691647210000768
    },
    {
        "question": "298×148950=？",
        "answer": 7.647256771627318
    },
    {
        "question": "10797÷534=？",
        "answer": 1.3057618443440173
    },
    {
        "question": "499186986÷35265060=？",
        "answer": 1.1509186275047072
    },
    {
        "question": "12707÷299=？",
        "answer": 1.6283718415975794
    },
    {
        "question": "5×360571=？",
        "answer": 6.255960798695673
    },
    {
        "question": "1×16601=？",
        "answer": 4.220134249570252
    },
    {
        "question": "2638×774=？",
        "answer": 6.310015751893239
    },
    {
        "question": "7767865÷1607=？",
        "answer": 3.684285792471243
    },
    {
        "question": "707151÷13606=？",
        "answer": 1.7157816932327314
    },
    {
        "question": "17439×1739=？",
        "answer": 7.481821159678763
    },
    {
        "question": "2312×54017=？",
        "answer": 8.096518290391762
    },
    {
        "question": "58790÷11505=？",
        "answer": 0.7084168371844195
    },
    {
        "question": "26860÷482=？",
        "answer": 1.746058970093847
    },
    {
        "question": "4×36756=？",
        "answer": 5.16738823418216
    },
    {
        "question": "5×15117=？",
        "answer": 4.87843561741145
    },
    {
        "question": "3389×36577=？",
        "answer": 8.093279651145773
    },
    {
        "question": "5×19558=？",
        "answer": 4.990294446128439
    },
    {
        "question": "858×581558=？",
        "answer": 8.69808032217341
    },
    {
        "question": "276540÷888=？",
        "answer": 2.493344992729563
    },
    {
        "question": "114722650÷4268=？",
        "answer": 4.429424759536815
    },
    {
        "question": "1×352831630=？",
        "answer": 8.547567511036657
    },
    {
        "question": "62×586431=？",
        "answer": 7.560608609475609
    },
    {
        "question": "3953835÷213824=？",
        "answer": 1.2669620919148894
    },
    {
        "question": "29970÷14897=？",
        "answer": 0.30358792517941646
    },
    {
        "question": "132466÷1375=？",
        "answer": 1.9838017242030273
    },
    {
        "question": "4972×9042=？",
        "answer": 7.652795622667883
    },
    {
        "question": "9670÷3703=？",
        "answer": 0.41687276203355905
    },
    {
        "question": "1016314÷3683=？",
        "answer": 2.440826189288826
    },
    {
        "question": "109637915÷2496=？",
        "answer": 4.642716186894973
    },
    {
        "question": "1×405755114=？",
        "answer": 8.60826400223329
    },
    {
        "question": "23×259=？",
        "answer": 3.7750276000988445
    },
    {
        "question": "15382128÷926669=？",
        "answer": 1.220091786204084
    },
    {
        "question": "639360÷12725=？",
        "answer": 1.7010876712010732
    },
    {
        "question": "12766189÷1277=？",
        "answer": 3.999870372491148
    },
    {
        "question": "1501327÷6380=？",
        "answer": 2.3716546163392853
    },
    {
        "question": "12544807÷5622000=？",
        "answer": 0.34857314287424335
    },
    {
        "question": "95488×6826=？",
        "answer": 8.814115081063157
    },
    {
        "question": "60344÷1153=？",
        "answer": 1.7188047874131887
    },
    {
        "question": "239307143÷4481309=？",
        "answer": 1.727550771037631
    },
    {
        "question": "11802885÷342=？",
        "answer": 4.537962069592253
    },
    {
        "question": "30×30816716=？",
        "answer": 8.965907610741615
    },
    {
        "question": "561163÷56627=？",
        "answer": 0.9960654742427411
    },
    {
        "question": "27985÷2170=？",
        "answer": 1.1104655773942191
    },
    {
        "question": "392×10203=？",
        "answer": 6.6020139536728415
    },
    {
        "question": "39180560÷20772=？",
        "answer": 3.27559232506525
    },
    {
        "question": "1×16902=？",
        "answer": 4.227938097369417
    },
    {
        "question": "1012×10489=？",
        "answer": 7.025914597915296
    },
    {
        "question": "2476814÷2016530=？",
        "answer": 0.08928870641715901
    },
    {
        "question": "3908×12835=？",
        "answer": 7.700350428054198
    },
    {
        "question": "27×428=？",
        "answer": 4.062807533172159
    },
    {
        "question": "727203936÷4729=？",
        "answer": 5.186886906828923
    },
    {
        "question": "1×416=？",
        "answer": 2.6190933306267428
    },
    {
        "question": "14704÷280=？",
        "answer": 1.7202774626998167
    },
    {
        "question": "487×666=？",
        "answer": 5.511003190384935
    },
    {
        "question": "1×14428=？",
        "answer": 4.159206133646325
    },
    {
        "question": "22116÷5359=？",
        "answer": 0.6156228242230868
    },
    {
        "question": "1×618=？",
        "answer": 2.790988475088816
    },
    {
        "question": "3680×1475=？",
        "answer": 6.734639838987699
    },
    {
        "question": "10×17800=？",
        "answer": 5.250420002308894
    },
    {
        "question": "19901×19427=？",
        "answer": 8.58728063988045
    },
    {
        "question": "372×784=？",
        "answer": 5.464859002566336
    },
    {
        "question": "1866×223366=？",
        "answer": 8.619928706416825
    },
    {
        "question": "922×265079=？",
        "answer": 8.388106244617095
    },
    {
        "question": "4775220÷388=？",
        "answer": 4.090161659243894
    },
    {
        "question": "16×5140=？",
        "answer": 4.9150831016512
    },
    {
        "question": "8104÷2142=？",
        "answer": 0.5778799658563871
    },
    {
        "question": "252718897÷34439=？",
        "answer": 3.865587184986627
    },
    {
        "question": "397754×1594=？",
        "answer": 8.802102872868826
    },
    {
        "question": "1495729÷209=？",
        "answer": 3.8547066279615168
    },
    {
        "question": "89159÷8863=？",
        "answer": 1.0025844395200576
    },
    {
        "question": "267483778÷16609=？",
        "answer": 4.206953963545386
    },
    {
        "question": "421646÷9234=？",
        "answer": 1.6595581144760618
    },
    {
        "question": "1×67690=？",
        "answer": 4.830524514097259
    },
    {
        "question": "1×149811=？",
        "answer": 5.1755437029756655
    },
    {
        "question": "74367486÷15103700=？",
        "answer": 0.6922997495828077
    },
    {
        "question": "34659÷2679=？",
        "answer": 1.111843314453847
    },
    {
        "question": "2×27471068=？",
        "answer": 7.739905539594568
    },
    {
        "question": "30831×20560=？",
        "answer": 8.802010721570625
    },
    {
        "question": "222020846÷1518546=？",
        "answer": 2.1649658010187
    },
    {
        "question": "582312118÷129462=？",
        "answer": 3.653013515980346
    },
    {
        "question": "1422199÷12296=？",
        "answer": 2.063196514444374
    },
    {
        "question": "10137÷864=？",
        "answer": 1.0693957040156654
    },
    {
        "question": "824323÷206=？",
        "answer": 3.6022301971910733
    },
    {
        "question": "61×209=？",
        "answer": 4.105476121121821
    },
    {
        "question": "4046812÷1276=？",
        "answer": 3.501262354750904
    },
    {
        "question": "3×2236963=？",
        "answer": 6.826780055522272
    },
    {
        "question": "11421461÷2229=？",
        "answer": 3.709611592667277
    },
    {
        "question": "18597421÷49001=？",
        "answer": 2.5792477794536834
    },
    {
        "question": "5934×1551=？",
        "answer": 6.963959339794428
    },
    {
        "question": "1×32527=？",
        "answer": 4.512244009684343
    },
    {
        "question": "5390900÷1396=？",
        "answer": 3.586775857549843
    },
    {
        "question": "5×72613368=？",
        "answer": 8.55998658528675
    },
    {
        "question": "158527×212=？",
        "answer": 7.526439101945515
    },
    {
        "question": "91832÷817=？",
        "answer": 2.0507719863439333
    },
    {
        "question": "406×98635=？",
        "answer": 7.6025570824908355
    },
    {
        "question": "106311×6436=？",
        "answer": 8.83519423872867
    },
    {
        "question": "13×197896=？",
        "answer": 6.410380368365259
    },
    {
        "question": "49221÷299=？",
        "answer": 2.216479244489534
    },
    {
        "question": "39713933÷6442317=？",
        "answer": 0.7899008079294072
    },
    {
        "question": "4514143÷338897=？",
        "answer": 1.1245075882620426
    },
    {
        "question": "1×34623=？",
        "answer": 4.539364695746141
    },
    {
        "question": "200×444383=？",
        "answer": 7.948787432189764
    },
    {
        "question": "50013×9843=？",
        "answer": 8.692210391330415
    },
    {
        "question": "553650÷73814=？",
        "answer": 0.8750965637546633
    },
    {
        "question": "617741156÷197865=？",
        "answer": 3.4944375570701762
    },
    {
        "question": "1217271÷11958=？",
        "answer": 2.0077287265186436
    },
    {
        "question": "1×3526=？",
        "answer": 3.5472823079633033
    },
    {
        "question": "24724466÷73235=？",
        "answer": 2.5284082345655836
    },
    {
        "question": "96323215÷2340=？",
        "answer": 4.614515112282858
    },
    {
        "question": "22×5645=？",
        "answer": 5.094086627083193
    },
    {
        "question": "2470×14770=？",
        "answer": 7.562077448571615
    },
    {
        "question": "10×1818402=？",
        "answer": 7.259689900383262
    },
    {
        "question": "18580765÷4719624=？",
        "answer": 0.5951561897125771
    },
    {
        "question": "38438963÷33886148=？",
        "answer": 0.05474945951087106
    },
    {
        "question": "92482392÷2207780=？",
        "answer": 1.622103259174365
    },
    {
        "question": "5×24792990=？",
        "answer": 8.09329890957083
    },
    {
        "question": "50595÷3014=？",
        "answer": 1.2249643522662697
    },
    {
        "question": "55×67850=？",
        "answer": 6.57191254149
    },
    {
        "question": "949×3258=？",
        "answer": 6.490217292399783
    },
    {
        "question": "16836×295=？",
        "answer": 6.696060933054148
    },
    {
        "question": "5×36225441=？",
        "answer": 8.257983685510307
    },
    {
        "question": "157777÷19030=？",
        "answer": 0.9186049057631432
    },
    {
        "question": "769489023÷434912439=？",
        "answer": 0.24780059969728088
    },
    {
        "question": "849×62726=？",
        "answer": 7.726355283961491
    },
    {
        "question": "876072÷521=？",
        "answer": 3.22570207683857
    },
    {
        "question": "465×688=？",
        "answer": 5.505041391125466
    },
    {
        "question": "366×7070=？",
        "answer": 6.41290049919131
    },
    {
        "question": "7067÷584=？",
        "answer": 1.082822244202323
    },
    {
        "question": "299768÷59900=？",
        "answer": 0.6993584480003207
    },
    {
        "question": "11898762÷129452=？",
        "answer": 1.963393013257517
    },
    {
        "question": "11525÷568=？",
        "answer": 1.307292598350667
    },
    {
        "question": "15863÷1912=？",
        "answer": 0.9188974362923056
    },
    {
        "question": "11029×726=？",
        "answer": 6.903472757422237
    },
    {
        "question": "62033458÷6627=？",
        "answer": 3.9713090206086856
    },
    {
        "question": "2546÷867=？",
        "answer": 0.4678393018414263
    },
    {
        "question": "1164÷598=？",
        "answer": 0.28925179632545883
    },
    {
        "question": "852×5051=？",
        "answer": 6.63381696327905
    },
    {
        "question": "195182÷2608=？",
        "answer": 1.874132176777321
    },
    {
        "question": "52×6878305=？",
        "answer": 8.553484773172574
    },
    {
        "question": "3×17117891=？",
        "answer": 7.7105715113526685
    },
    {
        "question": "255399152÷15648139=？",
        "answer": 1.2127567557134764
    },
    {
        "question": "2119556÷3450=？",
        "answer": 2.7884258003153737
    },
    {
        "question": "12573771÷3468925=？",
        "answer": 0.5592706362248682
    },
    {
        "question": "19801019÷12157=？",
        "answer": 3.211861123800952
    },
    {
        "question": "75811585÷5655641=？",
        "answer": 1.1272537423776376
    },
    {
        "question": "235932953÷1071285=？",
        "answer": 2.342883579464942
    },
    {
        "question": "110×83905=？",
        "answer": 6.965180526889284
    },
    {
        "question": "192727324÷778874=？",
        "answer": 2.393476084638788
    },
    {
        "question": "1248312÷297308=？",
        "answer": 0.6231165499862775
    },
    {
        "question": "160428÷95710=？",
        "answer": 0.2243228531066089
    },
    {
        "question": "75×54062=？",
        "answer": 6.607953371585651
    },
    {
        "question": "54193÷21954=？",
        "answer": 0.39242953335256103
    },
    {
        "question": "115527÷17060=？",
        "answer": 0.8307044689175181
    },
    {
        "question": "7017328÷301875=？",
        "answer": 1.3663446284561562
    },
    {
        "question": "3547÷222=？",
        "answer": 1.203508214021304
    },
    {
        "question": "20×20298=？",
        "answer": 5.608483243835606
    },
    {
        "question": "12244819÷5469189=？",
        "answer": 0.35002943822401716
    },
    {
        "question": "1509×624=？",
        "answer": 5.973873829458014
    },
    {
        "question": "34996428÷5624079=？",
        "answer": 0.7939723067562283
    },
    {
        "question": "2×5094108=？",
        "answer": 7.008098143850831
    },
    {
        "question": "128772×4484=？",
        "answer": 8.761487044839193
    },
    {
        "question": "32313÷617=？",
        "answer": 1.719092116576874
    },
    {
        "question": "3164×369=？",
        "answer": 6.067262840984699
    },
    {
        "question": "22302622÷241374=？",
        "answer": 1.965665436197832
    },
    {
        "question": "50×3207425=？",
        "answer": 8.205126514288063
    },
    {
        "question": "43×3101=？",
        "answer": 5.124970221816913
    },
    {
        "question": "29304×29253=？",
        "answer": 8.93309731681437
    },
    {
        "question": "497055196÷4750613=？",
        "answer": 2.0196549652294125
    },
    {
        "question": "22×249814=？",
        "answer": 6.7400394541412405
    },
    {
        "question": "1239248÷466=？",
        "answer": 3.424772309987721
    },
    {
        "question": "2253656÷6571=？",
        "answer": 2.5352561584932807
    },
    {
        "question": "1×8425243=？",
        "answer": 6.9255824356012035
    },
    {
        "question": "525×49955=？",
        "answer": 7.418738266713393
    },
    {
        "question": "441259400÷28091=？",
        "answer": 4.196126770375028
    },
    {
        "question": "3×27084069=？",
        "answer": 7.909835166265116
    },
    {
        "question": "581×119914=？",
        "answer": 7.843046022476708
    },
    {
        "question": "18603×26804=？",
        "answer": 8.69778259533049
    },
    {
        "question": "8×40492=？",
        "answer": 5.510459215168423
    },
    {
        "question": "50×302491=？",
        "answer": 7.1796824619741475
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1928122=？",
        "answer": 6.285134509987198
    },
    {
        "question": "1×335095879=？",
        "answer": 8.525169086926393
    },
    {
        "question": "89452÷7238=？",
        "answer": 1.0919714763520454
    },
    {
        "question": "158210203÷120281462=？",
        "answer": 0.11903578954830073
    },
    {
        "question": "11×87583=？",
        "answer": 5.9838125022547
    },
    {
        "question": "23×1477=？",
        "answer": 4.531108331329542
    },
    {
        "question": "56×1785907=？",
        "answer": 8.000046866531614
    },
    {
        "question": "2319661÷11026=？",
        "answer": 2.3230065327016223
    },
    {
        "question": "157102609÷30484=？",
        "answer": 3.712111444465332
    },
    {
        "question": "215979534÷13988514=？",
        "answer": 1.188641017964785
    },
    {
        "question": "1×359451665=？",
        "answer": 8.555640499628282
    },
    {
        "question": "1108719÷4753=？",
        "answer": 2.36785367575616
    },
    {
        "question": "1×38310494=？",
        "answer": 7.58331775208986
    },
    {
        "question": "11338÷5719=？",
        "answer": 0.2972163561082789
    },
    {
        "question": "432494×796=？",
        "answer": 8.536893154602163
    },
    {
        "question": "56×7299933=？",
        "answer": 8.611506901117915
    },
    {
        "question": "505326×241=？",
        "answer": 8.085588686678992
    },
    {
        "question": "254658721÷2008110=？",
        "answer": 2.1031710546893807
    },
    {
        "question": "26×16771330=？",
        "answer": 8.639540852363275
    },
    {
        "question": "823115÷189079=？",
        "answer": 0.6388172193643565
    },
    {
        "question": "4295971÷131197=？",
        "answer": 1.5151374365796286
    },
    {
        "question": "93028÷10226=？",
        "answer": 0.9589078958116539
    },
    {
        "question": "3×72668626=？",
        "answer": 8.338468203460337
    },
    {
        "question": "343895050÷43368006=？",
        "answer": 0.8992564703066958
    },
    {
        "question": "23073724÷10112=？",
        "answer": 3.358280632504757
    },
    {
        "question": "5963×2990=？",
        "answer": 7.251135997670169
    },
    {
        "question": "34624÷18618=？",
        "answer": 0.26944421312264727
    },
    {
        "question": "7614÷307=？",
        "answer": 1.394474497001162
    },
    {
        "question": "377270974÷5855=？",
        "answer": 4.809126493874921
    },
    {
        "question": "8×1113=？",
        "answer": 3.949585151326652
    },
    {
        "question": "90461÷361=？",
        "answer": 2.3989541824337293
    },
    {
        "question": "64196×281=？",
        "answer": 7.256214288284719
    },
    {
        "question": "1220948÷897=？",
        "answer": 3.1339047247550393
    },
    {
        "question": "13×945507=？",
        "answer": 7.089608100770941
    },
    {
        "question": "103×237=？",
        "answer": 4.387585570715276
    },
    {
        "question": "281578500÷1750=？",
        "answer": 5.206561442380978
    },
    {
        "question": "2255×12710=？",
        "answer": 7.457292096767987
    },
    {
        "question": "539177080÷19568=？",
        "answer": 4.440184982705433
    },
    {
        "question": "9019828÷238788=？",
        "answer": 1.5771857579504354
    },
    {
        "question": "23148÷3195=？",
        "answer": 0.8600426111970904
    },
    {
        "question": "410371668÷41021=？",
        "answer": 4.000171126224108
    },
    {
        "question": "1217986÷503=？",
        "answer": 3.384074311321643
    },
    {
        "question": "2891312÷445=？",
        "answer": 3.8127349477140187
    },
    {
        "question": "196563133÷249787=？",
        "answer": 2.895932233647427
    },
    {
        "question": "632915÷2884=？",
        "answer": 2.3413501324696777
    },
    {
        "question": "2×123734575=？",
        "answer": 8.393521066623762
    },
    {
        "question": "1×578688=？",
        "answer": 5.7624444766821625
    },
    {
        "question": "586912÷225897=？",
        "answer": 0.4146625258282256
    },
    {
        "question": "6962×5990=？",
        "answer": 7.620160841337581
    },
    {
        "question": "56450÷2825=？",
        "answer": 1.3006454941055294
    },
    {
        "question": "460÷425=？",
        "answer": 0.03436890163126251
    },
    {
        "question": "193675÷103147=？",
        "answer": 0.27361696347251424
    },
    {
        "question": "1119×844142=？",
        "answer": 8.975245595510817
    },
    {
        "question": "238×1524=？",
        "answer": 5.559561924060094
    },
    {
        "question": "116004466÷839237=？",
        "answer": 2.140590086605247
    },
    {
        "question": "5×11701=？",
        "answer": 4.7671929836824685
    },
    {
        "question": "75283×11692=？",
        "answer": 8.94458572392561
    },
    {
        "question": "16015×14031=？",
        "answer": 8.351615567628007
    },
    {
        "question": "5588×5497=？",
        "answer": 7.487382134407875
    },
    {
        "question": "1×123783140=？",
        "answer": 8.092661495220398
    },
    {
        "question": "24417989÷1902=？",
        "answer": 4.108499381152998
    },
    {
        "question": "127061463÷236215=？",
        "answer": 2.73070637905196
    },
    {
        "question": "24649×1369=？",
        "answer": 7.528202752952457
    },
    {
        "question": "3×3050404=？",
        "answer": 6.961478616476749
    },
    {
        "question": "1000×3004=？",
        "answer": 6.477699928332131
    },
    {
        "question": "99439857÷249085=？",
        "answer": 2.6012129161609785
    },
    {
        "question": "59689002÷62193=？",
        "answer": 2.9821528111938687
    },
    {
        "question": "13759848÷1050884=？",
        "answer": 1.1170588566000481
    },
    {
        "question": "13130187÷3315=？",
        "answer": 3.597787378610667
    },
    {
        "question": "422482163÷521394=？",
        "answer": 2.9086423487936144
    },
    {
        "question": "5951÷3246=？",
        "answer": 0.2632414347745814
    },
    {
        "question": "203119÷11446=？",
        "answer": 1.24909680817026
    },
    {
        "question": "327266513÷31229307=？",
        "answer": 1.0203392220819103
    },
    {
        "question": "61179491÷50980192=？",
        "answer": 0.07920439266589206
    },
    {
        "question": "3×68878111=？",
        "answer": 8.315202482690147
    },
    {
        "question": "68377858÷22204392=？",
        "answer": 0.48847660616113636
    },
    {
        "question": "48×137934=？",
        "answer": 6.820912568035579
    },
    {
        "question": "11386796÷2760560=？",
        "answer": 0.6154043492743917
    },
    {
        "question": "246410888÷2347=？",
        "answer": 5.021146804209735
    },
    {
        "question": "4×658=？",
        "answer": 3.4202858849419178
    },
    {
        "question": "702469÷1795=？",
        "answer": 2.592562710643564
    },
    {
        "question": "1391÷1357=？",
        "answer": 0.0107472823323093
    },
    {
        "question": "40644053÷20253=？",
        "answer": 3.302507646305801
    },
    {
        "question": "1716809÷608655=？",
        "answer": 0.4503507872978991
    },
    {
        "question": "55251÷51688=？",
        "answer": 0.028950414787509773
    },
    {
        "question": "150×1961=？",
        "answer": 5.4685688527234655
    },
    {
        "question": "31794×10464=？",
        "answer": 8.522042900878166
    },
    {
        "question": "5690519÷764=？",
        "answer": 3.8720585191650967
    },
    {
        "question": "400055÷314774=？",
        "answer": 0.10412084981130146
    },
    {
        "question": "3735×92473=？",
        "answer": 8.538305553347753
    },
    {
        "question": "38858×246=？",
        "answer": 6.980415551042997
    },
    {
        "question": "4×961824=？",
        "answer": 6.5851556009731365
    },
    {
        "question": "263006429÷383=？",
        "answer": 5.836767590662195
    },
    {
        "question": "3379÷1101=？",
        "answer": 0.4870008728031446
    },
    {
        "question": "88561÷392=？",
        "answer": 2.3539564447800867
    },
    {
        "question": "149399177÷97646031=？",
        "answer": 0.18469360977827298
    },
    {
        "question": "91616÷949=？",
        "answer": 1.984705113914212
    },
    {
        "question": "20394×41775=？",
        "answer": 8.930418873532131
    },
    {
        "question": "35355×321=？",
        "answer": 7.054955873984877
    },
    {
        "question": "797591÷858=？",
        "answer": 2.9682929569127805
    },
    {
        "question": "863781394÷23845=？",
        "answer": 4.559006518264403
    },
    {
        "question": "347797363÷10020961=？",
        "answer": 1.5404169129290504
    },
    {
        "question": "99895262÷14716696=？",
        "answer": 0.8317345714365141
    },
    {
        "question": "262167354÷3953121=？",
        "answer": 1.8216385030986988
    },
    {
        "question": "66128354÷4328877=？",
        "answer": 1.1840124668038141
    },
    {
        "question": "2006260÷4927=？",
        "answer": 2.6098046521763414
    },
    {
        "question": "603645200÷2916=？",
        "answer": 5.3159942319606435
    },
    {
        "question": "609901968÷473=？",
        "answer": 6.110398893981033
    },
    {
        "question": "252160431÷2734554=？",
        "answer": 1.9647904341894393
    },
    {
        "question": "96432÷5051=？",
        "answer": 1.2808438056114868
    },
    {
        "question": "10505933÷7795=？",
        "answer": 3.129618507303635
    },
    {
        "question": "101059×221=？",
        "answer": 7.348967270173602
    },
    {
        "question": "14696×61449=？",
        "answer": 8.955713963017935
    },
    {
        "question": "1455699÷3797=？",
        "answer": 2.583630986523271
    },
    {
        "question": "512153755÷44729985=？",
        "answer": 1.0588016086835021
    },
    {
        "question": "40006629÷115782=？",
        "answer": 2.5384909115877976
    },
    {
        "question": "1324÷1285=？",
        "answer": 0.012984857436367741
    },
    {
        "question": "12025623÷266=？",
        "answer": 4.655225948078307
    },
    {
        "question": "230×11370=？",
        "answer": 6.417488300705328
    },
    {
        "question": "101196895÷6451=？",
        "answer": 4.195540145460979
    },
    {
        "question": "227824729÷35357839=？",
        "answer": 0.8091151484008638
    },
    {
        "question": "74×2419931=？",
        "answer": 8.253034702758322
    },
    {
        "question": "215956115÷133502697=？",
        "answer": 0.20887546667687734
    },
    {
        "question": "7570054÷477=？",
        "answer": 4.200580598454461
    },
    {
        "question": "383770÷17078=？",
        "answer": 1.3516340129149906
    },
    {
        "question": "3×1800369=？",
        "answer": 6.732482781067393
    },
    {
        "question": "2983×283721=？",
        "answer": 8.927544735250937
    },
    {
        "question": "30682×6902=？",
        "answer": 8.325858620553591
    },
    {
        "question": "5281261÷200=？",
        "answer": 4.421707635194866
    },
    {
        "question": "369890×766=？",
        "answer": 8.452301359927386
    },
    {
        "question": "11831780÷908205=？",
        "answer": 1.1148661972754603
    },
    {
        "question": "99×9331895=？",
        "answer": 8.96560503818078
    },
    {
        "question": "5799×268=？",
        "answer": 6.191487902777005
    },
    {
        "question": "32×2899=？",
        "answer": 4.967398193674903
    },
    {
        "question": "3638×8873=？",
        "answer": 7.508933176246406
    },
    {
        "question": "4×201=？",
        "answer": 2.905256048748451
    },
    {
        "question": "60062÷650=？",
        "answer": 1.9656864330000285
    },
    {
        "question": "12×213680=？",
        "answer": 6.408945121060941
    },
    {
        "question": "1113135×406=？",
        "answer": 8.655073871945714
    },
    {
        "question": "3856603÷934924=？",
        "answer": 0.6154286262521087
    },
    {
        "question": "11244258÷1883=？",
        "answer": 3.7760804819392693
    },
    {
        "question": "79056÷65132=？",
        "answer": 0.08414042234135201
    },
    {
        "question": "288×1319=？",
        "answer": 5.579637283305596
    },
    {
        "question": "1112×594=？",
        "answer": 5.819891232227232
    },
    {
        "question": "451458298÷2595=？",
        "answer": 5.240480277769747
    },
    {
        "question": "339153÷1667=？",
        "answer": 2.308460063170215
    },
    {
        "question": "3×3071=？",
        "answer": 3.9644010711627313
    },
    {
        "question": "196937240÷373=？",
        "answer": 5.72261901534657
    },
    {
        "question": "117655÷52532=？",
        "answer": 0.3501864525824998
    },
    {
        "question": "4334690÷264013=？",
        "answer": 1.2153327318311333
    },
    {
        "question": "17811×30103=？",
        "answer": 8.729298082246949
    },
    {
        "question": "586154÷6773=？",
        "answer": 1.9372306574144404
    },
    {
        "question": "7343187÷1043909=？",
        "answer": 0.8472219461513064
    },
    {
        "question": "250970337÷3704=？",
        "answer": 4.830951415827725
    },
    {
        "question": "36589×4266=？",
        "answer": 8.193371391225417
    },
    {
        "question": "255542×2115=？",
        "answer": 8.73277266118843
    },
    {
        "question": "5765×19057=？",
        "answer": 8.040853845603966
    },
    {
        "question": "17421829÷4344=？",
        "answer": 3.603203930124755
    },
    {
        "question": "201655091÷97236=？",
        "answer": 3.3167821057593314
    },
    {
        "question": "16874181÷513583=？",
        "answer": 1.5166120634218734
    },
    {
        "question": "110775282÷3463=？",
        "answer": 4.504990372736567
    },
    {
        "question": "853×1004666=？",
        "answer": 8.932970736241586
    },
    {
        "question": "2×65509572=？",
        "answer": 8.117334757687198
    },
    {
        "question": "1101664÷208=？",
        "answer": 3.7239858228956466
    },
    {
        "question": "222×6636=？",
        "answer": 6.168259351802962
    },
    {
        "question": "346548796÷8915480=？",
        "answer": 1.5896196642388334
    },
    {
        "question": "26×7480=？",
        "answer": 5.288874945835279
    },
    {
        "question": "268620876÷1067746=？",
        "answer": 2.4006718079039984
    },
    {
        "question": "118275÷22778=？",
        "answer": 0.7153773681055061
    },
    {
        "question": "40×685090=？",
        "answer": 7.437807619661074
    },
    {
        "question": "17×1900826=？",
        "answer": 7.509391285114614
    },
    {
        "question": "72764÷12631=？",
        "answer": 0.7604788300488923
    },
    {
        "question": "3191×268679=？",
        "answer": 8.933160527416675
    },
    {
        "question": "1038×255827=？",
        "answer": 8.424143731544874
    },
    {
        "question": "29469467÷171027=？",
        "answer": 2.2363076032546494
    },
    {
        "question": "1727×80249=？",
        "answer": 8.141731966841405
    },
    {
        "question": "178×897163=？",
        "answer": 8.203291356801662
    },
    {
        "question": "23578826÷208=？",
        "answer": 5.054458842623507
    },
    {
        "question": "1×698=？",
        "answer": 2.843855422623161
    },
    {
        "question": "252×1689175=？",
        "answer": 8.629075185969654
    },
    {
        "question": "4610÷340=？",
        "answer": 1.132222008347393
    },
    {
        "question": "96626×1906=？",
        "answer": 8.265216897844311
    },
    {
        "question": "147×627=？",
        "answer": 4.964584875578892
    },
    {
        "question": "3183706÷1827340=？",
        "answer": 0.24111359498299897
    },
    {
        "question": "630316÷52704=？",
        "answer": 1.0777147539474197
    },
    {
        "question": "1957935÷14669=？",
        "answer": 2.125397761318048
    },
    {
        "question": "27485621÷59259=？",
        "answer": 2.6663512352477823
    },
    {
        "question": "50975214÷576984=？",
        "answer": 1.9461952875129622
    },
    {
        "question": "966395÷823789=？",
        "answer": 0.06933868574698145
    },
    {
        "question": "143066÷41708=？",
        "answer": 0.5353170699612322
    },
    {
        "question": "48×18500320=？",
        "answer": 8.9484204778344
    },
    {
        "question": "179×2652445=？",
        "answer": 8.676499418296288
    },
    {
        "question": "3571025÷533=？",
        "answer": 3.8260656815817913
    },
    {
        "question": "61769÷811=？",
        "answer": 1.8817497162377996
    },
    {
        "question": "12705335÷1014=？",
        "answer": 4.097948165529046
    },
    {
        "question": "5×12067810=？",
        "answer": 7.78059846820215
    },
    {
        "question": "4×38142934=？",
        "answer": 8.183474087772648
    },
    {
        "question": "214980×1870=？",
        "answer": 8.604239665086252
    },
    {
        "question": "252742056÷5582121=？",
        "answer": 1.6558782678838009
    },
    {
        "question": "579×32067=？",
        "answer": 7.268736895517777
    },
    {
        "question": "1733687÷219054=？",
        "answer": 0.8984195047036283
    },
    {
        "question": "7×54740332=？",
        "answer": 8.583405467091481
    },
    {
        "question": "1253×443615=？",
        "answer": 8.744957293563903
    },
    {
        "question": "177937÷2750=？",
        "answer": 1.8109335703022371
    },
    {
        "question": "99805÷910=？",
        "answer": 2.040110906661826
    },
    {
        "question": "5307×280=？",
        "answer": 6.172007118971605
    },
    {
        "question": "49529657÷29143930=？",
        "answer": 0.23031720532590672
    },
    {
        "question": "18589601÷23960=？",
        "answer": 2.8897832546260123
    },
    {
        "question": "1685352÷647=？",
        "answer": 3.415786340083019
    },
    {
        "question": "207033618÷4613089=？",
        "answer": 1.6520490381698152
    },
    {
        "question": "38036403÷1236=？",
        "answer": 4.488180969397081
    },
    {
        "question": "699×61980=？",
        "answer": 7.636728747648946
    },
    {
        "question": "6124003÷50943=？",
        "answer": 2.079950878077479
    },
    {
        "question": "2485023÷37991=？",
        "answer": 1.8156496874629533
    },
    {
        "question": "8979×1540=？",
        "answer": 7.140748692396317
    },
    {
        "question": "2×184484=？",
        "answer": 5.566988702131813
    },
    {
        "question": "420×171856=？",
        "answer": 7.858413989637531
    },
    {
        "question": "645×355101=？",
        "answer": 8.359911609955386
    },
    {
        "question": "13340×220=？",
        "answer": 6.467578510402737
    },
    {
        "question": "13×55872646=？",
        "answer": 8.861142591341752
    },
    {
        "question": "967624258÷781=？",
        "answer": 6.093055713559012
    },
    {
        "question": "7706×12043=？",
        "answer": 7.967563691030125
    },
    {
        "question": "6×87859548=？",
        "answer": 8.721940215058327
    },
    {
        "question": "10870×438=？",
        "answer": 6.6777036545903945
    },
    {
        "question": "106829÷652=？",
        "answer": 2.21444156735717
    },
    {
        "question": "31823735÷2623=？",
        "answer": 4.083952858783619
    },
    {
        "question": "39224÷665=？",
        "answer": 1.7707302349350171
    },
    {
        "question": "1219×801=？",
        "answer": 5.98963622170262
    },
    {
        "question": "537×528=？",
        "answer": 5.452608208233368
    },
    {
        "question": "759806÷25603=？",
        "answer": 1.4724118625337013
    },
    {
        "question": "634751×549=？",
        "answer": 8.542175738193
    },
    {
        "question": "12×29144=？",
        "answer": 5.543730404281484
    },
    {
        "question": "214057255÷37648=？",
        "answer": 3.754788042044389
    },
    {
        "question": "4725×1999=？",
        "answer": 6.975214606963399
    },
    {
        "question": "6339×511=？",
        "answer": 6.510441651906689
    },
    {
        "question": "21550724÷924=？",
        "answer": 4.367789893713915
    },
    {
        "question": "59178÷571=？",
        "answer": 2.015524175261409
    },
    {
        "question": "85229×6186=？",
        "answer": 8.721997308521003
    },
    {
        "question": "37295÷2146=？",
        "answer": 1.2400208938580162
    },
    {
        "question": "2339÷228=？",
        "answer": 1.0110953748086993
    },
    {
        "question": "1082374×405=？",
        "answer": 8.641832374623759
    },
    {
        "question": "3×19978=？",
        "answer": 4.777673263512548
    },
    {
        "question": "183459862÷1264=？",
        "answer": 5.161793988545494
    },
    {
        "question": "71726×2459=？",
        "answer": 8.246435140609064
    },
    {
        "question": "5648×1544=？",
        "answer": 6.940541984043465
    },
    {
        "question": "1×22854=？",
        "answer": 4.35896222304459
    },
    {
        "question": "564×261=？",
        "answer": 5.167919611321623
    },
    {
        "question": "429173794÷16025=？",
        "answer": 4.427835157235724
    },
    {
        "question": "139994÷1853=？",
        "answer": 1.8782340033398341
    },
    {
        "question": "4×1554187=？",
        "answer": 6.79356326331032
    },
    {
        "question": "2355430÷57540=？",
        "answer": 1.6121003446028535
    },
    {
        "question": "21270×605=？",
        "answer": 7.109522864555198
    },
    {
        "question": "2287×2667=？",
        "answer": 6.785289180296624
    },
    {
        "question": "21326694÷568236=？",
        "answer": 1.5743947931086808
    },
    {
        "question": "36818658÷991=？",
        "answer": 4.569994300410145
    },
    {
        "question": "105764×417=？",
        "answer": 7.644473922465901
    },
    {
        "question": "140901÷4171=？",
        "answer": 1.5286738855413162
    },
    {
        "question": "374159÷67849=？",
        "answer": 0.7415127450346576
    },
    {
        "question": "110×10980=？",
        "answer": 6.081995025272298
    },
    {
        "question": "105×3280058=？",
        "answer": 8.537070822311264
    },
    {
        "question": "2×7352259=？",
        "answer": 7.167450793319725
    },
    {
        "question": "2×462519=？",
        "answer": 5.9661595736593975
    },
    {
        "question": "7971965÷697=？",
        "answer": 4.058332605214405
    },
    {
        "question": "9038276÷1925387=？",
        "answer": 0.6715675639793797
    },
    {
        "question": "418932×433=？",
        "answer": 8.25863143144037
    },
    {
        "question": "209085281÷1615369=？",
        "answer": 2.1120517165895505
    },
    {
        "question": "951332816÷723029421=？",
        "answer": 0.11917650823346507
    },
    {
        "question": "20564094÷12712=？",
        "answer": 3.208895696192522
    },
    {
        "question": "4×1015589=？",
        "answer": 6.608777979645074
    },
    {
        "question": "1253688÷1405=？",
        "answer": 2.9505131446797597
    },
    {
        "question": "14960×66819=？",
        "answer": 8.99983156531347
    },
    {
        "question": "77448×513=？",
        "answer": 7.599127572227327
    },
    {
        "question": "135241048÷317484=？",
        "answer": 2.6293866841393343
    },
    {
        "question": "24668046÷4003=？",
        "answer": 3.7897491595051513
    },
    {
        "question": "38×2142036=？",
        "answer": 7.910610362118233
    },
    {
        "question": "25×11110=？",
        "answer": 5.443654067612905
    },
    {
        "question": "20×1005020=？",
        "answer": 7.30320470001075
    },
    {
        "question": "11362625÷8399=？",
        "answer": 3.131251092660699
    },
    {
        "question": "16×6000291=？",
        "answer": 7.982292295811173
    },
    {
        "question": "2×45452691=？",
        "answer": 7.958589596134056
    },
    {
        "question": "2×7979403=？",
        "answer": 7.20300039534747
    },
    {
        "question": "9×4057=？",
        "answer": 4.562447517143651
    },
    {
        "question": "8730×532=？",
        "answer": 6.666925876000618
    },
    {
        "question": "1×129935=？",
        "answer": 5.113726150760972
    },
    {
        "question": "19953×7083=？",
        "answer": 8.150225444352202
    },
    {
        "question": "1221214÷1120=？",
        "answer": 3.037573751737883
    },
    {
        "question": "87×1535=？",
        "answer": 5.125627632431824
    },
    {
        "question": "6×36550=？",
        "answer": 5.341038631677523
    },
    {
        "question": "11×40855882=？",
        "answer": 8.652647275677754
    },
    {
        "question": "2304355÷1661=？",
        "answer": 3.142179753178556
    },
    {
        "question": "42×1372487=？",
        "answer": 7.760757529964472
    },
    {
        "question": "1×84580=？",
        "answer": 4.927267680810882
    },
    {
        "question": "770705024÷21932920=？",
        "answer": 1.5457917354893183
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1453=？",
        "answer": 3.1622656142980214
    },
    {
        "question": "46083641÷18007624=？",
        "answer": 0.40809037073363974
    },
    {
        "question": "6759023÷819212=？",
        "answer": 0.9164876189680137
    },
    {
        "question": "1047274÷648=？",
        "answer": 3.208485315846487
    },
    {
        "question": "13×619=？",
        "answer": 3.9056340013269546
    },
    {
        "question": "24679019÷1532895=？",
        "answer": 1.2068154847021322
    },
    {
        "question": "11899317÷215=？",
        "answer": 4.743083574448034
    },
    {
        "question": "5089÷397=？",
        "answer": 1.1078419441101797
    },
    {
        "question": "76400687÷26831=？",
        "answer": 3.4544604045291702
    },
    {
        "question": "144703987÷119408034=？",
        "answer": 0.08344694937638873
    },
    {
        "question": "20517÷676=？",
        "answer": 1.4821671625110564
    },
    {
        "question": "266×678544=？",
        "answer": 8.256459651246768
    },
    {
        "question": "139347501÷6359=？",
        "answer": 4.34071035967933
    },
    {
        "question": "378953802÷469=？",
        "answer": 5.907413425935334
    },
    {
        "question": "11543769÷118618=？",
        "answer": 1.9881970304083034
    },
    {
        "question": "1142×802=？",
        "answer": 5.961840472193993
    },
    {
        "question": "5884÷1379=？",
        "answer": 0.6301083978796428
    },
    {
        "question": "603874765÷1625=？",
        "answer": 5.5700935161724825
    },
    {
        "question": "74×895=？",
        "answer": 4.821054755046888
    },
    {
        "question": "30×3170833=？",
        "answer": 7.978294624123491
    },
    {
        "question": "702043063÷1273699=？",
        "answer": 2.7412969445322988
    },
    {
        "question": "93025÷16313=？",
        "answer": 0.7560658425069646
    },
    {
        "question": "704008÷562=？",
        "answer": 3.097841278709578
    },
    {
        "question": "6432218÷55342=？",
        "answer": 2.0653059050277465
    },
    {
        "question": "44559÷394=？",
        "answer": 2.053439213945235
    },
    {
        "question": "817×2972=？",
        "answer": 6.3852708616209535
    },
    {
        "question": "569422÷33239=？",
        "answer": 1.2337862928950896
    },
    {
        "question": "240503527÷108896=？",
        "answer": 3.3441095222979023
    },
    {
        "question": "700996712÷149159222=？",
        "answer": 0.6720658714713215
    },
    {
        "question": "843×27480=？",
        "answer": 7.364844303012255
    },
    {
        "question": "4333÷863=？",
        "answer": 0.7007778933191652
    },
    {
        "question": "28547432÷534=？",
        "answer": 4.728025790110568
    },
    {
        "question": "572457÷290854=？",
        "answer": 0.29406782943298904
    },
    {
        "question": "402×1294=？",
        "answer": 5.716160329417152
    },
    {
        "question": "45×11424=？",
        "answer": 5.711030708207443
    },
    {
        "question": "86×225=？",
        "answer": 4.28668096935493
    },
    {
        "question": "972×200472=？",
        "answer": 8.289719988043739
    },
    {
        "question": "4×52259=？",
        "answer": 5.3202210863741275
    },
    {
        "question": "3507×6518=？",
        "answer": 7.359050122010628
    },
    {
        "question": "556773380÷505617=？",
        "answer": 3.041856795467587
    },
    {
        "question": "27×763=？",
        "answer": 4.313888302113868
    },
    {
        "question": "272705579÷3251195=？",
        "answer": 1.923651004443383
    },
    {
        "question": "655783737÷199298=？",
        "answer": 3.517257701772825
    },
    {
        "question": "127638÷12117=？",
        "answer": 1.0225848825881927
    },
    {
        "question": "237×14164=？",
        "answer": 6.525934264096177
    },
    {
        "question": "4×965942=？",
        "answer": 6.587011041308492
    },
    {
        "question": "172029285÷45029735=？",
        "answer": 0.5821029931515217
    },
    {
        "question": "45827410÷2692=？",
        "answer": 4.231050257627977
    },
    {
        "question": "3×1691=？",
        "answer": 3.7052648623174043
    },
    {
        "question": "2978×6409=？",
        "answer": 7.280714965000224
    },
    {
        "question": "463939311÷279021529=？",
        "answer": 0.22082345892076086
    },
    {
        "question": "4865÷2198=？",
        "answer": 0.34505515651689894
    },
    {
        "question": "3×16126374=？",
        "answer": 7.68465798238024
    },
    {
        "question": "3628929÷535=？",
        "answer": 3.831424689290418
    },
    {
        "question": "10033×90517=？",
        "answer": 8.958160963969256
    },
    {
        "question": "6305465÷71452=？",
        "answer": 1.945702729821231
    },
    {
        "question": "7543×9656=？",
        "answer": 7.8623413648052365
    },
    {
        "question": "66×2198=？",
        "answer": 5.1615716236293405
    },
    {
        "question": "58775321÷371020=？",
        "answer": 2.199797688606842
    },
    {
        "question": "43583679÷272442=？",
        "answer": 2.20404982748448
    },
    {
        "question": "511201120÷657514=？",
        "answer": 2.8906867922568864
    },
    {
        "question": "815224÷30860=？",
        "answer": 1.4218810349853448
    },
    {
        "question": "485965×1927=？",
        "answer": 8.971486706439908
    },
    {
        "question": "52×286654=？",
        "answer": 7.173361349978555
    },
    {
        "question": "273790659÷7613293=？",
        "answer": 1.5558460830164418
    },
    {
        "question": "18×350111=？",
        "answer": 6.799478261010449
    },
    {
        "question": "962866235÷186886135=？",
        "answer": 0.7119888750339157
    },
    {
        "question": "10×373314=？",
        "answer": 6.572074277118206
    },
    {
        "question": "288881473÷3165794=？",
        "answer": 1.9602370382230037
    },
    {
        "question": "28998101÷46422=？",
        "answer": 2.7956457109258177
    },
    {
        "question": "1634×2826=？",
        "answer": 6.664424209708937
    },
    {
        "question": "8142×678=？",
        "answer": 6.741960791910444
    },
    {
        "question": "2010×199=？",
        "answer": 5.602049133830196
    },
    {
        "question": "1×282=？",
        "answer": 2.450249108319361
    },
    {
        "question": "3539×604=？",
        "answer": 6.329917501258647
    },
    {
        "question": "15747×16007=？",
        "answer": 8.40150777242834
    },
    {
        "question": "44163×235=？",
        "answer": 7.016126429691977
    },
    {
        "question": "330×5339=？",
        "answer": 6.245973860735797
    },
    {
        "question": "1864÷1814=？",
        "answer": 0.011808625293886101
    },
    {
        "question": "115×4683=？",
        "answer": 5.731221998135692
    },
    {
        "question": "45662÷4787=？",
        "answer": 0.9794915022290219
    },
    {
        "question": "1×11841=？",
        "answer": 4.073388381115178
    },
    {
        "question": "22×686240=？",
        "answer": 7.178898709717204
    },
    {
        "question": "27165181÷13975=？",
        "answer": 3.2886607864994564
    },
    {
        "question": "1182708×706=？",
        "answer": 8.92168223550049
    },
    {
        "question": "15560046÷238=？",
        "answer": 4.815433919499256
    },
    {
        "question": "352660318÷169757=？",
        "answer": 3.3175289031533954
    },
    {
        "question": "4222276÷446420=？",
        "answer": 0.9758029755507671
    },
    {
        "question": "128409÷477=？",
        "answer": 2.4300770848279085
    },
    {
        "question": "24640×3824=？",
        "answer": 7.974158587096451
    },
    {
        "question": "5402×1449=？",
        "answer": 6.893622965322606
    },
    {
        "question": "51081÷5871=？",
        "answer": 0.939547310371718
    },
    {
        "question": "21193667÷14305666=？",
        "answer": 0.1706980251305274
    },
    {
        "question": "56684÷633=？",
        "answer": 1.9520567793462251
    },
    {
        "question": "206075622÷1305628=？",
        "answer": 2.198207164129428
    },
    {
        "question": "32534260÷24221908=？",
        "answer": 0.1281325827904789
    },
    {
        "question": "318568245÷4739235=？",
        "answer": 1.8274942388022708
    },
    {
        "question": "25942051÷1620=？",
        "answer": 4.204489294243603
    },
    {
        "question": "188861÷695=？",
        "answer": 2.4341574803117183
    },
    {
        "question": "207167810÷63170023=？",
        "answer": 0.5158112400621483
    },
    {
        "question": "50829357÷30354292=？",
        "answer": 0.2238945082318606
    },
    {
        "question": "342326385÷15871=？",
        "answer": 4.33383608227654
    },
    {
        "question": "26447337÷15986=？",
        "answer": 3.21864214053776
    },
    {
        "question": "922×1035=？",
        "answer": 5.979671270846566
    },
    {
        "question": "408237828÷11180=？",
        "answer": 4.562471441147364
    },
    {
        "question": "9574×29090=？",
        "answer": 8.44483714439299
    },
    {
        "question": "502500471÷66709658=？",
        "answer": 0.8769477589989894
    },
    {
        "question": "11636215÷322=？",
        "answer": 4.557955865324961
    },
    {
        "question": "241256÷656=？",
        "answer": 2.5655742836121433
    },
    {
        "question": "1189368÷112560=？",
        "answer": 1.0239321651810165
    },
    {
        "question": "96745191÷4412=？",
        "answer": 4.3409938825939
    },
    {
        "question": "94262÷42759=？",
        "answer": 0.3433091102876531
    },
    {
        "question": "11986×14490=？",
        "answer": 8.239742658831641
    },
    {
        "question": "144×205=？",
        "answer": 4.4701163531510035
    },
    {
        "question": "70×967=？",
        "answer": 4.830524514097259
    },
    {
        "question": "1260×32833=？",
        "answer": 7.616681111792096
    },
    {
        "question": "39×574=？",
        "answer": 4.349976499424472
    },
    {
        "question": "34265958÷29408606=？",
        "answer": 0.06638843926843421
    },
    {
        "question": "367802×1670=？",
        "answer": 8.788330557622785
    },
    {
        "question": "69105×451=？",
        "answer": 7.493686013186322
    },
    {
        "question": "65444416÷7182=？",
        "answer": 3.9596271957981104
    },
    {
        "question": "92387×351=？",
        "answer": 7.510917981349727
    },
    {
        "question": "213204÷20161=？",
        "answer": 1.0242832787679712
    },
    {
        "question": "28928048÷17214177=？",
        "answer": 0.22543286525090417
    },
    {
        "question": "53942873÷824132=？",
        "answer": 1.8159372957064006
    },
    {
        "question": "2×207=？",
        "answer": 2.617000341120899
    },
    {
        "question": "270×3372=？",
        "answer": 5.959251330111692
    },
    {
        "question": "64057889÷33611=？",
        "answer": 3.280091188714432
    },
    {
        "question": "130876×395=？",
        "answer": 7.713457108692138
    },
    {
        "question": "33982125÷57534=？",
        "answer": 2.7713259640536667
    },
    {
        "question": "70093791÷3243=？",
        "answer": 4.334732600622275
    },
    {
        "question": "100600÷89918=？",
        "answer": 0.048751342177123805
    },
    {
        "question": "327928784÷883=？",
        "answer": 5.5698188350305715
    },
    {
        "question": "44120×261=？",
        "answer": 7.061276011106434
    },
    {
        "question": "3398×60889=？",
        "answer": 8.315762216085526
    },
    {
        "question": "32075319÷13044=？",
        "answer": 3.390760194141443
    },
    {
        "question": "271490208÷152758292=？",
        "answer": 0.24974937639333528
    },
    {
        "question": "35×769712=？",
        "answer": 7.430396301720666
    },
    {
        "question": "1070573÷561654=？",
        "answer": 0.28014743001924713
    },
    {
        "question": "20783978÷969=？",
        "answer": 4.3314048969743935
    },
    {
        "question": "3720747÷1123=？",
        "answer": 3.5202503839993993
    },
    {
        "question": "10×274711=？",
        "answer": 6.438876049823381
    },
    {
        "question": "4973931÷10953=？",
        "answer": 2.657166668631013
    },
    {
        "question": "1716÷424=？",
        "answer": 0.607151426919954
    },
    {
        "question": "469663527÷350256=？",
        "answer": 3.1274012515439815
    },
    {
        "question": "284753÷6911=？",
        "answer": 1.6149274152925552
    },
    {
        "question": "110804736÷402044=？",
        "answer": 2.4402847381383834
    },
    {
        "question": "1×279808=？",
        "answer": 5.446860127261552
    },
    {
        "question": "29423975÷2029=？",
        "answer": 4.161419295863692
    },
    {
        "question": "31077÷251=？",
        "answer": 2.092765366307741
    },
    {
        "question": "10325÷561=？",
        "answer": 1.2649271990722772
    },
    {
        "question": "1095137÷7374=？",
        "answer": 2.171765318894431
    },
    {
        "question": "777×228=？",
        "answer": 5.2483558658013685
    },
    {
        "question": "1057×526=？",
        "answer": 5.745060731461165
    },
    {
        "question": "30138945÷6567592=？",
        "answer": 0.661721880789487
    },
    {
        "question": "2420668÷1721=？",
        "answer": 3.148154358744392
    },
    {
        "question": "11119567÷18006=？",
        "answer": 2.79067063018107
    },
    {
        "question": "13282160÷9979701=？",
        "answer": 0.12415117788245669
    },
    {
        "question": "45959089÷415834=？",
        "answer": 2.043451415687477
    },
    {
        "question": "969493228÷538026192=？",
        "answer": 0.2557413614873822
    },
    {
        "question": "20183×12917=？",
        "answer": 8.41614737978426
    },
    {
        "question": "399929÷26744=？",
        "answer": 1.1747565336306076
    },
    {
        "question": "28×42813=？",
        "answer": 6.078733692201446
    },
    {
        "question": "18×12659=？",
        "answer": 5.357671904968289
    },
    {
        "question": "1919083÷8844=？",
        "answer": 2.336445024394447
    },
    {
        "question": "642261138÷928=？",
        "answer": 5.840163668257079
    },
    {
        "question": "493×1348=？",
        "answer": 5.822536811476531
    },
    {
        "question": "2364993÷1571759=？",
        "answer": 0.17744390380433472
    },
    {
        "question": "6×569=？",
        "answer": 3.5332635167787148
    },
    {
        "question": "3612784÷1262=？",
        "answer": 3.4567826419734122
    },
    {
        "question": "9440889÷33934=？",
        "answer": 2.4443778359977855
    },
    {
        "question": "2420326÷1757536=？",
        "answer": 0.13896963663966294
    },
    {
        "question": "5344×13264=？",
        "answer": 7.850540962673688
    },
    {
        "question": "19×20695=？",
        "answer": 5.594619031689608
    },
    {
        "question": "3×195792290=？",
        "answer": 8.768916840673082
    },
    {
        "question": "7851753÷1958391=？",
        "answer": 0.6030672245094344
    },
    {
        "question": "21813875÷18066=？",
        "answer": 3.08187081427353
    },
    {
        "question": "42546857÷1451=？",
        "answer": 4.467200071184464
    },
    {
        "question": "10853624÷2454203=？",
        "answer": 0.6456642896734051
    },
    {
        "question": "12×1784126=？",
        "answer": 7.330606768269565
    },
    {
        "question": "413796166÷32889378=？",
        "answer": 1.0997308021878212
    },
    {
        "question": "670×19235=？",
        "answer": 7.110166993343661
    },
    {
        "question": "3451×274630=？",
        "answer": 8.976692936193716
    },
    {
        "question": "16758870÷475=？",
        "answer": 4.54755112249104
    },
    {
        "question": "245132423÷9831=？",
        "answer": 4.396803061901199
    },
    {
        "question": "103424×1218=？",
        "answer": 8.10026861871931
    },
    {
        "question": "32412960÷2701700=？",
        "answer": 1.079081570480616
    },
    {
        "question": "217×25223=？",
        "answer": 6.738256473736693
    },
    {
        "question": "3064×491=？",
        "answer": 6.177370253083534
    },
    {
        "question": "382642858÷623335=？",
        "answer": 2.7880720986369907
    },
    {
        "question": "12×3252=？",
        "answer": 4.591331782969656
    },
    {
        "question": "92780÷2706=？",
        "answer": 1.5351265759211365
    },
    {
        "question": "158743×4104=？",
        "answer": 8.813901935652654
    },
    {
        "question": "1422583÷113720=？",
        "answer": 1.097240763514729
    },
    {
        "question": "2640632÷39514=？",
        "answer": 1.8249568863812895
    },
    {
        "question": "26×465=？",
        "answer": 4.082426300860772
    },
    {
        "question": "355350807÷1449925=？",
        "answer": 2.3893117679139606
    },
    {
        "question": "57548×464=？",
        "answer": 7.426548215487556
    },
    {
        "question": "15382002÷365=？",
        "answer": 4.624719999030358
    },
    {
        "question": "924463440÷3078=？",
        "answer": 5.4776211251806775
    },
    {
        "question": "158387372÷19572508=？",
        "answer": 0.908074073703268
    },
    {
        "question": "28×10794065=？",
        "answer": 8.480343060325845
    },
    {
        "question": "80979199÷1035=？",
        "answer": 4.893433126867657
    },
    {
        "question": "208×3450=？",
        "answer": 5.8558824300360355
    },
    {
        "question": "10618664÷140372=？",
        "answer": 1.8787893911782152
    },
    {
        "question": "106597391÷10007190=？",
        "answer": 1.0274344298160125
    },
    {
        "question": "8056×4203=？",
        "answer": 7.529678847550999
    },
    {
        "question": "171×290555=？",
        "answer": 7.6962244637643495
    },
    {
        "question": "13603×3234=？",
        "answer": 7.64337471362931
    },
    {
        "question": "248×774710=？",
        "answer": 8.283590842726579
    },
    {
        "question": "2451×225=？",
        "answer": 5.74152582936344
    },
    {
        "question": "8281259÷1874882=？",
        "answer": 0.6451224280003378
    },
    {
        "question": "916885÷52059=？",
        "answer": 1.2458190463412526
    },
    {
        "question": "967×626=？",
        "answer": 5.782000807293431
    },
    {
        "question": "8934×2284=？",
        "answer": 7.30974204770963
    },
    {
        "question": "10×61039304=？",
        "answer": 8.78560957293695
    },
    {
        "question": "3×768=？",
        "answer": 3.3624824747511743
    },
    {
        "question": "11915959÷747193=？",
        "answer": 1.2026962056425012
    },
    {
        "question": "114894774÷145719=？",
        "answer": 2.896784092986463
    },
    {
        "question": "8×647=？",
        "answer": 3.713994267660644
    },
    {
        "question": "2619395÷450366=？",
        "answer": 0.7646353977948612
    },
    {
        "question": "800÷738=？",
        "answer": 0.03503362516890198
    },
    {
        "question": "36×679352=？",
        "answer": 7.388397359062907
    },
    {
        "question": "23397687÷232=？",
        "answer": 5.00368494205828
    },
    {
        "question": "20×9670=？",
        "answer": 5.286456469746983
    },
    {
        "question": "133×62034=？",
        "answer": 6.916481426676936
    },
    {
        "question": "50559885÷316=？",
        "answer": 5.204118994841007
    },
    {
        "question": "2691×6055=？",
        "answer": 7.212027845242826
    },
    {
        "question": "40×504815=？",
        "answer": 7.3051922423192766
    },
    {
        "question": "5×3762=？",
        "answer": 4.2743887955503785
    },
    {
        "question": "764352568÷265440=？",
        "answer": 3.45932736033717
    },
    {
        "question": "20×8252707=？",
        "answer": 8.217626422072
    },
    {
        "question": "184850030÷1093=？",
        "answer": 5.228199363442698
    },
    {
        "question": "2932865÷12607=？",
        "answer": 2.3666803199986535
    },
    {
        "question": "258219202÷5552=？",
        "answer": 4.667539077201514
    },
    {
        "question": "9202964÷8602=？",
        "answer": 3.029328284945948
    },
    {
        "question": "272928÷312=？",
        "answer": 2.941893498711568
    },
    {
        "question": "36×22261=？",
        "answer": 5.9038471704123
    },
    {
        "question": "257954630÷92777526=？",
        "answer": 0.4441005399181065
    },
    {
        "question": "201720879÷207349=？",
        "answer": 2.9880489067367226
    },
    {
        "question": "53382700÷63873=？",
        "answer": 2.9220832211648204
    },
    {
        "question": "9×11043=？",
        "answer": 4.997329581605654
    },
    {
        "question": "102409346÷1702=？",
        "answer": 4.779380036936277
    },
    {
        "question": "4×528191=？",
        "answer": 6.324850988191981
    },
    {
        "question": "4845÷1287=？",
        "answer": 0.5757152344823975
    },
    {
        "question": "4511÷1229=？",
        "answer": 0.5647209442112564
    },
    {
        "question": "639206545÷417615=？",
        "answer": 3.1848651238092933
    },
    {
        "question": "972314940÷254=？",
        "answer": 6.5829732422880705
    },
    {
        "question": "436226982÷8766=？",
        "answer": 4.696911058224378
    },
    {
        "question": "1619062×228=？",
        "answer": 8.567198326848526
    },
    {
        "question": "250543570÷1461=？",
        "answer": 5.234233045467279
    },
    {
        "question": "84698÷655=？",
        "answer": 2.1116318553304367
    },
    {
        "question": "2171643×446=？",
        "answer": 8.98612329110536
    },
    {
        "question": "205092674÷53359524=？",
        "answer": 0.5847382007065907
    },
    {
        "question": "550123121÷167730604=？",
        "answer": 0.5158475873167176
    },
    {
        "question": "10×4740=？",
        "answer": 4.675778341674085
    },
    {
        "question": "2161×17355=？",
        "answer": 7.5740793848906725
    },
    {
        "question": "37×14645=？",
        "answer": 5.7338911000846124
    },
    {
        "question": "18458×45425=？",
        "answer": 8.923479577630978
    },
    {
        "question": "372×45198=？",
        "answer": 7.225662157698126
    },
    {
        "question": "950058812÷11321630=？",
        "answer": 1.9238415327986182
    },
    {
        "question": "35577×229=？",
        "answer": 6.911004806122183
    },
    {
        "question": "4×205=？",
        "answer": 2.9138138523837167
    },
    {
        "question": "325016×2589=？",
        "answer": 8.925036791538888
    },
    {
        "question": "3669221×263=？",
        "answer": 8.984529618923819
    },
    {
        "question": "13×9423906=？",
        "answer": 8.08817429784357
    },
    {
        "question": "817403÷367=？",
        "answer": 3.3477701630567553
    },
    {
        "question": "171800×3184=？",
        "answer": 8.737996218560856
    },
    {
        "question": "125785÷14244=？",
        "answer": 0.9459968890987763
    },
    {
        "question": "153681125÷114791759=？",
        "answer": 0.1267098202506419
    },
    {
        "question": "1069556÷33660=？",
        "answer": 1.502089416729441
    },
    {
        "question": "160377386÷2291865=？",
        "answer": 1.8449540982381578
    },
    {
        "question": "5374899÷37000=？",
        "answer": 2.1621685837476634
    },
    {
        "question": "83797033÷11328=？",
        "answer": 3.869075401500103
    },
    {
        "question": "4×11724258=？",
        "answer": 7.6711453581349165
    },
    {
        "question": "82327÷40519=？",
        "answer": 0.3078835714589068
    },
    {
        "question": "31868×2578=？",
        "answer": 7.914637721510914
    },
    {
        "question": "1487×3523=？",
        "answer": 6.719223611703197
    },
    {
        "question": "2774308÷397=？",
        "answer": 3.844364167448943
    },
    {
        "question": "9×1261858=？",
        "answer": 7.0552529948654845
    },
    {
        "question": "605325149÷210=？",
        "answer": 6.459769422867773
    },
    {
        "question": "932478023÷4448=？",
        "answer": 5.321473826408277
    },
    {
        "question": "382497÷111748=？",
        "answer": 0.5343882741188055
    },
    {
        "question": "60127084÷6250=？",
        "answer": 3.983190124911248
    },
    {
        "question": "4×115808=？",
        "answer": 5.665798552756068
    },
    {
        "question": "471×218=？",
        "answer": 5.011477400733501
    },
    {
        "question": "1183803÷556044=？",
        "answer": 0.32817027737838333
    },
    {
        "question": "2197÷716=？",
        "answer": 0.4869170346126548
    },
    {
        "question": "84×9547823=？",
        "answer": 8.904183645408349
    },
    {
        "question": "2377633÷724697=？",
        "answer": 0.5159883563573089
    },
    {
        "question": "117519428÷55518855=？",
        "answer": 0.32566916814137387
    },
    {
        "question": "9577×22892=？",
        "answer": 8.340913224656353
    },
    {
        "question": "234469588÷795225=？",
        "answer": 2.4695964955131138
    },
    {
        "question": "251143838÷7020427=？",
        "answer": 1.5535589990754979
    },
    {
        "question": "333827÷136670=？",
        "answer": 0.38784826517623755
    },
    {
        "question": "20220448÷53986=？",
        "answer": 2.5735096231397887
    },
    {
        "question": "81017×4879=？",
        "answer": 8.596906975651914
    },
    {
        "question": "1×31232729=？",
        "answer": 7.494609932928913
    },
    {
        "question": "1459770×520=？",
        "answer": 8.88028777777572
    },
    {
        "question": "207741311÷112550195=？",
        "answer": 0.2661766162315173
    },
    {
        "question": "1701×599=？",
        "answer": 6.0081311360018805
    },
    {
        "question": "82535÷53630=？",
        "answer": 0.18723035865922952
    },
    {
        "question": "8822112÷7135132=？",
        "answer": 0.09217055503127322
    },
    {
        "question": "13910÷1542=？",
        "answer": 0.9552427562771082
    },
    {
        "question": "14361607÷133634=？",
        "answer": 2.0312860701247923
    },
    {
        "question": "3436411÷16359=？",
        "answer": 2.322348348141981
    },
    {
        "question": "136485×6306=？",
        "answer": 8.934838890497893
    },
    {
        "question": "4306091÷17556=？",
        "answer": 2.3896576312941558
    },
    {
        "question": "95941361÷2426=？",
        "answer": 4.597115078435237
    },
    {
        "question": "135493223÷664=？",
        "answer": 5.309749494164855
    },
    {
        "question": "244001÷5318=？",
        "answer": 1.6616432732349515
    },
    {
        "question": "7052×6216=？",
        "answer": 7.641823309420142
    },
    {
        "question": "25×61142=？",
        "answer": 6.184279649387877
    },
    {
        "question": "73764×508=？",
        "answer": 7.5737081714524015
    },
    {
        "question": "507444÷438731=？",
        "answer": 0.0631897997791846
    },
    {
        "question": "57×10894=？",
        "answer": 5.793062226609605
    },
    {
        "question": "31929601÷468773=？",
        "answer": 1.8332309019291138
    },
    {
        "question": "13482816÷60346=？",
        "answer": 2.3491321193169274
    },
    {
        "question": "273503×3173=？",
        "answer": 8.938432166485768
    },
    {
        "question": "1845×38994=？",
        "answer": 7.8569941578457945
    },
    {
        "question": "5794×1226=？",
        "answer": 6.85146896105014
    },
    {
        "question": "245270÷34573=？",
        "answer": 0.8509073649036738
    },
    {
        "question": "382850465÷9109068=？",
        "answer": 1.623555234778804
    },
    {
        "question": "15×1325=？",
        "answer": 4.298307137328508
    },
    {
        "question": "369499÷359=？",
        "answer": 3.0125188187937444
    },
    {
        "question": "33603633÷149996=？",
        "answer": 2.3503065552271325
    },
    {
        "question": "761×601=？",
        "answer": 5.660259128773312
    },
    {
        "question": "29430×18712=？",
        "answer": 8.740910470900708
    },
    {
        "question": "20×543=？",
        "answer": 4.035829825252828
    },
    {
        "question": "4×26489206=？",
        "answer": 8.025128932071905
    },
    {
        "question": "734395491÷412862=？",
        "answer": 3.250125089685533
    },
    {
        "question": "1794×1595=？",
        "answer": 6.456583126101274
    },
    {
        "question": "13×426609=？",
        "answer": 6.7439733656544405
    },
    {
        "question": "110472113÷5567381=？",
        "answer": 1.2976017178613446
    },
    {
        "question": "263239643÷11807=？",
        "answer": 4.348211729907686
    },
    {
        "question": "34330928÷122766=？",
        "answer": 2.446607437251889
    },
    {
        "question": "25252×500=？",
        "answer": 7.101265784991335
    },
    {
        "question": "8014÷1348=？",
        "answer": 0.77415944589738
    },
    {
        "question": "18034421÷281624=？",
        "answer": 1.8064325411084012
    },
    {
        "question": "133×4612866=？",
        "answer": 8.787822479857635
    },
    {
        "question": "566964902÷451206=？",
        "answer": 3.0991813085667537
    },
    {
        "question": "1265378÷553=？",
        "answer": 3.359495148192812
    },
    {
        "question": "30×34048=？",
        "answer": 6.0092128609985975
    },
    {
        "question": "220817÷6128=？",
        "answer": 1.5567137486735012
    },
    {
        "question": "484841445÷181290=？",
        "answer": 3.4272258879439788
    },
    {
        "question": "8448723÷362375=？",
        "answer": 1.3676328431944584
    },
    {
        "question": "2×218569308=？",
        "answer": 8.640619172938852
    },
    {
        "question": "56×9897=？",
        "answer": 5.743691597271207
    },
    {
        "question": "619×25820=？",
        "answer": 7.203646886950519
    },
    {
        "question": "3842215÷441543=？",
        "answer": 0.9396086590840915
    },
    {
        "question": "634251506÷1351=？",
        "answer": 5.671606158084529
    },
    {
        "question": "1053×25537=？",
        "answer": 7.429598247669192
    },
    {
        "question": "48227104÷13997136=？",
        "answer": 0.5372520013128602
    },
    {
        "question": "1162×32419=？",
        "answer": 7.576005742478592
    },
    {
        "question": "8×246375=？",
        "answer": 6.294686624279443
    },
    {
        "question": "2475÷1627=？",
        "answer": 0.18218765033272874
    },
    {
        "question": "1975×1747=？",
        "answer": 6.53786000494541
    },
    {
        "question": "671651359÷48977903=？",
        "answer": 1.1371437110553444
    },
    {
        "question": "178×1028=？",
        "answer": 5.262413116968151
    },
    {
        "question": "105144÷4207=？",
        "answer": 1.397811982872785
    },
    {
        "question": "31101×1476=？",
        "answer": 7.66186071074215
    },
    {
        "question": "139×1604=？",
        "answer": 5.34821916420224
    },
    {
        "question": "300300÷47408=？",
        "answer": 0.8017036980630052
    },
    {
        "question": "16×3142=？",
        "answer": 4.701326163359879
    },
    {
        "question": "2×2891=？",
        "answer": 3.762078087334639
    },
    {
        "question": "25161×29008=？",
        "answer": 8.863245684488556
    },
    {
        "question": "51109175÷117077=？",
        "answer": 2.6400272851946287
    },
    {
        "question": "52120390÷231986=？",
        "answer": 2.3515458800631794
    },
    {
        "question": "4147638÷33630=？",
        "answer": 2.091073977446007
    },
    {
        "question": "67×449003=？",
        "answer": 7.478324045439323
    },
    {
        "question": "1054631÷2908=？",
        "answer": 2.559506130720704
    },
    {
        "question": "2×11413442=？",
        "answer": 7.358446631859689
    },
    {
        "question": "503201÷8023=？",
        "answer": 1.7974047032992055
    },
    {
        "question": "838×1611=？",
        "answer": 6.130339559049495
    },
    {
        "question": "4738×247=？",
        "answer": 6.068292009646412
    },
    {
        "question": "158×407=？",
        "answer": 4.8082514961796425
    },
    {
        "question": "237346232÷104225=？",
        "answer": 3.3574104376506204
    },
    {
        "question": "33757÷17469=？",
        "answer": 0.28609579889198666
    },
    {
        "question": "5832597÷4944=？",
        "answer": 3.0717835080536027
    },
    {
        "question": "667451÷1860=？",
        "answer": 2.554906443855055
    },
    {
        "question": "385453843÷6296464=？",
        "answer": 1.7868756553465686
    },
    {
        "question": "1239×5790=？",
        "answer": 6.8557498701035
    },
    {
        "question": "100349÷403=？",
        "answer": 2.3962080028633035
    },
    {
        "question": "142×1617560=？",
        "answer": 8.361148743266689
    },
    {
        "question": "5×3894260=？",
        "answer": 7.289394948129117
    },
    {
        "question": "43504246÷21418163=？",
        "answer": 0.30774942663868804
    },
    {
        "question": "691180÷242709=？",
        "answer": 0.4545052820010753
    },
    {
        "question": "1×9965=？",
        "answer": 3.9984773030365064
    },
    {
        "question": "203301÷3517=？",
        "answer": 1.7619671465405442
    },
    {
        "question": "9×67332727=？",
        "answer": 8.782468713348369
    },
    {
        "question": "51876÷41857=？",
        "answer": 0.09319838347768
    },
    {
        "question": "58362493÷416=？",
        "answer": 5.147040504222823
    },
    {
        "question": "82368780÷30414=？",
        "answer": 3.432689091898895
    },
    {
        "question": "868348261÷23359679=？",
        "answer": 1.5702270683138269
    },
    {
        "question": "822588369÷961=？",
        "answer": 5.93245917683499
    },
    {
        "question": "2633179÷37879=？",
        "answer": 1.842081877697345
    },
    {
        "question": "28847913÷937500=？",
        "answer": 1.4881431232282618
    },
    {
        "question": "8531×6733=？",
        "answer": 7.759208556424097
    },
    {
        "question": "202335009÷811=？",
        "answer": 5.397050178831952
    },
    {
        "question": "2095×9970=？",
        "answer": 7.31987918561397
    },
    {
        "question": "1×4842=？",
        "answer": 3.685024785105714
    },
    {
        "question": "346×56428=？",
        "answer": 7.290570756463908
    },
    {
        "question": "261412234÷865=？",
        "answer": 5.480309801083318
    },
    {
        "question": "315×29854=？",
        "answer": 6.9733130822715435
    },
    {
        "question": "13728530÷23812=？",
        "answer": 2.760828163206521
    },
    {
        "question": "31384673÷340=？",
        "answer": 4.965238691011054
    },
    {
        "question": "1640370÷9375=？",
        "answer": 2.2429705416689973
    },
    {
        "question": "128×2753=？",
        "answer": 5.547016181041198
    },
    {
        "question": "3955657÷1087502=？",
        "answer": 0.5607885620078557
    },
    {
        "question": "32684÷2706=？",
        "answer": 1.0820074095651706
    },
    {
        "question": "1071÷496=？",
        "answer": 0.33430779434165814
    },
    {
        "question": "4039×30964=？",
        "answer": 8.09713091195463
    },
    {
        "question": "12933×502=？",
        "answer": 6.81240299471857
    },
    {
        "question": "699605355÷310971109=？",
        "answer": 0.3521330825940754
    },
    {
        "question": "1007469×936=？",
        "answer": 8.974507540438529
    },
    {
        "question": "677460÷4044=？",
        "answer": 2.2240725108678987
    },
    {
        "question": "22×2004=？",
        "answer": 4.644320398017414
    },
    {
        "question": "122×2882=？",
        "answer": 5.546053807152719
    },
    {
        "question": "1×6055230=？",
        "answer": 6.782130643900832
    },
    {
        "question": "5110×418=？",
        "answer": 6.329597181909748
    },
    {
        "question": "19×290375=？",
        "answer": 6.741712823761121
    },
    {
        "question": "6360×1540=？",
        "answer": 6.990977836484877
    },
    {
        "question": "1×78583566=？",
        "answer": 7.8953317325310595
    },
    {
        "question": "60×98769=？",
        "answer": 6.772771907101722
    },
    {
        "question": "54256×739=？",
        "answer": 7.603092210828837
    },
    {
        "question": "155077640÷30306=？",
        "answer": 3.7090205643163
    },
    {
        "question": "794445072÷29991249=？",
        "answer": 1.423069322885011
    },
    {
        "question": "830694846÷299=？",
        "answer": 6.443770327593192
    },
    {
        "question": "336994÷75455=？",
        "answer": 0.6499341451147488
    },
    {
        "question": "104722591÷50009=？",
        "answer": 3.32099220848946
    },
    {
        "question": "541137×310=？",
        "answer": 8.22466892347276
    },
    {
        "question": "4067030÷20376=？",
        "answer": 2.3001584439863794
    },
    {
        "question": "3100×257135=？",
        "answer": 8.90152288861141
    },
    {
        "question": "28018205÷7323=？",
        "answer": 3.5827512744158354
    },
    {
        "question": "186876429÷12125=？",
        "answer": 4.187872779354428
    },
    {
        "question": "307807378÷41895=？",
        "answer": 3.8661168307007143
    },
    {
        "question": "79996÷30351=？",
        "answer": 0.4208952670113039
    },
    {
        "question": "331427×1465=？",
        "answer": 8.686225510407018
    },
    {
        "question": "191906÷146147=？",
        "answer": 0.11829864839635504
    },
    {
        "question": "42355262÷8166=？",
        "answer": 3.714897996945239
    },
    {
        "question": "214×8210=？",
        "answer": 6.244756930468632
    },
    {
        "question": "3×46260164=？",
        "answer": 8.142328422803393
    },
    {
        "question": "44084653÷2238984=？",
        "answer": 1.294236436635346
    },
    {
        "question": "25330×338=？",
        "answer": 6.932551890068202
    },
    {
        "question": "4301059÷2300=？",
        "answer": 3.27184756403445
    },
    {
        "question": "2134601÷1136=？",
        "answer": 3.273938377169948
    },
    {
        "question": "1×7492380=？",
        "answer": 6.874619795894603
    },
    {
        "question": "7065009÷1912=？",
        "answer": 3.567624831485522
    },
    {
        "question": "1×5530951=？",
        "answer": 6.742799810968917
    },
    {
        "question": "918789÷509806=？",
        "answer": 0.2558108446041127
    },
    {
        "question": "6×37439=？",
        "answer": 5.35147549054902
    },
    {
        "question": "9250435÷2583718=？",
        "answer": 0.5539170450153503
    },
    {
        "question": "2×90427030=？",
        "answer": 8.257328262701204
    },
    {
        "question": "80×53712=？",
        "answer": 6.633161310895881
    },
    {
        "question": "2601×1047=？",
        "answer": 6.435087033874715
    },
    {
        "question": "14961757÷264=？",
        "answer": 4.753378670040905
    },
    {
        "question": "75232÷1007=？",
        "answer": 1.8733731368912272
    },
    {
        "question": "19796444÷8066190=？",
        "answer": 0.38991873807567734
    },
    {
        "question": "5×24728=？",
        "answer": 5.092158996391268
    },
    {
        "question": "3×7675523=？",
        "answer": 7.362229232129536
    },
    {
        "question": "2×432993=？",
        "answer": 5.937510871033636
    },
    {
        "question": "14470713÷3910536=？",
        "answer": 0.5682536418611902
    },
    {
        "question": "730÷615=？",
        "answer": 0.07444774434503917
    },
    {
        "question": "47×4031=？",
        "answer": 5.277510656088769
    },
    {
        "question": "9673973÷234=？",
        "answer": 4.616389013530719
    },
    {
        "question": "394087÷15756=？",
        "answer": 1.3981461366148602
    },
    {
        "question": "244×1156=？",
        "answer": 5.4503476604232395
    },
    {
        "question": "341×68265=？",
        "answer": 7.366952473554572
    },
    {
        "question": "4027×236267=？",
        "answer": 8.97838469648428
    },
    {
        "question": "24969514÷8111=？",
        "answer": 3.4883356880400602
    },
    {
        "question": "277×2770=？",
        "answer": 5.884959538128897
    },
    {
        "question": "199×4659=？",
        "answer": 5.967145786857928
    },
    {
        "question": "688×1246=？",
        "answer": 5.933106480558662
    },
    {
        "question": "490677761÷254739=？",
        "answer": 3.284700935270819
    },
    {
        "question": "7647×244=？",
        "answer": 6.270880916527659
    },
    {
        "question": "398643492÷349783=？",
        "answer": 3.056785980206293
    },
    {
        "question": "900÷269=？",
        "answer": 0.5244902294369169
    },
    {
        "question": "2679817÷8763=？",
        "answer": 2.4854523261401433
    },
    {
        "question": "48×53590=？",
        "answer": 6.410324994419199
    },
    {
        "question": "1852326×229=？",
        "answer": 8.627552905043085
    },
    {
        "question": "12951439÷391=？",
        "answer": 4.520141267009042
    },
    {
        "question": "44826605÷3652=？",
        "answer": 4.089005079403518
    },
    {
        "question": "1174÷805=？",
        "answer": 0.16387221654372713
    },
    {
        "question": "1256883÷1118=？",
        "answer": 3.0508530486627534
    },
    {
        "question": "88×1313842=？",
        "answer": 8.063025813131969
    },
    {
        "question": "9882×15380=？",
        "answer": 8.181801185018811
    },
    {
        "question": "6×121018811=？",
        "answer": 8.861004132092962
    },
    {
        "question": "63607939÷1792=？",
        "answer": 4.5501733186354585
    },
    {
        "question": "175721859÷5171=？",
        "answer": 4.531251251341878
    },
    {
        "question": "156389÷3178=？",
        "answer": 1.692052309769947
    },
    {
        "question": "69305092÷27430424=？",
        "answer": 0.40253262369838666
    },
    {
        "question": "180×487519=？",
        "answer": 7.943264051157062
    },
    {
        "question": "22770340÷19917527=？",
        "answer": 0.05813410085740022
    },
    {
        "question": "2474×627=？",
        "answer": 6.190667236123819
    },
    {
        "question": "3841267÷30626=？",
        "answer": 2.098384217107009
    },
    {
        "question": "305639796÷6793=？",
        "answer": 4.6531482865497376
    },
    {
        "question": "10451817÷6337=？",
        "answer": 3.217308089970428
    },
    {
        "question": "83598÷5511=？",
        "answer": 1.1809654764691222
    },
    {
        "question": "3×1720271=？",
        "answer": 6.71271812286777
    },
    {
        "question": "14×3244=？",
        "answer": 4.657208881217357
    },
    {
        "question": "1659057÷220530=？",
        "answer": 0.8763936298089936
    },
    {
        "question": "1×216=？",
        "answer": 2.3344537511509307
    },
    {
        "question": "18×4616=？",
        "answer": 4.919538305250981
    },
    {
        "question": "7067×84317=？",
        "answer": 8.775150237254545
    },
    {
        "question": "851×16850=？",
        "answer": 7.156529465291945
    },
    {
        "question": "169289÷111356=？",
        "answer": 0.18191511726623805
    },
    {
        "question": "436×585=？",
        "answer": 5.406642355350766
    },
    {
        "question": "3×121296748=？",
        "answer": 8.560970412184854
    },
    {
        "question": "5×444=？",
        "answer": 3.346352974450639
    },
    {
        "question": "5×87694176=？",
        "answer": 8.641940756025315
    },
    {
        "question": "2×4136480=？",
        "answer": 6.917660924506117
    },
    {
        "question": "40654948÷4926=？",
        "answer": 3.9166190024103607
    },
    {
        "question": "135×6024=？",
        "answer": 5.91021873168765
    },
    {
        "question": "140×319=？",
        "answer": 4.649918718735419
    },
    {
        "question": "148×1343=？",
        "answer": 5.2983377280636725
    },
    {
        "question": "9×223492=？",
        "answer": 6.3035044914127045
    },
    {
        "question": "676631275÷2192235=？",
        "answer": 2.4894649605422585
    },
    {
        "question": "45106300÷815=？",
        "answer": 4.74307959531436
    },
    {
        "question": "2×46313=？",
        "answer": 4.96673290970142
    },
    {
        "question": "2×1150425=？",
        "answer": 6.36188830650188
    },
    {
        "question": "3×3745=？",
        "answer": 4.050573076755148
    },
    {
        "question": "38679÷9524=？",
        "answer": 0.6086558506508224
    },
    {
        "question": "83737732÷153798=？",
        "answer": 2.7359705061314425
    },
    {
        "question": "3200×51318=？",
        "answer": 8.215419700732673
    },
    {
        "question": "432386÷312135=？",
        "answer": 0.14152915445829994
    },
    {
        "question": "894×319953=？",
        "answer": 8.456423705428977
    },
    {
        "question": "251×261023=？",
        "answer": 7.816352498294381
    },
    {
        "question": "2447797÷4969=？",
        "answer": 2.6925064014357405
    },
    {
        "question": "116062632÷1219407=？",
        "answer": 1.9785437312561822
    },
    {
        "question": "27724304÷9452589=？",
        "answer": 0.4673098771728716
    },
    {
        "question": "39340347÷20137075=？",
        "answer": 0.2908417986904952
    },
    {
        "question": "22035922÷1461=？",
        "answer": 4.178481010508431
    },
    {
        "question": "107×407=？",
        "answer": 4.63897818691043
    },
    {
        "question": "1176088÷930824=？",
        "answer": 0.10157224631359488
    },
    {
        "question": "7720318÷976291=？",
        "answer": 0.8980559035411292
    },
    {
        "question": "168×3804=？",
        "answer": 5.80554978999124
    },
    {
        "question": "900870423÷452752=？",
        "answer": 3.2988019511228206
    },
    {
        "question": "611337852÷75293=？",
        "answer": 3.9095266850245016
    },
    {
        "question": "2×35237=？",
        "answer": 4.848028922109257
    },
    {
        "question": "13×19206=？",
        "answer": 5.397380276834613
    },
    {
        "question": "315069970÷5337520=？",
        "answer": 1.7710674962375592
    },
    {
        "question": "63534541÷542=？",
        "answer": 5.06901061020666
    },
    {
        "question": "470×934206=？",
        "answer": 8.642540510181554
    },
    {
        "question": "1582415÷292=？",
        "answer": 3.7339375395806926
    },
    {
        "question": "122370212÷6126=？",
        "answer": 4.300498719959358
    },
    {
        "question": "214848÷1833=？",
        "answer": 2.068968850269683
    },
    {
        "question": "1×17668296=？",
        "answer": 7.24719466645741
    },
    {
        "question": "26791348÷2024362=？",
        "answer": 1.1217063891554337
    },
    {
        "question": "955040÷118406=？",
        "answer": 0.906647851552006
    },
    {
        "question": "157319÷1686=？",
        "answer": 1.969923606859981
    },
    {
        "question": "3313596÷146054=？",
        "answer": 1.3557861017398614
    },
    {
        "question": "692066441÷17496303=？",
        "answer": 1.5972014991913825
    },
    {
        "question": "346573407÷621202=？",
        "answer": 2.7465623904133816
    },
    {
        "question": "2784×608=？",
        "answer": 6.22857281021126
    },
    {
        "question": "1×24520=？",
        "answer": 4.389520465846378
    },
    {
        "question": "1205×24607=？",
        "answer": 7.472045716165742
    },
    {
        "question": "2937×2390=？",
        "answer": 6.846301847470938
    },
    {
        "question": "13×945007=？",
        "answer": 7.089378377800347
    },
    {
        "question": "839461202÷40102735=？",
        "answer": 1.32082663638502
    },
    {
        "question": "1725×239203=？",
        "answer": 8.615555721528658
    },
    {
        "question": "826×980=？",
        "answer": 5.908206123012877
    },
    {
        "question": "14×7802=？",
        "answer": 5.03833398165401
    },
    {
        "question": "3047136÷2704370=？",
        "answer": 0.05182572852469266
    },
    {
        "question": "135364×417=？",
        "answer": 7.751639234240371
    },
    {
        "question": "274856677÷1148=？",
        "answer": 5.379164403536443
    },
    {
        "question": "102216÷484=？",
        "answer": 2.3246735201409425
    },
    {
        "question": "9773×50652=？",
        "answer": 8.694624496972327
    },
    {
        "question": "7×3532=？",
        "answer": 4.3931187349197875
    },
    {
        "question": "3765×60928=？",
        "answer": 8.36058190290508
    },
    {
        "question": "1×46893514=？",
        "answer": 7.6711127781350505
    },
    {
        "question": "969107÷368=？",
        "answer": 3.420523911879929
    },
    {
        "question": "31917×527=？",
        "answer": 7.2258326788224645
    },
    {
        "question": "602×251=？",
        "answer": 5.179270212738863
    },
    {
        "question": "33435×8922=？",
        "answer": 8.474663546441517
    },
    {
        "question": "56174022÷475290=？",
        "answer": 2.072576843082783
    },
    {
        "question": "12×129875=？",
        "answer": 6.1927068066128585
    },
    {
        "question": "72469÷7612=？",
        "answer": 0.9786534889134747
    },
    {
        "question": "14769092÷2435=？",
        "answer": 3.78285483026832
    },
    {
        "question": "4308788÷212356=？",
        "answer": 1.307290590308706
    },
    {
        "question": "38666456÷3482845=？",
        "answer": 1.0454002212314142
    },
    {
        "question": "131226235÷2518365=？",
        "answer": 1.7169019937667087
    },
    {
        "question": "1×20771243=？",
        "answer": 7.317462486515282
    },
    {
        "question": "9×992=？",
        "answer": 3.9507541815935037
    },
    {
        "question": "32916209÷7029=？",
        "answer": 3.670516267877714
    },
    {
        "question": "212493998÷24747=？",
        "answer": 3.9338241093696493
    },
    {
        "question": "6×602=？",
        "answer": 3.5577477416414682
    },
    {
        "question": "373283498÷685067=？",
        "answer": 2.73630574334267
    },
    {
        "question": "3226859÷16946=？",
        "answer": 2.2797127869277745
    },
    {
        "question": "7366×268=？",
        "answer": 6.295366508547683
    },
    {
        "question": "6087÷4225=？",
        "answer": 0.15857658846729725
    },
    {
        "question": "6×759=？",
        "answer": 3.658393026279124
    },
    {
        "question": "539780138÷167132=？",
        "answer": 3.509157289779676
    },
    {
        "question": "42799×2256=？",
        "answer": 7.9847727171386005
    },
    {
        "question": "114376636÷1572=？",
        "answer": 4.861884777399014
    },
    {
        "question": "17×1033927=？",
        "answer": 7.244938798031402
    },
    {
        "question": "14093513÷16420=？",
        "answer": 2.9336461076326272
    },
    {
        "question": "91×59163=？",
        "answer": 6.731091580134323
    },
    {
        "question": "148798806÷48122306=？",
        "answer": 0.4902530159635209
    },
    {
        "question": "5825×113684=？",
        "answer": 8.820995275646373
    },
    {
        "question": "749×676=？",
        "answer": 5.704428513641102
    },
    {
        "question": "1×6951=？",
        "answer": 3.842047288509638
    },
    {
        "question": "15×9380400=？",
        "answer": 8.148312617060425
    },
    {
        "question": "202448÷2900=？",
        "answer": 1.8439154927967123
    },
    {
        "question": "79×827001=？",
        "answer": 7.815133125987147
    },
    {
        "question": "3×464=？",
        "answer": 3.1436392352745433
    },
    {
        "question": "222511×392=？",
        "answer": 7.940637552545119
    },
    {
        "question": "2×121608=？",
        "answer": 5.385992141666258
    },
    {
        "question": "127×1065065=？",
        "answer": 8.131179834157855
    },
    {
        "question": "2120÷1511=？",
        "answer": 0.14707139658972604
    },
    {
        "question": "1067065÷194712=？",
        "answer": 0.7387981574815159
    },
    {
        "question": "6×348236=？",
        "answer": 6.32002491605405
    },
    {
        "question": "2889÷945=？",
        "answer": 0.485315733334934
    },
    {
        "question": "708610×776=？",
        "answer": 8.740268998120962
    },
    {
        "question": "10747502÷1268=？",
        "answer": 3.9281882810610913
    },
    {
        "question": "32799×229=？",
        "answer": 6.875696085164299
    },
    {
        "question": "71047644÷1024710=？",
        "answer": 1.8409487064840737
    },
    {
        "question": "329483×327=？",
        "answer": 8.0323807643167
    },
    {
        "question": "4729÷1849=？",
        "answer": 0.4078324028562532
    },
    {
        "question": "12×222=？",
        "answer": 3.4255342204982635
    },
    {
        "question": "34152×1960=？",
        "answer": 7.825672213152367
    },
    {
        "question": "29×24258906=？",
        "answer": 8.847269209562395
    },
    {
        "question": "11433÷1284=？",
        "answer": 0.9495951797589952
    },
    {
        "question": "20847043÷5112655=？",
        "answer": 0.6103979745042832
    },
    {
        "question": "30×373560=？",
        "answer": 7.049481621449803
    },
    {
        "question": "62504237÷14710=？",
        "answer": 3.6282967853101518
    },
    {
        "question": "48511222÷663=？",
        "answer": 4.8643286862578305
    },
    {
        "question": "26762025÷2499681=？",
        "answer": 1.0296343829045564
    },
    {
        "question": "883302087÷151208579=？",
        "answer": 0.7665328244743077
    },
    {
        "question": "9408408÷23474=？",
        "answer": 2.602929042276475
    },
    {
        "question": "73×134323=？",
        "answer": 6.9914732429891036
    },
    {
        "question": "101353974÷362995=？",
        "answer": 2.445940138689515
    },
    {
        "question": "8×187306=？",
        "answer": 6.17564167640752
    },
    {
        "question": "1228×54902=？",
        "answer": 7.828786532259665
    },
    {
        "question": "8×4183=？",
        "answer": 4.524577851572574
    },
    {
        "question": "1008×415378=？",
        "answer": 8.621904023028813
    },
    {
        "question": "6×1189=？",
        "answer": 3.8533331050023354
    },
    {
        "question": "386141÷1350=？",
        "answer": 2.4564121484577415
    },
    {
        "question": "212×29505=？",
        "answer": 6.79623147990377
    },
    {
        "question": "55×2993=？",
        "answer": 5.2164694063344355
    },
    {
        "question": "32×1081=？",
        "answer": 4.538975672273216
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1922=？",
        "answer": 3.2837533833325265
    },
    {
        "question": "1999242÷1376=？",
        "answer": 3.1622469329567173
    },
    {
        "question": "4871×39390=？",
        "answer": 8.283004110380912
    },
    {
        "question": "2687×39071=？",
        "answer": 8.021122193320203
    },
    {
        "question": "159×2255992=？",
        "answer": 8.55473467957767
    },
    {
        "question": "313×612=？",
        "answer": 5.282295759692009
    },
    {
        "question": "2×555=？",
        "answer": 3.0453229787866576
    },
    {
        "question": "294000÷71013=？",
        "answer": 0.6170094702641211
    },
    {
        "question": "1×3665=？",
        "answer": 3.564073978977147
    },
    {
        "question": "880÷269=？",
        "answer": 0.5147303921477606
    },
    {
        "question": "378151÷13395=？",
        "answer": 1.450722535257839
    },
    {
        "question": "55×23838=？",
        "answer": 6.11763250493325
    },
    {
        "question": "10064×205=？",
        "answer": 6.314524489156948
    },
    {
        "question": "319×1057=？",
        "answer": 5.527865670364608
    },
    {
        "question": "3×540666=？",
        "answer": 6.210050314369897
    },
    {
        "question": "8164052÷4227438=？",
        "answer": 0.28582851532900655
    },
    {
        "question": "1×61853655=？",
        "answer": 7.791365367658453
    },
    {
        "question": "10×6867=？",
        "answer": 4.836767047394205
    },
    {
        "question": "364406051÷3628721=？",
        "answer": 2.001832001804974
    },
    {
        "question": "370×652464=？",
        "answer": 8.38275827834143
    },
    {
        "question": "77×62812=？",
        "answer": 6.684533347188802
    },
    {
        "question": "91×6505=？",
        "answer": 5.772288693218699
    },
    {
        "question": "610×1973=？",
        "answer": 6.080456920262958
    },
    {
        "question": "1454×88599=？",
        "answer": 8.109993226638819
    },
    {
        "question": "62128952÷165717=？",
        "answer": 2.5739269653352967
    },
    {
        "question": "3×70832=？",
        "answer": 5.327350759354435
    },
    {
        "question": "8329÷739=？",
        "answer": 1.0519484236899828
    },
    {
        "question": "4×17218=？",
        "answer": 4.838042694809801
    },
    {
        "question": "1703191÷37453=？",
        "answer": 1.6577767429506585
    },
    {
        "question": "14393182÷131954=？",
        "answer": 2.037734257244975
    },
    {
        "question": "19×5948=？",
        "answer": 5.053124560802746
    },
    {
        "question": "479517067÷95773101=？",
        "answer": 0.6995605197169985
    },
    {
        "question": "178274994÷15467501=？",
        "answer": 1.0616702777334126
    },
    {
        "question": "1333546÷16632=？",
        "answer": 1.904063524731058
    },
    {
        "question": "119600212÷50807467=？",
        "answer": 0.3718044057191843
    },
    {
        "question": "1×281=？",
        "answer": 2.44870631990508
    },
    {
        "question": "28×3185922=？",
        "answer": 7.950393170232235
    },
    {
        "question": "61544526÷376=？",
        "answer": 5.214001586284191
    },
    {
        "question": "7×39308=？",
        "answer": 5.439578987394244
    },
    {
        "question": "9759÷7524=？",
        "answer": 0.11295653112317475
    },
    {
        "question": "2522×1369=？",
        "answer": 6.5381485303710525
    },
    {
        "question": "13141×201=？",
        "answer": 6.421824472717088
    },
    {
        "question": "147656÷42023=？",
        "answer": 0.5457640459786667
    },
    {
        "question": "1419155÷865=？",
        "answer": 3.2150137241931223
    },
    {
        "question": "242123×1143=？",
        "answer": 8.442082276750012
    },
    {
        "question": "3490×1670=？",
        "answer": 6.765541898106763
    },
    {
        "question": "100971×1967=？",
        "answer": 8.298001017380708
    },
    {
        "question": "1094935÷117340=？",
        "answer": 0.9699422544928945
    },
    {
        "question": "192685700÷19413=？",
        "answer": 3.9967568305259564
    },
    {
        "question": "67167921÷514896=？",
        "answer": 2.1154423881062487
    },
    {
        "question": "237×20532=？",
        "answer": 6.687179601598829
    },
    {
        "question": "11×343084=？",
        "answer": 6.5767931500120165
    },
    {
        "question": "23085106÷1058932=？",
        "answer": 1.3384638005407645
    },
    {
        "question": "3×1377=？",
        "answer": 3.6160551949765862
    },
    {
        "question": "131283633÷536900=？",
        "answer": 2.3883171824396716
    },
    {
        "question": "3239×1654=？",
        "answer": 6.728946453226705
    },
    {
        "question": "16868754÷1303=？",
        "answer": 4.112138589170014
    },
    {
        "question": "516175677÷827338=？",
        "answer": 2.7951145639361643
    },
    {
        "question": "653118803÷6366=？",
        "answer": 5.011125552800828
    },
    {
        "question": "15653671÷513324=？",
        "answer": 1.4842246320423855
    },
    {
        "question": "1×24802=？",
        "answer": 4.394486703162585
    },
    {
        "question": "16304045÷44857=？",
        "answer": 2.5604651403857286
    },
    {
        "question": "28436309÷10716376=？",
        "answer": 0.42382528172298195
    },
    {
        "question": "73797200÷38043093=？",
        "answer": 0.2877640652687649
    },
    {
        "question": "245221×1507=？",
        "answer": 8.567670911446474
    },
    {
        "question": "107×1259=？",
        "answer": 5.129409507793072
    },
    {
        "question": "414731982÷1732=？",
        "answer": 5.379219639533567
    },
    {
        "question": "2×96959=？",
        "answer": 5.287618123353338
    },
    {
        "question": "22028420÷206412=？",
        "answer": 2.0282484063675312
    },
    {
        "question": "12×813=？",
        "answer": 3.989271791641693
    },
    {
        "question": "2×5107635=？",
        "answer": 7.009249849966063
    },
    {
        "question": "192576199÷2254=？",
        "answer": 4.9316486987954375
    },
    {
        "question": "54×17983130=？",
        "answer": 8.9872590436286
    },
    {
        "question": "57931÷844=？",
        "answer": 1.8365685786925545
    },
    {
        "question": "2535×19440=？",
        "answer": 7.69267422425961
    },
    {
        "question": "975×517=？",
        "answer": 5.7024951587924795
    },
    {
        "question": "337091÷16184=？",
        "answer": 1.3186612876751171
    },
    {
        "question": "7196485÷4331=？",
        "answer": 3.2205322407777275
    },
    {
        "question": "307×15763=？",
        "answer": 6.684777251032756
    },
    {
        "question": "14452486÷12936=？",
        "answer": 3.048142550451649
    },
    {
        "question": "153×1309=？",
        "answer": 5.301631077368355
    },
    {
        "question": "60891÷355=？",
        "answer": 2.2343247533843145
    },
    {
        "question": "30×1940834=？",
        "answer": 7.765109646384703
    },
    {
        "question": "50×3789=？",
        "answer": 5.277494609611012
    },
    {
        "question": "10758×66261=？",
        "answer": 8.852989525841371
    },
    {
        "question": "121259÷969=？",
        "answer": 2.097390205318637
    },
    {
        "question": "751448353÷323750=？",
        "answer": 3.3656893598257733
    },
    {
        "question": "669918634÷542=？",
        "answer": 6.092022771459946
    },
    {
        "question": "434998211÷18953484=？",
        "answer": 1.3607984178729435
    },
    {
        "question": "724×211=？",
        "answer": 5.184021021494839
    },
    {
        "question": "113013155÷355773=？",
        "answer": 2.501956013418571
    },
    {
        "question": "3257628÷11738=？",
        "answer": 2.443307384011839
    },
    {
        "question": "86445793÷11912768=？",
        "answer": 0.8607311785800398
    },
    {
        "question": "6×24770311=？",
        "answer": 8.172082709724263
    },
    {
        "question": "25688953÷883906=？",
        "answer": 1.4633403222429422
    },
    {
        "question": "642×226=？",
        "answer": 5.161643467216254
    },
    {
        "question": "1193487÷541676=？",
        "answer": 0.3430780990779313
    },
    {
        "question": "13264050÷15195=？",
        "answer": 2.9409754459044684
    },
    {
        "question": "11×1503=？",
        "answer": 4.218351665745133
    },
    {
        "question": "29×13736=？",
        "answer": 5.600258280051817
    },
    {
        "question": "62680×283=？",
        "answer": 7.248915423320843
    },
    {
        "question": "1×2941=？",
        "answer": 3.468495024507069
    },
    {
        "question": "29770÷3712=？",
        "answer": 0.9041708670999002
    },
    {
        "question": "8×3268210=？",
        "answer": 7.4173999414958445
    },
    {
        "question": "1555553÷43392=？",
        "answer": 1.5544751449035847
    },
    {
        "question": "4395×835=？",
        "answer": 6.5646453548933925
    },
    {
        "question": "389075197÷6574536=？",
        "answer": 1.7721684382498486
    },
    {
        "question": "204×2921713=？",
        "answer": 8.775267720352744
    },
    {
        "question": "3×414124=？",
        "answer": 6.094251654904562
    },
    {
        "question": "996783÷275=？",
        "answer": 3.559267928714015
    },
    {
        "question": "8513÷1905=？",
        "answer": 0.6501876533807331
    },
    {
        "question": "93275×1335=？",
        "answer": 8.095246523413461
    },
    {
        "question": "25286414÷290080=？",
        "answer": 1.9403694573641446
    },
    {
        "question": "22357×6067=？",
        "answer": 8.13238752175878
    },
    {
        "question": "16430913÷4388652=？",
        "answer": 0.5733305514624943
    },
    {
        "question": "273×2421874=？",
        "answer": 8.820314191905531
    },
    {
        "question": "1×162217=？",
        "answer": 5.210096365407302
    },
    {
        "question": "925260÷157852=？",
        "answer": 0.7680136987327776
    },
    {
        "question": "3×294120=？",
        "answer": 5.945645812019365
    },
    {
        "question": "120084÷76074=？",
        "answer": 0.19824889360717923
    },
    {
        "question": "5338543÷1201=？",
        "answer": 3.647879737752999
    },
    {
        "question": "157840346÷45257657=？",
        "answer": 0.5425259575882353
    },
    {
        "question": "4×39576=？",
        "answer": 5.199491888684087
    },
    {
        "question": "3×557=？",
        "answer": 3.2229764498933915
    },
    {
        "question": "582328÷242=？",
        "answer": 3.3813523067536266
    },
    {
        "question": "13386÷6664=？",
        "answer": 0.3029158322687502
    },
    {
        "question": "992666÷2740=？",
        "answer": 2.5590525842074516
    },
    {
        "question": "888143477÷55289=？",
        "answer": 4.2058443954379285
    },
    {
        "question": "58006626÷596=？",
        "answer": 4.988231345389547
    },
    {
        "question": "426848÷198089=？",
        "answer": 0.3334128912946892
    },
    {
        "question": "110×378807=？",
        "answer": 7.6198106809205175
    },
    {
        "question": "107×287=？",
        "answer": 4.487265674419202
    },
    {
        "question": "1×2614=？",
        "answer": 3.4173055832445254
    },
    {
        "question": "19084468÷251=？",
        "answer": 4.881006336548661
    },
    {
        "question": "1×82834881=？",
        "answer": 7.918213252677424
    },
    {
        "question": "14225×206=？",
        "answer": 6.4669194954362625
    },
    {
        "question": "12133179÷125327=？",
        "answer": 1.9859299608421983
    },
    {
        "question": "99180÷3776=？",
        "answer": 1.4193921183290596
    },
    {
        "question": "4×796196=？",
        "answer": 6.503079982734429
    },
    {
        "question": "287×1237=？",
        "answer": 5.550251596363113
    },
    {
        "question": "3×1243227=？",
        "answer": 6.571671688145356
    },
    {
        "question": "157376942÷33265663=？",
        "answer": 0.6749449186984914
    },
    {
        "question": "7286650÷1529=？",
        "answer": 3.678120424126307
    },
    {
        "question": "55×686=？",
        "answer": 4.576686805200995
    },
    {
        "question": "1×78867=？",
        "answer": 4.896895321132537
    },
    {
        "question": "3×30869=？",
        "answer": 4.96664381547755
    },
    {
        "question": "4×2042399=？",
        "answer": 6.912200580484816
    },
    {
        "question": "47282092÷786=？",
        "answer": 4.779274137653515
    },
    {
        "question": "289110÷123732=？",
        "answer": 0.36858108079903806
    },
    {
        "question": "20290×14850=？",
        "answer": 8.479008500686577
    },
    {
        "question": "37464×1734=？",
        "answer": 7.812663237914215
    },
    {
        "question": "9×6365199=？",
        "answer": 7.758054495316022
    },
    {
        "question": "13974×3519=？",
        "answer": 7.691740005753516
    },
    {
        "question": "90776÷1570=？",
        "answer": 1.7620713894454816
    },
    {
        "question": "164813852÷39841685=？",
        "answer": 0.6166560122632052
    },
    {
        "question": "792665922÷544=？",
        "answer": 6.163491287868897
    },
    {
        "question": "18346378÷347551=？",
        "answer": 1.7225317948272514
    },
    {
        "question": "24×306191=？",
        "answer": 6.866203662862285
    },
    {
        "question": "40079×1171=？",
        "answer": 7.671473772105708
    },
    {
        "question": "68×5557=？",
        "answer": 5.577349309491615
    },
    {
        "question": "91×2158=？",
        "answer": 5.293092832667986
    },
    {
        "question": "58×5288227=？",
        "answer": 8.486738082765834
    },
    {
        "question": "3481571÷3798=？",
        "answer": 2.962220295808519
    },
    {
        "question": "2512×248=？",
        "answer": 5.794471315891375
    },
    {
        "question": "12×4979365=？",
        "answer": 7.776355208369657
    },
    {
        "question": "27×16890=？",
        "answer": 5.658993413729996
    },
    {
        "question": "248440970÷123319=？",
        "answer": 3.3041932218607486
    },
    {
        "question": "6632×94180=？",
        "answer": 8.795603203648922
    },
    {
        "question": "21932÷268=？",
        "answer": 1.9129434431826544
    },
    {
        "question": "475234044÷44606=？",
        "answer": 4.027514264280354
    },
    {
        "question": "26370÷16718=？",
        "answer": 0.19792580889839428
    },
    {
        "question": "58×187371=？",
        "answer": 7.036130368190613
    },
    {
        "question": "8277÷630=？",
        "answer": 1.1185324057452661
    },
    {
        "question": "1×20572=？",
        "answer": 4.3132765156490525
    },
    {
        "question": "13×9666054=？",
        "answer": 8.099192569329077
    },
    {
        "question": "4×627=？",
        "answer": 3.399327532158679
    },
    {
        "question": "7×150743=？",
        "answer": 6.023335194113628
    },
    {
        "question": "15×23921170=？",
        "answer": 8.554873676517426
    },
    {
        "question": "575×1732=？",
        "answer": 5.998215732370959
    },
    {
        "question": "3×473=？",
        "answer": 3.151982395457474
    },
    {
        "question": "2177036÷7844=？",
        "answer": 2.4433280257045484
    },
    {
        "question": "22241×2910=？",
        "answer": 7.811047299086502
    },
    {
        "question": "23160863÷546154=？",
        "answer": 1.627439618912711
    },
    {
        "question": "7×1226797=？",
        "answer": 6.933870745305599
    },
    {
        "question": "679257÷1016=？",
        "answer": 2.8251404147337964
    },
    {
        "question": "1023×2831=？",
        "answer": 6.461815503077263
    },
    {
        "question": "223983÷610=？",
        "answer": 2.564885222223551
    },
    {
        "question": "29020390÷1721968=？",
        "answer": 1.2266781680197063
    },
    {
        "question": "8105878÷1258=？",
        "answer": 3.809119421863471
    },
    {
        "question": "498084×619=？",
        "answer": 8.488993240093365
    },
    {
        "question": "9×3480=？",
        "answer": 4.495821753385906
    },
    {
        "question": "62075÷573=？",
        "answer": 2.034762106259212
    },
    {
        "question": "7476÷2429=？",
        "answer": 0.48824177790166384
    },
    {
        "question": "95355÷916=？",
        "answer": 2.0174479968182877
    },
    {
        "question": "27233902÷11473254=？",
        "answer": 0.3754232620441046
    },
    {
        "question": "1871×37011=？",
        "answer": 7.840404606953801
    },
    {
        "question": "1×432=？",
        "answer": 2.635483746814912
    },
    {
        "question": "50240086÷51763=？",
        "answer": 2.9870309355877827
    },
    {
        "question": "164422113÷5708009=？",
        "answer": 1.459475575844436
    },
    {
        "question": "9798269÷3309=？",
        "answer": 3.471452591170498
    },
    {
        "question": "6263310÷31437=？",
        "answer": 2.299362812386363
    },
    {
        "question": "2992×7424=？",
        "answer": 7.346599552403229
    },
    {
        "question": "157717÷6228=？",
        "answer": 1.4035299036894995
    },
    {
        "question": "469009801÷289=？",
        "answer": 6.210284075599777
    },
    {
        "question": "27167662÷37658=？",
        "answer": 2.8581950143239636
    },
    {
        "question": "11×542=？",
        "answer": 3.775391971696612
    },
    {
        "question": "6×2755895=？",
        "answer": 7.218413917251565
    },
    {
        "question": "37×8412=？",
        "answer": 5.493100988081278
    },
    {
        "question": "850406706÷565630=？",
        "answer": 3.177094240618547
    },
    {
        "question": "9048092÷5907947=？",
        "answer": 0.18512041718242492
    },
    {
        "question": "133467087÷693=？",
        "answer": 5.284640947219267
    },
    {
        "question": "9313×749=？",
        "answer": 6.843571420654388
    },
    {
        "question": "1109950×452=？",
        "answer": 8.700441850342923
    },
    {
        "question": "1558×81403=？",
        "answer": 8.10320786386994
    },
    {
        "question": "2339540÷2354=？",
        "answer": 2.997324016381232
    },
    {
        "question": "5175×207=？",
        "answer": 6.029880699585873
    },
    {
        "question": "19×42580=？",
        "answer": 5.907959258055133
    },
    {
        "question": "1×179321=？",
        "answer": 5.25363115208351
    },
    {
        "question": "33509394÷17342109=？",
        "answer": 0.2860646623578758
    },
    {
        "question": "46622÷1237=？",
        "answer": 1.5762212004077127
    },
    {
        "question": "25603107÷182737=？",
        "answer": 2.146466180407434
    },
    {
        "question": "77×4092=？",
        "answer": 5.498426350212604
    },
    {
        "question": "1743×55259=？",
        "answer": 7.983700408508229
    },
    {
        "question": "68975834÷4779=？",
        "answer": 4.159359929799812
    },
    {
        "question": "10450×1960=？",
        "answer": 7.311372361803548
    },
    {
        "question": "11933149÷1702553=？",
        "answer": 0.845654423095737
    },
    {
        "question": "83382802÷9544592=？",
        "answer": 0.9413191166278452
    },
    {
        "question": "2791053÷424489=？",
        "answer": 0.8179016428615983
    },
    {
        "question": "797968126÷10739700=？",
        "answer": 1.8709933941962031
    },
    {
        "question": "24162735÷7864=？",
        "answer": 3.487502586059688
    },
    {
        "question": "814448×409=？",
        "answer": 8.522586669170002
    },
    {
        "question": "1004÷407=？",
        "answer": 0.3921393035837805
    },
    {
        "question": "2×3057872=？",
        "answer": 6.786449297911918
    },
    {
        "question": "33×3274762=？",
        "answer": 8.033693682116338
    },
    {
        "question": "111683÷4829=？",
        "answer": 1.3641298659420158
    },
    {
        "question": "5648÷3940=？",
        "answer": 0.15639846621817322
    },
    {
        "question": "15735002÷12638887=？",
        "answer": 0.09515797146604232
    },
    {
        "question": "127758563÷50281=？",
        "answer": 3.4049861118622675
    },
    {
        "question": "96245291÷214652=？",
        "answer": 2.651644550611571
    },
    {
        "question": "222180290÷71332618=？",
        "answer": 0.4934173658083272
    },
    {
        "question": "7442960÷760=？",
        "answer": 3.9909320927293583
    },
    {
        "question": "1908247÷800=？",
        "answer": 3.377544601297656
    },
    {
        "question": "1×771334=？",
        "answer": 5.887242475258466
    },
    {
        "question": "10×768=？",
        "answer": 3.885361220031512
    },
    {
        "question": "5795143÷141239=？",
        "answer": 1.6131095230000934
    },
    {
        "question": "405814145÷23899=？",
        "answer": 4.229947451416977
    },
    {
        "question": "1038×7045=？",
        "answer": 6.864078350957814
    },
    {
        "question": "237×369=？",
        "answer": 4.941774712169164
    },
    {
        "question": "906376031÷1791640=？",
        "answer": 2.7040576622423065
    },
    {
        "question": "784×4164=？",
        "answer": 6.513826783522937
    },
    {
        "question": "63047845÷645=？",
        "answer": 4.9901105321722765
    },
    {
        "question": "33×8059=？",
        "answer": 5.42479509565004
    },
    {
        "question": "8042×367=？",
        "answer": 6.470030133018982
    },
    {
        "question": "204964570÷37659=？",
        "answer": 3.735810012226817
    },
    {
        "question": "3×238623=？",
        "answer": 5.854833556131427
    },
    {
        "question": "950×71840=？",
        "answer": 7.834089928948096
    },
    {
        "question": "2195779÷2271=？",
        "answer": 2.9853714930381128
    },
    {
        "question": "24571482÷13331930=？",
        "answer": 0.265538326521818
    },
    {
        "question": "750×76173=？",
        "answer": 7.756862323590427
    },
    {
        "question": "356555534÷215=？",
        "answer": 6.219688721485313
    },
    {
        "question": "389033×216=？",
        "answer": 7.924440193376475
    },
    {
        "question": "33673452÷34522=？",
        "answer": 2.989191691712072
    },
    {
        "question": "474646498÷96609008=？",
        "answer": 0.6913526582307916
    },
    {
        "question": "95×592=？",
        "answer": 4.750045312011768
    },
    {
        "question": "28751×34449=？",
        "answer": 8.995829574202475
    },
    {
        "question": "2×1285=？",
        "answer": 3.4099331233312946
    },
    {
        "question": "141965×2099=？",
        "answer": 8.474193725356642
    },
    {
        "question": "1338×16762=？",
        "answer": 7.35078194975129
    },
    {
        "question": "58843×632=？",
        "answer": 7.5704118845920005
    },
    {
        "question": "3323×8344=？",
        "answer": 7.442904636697185
    },
    {
        "question": "57261÷6657=？",
        "answer": 0.9345803712726733
    },
    {
        "question": "7×444=？",
        "answer": 3.4924810101288766
    },
    {
        "question": "3×150499425=？",
        "answer": 8.654656095381723
    },
    {
        "question": "129×5847088=？",
        "answer": 8.877529340416132
    },
    {
        "question": "3×911=？",
        "answer": 3.436639631692661
    },
    {
        "question": "44004099÷612=？",
        "answer": 4.856741710935327
    },
    {
        "question": "93012×1465=？",
        "answer": 8.134376607626685
    },
    {
        "question": "335×2832187=？",
        "answer": 8.977166732038667
    },
    {
        "question": "84529641÷33001919=？",
        "answer": 0.4084698304917138
    },
    {
        "question": "13405÷446=？",
        "answer": 1.4779319596067566
    },
    {
        "question": "727215÷463=？",
        "answer": 3.1960818373230797
    },
    {
        "question": "17×420102=？",
        "answer": 6.853803670488025
    },
    {
        "question": "4526×1816=？",
        "answer": 6.9148303938037765
    },
    {
        "question": "14323×37325=？",
        "answer": 8.728033808320683
    },
    {
        "question": "757879663÷87385=？",
        "answer": 3.938163362759988
    },
    {
        "question": "9750443÷303=？",
        "answer": 4.507581719307499
    },
    {
        "question": "174120×410=？",
        "answer": 7.8536325152050965
    },
    {
        "question": "279265215÷310180=？",
        "answer": 2.95440305213587
    },
    {
        "question": "154094×920=？",
        "answer": 8.151573556150792
    },
    {
        "question": "41×53073=？",
        "answer": 6.337657493936867
    },
    {
        "question": "186374009÷4373999=？",
        "answer": 1.6295066677967285
    },
    {
        "question": "5×128026264=？",
        "answer": 8.80626907664183
    },
    {
        "question": "1540904÷178123=？",
        "answer": 0.9370555815049894
    },
    {
        "question": "2203933÷11782=？",
        "answer": 2.271979369342127
    },
    {
        "question": "3×181176=？",
        "answer": 5.7352219218027525
    },
    {
        "question": "17×225=？",
        "answer": 3.5826314394896364
    },
    {
        "question": "932144360÷92168922=？",
        "answer": 1.0048986681436674
    },
    {
        "question": "2310×38115=？",
        "answer": 7.944707903998195
    },
    {
        "question": "6674×4033=？",
        "answer": 7.430014424326393
    },
    {
        "question": "1304510÷13795=？",
        "answer": 1.9757257078108958
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1090=？",
        "answer": 3.037426497940624
    },
    {
        "question": "3×61527180=？",
        "answer": 8.266188265070086
    },
    {
        "question": "6664×5641=？",
        "answer": 7.5750910881241245
    },
    {
        "question": "352×16325=？",
        "answer": 6.759395853425243
    },
    {
        "question": "331×768=？",
        "answer": 5.405189213807231
    },
    {
        "question": "48×110607=？",
        "answer": 6.725023850466988
    },
    {
        "question": "249036533÷34604=？",
        "answer": 3.85713675827442
    },
    {
        "question": "2045765÷16341=？",
        "answer": 2.0975771142099022
    },
    {
        "question": "192541×4161=？",
        "answer": 8.903720938872771
    },
    {
        "question": "856353527÷174313462=？",
        "answer": 0.6913221623643424
    },
    {
        "question": "16597131÷333=？",
        "answer": 4.697588788355777
    },
    {
        "question": "209×1604407=？",
        "answer": 8.525460834244113
    },
    {
        "question": "55366858÷28735=？",
        "answer": 3.2848386770723823
    },
    {
        "question": "25474÷1907=？",
        "answer": 1.1257464514280988
    },
    {
        "question": "17×9663612=？",
        "answer": 8.215588405813262
    },
    {
        "question": "990154490÷20202772=？",
        "answer": 1.690291998582859
    },
    {
        "question": "116008700÷152825=？",
        "answer": 2.880296155629851
    },
    {
        "question": "1×19435=？",
        "answer": 4.288584544967285
    },
    {
        "question": "575×27142=？",
        "answer": 7.193309690849066
    },
    {
        "question": "6027271÷7003=？",
        "answer": 2.93483659244009
    },
    {
        "question": "910798268÷1100=？",
        "answer": 5.918029510918875
    },
    {
        "question": "122880416÷61557=？",
        "answer": 3.3002052267574395
    },
    {
        "question": "188045143÷124975478=？",
        "answer": 0.17743731405691143
    },
    {
        "question": "75706÷61550=？",
        "answer": 0.08990224315255302
    },
    {
        "question": "182779÷57141=？",
        "answer": 0.5049784604201211
    },
    {
        "question": "135335÷6661=？",
        "answer": 1.3078706936219497
    },
    {
        "question": "8735÷2811=？",
        "answer": 0.492402063711509
    },
    {
        "question": "7×2783=？",
        "answer": 4.2896112463483
    },
    {
        "question": "1×63930224=？",
        "answer": 7.805706226126239
    },
    {
        "question": "1×103918600=？",
        "answer": 8.016693287253094
    },
    {
        "question": "276506÷441=？",
        "answer": 2.797265970182352
    },
    {
        "question": "251628÷9112=？",
        "answer": 1.441145254672379
    },
    {
        "question": "31×898=？",
        "answer": 4.444638030501577
    },
    {
        "question": "43990÷6801=？",
        "answer": 0.8107811871306831
    },
    {
        "question": "24702×19644=？",
        "answer": 8.685962042840696
    },
    {
        "question": "633537×1216=？",
        "answer": 8.886705558681182
    },
    {
        "question": "717×762=？",
        "answer": 5.737474127007401
    },
    {
        "question": "159×5327496=？",
        "answer": 8.92792025662906
    },
    {
        "question": "1×17859=？",
        "answer": 4.251857137271416
    },
    {
        "question": "554×487952=？",
        "answer": 8.431886867140118
    },
    {
        "question": "155735342÷131214=？",
        "answer": 3.0744070059630877
    },
    {
        "question": "559088373÷1801184=？",
        "answer": 2.491922380160335
    },
    {
        "question": "82747÷60282=？",
        "answer": 0.1375646047041181
    },
    {
        "question": "11981÷3056=？",
        "answer": 0.5933397182629206
    },
    {
        "question": "48345÷7077=？",
        "answer": 0.8345023689627579
    },
    {
        "question": "8321636÷36712=？",
        "answer": 2.3554006705375987
    },
    {
        "question": "65579÷4287=？",
        "answer": 1.184611306410498
    },
    {
        "question": "145003607÷3865320=？",
        "answer": 1.5741933516732796
    },
    {
        "question": "33705÷9263=？",
        "answer": 0.5609426674234322
    },
    {
        "question": "993×792769=？",
        "answer": 8.896095907893686
    },
    {
        "question": "49×4754=？",
        "answer": 5.367255257420675
    },
    {
        "question": "37628480÷17073=？",
        "answer": 3.3432068350488735
    },
    {
        "question": "3×651=？",
        "answer": 3.2907022432878543
    },
    {
        "question": "689×6799=？",
        "answer": 6.670664263081737
    },
    {
        "question": "17×65337=？",
        "answer": 6.04560811100106
    },
    {
        "question": "936298775÷68993=？",
        "answer": 4.132609425537446
    },
    {
        "question": "189×241=？",
        "answer": 4.658478846748112
    },
    {
        "question": "456574856÷281555=？",
        "answer": 3.209948746640986
    },
    {
        "question": "952×12318=？",
        "answer": 7.06917714813871
    },
    {
        "question": "395652093÷1113=？",
        "answer": 5.550818303153176
    },
    {
        "question": "1939×9330=？",
        "answer": 7.257459452825206
    },
    {
        "question": "2225850×436=？",
        "answer": 8.986982383154396
    },
    {
        "question": "5×5326=？",
        "answer": 4.425371166438941
    },
    {
        "question": "5×78680566=？",
        "answer": 8.59483747975455
    },
    {
        "question": "14×8652=？",
        "answer": 5.083244546445292
    },
    {
        "question": "14206÷6546=？",
        "answer": 0.3364958093640507
    },
    {
        "question": "44753÷29314=？",
        "answer": 0.1837470698747264
    },
    {
        "question": "28663729÷955042=？",
        "answer": 1.4773102181330648
    },
    {
        "question": "89×738=？",
        "answer": 4.817446368467954
    },
    {
        "question": "41104957÷70789=？",
        "answer": 2.763928420908699
    },
    {
        "question": "411770377÷56255=？",
        "answer": 3.864493970986891
    },
    {
        "question": "89×1804581=？",
        "answer": 8.205766387118317
    },
    {
        "question": "4×181237928=？",
        "answer": 8.860309079798085
    },
    {
        "question": "9189507÷1919907=？",
        "answer": 0.6800120208628203
    },
    {
        "question": "30×722114=？",
        "answer": 7.33572701968916
    },
    {
        "question": "1915×132809=？",
        "answer": 8.405396284947306
    },
    {
        "question": "27661685÷3058001=？",
        "answer": 0.9564410083508226
    },
    {
        "question": "199×1034708=？",
        "answer": 8.313670883322626
    },
    {
        "question": "334818÷1403=？",
        "answer": 2.377751126830913
    },
    {
        "question": "54781660÷8470783=？",
        "answer": 0.8107116317980657
    },
    {
        "question": "785×813691=？",
        "answer": 8.805329169162208
    },
    {
        "question": "716×2444=？",
        "answer": 6.243014223878372
    },
    {
        "question": "32072568÷14116=？",
        "answer": 3.356422084907782
    },
    {
        "question": "5×46615=？",
        "answer": 5.367495692892881
    },
    {
        "question": "12497÷1000=？",
        "answer": 1.096805769822717
    },
    {
        "question": "6662×239=？",
        "answer": 6.202002529303296
    },
    {
        "question": "2631245÷189599=？",
        "answer": 1.1423252455029895
    },
    {
        "question": "1460×12628=？",
        "answer": 7.2656874290046165
    },
    {
        "question": "38954457÷131201=？",
        "answer": 2.4726200097438915
    },
    {
        "question": "4584424÷2016861=？",
        "answer": 0.35660880933435946
    },
    {
        "question": "1782723÷339651=？",
        "answer": 0.720050970041101
    },
    {
        "question": "12474÷321=？",
        "answer": 1.5895007073102407
    },
    {
        "question": "13586×311=？",
        "answer": 6.6258519992815454
    },
    {
        "question": "14843254÷2122433=？",
        "answer": 0.8446951297050576
    },
    {
        "question": "14303095÷1903=？",
        "answer": 3.8759912349111754
    },
    {
        "question": "8534×3175=？",
        "answer": 7.432896368151288
    },
    {
        "question": "39880074÷961817=？",
        "answer": 1.6176635065927962
    },
    {
        "question": "989038÷510=？",
        "answer": 3.2876428019231785
    },
    {
        "question": "347902÷2629=？",
        "answer": 2.12166633929678
    },
    {
        "question": "839÷469=？",
        "answer": 0.252589118113617
    },
    {
        "question": "186398×1524=？",
        "answer": 8.453426215184507
    },
    {
        "question": "1×10077=？",
        "answer": 4.003331258561326
    },
    {
        "question": "9503594÷7849=？",
        "answer": 3.0830735455944396
    },
    {
        "question": "165×6792=？",
        "answer": 6.049481621449803
    },
    {
        "question": "545148÷84572=？",
        "answer": 0.8092878219953041
    },
    {
        "question": "9×261=？",
        "answer": 3.370883016777606
    },
    {
        "question": "195×4213066=？",
        "answer": 8.914632874004981
    },
    {
        "question": "2337497÷409381=？",
        "answer": 0.7566233796395915
    },
    {
        "question": "1×90876234=？",
        "answer": 7.958450321151848
    },
    {
        "question": "70805798÷13198=？",
        "answer": 3.7295606977358013
    },
    {
        "question": "3×6877=？",
        "answer": 4.314520279061685
    },
    {
        "question": "1523×408=？",
        "answer": 5.793360066425922
    },
    {
        "question": "40880985÷1162=？",
        "answer": 4.546315223233575
    },
    {
        "question": "21×72797=？",
        "answer": 6.184332776927567
    },
    {
        "question": "968×151430=？",
        "answer": 8.166087279657335
    },
    {
        "question": "32371÷989=？",
        "answer": 1.5149598241715894
    },
    {
        "question": "3×60397222=？",
        "answer": 8.258138218211384
    },
    {
        "question": "122×338084=？",
        "answer": 7.6153844487160764
    },
    {
        "question": "21×7810584=？",
        "answer": 8.214902802170153
    },
    {
        "question": "1072948×296=？",
        "answer": 8.5018703856248
    },
    {
        "question": "1600695÷469=？",
        "answer": 3.5331357456465815
    },
    {
        "question": "845253÷8263=？",
        "answer": 2.0098489680964864
    },
    {
        "question": "122400612÷80502=？",
        "answer": 3.1819769191176728
    },
    {
        "question": "2479591÷4906=？",
        "answer": 2.7036525074833784
    },
    {
        "question": "313×8560=？",
        "answer": 6.428018102223602
    },
    {
        "question": "1187×531=？",
        "answer": 5.7995452400360605
    },
    {
        "question": "91×2388=？",
        "answer": 5.337075714778425
    },
    {
        "question": "14101996÷585490=？",
        "answer": 1.3817611053068892
    },
    {
        "question": "1356133÷605=？",
        "answer": 3.3505469095198706
    },
    {
        "question": "592618÷214=？",
        "answer": 3.442361065124495
    },
    {
        "question": "324863954÷295=？",
        "answer": 6.041879509933281
    },
    {
        "question": "15490313÷80263=？",
        "answer": 2.2855448048995273
    },
    {
        "question": "81×140006=？",
        "answer": 7.05463166677871
    },
    {
        "question": "23156913÷12252255=？",
        "answer": 0.276464637037687
    },
    {
        "question": "325594037÷3179600=？",
        "answer": 2.0103039542147205
    },
    {
        "question": "206×1353110=？",
        "answer": 8.445200324026013
    },
    {
        "question": "23705÷12489=？",
        "answer": 0.27831229404853564
    },
    {
        "question": "230627044÷2332663=？",
        "answer": 1.9950582318138688
    },
    {
        "question": "813×986=？",
        "answer": 5.903967460535279
    },
    {
        "question": "11×715=？",
        "answer": 3.8956987269593055
    },
    {
        "question": "235421125÷95551666=？",
        "answer": 0.391607167082851
    },
    {
        "question": "789772800÷5536868=？",
        "answer": 2.154238002461312
    },
    {
        "question": "3×1009780=？",
        "answer": 6.481348019399931
    },
    {
        "question": "249690571÷10210814=？",
        "answer": 1.3883417773476123
    },
    {
        "question": "7×950749=？",
        "answer": 6.823163917306175
    },
    {
        "question": "22×7102=？",
        "answer": 5.193803348787803
    },
    {
        "question": "104624911÷2918396=？",
        "answer": 1.554490880167669
    },
    {
        "question": "3051206÷2384922=？",
        "answer": 0.10699734991256052
    },
    {
        "question": "306294÷727=？",
        "answer": 2.6246040786265636
    },
    {
        "question": "6858÷6541=？",
        "answer": 0.02055333164696005
    },
    {
        "question": "9×3377345=？",
        "answer": 7.482817936063263
    },
    {
        "question": "253405188÷1258092=？",
        "answer": 2.304103101257698
    },
    {
        "question": "8×46479=？",
        "answer": 5.5703467625886365
    },
    {
        "question": "1×67585=？",
        "answer": 4.829850318129671
    },
    {
        "question": "1252038÷12862=？",
        "answer": 1.9883090048895384
    },
    {
        "question": "136×2117=？",
        "answer": 5.459259766389629
    },
    {
        "question": "10×707=？",
        "answer": 3.8494194137968996
    },
    {
        "question": "61359×14400=？",
        "answer": 8.946240765167516
    },
    {
        "question": "463246÷10885=？",
        "answer": 1.6289832446182957
    },
    {
        "question": "153402959÷2361518=？",
        "answer": 1.8126424766176146
    },
    {
        "question": "549295÷163036=？",
        "answer": 0.5275221342273634
    },
    {
        "question": "267010429÷207=？",
        "answer": 6.110557879086301
    },
    {
        "question": "93×215011=？",
        "answer": 7.300943627618827
    },
    {
        "question": "47864475÷166017=？",
        "answer": 2.4598607380261015
    },
    {
        "question": "319470÷105234=？",
        "answer": 0.48227400328011155
    },
    {
        "question": "754769889÷4391420=？",
        "answer": 2.2352095905044562
    },
    {
        "question": "197×923=？",
        "answer": 5.259667927187505
    },
    {
        "question": "1010×7630=？",
        "answer": 6.886845911737523
    },
    {
        "question": "10×2576=？",
        "answer": 4.410945858687774
    },
    {
        "question": "239×324092=？",
        "answer": 7.889066211836146
    },
    {
        "question": "1×29601122=？",
        "answer": 7.4713081728553465
    },
    {
        "question": "20×2864513=？",
        "answer": 7.758080793209799
    },
    {
        "question": "46686×4031=？",
        "answer": 8.274599463852006
    },
    {
        "question": "60×1710=？",
        "answer": 5.011147360775797
    },
    {
        "question": "70×14805=？",
        "answer": 6.015506451739575
    },
    {
        "question": "978×4104=？",
        "answer": 6.6035462068913615
    },
    {
        "question": "319983689÷5616=？",
        "answer": 4.755700741829916
    },
    {
        "question": "2×1499259=？",
        "answer": 6.476906660236399
    },
    {
        "question": "12945978÷12131206=？",
        "answer": 0.028230887110685665
    },
    {
        "question": "192547033÷15874006=？",
        "answer": 1.0838502907474503
    },
    {
        "question": "16×4752=？",
        "answer": 4.880996414629062
    },
    {
        "question": "253470863÷56200259=？",
        "answer": 0.654189726461149
    },
    {
        "question": "1482÷768=？",
        "answer": 0.28548698361179736
    },
    {
        "question": "17×2791960=？",
        "answer": 7.676358113300846
    },
    {
        "question": "1×415=？",
        "answer": 2.6180480967120925
    },
    {
        "question": "552516÷452=？",
        "answer": 3.087206424217436
    },
    {
        "question": "4044×12595=？",
        "answer": 7.707009318753095
    },
    {
        "question": "7647×4554=？",
        "answer": 7.541884116468054
    },
    {
        "question": "5843962÷247440=？",
        "answer": 1.3732374763034187
    },
    {
        "question": "12890930÷133049=？",
        "answer": 1.9862726353849074
    },
    {
        "question": "4003×480=？",
        "answer": 6.283626827480692
    },
    {
        "question": "27216÷5318=？",
        "answer": 0.7090759632729455
    },
    {
        "question": "164822940÷11239676=？",
        "answer": 1.1662638642804994
    },
    {
        "question": "2874086÷67614=？",
        "answer": 1.6284631299201837
    },
    {
        "question": "252280÷7050=？",
        "answer": 1.5536937053298834
    },
    {
        "question": "82991476÷514881=？",
        "answer": 2.207326622660698
    },
    {
        "question": "4413÷1504=？",
        "answer": 0.46748609119156914
    },
    {
        "question": "70716499÷35603778=？",
        "answer": 0.2980246672657788
    },
    {
        "question": "50×15237879=？",
        "answer": 8.881894524968144
    },
    {
        "question": "36×26240303=？",
        "answer": 8.97527134635156
    },
    {
        "question": "251856×1098=？",
        "answer": 8.441754641688
    },
    {
        "question": "320978447÷5659=？",
        "answer": 4.753736177524918
    },
    {
        "question": "4744124÷339=？",
        "answer": 4.14595633371551
    },
    {
        "question": "586857260÷2366=？",
        "answer": 5.3945177413088095
    },
    {
        "question": "5698×235=？",
        "answer": 6.126790307175194
    },
    {
        "question": "1647×848=？",
        "answer": 6.145089451426468
    },
    {
        "question": "488319914÷725=？",
        "answer": 5.828366428882418
    },
    {
        "question": "44309÷991=？",
        "answer": 1.6504182941610372
    },
    {
        "question": "47517246÷55984=？",
        "answer": 2.9287873367656467
    },
    {
        "question": "1×782563=？",
        "answer": 5.893519310373123
    },
    {
        "question": "16×556=？",
        "answer": 3.949194774237982
    },
    {
        "question": "534839687÷16740=？",
        "answer": 4.504468172317909
    },
    {
        "question": "38×2973=？",
        "answer": 5.052978505821748
    },
    {
        "question": "295×675=？",
        "answer": 5.299125788809188
    },
    {
        "question": "7619453÷113255=？",
        "answer": 1.8278664100771589
    },
    {
        "question": "8895094÷5934605=？",
        "answer": 0.17575872375786508
    },
    {
        "question": "405×411=？",
        "answer": 5.2212968450907375
    },
    {
        "question": "27116510÷26856=？",
        "answer": 3.0041924651676397
    },
    {
        "question": "233×6077=？",
        "answer": 6.151045157373336
    },
    {
        "question": "49948550÷19908726=？",
        "answer": 0.3994794157053672
    },
    {
        "question": "2×2129=？",
        "answer": 3.629205657102304
    },
    {
        "question": "33×2846=？",
        "answer": 4.972748835626153
    },
    {
        "question": "14106927÷392=？",
        "answer": 4.55614635195763
    },
    {
        "question": "4×6823008=？",
        "answer": 7.436035871819919
    },
    {
        "question": "129763198÷241497=？",
        "answer": 2.7302398000480603
    },
    {
        "question": "290298÷43455=？",
        "answer": 0.8248042895227788
    },
    {
        "question": "5×1037=？",
        "answer": 3.7147487607250596
    },
    {
        "question": "96×4942=？",
        "answer": 5.676173974105629
    },
    {
        "question": "2561÷2259=？",
        "answer": 0.054493347548066694
    },
    {
        "question": "33053×1845=？",
        "answer": 7.7852072541145265
    },
    {
        "question": "71818÷23638=？",
        "answer": 0.4826225783381927
    },
    {
        "question": "208453896÷36980=？",
        "answer": 3.7510431096719734
    },
    {
        "question": "30128÷2221=？",
        "answer": 1.1324217441241156
    },
    {
        "question": "13571110÷1396=？",
        "answer": 3.9877299523762733
    },
    {
        "question": "1×399316559=？",
        "answer": 8.601317320044611
    },
    {
        "question": "68633893÷3432=？",
        "answer": 4.300991354137253
    },
    {
        "question": "2×21243=？",
        "answer": 4.628245844770344
    },
    {
        "question": "145190912÷10021219=？",
        "answer": 1.1610188800798211
    },
    {
        "question": "27×142545=？",
        "answer": 6.5853157524793655
    },
    {
        "question": "587×484042=？",
        "answer": 8.453521147968194
    },
    {
        "question": "18614386÷1339601=？",
        "answer": 1.1428732524178673
    },
    {
        "question": "19797492÷1515=？",
        "answer": 4.116197543304532
    },
    {
        "question": "154269÷79728=？",
        "answer": 0.2866677945281901
    },
    {
        "question": "43×16987=？",
        "answer": 5.863585142365806
    },
    {
        "question": "214288297÷1964=？",
        "answer": 5.037856969965575
    },
    {
        "question": "1×42269=？",
        "answer": 4.6260219734117225
    },
    {
        "question": "1496234÷3588=？",
        "answer": 2.6201470849328965
    },
    {
        "question": "617466164÷178023365=？",
        "answer": 0.540136158233906
    },
    {
        "question": "2062×51992=？",
        "answer": 8.030225184906513
    },
    {
        "question": "6700467÷1616=？",
        "answer": 3.6176637161809313
    },
    {
        "question": "2×853=？",
        "answer": 3.231979026831504
    },
    {
        "question": "10×115719=？",
        "answer": 6.063404671982872
    },
    {
        "question": "10×64770=？",
        "answer": 5.811373897053893
    },
    {
        "question": "51483÷2037=？",
        "answer": 1.4026728170310268
    },
    {
        "question": "143974084÷2076883=？",
        "answer": 1.8408722926217067
    },
    {
        "question": "829565971÷173510178=？",
        "answer": 0.679525973559489
    },
    {
        "question": "14060÷1506=？",
        "answer": 0.9701603488191234
    },
    {
        "question": "318498851÷40113265=？",
        "answer": 0.8998198573240883
    },
    {
        "question": "643865÷810=？",
        "answer": 2.900309798945269
    },
    {
        "question": "525844777÷47934045=？",
        "answer": 1.0402134853542602
    },
    {
        "question": "421288116÷2888446=？",
        "answer": 2.163914955664152
    },
    {
        "question": "39732173÷2458688=？",
        "answer": 1.2084388961974648
    },
    {
        "question": "215875×501=？",
        "answer": 8.03404007644276
    },
    {
        "question": "208444×476=？",
        "answer": 7.996596351322199
    },
    {
        "question": "45×800642=？",
        "answer": 7.556650882319606
    },
    {
        "question": "122×7740101=？",
        "answer": 8.975106458470881
    },
    {
        "question": "21801÷276=？",
        "answer": 1.8975673328477047
    },
    {
        "question": "35×300=？",
        "answer": 4.021189299069938
    },
    {
        "question": "464807939÷6593399=？",
        "answer": 1.8481641793707149
    },
    {
        "question": "70661÷1409=？",
        "answer": 1.700268786202445
    },
    {
        "question": "5×31458=？",
        "answer": 5.196701112433386
    },
    {
        "question": "484×68219=？",
        "answer": 7.51875071058174
    },
    {
        "question": "942206÷1636=？",
        "answer": 2.7603625661778155
    },
    {
        "question": "56×1634976=？",
        "answer": 7.961699408990844
    },
    {
        "question": "11×28678024=？",
        "answer": 8.498941909020772
    },
    {
        "question": "183348313÷669800=？",
        "answer": 2.437331775138797
    },
    {
        "question": "1482×28086=？",
        "answer": 7.619338095154395
    },
    {
        "question": "7535961÷300=？",
        "answer": 4.400017387516244
    },
    {
        "question": "3×1450182=？",
        "answer": 6.638543764979175
    },
    {
        "question": "2×69247744=？",
        "answer": 8.141435624890564
    },
    {
        "question": "4383151÷7975=？",
        "answer": 2.7400557406717545
    },
    {
        "question": "3×1791734=？",
        "answer": 6.730394789673582
    },
    {
        "question": "155×2470=？",
        "answer": 5.583028651429958
    },
    {
        "question": "532361690÷1512646=？",
        "answer": 2.546469491793135
    },
    {
        "question": "2078×197593=？",
        "answer": 8.613417098274278
    },
    {
        "question": "61382÷351=？",
        "answer": 2.2427339184089483
    },
    {
        "question": "2×340784048=？",
        "answer": 8.833509253038812
    },
    {
        "question": "220×255522=？",
        "answer": 7.749850978902637
    },
    {
        "question": "913÷295=？",
        "answer": 0.4906487615561359
    },
    {
        "question": "2×75047=？",
        "answer": 5.1763633316904825
    },
    {
        "question": "1583693÷47056=？",
        "answer": 1.5270559899591598
    },
    {
        "question": "46×1950=？",
        "answer": 4.952792443044092
    },
    {
        "question": "212483114÷255114=？",
        "answer": 2.9205901302151185
    },
    {
        "question": "14318516÷445=？",
        "answer": 4.507537998163512
    },
    {
        "question": "926801421÷23117650=？",
        "answer": 1.6030430067409973
    },
    {
        "question": "2378×22343=？",
        "answer": 7.725353335802306
    },
    {
        "question": "3855÷224=？",
        "answer": 1.235776364052813
    },
    {
        "question": "3487543÷49324=？",
        "answer": 1.8494612819094813
    },
    {
        "question": "1143×773=？",
        "answer": 5.9462257243136065
    },
    {
        "question": "138386303÷54458010=？",
        "answer": 0.4050313399330663
    },
    {
        "question": "527719510÷4278=？",
        "answer": 5.091162370278005
    },
    {
        "question": "92×1744=？",
        "answer": 5.2053343079421035
    },
    {
        "question": "48952×473=？",
        "answer": 7.364631580926404
    },
    {
        "question": "6070364÷46820=？",
        "answer": 2.1127833242931877
    },
    {
        "question": "3×9692=？",
        "answer": 4.463534660185131
    },
    {
        "question": "25423÷317=？",
        "answer": 1.9041675352421874
    },
    {
        "question": "3145÷226=？",
        "answer": 1.1435122106338869
    },
    {
        "question": "29908÷8032=？",
        "answer": 0.5709636721736978
    },
    {
        "question": "3079×529=？",
        "answer": 6.211865360938384
    },
    {
        "question": "798789341÷355768714=？",
        "answer": 0.3512645070987963
    },
    {
        "question": "133014374÷116184258=？",
        "answer": 0.05875128613618562
    },
    {
        "question": "1497×716=？",
        "answer": 6.030134822650908
    },
    {
        "question": "18688405÷176187=？",
        "answer": 2.0255983764772933
    },
    {
        "question": "46332×351=？",
        "answer": 7.211188164137498
    },
    {
        "question": "25961291÷574=？",
        "answer": 4.655414392811843
    },
    {
        "question": "103127÷39155=？",
        "answer": 0.42058515585368744
    },
    {
        "question": "645925614÷154071257=？",
        "answer": 0.6224608809103371
    },
    {
        "question": "125252252÷230081=？",
        "answer": 2.7359047868221915
    },
    {
        "question": "44203160÷5209817=？",
        "answer": 0.928630848804867
    },
    {
        "question": "5116×264=？",
        "answer": 6.130534462676447
    },
    {
        "question": "4959÷1478=？",
        "answer": 0.525719674232303
    },
    {
        "question": "4086×67816=？",
        "answer": 8.442630532445682
    },
    {
        "question": "1×22998=？",
        "answer": 4.361690069637996
    },
    {
        "question": "11713÷4907=？",
        "answer": 0.3778520853049842
    },
    {
        "question": "10996×333=？",
        "answer": 6.5636789646777505
    },
    {
        "question": "576×704881=？",
        "answer": 8.608538287782595
    },
    {
        "question": "57511÷2685=？",
        "answer": 1.3308066291306802
    },
    {
        "question": "1×105267=？",
        "answer": 5.022292246170454
    },
    {
        "question": "45×3298=？",
        "answer": 5.171463165083844
    },
    {
        "question": "22×13955072=？",
        "answer": 8.487154762357857
    },
    {
        "question": "25031796÷21701144=？",
        "answer": 0.06200938204126512
    },
    {
        "question": "111993÷15302=？",
        "answer": 0.8644426807888551
    },
    {
        "question": "56426260÷197955=？",
        "answer": 2.4549147899140755
    },
    {
        "question": "440385411÷1315=？",
        "answer": 5.524907170491324
    },
    {
        "question": "38842×15122=？",
        "answer": 8.768910817645002
    },
    {
        "question": "720073577÷317474=？",
        "answer": 3.355668710938323
    },
    {
        "question": "15304×5265=？",
        "answer": 7.906203332540745
    },
    {
        "question": "679030÷1074=？",
        "answer": 2.800884680761798
    },
    {
        "question": "110×339758=？",
        "answer": 7.572562376655328
    },
    {
        "question": "1×112810=？",
        "answer": 5.052347599224664
    },
    {
        "question": "11673476÷24661=？",
        "answer": 2.675189511567914
    },
    {
        "question": "7219×4188=？",
        "answer": 7.480483714820145
    },
    {
        "question": "2×77017445=？",
        "answer": 8.187619102773253
    },
    {
        "question": "641349380÷73022=？",
        "answer": 3.9436409555664302
    },
    {
        "question": "8×307360=？",
        "answer": 6.390737334509562
    },
    {
        "question": "96990÷507=？",
        "answer": 2.2817189999978824
    },
    {
        "question": "466355÷57341=？",
        "answer": 0.9102513748212419
    },
    {
        "question": "10×1200=？",
        "answer": 4.079181246047625
    },
    {
        "question": "67685736÷60934=？",
        "answer": 3.0456374674657614
    },
    {
        "question": "74043067÷84197=？",
        "answer": 2.944187782180701
    },
    {
        "question": "38094674÷28336=？",
        "answer": 3.128525717548871
    },
    {
        "question": "18594×26682=？",
        "answer": 8.695591206455505
    },
    {
        "question": "6312619÷376261=？",
        "answer": 1.2247203727476945
    },
    {
        "question": "255311875÷1046=？",
        "answer": 5.387539330535566
    },
    {
        "question": "419471424÷946=？",
        "answer": 5.646811243967152
    },
    {
        "question": "365636÷4440=？",
        "answer": 1.9156659790687356
    },
    {
        "question": "193659374÷3813=？",
        "answer": 4.705771718397734
    },
    {
        "question": "415307948÷1888130=？",
        "answer": 2.342338349862245
    },
    {
        "question": "1×61829=？",
        "answer": 4.7911922224329855
    },
    {
        "question": "12284×2419=？",
        "answer": 7.472975676132911
    },
    {
        "question": "76543370÷116741=？",
        "answer": 2.816684169990755
    },
    {
        "question": "1013582÷86863=？",
        "answer": 1.0670240648184348
    },
    {
        "question": "306×1247=？",
        "answer": 5.581587879960122
    },
    {
        "question": "2191958÷300791=？",
        "answer": 0.862567390854829
    },
    {
        "question": "3986×17428=？",
        "answer": 7.841784845628185
    },
    {
        "question": "9041791÷360322=？",
        "answer": 1.3995636847124224
    },
    {
        "question": "1×495341153=？",
        "answer": 8.694904410716894
    },
    {
        "question": "4054×48230=？",
        "answer": 8.291201006278872
    },
    {
        "question": "26122×2409=？",
        "answer": 7.7988432251171425
    },
    {
        "question": "93952×326=？",
        "answer": 7.486123629631878
    },
    {
        "question": "1×66409084=？",
        "answer": 7.822227489928816
    },
    {
        "question": "9×76937=？",
        "answer": 5.84037775732061
    },
    {
        "question": "298660×275=？",
        "answer": 7.914509754591275
    },
    {
        "question": "1×9112=？",
        "answer": 3.959613711071044
    },
    {
        "question": "90×679=？",
        "answer": 4.786112283719826
    },
    {
        "question": "343403÷36637=？",
        "answer": 0.9718841803837861
    },
    {
        "question": "2686530÷100478=？",
        "answer": 1.4271207127100387
    },
    {
        "question": "295497627÷40701=？",
        "answer": 3.860948917899948
    },
    {
        "question": "22×136430=？",
        "answer": 6.4773325599540845
    },
    {
        "question": "651×986=？",
        "answer": 5.807457903509403
    },
    {
        "question": "25710900÷1111=？",
        "answer": 4.364403220276579
    },
    {
        "question": "4308×3562=？",
        "answer": 7.185969609753169
    },
    {
        "question": "8774988÷1536=？",
        "answer": 3.7568553155349784
    },
    {
        "question": "176×316=？",
        "answer": 4.745199750432554
    },
    {
        "question": "97481522÷48475=？",
        "answer": 3.3034044835481695
    },
    {
        "question": "750÷437=？",
        "answer": 0.23457982642127823
    },
    {
        "question": "32511230÷51011=？",
        "answer": 2.8043695631488674
    },
    {
        "question": "653611÷7316=？",
        "answer": 1.9510456557761322
    },
    {
        "question": "399584052÷576747=？",
        "answer": 2.840622802376169
    },
    {
        "question": "959804÷4606=？",
        "answer": 2.31885862190183
    },
    {
        "question": "89×10134=？",
        "answer": 5.955170906599565
    },
    {
        "question": "59059×733=？",
        "answer": 7.63639006376259
    },
    {
        "question": "4×61027798=？",
        "answer": 8.387587691389392
    },
    {
        "question": "117236÷106446=？",
        "answer": 0.04193164595715257
    },
    {
        "question": "33670885÷7194=？",
        "answer": 3.6702840979803018
    },
    {
        "question": "5×213=？",
        "answer": 3.0273496077747564
    },
    {
        "question": "1752×28290=？",
        "answer": 7.6951670492890525
    },
    {
        "question": "66149200÷31763774=？",
        "answer": 0.3185924989086277
    },
    {
        "question": "26593÷2271=？",
        "answer": 1.068550199349242
    },
    {
        "question": "84×10885208=？",
        "answer": 8.961116018234508
    },
    {
        "question": "5×13673=？",
        "answer": 4.8348338181358885
    },
    {
        "question": "2×267351=？",
        "answer": 5.728111808538978
    },
    {
        "question": "79×34451=？",
        "answer": 6.434828923867287
    },
    {
        "question": "9609693÷1508544=？",
        "answer": 0.8041515316748735
    },
    {
        "question": "765577×254=？",
        "answer": 8.288822594205957
    },
    {
        "question": "1421×129354=？",
        "answer": 8.264373940829804
    },
    {
        "question": "147453105÷16220=？",
        "answer": 3.9586030722834042
    },
    {
        "question": "20351906÷677=？",
        "answer": 4.478016419397976
    },
    {
        "question": "9110×46557=？",
        "answer": 8.627503364821406
    },
    {
        "question": "9×100513=？",
        "answer": 5.956464744958451
    },
    {
        "question": "7×512993=？",
        "answer": 6.555209479040079
    },
    {
        "question": "37×7360=？",
        "answer": 5.435079538404493
    },
    {
        "question": "15×364=？",
        "answer": 3.7371926427047373
    },
    {
        "question": "8×20912=？",
        "answer": 5.223485557228413
    },
    {
        "question": "678134295÷1378=？",
        "answer": 5.692066490752657
    },
    {
        "question": "1142911÷9974=？",
        "answer": 2.059143048740584
    },
    {
        "question": "649709031÷3811=？",
        "answer": 5.231679954758181
    },
    {
        "question": "2679÷220=？",
        "answer": 1.0855500327860026
    },
    {
        "question": "10248×202=？",
        "answer": 6.315990486183254
    },
    {
        "question": "1×712892=？",
        "answer": 5.853023741132755
    },
    {
        "question": "10×33494131=？",
        "answer": 8.52496871457075
    },
    {
        "question": "1721684÷445=？",
        "answer": 3.5875934325072967
    },
    {
        "question": "1×108876324=？",
        "answer": 8.036933449323621
    },
    {
        "question": "13374×200=？",
        "answer": 6.427291314527863
    },
    {
        "question": "11×17999=？",
        "answer": 5.296641062120082
    },
    {
        "question": "30×12328=？",
        "answer": 5.568013880430025
    },
    {
        "question": "38631÷338=？",
        "answer": 2.058019250136407
    },
    {
        "question": "81962÷619=？",
        "answer": 2.1219218982976957
    },
    {
        "question": "3761360÷245203=？",
        "answer": 1.1858191223957202
    },
    {
        "question": "762904372÷387448=？",
        "answer": 3.294256680313464
    },
    {
        "question": "2214÷389=？",
        "answer": 0.7552280152169962
    },
    {
        "question": "2128697÷1623=？",
        "answer": 3.1177953282758017
    },
    {
        "question": "2484×387647=？",
        "answer": 8.983588018818228
    },
    {
        "question": "278×249232=？",
        "answer": 7.8406485984766645
    },
    {
        "question": "183473461÷1925295=？",
        "answer": 1.979075970501843
    },
    {
        "question": "19×3943417=？",
        "answer": 7.874626305295463
    },
    {
        "question": "8953356÷112254=？",
        "answer": 1.901784027719088
    },
    {
        "question": "155019098÷32031097=？",
        "answer": 0.6848133929356831
    },
    {
        "question": "70306770÷63578642=？",
        "answer": 0.04368589882478276
    },
    {
        "question": "41×1951=？",
        "answer": 4.903041126114253
    },
    {
        "question": "234838×511=？",
        "answer": 8.079189273183115
    },
    {
        "question": "9×1260054=？",
        "answer": 7.05463166677871
    },
    {
        "question": "686×540004=？",
        "answer": 8.568721092513968
    },
    {
        "question": "328×17280=？",
        "answer": 6.753417581854554
    },
    {
        "question": "160398274÷1068665=？",
        "answer": 2.1763581046716753
    },
    {
        "question": "740891334÷425624=？",
        "answer": 3.240728406103443
    },
    {
        "question": "1106713÷359=？",
        "answer": 3.488940562836571
    },
    {
        "question": "463531÷1276=？",
        "answer": 2.560228109788438
    },
    {
        "question": "135223÷526=？",
        "answer": 2.4100648226260155
    },
    {
        "question": "2090372÷4332=？",
        "answer": 2.6835351315410847
    },
    {
        "question": "61851×266=？",
        "answer": 7.216228362277226
    },
    {
        "question": "16×11430=？",
        "answer": 5.262166213051207
    },
    {
        "question": "37×46492=？",
        "answer": 6.235579953198695
    },
    {
        "question": "25067×4036=？",
        "answer": 8.005053518591033
    },
    {
        "question": "4×6569249=？",
        "answer": 7.419575714951927
    },
    {
        "question": "17247×2695=？",
        "answer": 7.667272332888395
    },
    {
        "question": "1×52607160=？",
        "answer": 7.7210448570220125
    },
    {
        "question": "557×10890=？",
        "answer": 6.7828830749295035
    },
    {
        "question": "235013110÷1509428=？",
        "answer": 2.192279687759295
    },
    {
        "question": "171727104÷66853=？",
        "answer": 3.4097179452400153
    },
    {
        "question": "5176×2713=？",
        "answer": 7.14744406142224
    },
    {
        "question": "41583×5217=？",
        "answer": 8.336336654965695
    },
    {
        "question": "103900÷63373=？",
        "answer": 0.21471128097783063
    },
    {
        "question": "38×6117230=？",
        "answer": 8.366338406336942
    },
    {
        "question": "247÷228=？",
        "answer": 0.03476210625921191
    },
    {
        "question": "23975869÷3695=？",
        "answer": 3.8121599143033174
    },
    {
        "question": "58966162÷8695=？",
        "answer": 3.831333274922786
    },
    {
        "question": "950967÷90544=？",
        "answer": 1.021305769929162
    },
    {
        "question": "15766564÷72388=？",
        "answer": 2.3380704803246
    },
    {
        "question": "34046668÷1914183=？",
        "answer": 1.2500911608981757
    },
    {
        "question": "113202692÷498=？",
        "answer": 5.356627411891512
    },
    {
        "question": "59105631÷415066=？",
        "answer": 2.1535116983951075
    },
    {
        "question": "60741÷1808=？",
        "answer": 1.5262835114413693
    },
    {
        "question": "1310×1732=？",
        "answer": 6.3558191833370925
    },
    {
        "question": "8399÷226=？",
        "answer": 1.5701191421127167
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1470=？",
        "answer": 3.167317334748176
    },
    {
        "question": "3×891=？",
        "answer": 3.426998958756537
    },
    {
        "question": "7388658÷96314=？",
        "answer": 1.88487614492211
    },
    {
        "question": "14021393÷105421=？",
        "answer": 2.123864030625567
    },
    {
        "question": "12×7348935=？",
        "answer": 7.945405652188169
    },
    {
        "question": "940435505÷102219=？",
        "answer": 3.9637973890498803
    },
    {
        "question": "10484÷566=？",
        "answer": 1.2677105810862914
    },
    {
        "question": "213160÷1314=？",
        "answer": 2.2101103463451124
    },
    {
        "question": "37239414÷1253=？",
        "answer": 4.473051767304178
    },
    {
        "question": "30×595893=？",
        "answer": 7.252289538484391
    },
    {
        "question": "174994351÷678569=？",
        "answer": 2.4114300141434115
    },
    {
        "question": "866226÷15946=？",
        "answer": 1.734979455294609
    },
    {
        "question": "1011×6863=？",
        "answer": 6.841265154481673
    },
    {
        "question": "1207653÷8362=？",
        "answer": 2.159632001340746
    },
    {
        "question": "2×478640=？",
        "answer": 5.981038985497971
    },
    {
        "question": "687693÷13349=？",
        "answer": 1.7119458706378083
    },
    {
        "question": "5×1085=？",
        "answer": 3.734399742520567
    },
    {
        "question": "28×11831=？",
        "answer": 5.520179485701958
    },
    {
        "question": "11×57709757=？",
        "answer": 8.802641930775478
    },
    {
        "question": "5×3410=？",
        "answer": 4.231724383328516
    },
    {
        "question": "14×14124914=？",
        "answer": 8.296113847961633
    },
    {
        "question": "1974×18961=？",
        "answer": 7.5732083865587345
    },
    {
        "question": "46365÷1565=？",
        "answer": 1.4716759222365188
    },
    {
        "question": "162755227÷2161=？",
        "answer": 4.876880178257475
    },
    {
        "question": "3021×4168=？",
        "answer": 7.100078435564749
    },
    {
        "question": "3144234÷92748=？",
        "answer": 1.5302103062632841
    },
    {
        "question": "23×8419040=？",
        "answer": 8.28699040893387
    },
    {
        "question": "54979÷2770=？",
        "answer": 1.2977170672354434
    },
    {
        "question": "52151816÷28275=？",
        "answer": 3.2658668221765144
    },
    {
        "question": "1958419÷4796=？",
        "answer": 2.6110264394552862
    },
    {
        "question": "376514827÷77645=？",
        "answer": 3.685668588921747
    },
    {
        "question": "5653÷1871=？",
        "answer": 0.4802051979601088
    },
    {
        "question": "4069231÷13172=？",
        "answer": 2.489860622317655
    },
    {
        "question": "144500÷202=？",
        "answer": 2.854516477645943
    },
    {
        "question": "496×738829=？",
        "answer": 8.564025610216706
    },
    {
        "question": "9062627÷60850=？",
        "answer": 2.1729935230833375
    },
    {
        "question": "156×81920=？",
        "answer": 7.1065145419862175
    },
    {
        "question": "176422196÷64617340=？",
        "answer": 0.4362041474839638
    },
    {
        "question": "2×2753788=？",
        "answer": 6.740960498769313
    },
    {
        "question": "13×2437116=？",
        "answer": 7.500819553203072
    },
    {
        "question": "19774×3192=？",
        "answer": 7.800157412498814
    },
    {
        "question": "2×640=？",
        "answer": 3.1072099696478683
    },
    {
        "question": "1×367662=？",
        "answer": 5.565448745334913
    },
    {
        "question": "36096585÷59783=？",
        "answer": 2.7808884116319734
    },
    {
        "question": "71×25724=？",
        "answer": 6.261596849629806
    },
    {
        "question": "260513÷421=？",
        "answer": 2.791547304304269
    },
    {
        "question": "13×3761406=？",
        "answer": 7.689293565294052
    },
    {
        "question": "724×669=？",
        "answer": 5.68516468396497
    },
    {
        "question": "32298843÷17673128=？",
        "answer": 0.2618735425328104
    },
    {
        "question": "6026301÷1379=？",
        "answer": 3.640486553722781
    },
    {
        "question": "399518÷12484=？",
        "answer": 1.5051825909272287
    },
    {
        "question": "3×281=？",
        "answer": 2.9258275746247424
    },
    {
        "question": "221251682÷67571=？",
        "answer": 3.5151262347724685
    },
    {
        "question": "535542217÷245=？",
        "answer": 6.339627627754717
    },
    {
        "question": "145492522÷17223=？",
        "answer": 3.926731870514057
    },
    {
        "question": "7978÷2503=？",
        "answer": 0.5034331823655975
    },
    {
        "question": "13073×20366=？",
        "answer": 8.425281000611271
    },
    {
        "question": "10240343÷1136=？",
        "answer": 3.9549361721898615
    },
    {
        "question": "2×218535866=？",
        "answer": 8.640552719019034
    },
    {
        "question": "1×839=？",
        "answer": 2.9237619608287004
    },
    {
        "question": "20158×396=？",
        "answer": 6.902142626791687
    },
    {
        "question": "298305021÷106503714=？",
        "answer": 0.447295810600092
    },
    {
        "question": "84×403785=？",
        "answer": 7.530429467588206
    },
    {
        "question": "135800728÷2858180=？",
        "answer": 1.6768125221745434
    },
    {
        "question": "70296995÷30244519=？",
        "answer": 0.36629007853606166
    },
    {
        "question": "1×42528=？",
        "answer": 4.628674959262638
    },
    {
        "question": "171310762÷4339=？",
        "answer": 4.5963949967265565
    },
    {
        "question": "58685481÷23232630=？",
        "answer": 0.40243229255540275
    },
    {
        "question": "8709÷2374=？",
        "answer": 0.5644875759327638
    },
    {
        "question": "47×36290=？",
        "answer": 6.231884826136274
    },
    {
        "question": "29516280÷2220=？",
        "answer": 4.123708647085338
    },
    {
        "question": "890181065÷224=？",
        "answer": 6.599230333852878
    },
    {
        "question": "1504×12155=？",
        "answer": 7.262002799434978
    },
    {
        "question": "23318×319=？",
        "answer": 6.871481981021839
    },
    {
        "question": "208953091÷3557378=？",
        "answer": 1.7689187850394485
    },
    {
        "question": "376×16189=？",
        "answer": 6.784407867992654
    },
    {
        "question": "9828334÷1953096=？",
        "answer": 0.7017563162810061
    },
    {
        "question": "288514130÷339969=？",
        "answer": 2.9287277698167795
    },
    {
        "question": "82458÷960=？",
        "answer": 1.9339615638398213
    },
    {
        "question": "119×2299=？",
        "answer": 5.43708593266181
    },
    {
        "question": "4790×269=？",
        "answer": 6.110087793416971
    },
    {
        "question": "55×6389=？",
        "answer": 5.545795577626384
    },
    {
        "question": "20347×675=？",
        "answer": 7.137804157916058
    },
    {
        "question": "15723541÷788=？",
        "answer": 4.300024139963461
    },
    {
        "question": "2900×5985=？",
        "answer": 7.239462152641385
    },
    {
        "question": "18172×707=？",
        "answer": 7.108822141939488
    },
    {
        "question": "10158÷5243=？",
        "answer": 0.28722835077885556
    },
    {
        "question": "1095×87999=？",
        "answer": 7.983891856133698
    },
    {
        "question": "881×1607=？",
        "answer": 6.150991785175393
    },
    {
        "question": "77557102÷35985=？",
        "answer": 3.3335000658312937
    },
    {
        "question": "11×4569=？",
        "answer": 4.70121384321393
    },
    {
        "question": "1950633÷1456=？",
        "answer": 3.127014192178807
    },
    {
        "question": "170849×498=？",
        "answer": 7.929841783923455
    },
    {
        "question": "264255118÷435206=？",
        "answer": 2.7833285331587105
    },
    {
        "question": "1373×2715=？",
        "answer": 6.5714403711616205
    },
    {
        "question": "456329×1540=？",
        "answer": 8.846798790178424
    },
    {
        "question": "138378820÷2479794=？",
        "answer": 1.7466540180498653
    },
    {
        "question": "174×355=？",
        "answer": 4.790777601337694
    },
    {
        "question": "975×469=？",
        "answer": 5.66017745841362
    },
    {
        "question": "69012×1006=？",
        "answer": 7.841522594365259
    },
    {
        "question": "3822273÷276998=？",
        "answer": 1.1398450692926765
    },
    {
        "question": "216640÷25141=？",
        "answer": 0.9353560989596216
    },
    {
        "question": "520189×347=？",
        "answer": 8.256490639087078
    },
    {
        "question": "2×25425936=？",
        "answer": 7.706306945150711
    },
    {
        "question": "335543851÷630=？",
        "answer": 5.726408735119567
    },
    {
        "question": "18×3017=？",
        "answer": 4.734847815278295
    },
    {
        "question": "1263×27165=？",
        "answer": 7.53541305992507
    },
    {
        "question": "4283668÷463887=？",
        "answer": 0.9654036020550214
    },
    {
        "question": "4074×179017=？",
        "answer": 8.862915299530211
    },
    {
        "question": "20×16046=？",
        "answer": 5.506396783530457
    },
    {
        "question": "8083×208=？",
        "answer": 6.225635913761312
    },
    {
        "question": "22997135÷110367=？",
        "answer": 2.318834496959328
    },
    {
        "question": "233295÷84861=？",
        "answer": 0.4391972858774556
    },
    {
        "question": "219054÷544=？",
        "answer": 2.6049522882522926
    },
    {
        "question": "5877÷1493=？",
        "answer": 0.5950958829893734
    },
    {
        "question": "18094×223=？",
        "answer": 6.6058394490288395
    },
    {
        "question": "5804×46419=？",
        "answer": 8.43042318402261
    },
    {
        "question": "452718526÷40464425=？",
        "answer": 1.0487548934739235
    },
    {
        "question": "1×3119=？",
        "answer": 3.4940153747571436
    },
    {
        "question": "228×112066=？",
        "answer": 7.407408717828184
    },
    {
        "question": "2514÷1123=？",
        "answer": 0.34998551708848114
    },
    {
        "question": "8808÷2504=？",
        "answer": 0.5462429814253033
    },
    {
        "question": "118274404÷3322=？",
        "answer": 4.551491140144746
    },
    {
        "question": "8×14144=？",
        "answer": 5.053662234660941
    },
    {
        "question": "38×13220=？",
        "answer": 5.701015051766432
    },
    {
        "question": "38126112÷13354816=？",
        "answer": 0.4555846105542462
    },
    {
        "question": "113133071÷3271819=？",
        "answer": 1.538800306121243
    },
    {
        "question": "409602218÷213393092=？",
        "answer": 0.2831819434269696
    },
    {
        "question": "241521÷970=？",
        "answer": 2.396183163916993
    },
    {
        "question": "29899×450=？",
        "answer": 7.128869176957816
    },
    {
        "question": "30283906÷19541=？",
        "answer": 3.1902651047477657
    },
    {
        "question": "104×3084=？",
        "answer": 5.5061477086777
    },
    {
        "question": "170×11418=？",
        "answer": 6.288038960048938
    },
    {
        "question": "318061449÷784882=？",
        "answer": 2.607706663784581
    },
    {
        "question": "169534833÷8488=？",
        "answer": 4.300453571914184
    },
    {
        "question": "2092÷617=？",
        "answer": 0.530276516161995
    },
    {
        "question": "29×154691=？",
        "answer": 6.651863044862457
    },
    {
        "question": "4×52380=？",
        "answer": 5.321225485417176
    },
    {
        "question": "512×193656=？",
        "answer": 7.996300918153982
    },
    {
        "question": "25362110÷3176300=？",
        "answer": 0.9022638672332435
    },
    {
        "question": "178819722÷10030303=？",
        "answer": 1.2511013627881729
    },
    {
        "question": "39007140÷2610=？",
        "answer": 4.174503601708404
    },
    {
        "question": "34118676÷80418=？",
        "answer": 2.627638901735713
    },
    {
        "question": "1286738×313=？",
        "answer": 8.605034464297228
    },
    {
        "question": "199×308818=？",
        "answer": 7.7885556824284805
    },
    {
        "question": "820763178÷2894=？",
        "answer": 5.452719337614688
    },
    {
        "question": "103×4290917=？",
        "answer": 8.645387338680719
    },
    {
        "question": "1×207=？",
        "answer": 2.315970345456918
    },
    {
        "question": "2×707262=？",
        "answer": 6.150610320459776
    },
    {
        "question": "2158÷259=？",
        "answer": 0.92075167626564
    },
    {
        "question": "79595908÷1664=？",
        "answer": 4.679737419417385
    },
    {
        "question": "7263×506=？",
        "answer": 6.565266561001194
    },
    {
        "question": "169012÷3752=？",
        "answer": 1.6536547112898818
    },
    {
        "question": "1042535÷21808=？",
        "answer": 1.6794748055405313
    },
    {
        "question": "5608×311=？",
        "answer": 6.24156839398544
    },
    {
        "question": "762558445÷291428=？",
        "answer": 3.417741859206187
    },
    {
        "question": "49×1048978=？",
        "answer": 7.710962459948675
    },
    {
        "question": "168×2599369=？",
        "answer": 8.640177216974704
    },
    {
        "question": "6670437÷9561=？",
        "answer": 2.8436509685674887
    },
    {
        "question": "206019÷27578=？",
        "answer": 0.8733445075472561
    },
    {
        "question": "2113226÷199176=？",
        "answer": 1.025708939075327
    },
    {
        "question": "50041×2516=？",
        "answer": 8.100036616654375
    },
    {
        "question": "4491×5397=？",
        "answer": 7.384495473127928
    },
    {
        "question": "380497852÷1360150=？",
        "answer": 2.4467654035633233
    },
    {
        "question": "24863÷569=？",
        "answer": 1.640441263575832
    },
    {
        "question": "3×2285894=？",
        "answer": 6.83617734242266
    },
    {
        "question": "294004174÷9112598=？",
        "answer": 1.5087112842655264
    },
    {
        "question": "933695÷1703=？",
        "answer": 2.7389903851740987
    },
    {
        "question": "3847275÷4412=？",
        "answer": 2.940517726654599
    },
    {
        "question": "1003×453852=？",
        "answer": 8.658215186621495
    },
    {
        "question": "36625÷17002=？",
        "answer": 0.33327762152069523
    },
    {
        "question": "13×6373660=？",
        "answer": 7.91833224482042
    },
    {
        "question": "617×750451=？",
        "answer": 8.66560750468403
    },
    {
        "question": "78446÷511=？",
        "answer": 2.1861499034642575
    },
    {
        "question": "2925905÷758=？",
        "answer": 3.586591015458138
    },
    {
        "question": "119176×6408=？",
        "answer": 8.882911307834354
    },
    {
        "question": "84342841÷49765=？",
        "answer": 3.2291242172732177
    },
    {
        "question": "21×23123=？",
        "answer": 5.686263473916814
    },
    {
        "question": "665233815÷67046=？",
        "answer": 3.9966014443369335
    },
    {
        "question": "7834816÷2029=？",
        "answer": 3.586746754521358
    },
    {
        "question": "53563087÷5041=？",
        "answer": 4.026348901305696
    },
    {
        "question": "4536559÷2317=？",
        "answer": 3.291800529656059
    },
    {
        "question": "142388548÷1277=？",
        "answer": 5.047284164085126
    },
    {
        "question": "347×1681326=？",
        "answer": 8.765981403741597
    },
    {
        "question": "3870÷889=？",
        "answer": 0.6388092040486977
    },
    {
        "question": "70×3192=？",
        "answer": 5.349160922692949
    },
    {
        "question": "878÷465=？",
        "answer": 0.27604156301614863
    },
    {
        "question": "29004487÷349=？",
        "answer": 4.919639761581224
    },
    {
        "question": "6747×91955=？",
        "answer": 8.792686058882976
    },
    {
        "question": "288070804÷2235035=？",
        "answer": 2.1102149162819597
    },
    {
        "question": "26841835÷104352=？",
        "answer": 2.410311425247888
    },
    {
        "question": "4832897÷286=？",
        "answer": 4.227841506307725
    },
    {
        "question": "557059722÷562442=？",
        "answer": 2.9958240142025545
    },
    {
        "question": "6487×2164=？",
        "answer": 7.147301154364759
    },
    {
        "question": "2733×9167=？",
        "answer": 7.398866863042746
    },
    {
        "question": "50820478÷7278=？",
        "answer": 3.8440266943084094
    },
    {
        "question": "245335659÷1662=？",
        "answer": 5.169129657096699
    },
    {
        "question": "1×127261=？",
        "answer": 5.1046953315418495
    },
    {
        "question": "18×2211947=？",
        "answer": 7.600047221821275
    },
    {
        "question": "1×223=？",
        "answer": 2.3483048630481607
    },
    {
        "question": "485658614÷106422034=？",
        "answer": 0.6592995409503991
    },
    {
        "question": "181249÷66607=？",
        "answer": 0.4347557457901424
    },
    {
        "question": "75989838÷3422=？",
        "answer": 4.346475513449344
    },
    {
        "question": "7×9336=？",
        "answer": 4.815258883051571
    },
    {
        "question": "61546×2329=？",
        "answer": 8.156369321035521
    },
    {
        "question": "91878×3550=？",
        "answer": 8.51343988596013
    },
    {
        "question": "131620522÷178279=？",
        "answer": 2.868223419473627
    },
    {
        "question": "2770639÷11371=？",
        "answer": 2.3867812836003983
    },
    {
        "question": "116163÷96336=？",
        "answer": 0.08127920963121689
    },
    {
        "question": "7211×947=？",
        "answer": 6.834345474564198
    },
    {
        "question": "230520÷300=？",
        "answer": 2.885587356189656
    },
    {
        "question": "77160166÷42201=？",
        "answer": 3.262070411122424
    },
    {
        "question": "16463×291=？",
        "answer": 6.680401967172507
    },
    {
        "question": "58×36507=？",
        "answer": 6.325804139386476
    },
    {
        "question": "1327×242647=？",
        "answer": 8.507845849088582
    },
    {
        "question": "2505187÷2735=？",
        "answer": 2.9618828187102464
    },
    {
        "question": "44×2356=？",
        "answer": 5.015627962601251
    },
    {
        "question": "1444597÷459298=？",
        "answer": 0.4976521543250873
    },
    {
        "question": "5423263÷22749=？",
        "answer": 2.3772983552595957
    },
    {
        "question": "1×22432530=？",
        "answer": 7.350878257224344
    },
    {
        "question": "32×378727=？",
        "answer": 7.083476246031229
    },
    {
        "question": "735×713=？",
        "answer": 5.7193768689360605
    },
    {
        "question": "57×1779622=？",
        "answer": 8.006202621606413
    },
    {
        "question": "41625031÷35428924=？",
        "answer": 0.06999660723176455
    },
    {
        "question": "135×3478140=？",
        "answer": 8.671680827473885
    },
    {
        "question": "3758×381=？",
        "answer": 6.155881751440126
    },
    {
        "question": "21074825÷137266=？",
        "answer": 2.1862009987328777
    },
    {
        "question": "38545972÷1698953=？",
        "answer": 1.355797636923235
    },
    {
        "question": "33075203÷123172=？",
        "answer": 2.4289905250433823
    },
    {
        "question": "5×161235543=？",
        "answer": 8.906430788872484
    },
    {
        "question": "1×289649=？",
        "answer": 5.461872033455716
    },
    {
        "question": "116×54311=？",
        "answer": 6.799345788530017
    },
    {
        "question": "8271108÷7853021=？",
        "answer": 0.022526932849208817
    },
    {
        "question": "365142521÷314465286=？",
        "answer": 0.06488969925467579
    },
    {
        "question": "2×1297=？",
        "answer": 3.4139699717480614
    },
    {
        "question": "584×45748=？",
        "answer": 7.4267849595487485
    },
    {
        "question": "26706×14390=？",
        "answer": 8.58466963860277
    },
    {
        "question": "3×2069=？",
        "answer": 3.792881745385397
    },
    {
        "question": "7427166÷5000612=？",
        "answer": 0.17179997194418165
    },
    {
        "question": "4×30294587=？",
        "answer": 8.08342502755171
    },
    {
        "question": "217124×333=？",
        "answer": 7.859152064752001
    },
    {
        "question": "18167÷439=？",
        "answer": 1.616818695947842
    },
    {
        "question": "611370307÷4544491=？",
        "answer": 2.1288190944368486
    },
    {
        "question": "1141413÷5569=？",
        "answer": 2.311665596701412
    },
    {
        "question": "4×124335=？",
        "answer": 5.696653390019818
    },
    {
        "question": "25172618÷24966=？",
        "answer": 3.0035794191702374
    },
    {
        "question": "32×2010910=？",
        "answer": 7.808542612129958
    },
    {
        "question": "4394÷382=？",
        "answer": 1.0607966896727827
    },
    {
        "question": "306737÷25036=？",
        "answer": 1.0882012228196491
    },
    {
        "question": "24245×2260=？",
        "answer": 7.738730627598944
    },
    {
        "question": "2×16442428=？",
        "answer": 7.516995944460675
    },
    {
        "question": "4×1767677=？",
        "answer": 6.849462902495406
    },
    {
        "question": "66×479=？",
        "answer": 4.499879448956432
    },
    {
        "question": "31×434=？",
        "answer": 4.1288514233467835
    },
    {
        "question": "492001877÷1645=？",
        "answer": 5.475800857329309
    },
    {
        "question": "681×7898=？",
        "answer": 6.730664241313311
    },
    {
        "question": "83021×674=？",
        "answer": 7.747847856749422
    },
    {
        "question": "460117×1344=？",
        "answer": 8.791267548211248
    },
    {
        "question": "56×11891115=？",
        "answer": 8.823410606237482
    },
    {
        "question": "9×43917=？",
        "answer": 5.5968751749445405
    },
    {
        "question": "29700153÷48875=？",
        "answer": 2.78367191618213
    },
    {
        "question": "236304×534=？",
        "answer": 8.1010123301769
    },
    {
        "question": "772572240÷13001857=？",
        "answer": 1.773933713884038
    },
    {
        "question": "1×92942=？",
        "answer": 4.968212013738054
    },
    {
        "question": "48057×7794=？",
        "answer": 8.573517057560181
    },
    {
        "question": "4880256÷31333=？",
        "answer": 2.1924406253651014
    },
    {
        "question": "18907×15058=？",
        "answer": 8.454389917006353
    },
    {
        "question": "186575501÷44828=？",
        "answer": 3.6193052532173984
    },
    {
        "question": "721×32071=？",
        "answer": 7.364047766516002
    },
    {
        "question": "177373492÷37781639=？",
        "answer": 0.6716079221189114
    },
    {
        "question": "79022662÷501121=？",
        "answer": 2.1978090527812917
    },
    {
        "question": "100×2800=？",
        "answer": 5.447158031342219
    },
    {
        "question": "293679124÷10061827=？",
        "answer": 1.4651962301373183
    },
    {
        "question": "38940×20980=？",
        "answer": 8.912201431041552
    },
    {
        "question": "1610443÷16933=？",
        "answer": 1.9782114496379726
    },
    {
        "question": "90941×805=？",
        "answer": 7.864555605826292
    },
    {
        "question": "174107437÷2145911=？",
        "answer": 1.9092056164289053
    },
    {
        "question": "2661×201=？",
        "answer": 5.728240931971878
    },
    {
        "question": "373188367÷1351202=？",
        "answer": 2.4412078180998855
    },
    {
        "question": "1×634691=？",
        "answer": 5.802562340006016
    },
    {
        "question": "27×5544878=？",
        "answer": 8.175255759277228
    },
    {
        "question": "11583÷2385=？",
        "answer": 0.6863326729675788
    },
    {
        "question": "7×8687=？",
        "answer": 4.783967861527244
    },
    {
        "question": "35824÷504=？",
        "answer": 1.8517435397894297
    },
    {
        "question": "272×6199=？",
        "answer": 6.226890540385773
    },
    {
        "question": "234552039÷18716=？",
        "answer": 4.0980261761738195
    },
    {
        "question": "1421×6900=？",
        "answer": 6.991443168664725
    },
    {
        "question": "428037292÷194332=？",
        "answer": 3.3429372875011087
    },
    {
        "question": "560951780÷3167840=？",
        "answer": 2.248162292155261
    },
    {
        "question": "87×345=？",
        "answer": 4.477338347691893
    },
    {
        "question": "79×39362=？",
        "answer": 6.492704248298138
    },
    {
        "question": "207558843÷1840=？",
        "answer": 5.052323418122449
    },
    {
        "question": "11957÷864=？",
        "answer": 1.1411084867656263
    },
    {
        "question": "8×4552=？",
        "answer": 4.561292240378958
    },
    {
        "question": "78855985÷29867=？",
        "answer": 3.421643058982794
    },
    {
        "question": "291723÷4051=？",
        "answer": 1.8574084278966856
    },
    {
        "question": "48309156÷797=？",
        "answer": 4.78257112868108
    },
    {
        "question": "618851÷3100=？",
        "answer": 2.3002244032193873
    },
    {
        "question": "18830×2178=？",
        "answer": 7.612908195436421
    },
    {
        "question": "237823803÷3327=？",
        "answer": 4.8542025186914435
    },
    {
        "question": "19916×8209=？",
        "answer": 8.213492373269371
    },
    {
        "question": "33×37723=？",
        "answer": 6.095120163488169
    },
    {
        "question": "66×61925=？",
        "answer": 6.611409950799743
    },
    {
        "question": "794×4389=？",
        "answer": 6.542186083272069
    },
    {
        "question": "23391÷7266=？",
        "answer": 0.5077533954136416
    },
    {
        "question": "168×113863=？",
        "answer": 7.281691903905429
    },
    {
        "question": "27949×4268=？",
        "answer": 8.07659068443279
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1185=？",
        "answer": 3.0737183503461227
    },
    {
        "question": "204327×1022=？",
        "answer": 8.319776654385311
    },
    {
        "question": "55989485÷21405426=？",
        "answer": 0.4175825974388652
    },
    {
        "question": "15449÷493=？",
        "answer": 1.4960534538986818
    },
    {
        "question": "66422÷2228=？",
        "answer": 1.474396761783964
    },
    {
        "question": "2290921÷362079=？",
        "answer": 0.8012067760938467
    },
    {
        "question": "17956×3131=？",
        "answer": 7.749892664346531
    },
    {
        "question": "609×553=？",
        "answer": 5.527342423937574
    },
    {
        "question": "11630620÷323=？",
        "answer": 4.556400344194576
    },
    {
        "question": "8222×2659=？",
        "answer": 7.339695809775898
    },
    {
        "question": "241224÷71356=？",
        "answer": 0.5289900178749559
    },
    {
        "question": "16503314÷734=？",
        "answer": 4.351875102927933
    },
    {
        "question": "119707659÷16735=？",
        "answer": 3.8544962211397333
    },
    {
        "question": "4801745÷2176=？",
        "answer": 3.3437402017974422
    },
    {
        "question": "7036÷1738=？",
        "answer": 0.607276058672776
    },
    {
        "question": "5099×3964=？",
        "answer": 7.305618657780712
    },
    {
        "question": "101276646÷2560=？",
        "answer": 4.597269344977824
    },
    {
        "question": "16343÷7007=？",
        "answer": 0.36779966321301727
    },
    {
        "question": "3144318÷473=？",
        "answer": 3.822665321140171
    },
    {
        "question": "28×1543259=？",
        "answer": 7.635596849713548
    },
    {
        "question": "16×120215=？",
        "answer": 6.284078643424049
    },
    {
        "question": "715×4956=？",
        "answer": 6.549437339505107
    },
    {
        "question": "88×235=？",
        "answer": 4.315550534421905
    },
    {
        "question": "14557839÷41297=？",
        "answer": 2.547178408367007
    },
    {
        "question": "82839×319=？",
        "answer": 7.422025530677157
    },
    {
        "question": "115279905÷3649=？",
        "answer": 4.499579746547523
    },
    {
        "question": "4×6851=？",
        "answer": 4.437813958847346
    },
    {
        "question": "295779÷1211=？",
        "answer": 2.3878231931578684
    },
    {
        "question": "398988363÷302804975=？",
        "answer": 0.11979722290185571
    },
    {
        "question": "2113×2157=？",
        "answer": 6.658749642154858
    },
    {
        "question": "12×3600=？",
        "answer": 4.635483746814912
    },
    {
        "question": "708475×412=？",
        "answer": 8.465221745911451
    },
    {
        "question": "342284482÷486795=？",
        "answer": 2.847041101339942
    },
    {
        "question": "130894÷740=？",
        "answer": 2.247688019817389
    },
    {
        "question": "39700×692=？",
        "answer": 7.438896601219873
    },
    {
        "question": "22122435÷1030133=？",
        "answer": 1.3319396278480171
    },
    {
        "question": "647×26510=？",
        "answer": 7.234314008401793
    },
    {
        "question": "25883223÷15598167=？",
        "answer": 0.2199447883117446
    },
    {
        "question": "999÷359=？",
        "answer": 0.4444710396476632
    },
    {
        "question": "11035×11319=？",
        "answer": 8.096580397418332
    },
    {
        "question": "862×1023342=？",
        "answer": 8.945528064630679
    },
    {
        "question": "77672×1250=？",
        "answer": 7.987174501087542
    },
    {
        "question": "10961798÷1110=？",
        "answer": 3.994558816003561
    },
    {
        "question": "83×39108=？",
        "answer": 6.511343698888843
    },
    {
        "question": "39×9802=？",
        "answer": 5.58237930520311
    },
    {
        "question": "954612÷512=？",
        "answer": 3.2705569284101736
    },
    {
        "question": "65312874÷13395=？",
        "answer": 3.688056076747149
    },
    {
        "question": "10502×7017=？",
        "answer": 7.867423490479854
    },
    {
        "question": "4600219÷3281=？",
        "answer": 3.146772276997171
    },
    {
        "question": "1×307743=？",
        "answer": 5.488188183143734
    },
    {
        "question": "165409374÷500237=？",
        "answer": 2.519384306892597
    },
    {
        "question": "330234÷2718=？",
        "answer": 2.0845723326181984
    },
    {
        "question": "3×1847880=？",
        "answer": 6.743795019747712
    },
    {
        "question": "78563÷69665=？",
        "answer": 0.0522034175805184
    },
    {
        "question": "25344169÷904=？",
        "answer": 4.447709625406366
    },
    {
        "question": "2026078÷42979=？",
        "answer": 1.6733998543592041
    },
    {
        "question": "278×231179=？",
        "answer": 7.8079931767118085
    },
    {
        "question": "254758075÷106317=？",
        "answer": 3.3795252452123012
    },
    {
        "question": "97148÷13908=？",
        "answer": 0.8441691821329734
    },
    {
        "question": "748×79025=？",
        "answer": 7.771666102376079
    },
    {
        "question": "1×780449817=？",
        "answer": 8.892344983118289
    },
    {
        "question": "26×9748060=？",
        "answer": 8.40389154160504
    },
    {
        "question": "422×281=？",
        "answer": 5.074018770866754
    },
    {
        "question": "98×2734=？",
        "answer": 5.428024585924298
    },
    {
        "question": "248×2797409=？",
        "answer": 8.841207648612608
    },
    {
        "question": "40×2010238=？",
        "answer": 7.905307469627918
    },
    {
        "question": "79865×1822=？",
        "answer": 8.162904868633476
    },
    {
        "question": "357×123466=？",
        "answer": 7.644215594393494
    },
    {
        "question": "550383÷766=？",
        "answer": 2.856436241495627
    },
    {
        "question": "1675051÷204374=？",
        "answer": 0.9136023894553593
    },
    {
        "question": "189×427=？",
        "answer": 4.906889679198268
    },
    {
        "question": "1050×51167=？",
        "answer": 7.730179253434278
    },
    {
        "question": "120365086÷14082=？",
        "answer": 3.9318361904904897
    },
    {
        "question": "8865×85902=？",
        "answer": 8.881682015279848
    },
    {
        "question": "173931÷10139=？",
        "answer": 1.2343818708461822
    },
    {
        "question": "3750597÷250510=？",
        "answer": 1.1752753349440135
    },
    {
        "question": "1099×890=？",
        "answer": 5.990387699068403
    },
    {
        "question": "2213×339=？",
        "answer": 5.87518111213034
    },
    {
        "question": "4354171÷155578=？",
        "answer": 1.446957296743541
    },
    {
        "question": "8×744846=？",
        "answer": 6.775156476835894
    },
    {
        "question": "256637990÷798=？",
        "answer": 5.507318053853219
    },
    {
        "question": "77×5261353=？",
        "answer": 8.607588166070405
    },
    {
        "question": "3461×788=？",
        "answer": 6.435727816783683
    },
    {
        "question": "2746×740=？",
        "answer": 6.307932252631712
    },
    {
        "question": "225473×617=？",
        "answer": 8.143379707351148
    },
    {
        "question": "22946644÷230644=？",
        "answer": 1.9977770166367463
    },
    {
        "question": "781325÷560=？",
        "answer": 3.144643693615093
    },
    {
        "question": "2385907÷802=？",
        "answer": 3.4734791430644205
    },
    {
        "question": "51493÷472=？",
        "answer": 2.037806196077042
    },
    {
        "question": "3×494604=？",
        "answer": 6.1713788790193105
    },
    {
        "question": "34702629÷921=？",
        "answer": 4.576102747099591
    },
    {
        "question": "3043369÷120974=？",
        "answer": 1.4006625717313914
    },
    {
        "question": "168391441÷44699348=？",
        "answer": 0.5760188249950307
    },
    {
        "question": "24×351=？",
        "answer": 3.9255183581774302
    },
    {
        "question": "798613525÷1549346=？",
        "answer": 2.7121882457102324
    },
    {
        "question": "6467324÷1962=？",
        "answer": 3.518025615733309
    },
    {
        "question": "26980×23420=？",
        "answer": 8.80062883607223
    },
    {
        "question": "4243×472=？",
        "answer": 6.301615030400703
    },
    {
        "question": "14837×2709=？",
        "answer": 7.6041551017203455
    },
    {
        "question": "987736107÷31512990=？",
        "answer": 1.496151318184207
    },
    {
        "question": "17567837÷5724898=？",
        "answer": 0.48695053997126087
    },
    {
        "question": "69×15063=？",
        "answer": 6.016760566831264
    },
    {
        "question": "379334216÷273198=？",
        "answer": 3.1425445022109177
    },
    {
        "question": "7552÷280=？",
        "answer": 1.4309039499477934
    },
    {
        "question": "151560870÷64865=？",
        "answer": 3.368576667152954
    },
    {
        "question": "53782558÷543=？",
        "answer": 4.995841624655175
    },
    {
        "question": "695058÷188521=？",
        "answer": 0.5666613115718232
    },
    {
        "question": "734324÷598679=？",
        "answer": 0.08869369797264923
    },
    {
        "question": "660×389=？",
        "answer": 5.4094935368675765
    },
    {
        "question": "84782÷1659=？",
        "answer": 1.7084572712977066
    },
    {
        "question": "98×571=？",
        "answer": 4.747862183938343
    },
    {
        "question": "214289÷640=？",
        "answer": 2.52481990418854
    },
    {
        "question": "777995÷75762=？",
        "answer": 1.0115253750337496
    },
    {
        "question": "28917794÷43885=？",
        "answer": 2.8188490569475597
    },
    {
        "question": "2×1879025=？",
        "answer": 6.574962553992192
    },
    {
        "question": "43505743÷300200=？",
        "answer": 2.16113590211822
    },
    {
        "question": "1×2881=？",
        "answer": 3.459543258280413
    },
    {
        "question": "2510864÷1243=？",
        "answer": 3.3053520613117793
    },
    {
        "question": "149×1797353=？",
        "answer": 8.427819649303377
    },
    {
        "question": "388÷251=？",
        "answer": 0.1891580041131691
    },
    {
        "question": "93785×1372=？",
        "answer": 8.109487494119097
    },
    {
        "question": "90488332÷74191843=？",
        "answer": 0.08623642327293558
    },
    {
        "question": "2651×162243=？",
        "answer": 8.63357569590532
    },
    {
        "question": "859930÷1385=？",
        "answer": 2.7930133268535253
    },
    {
        "question": "1×382801410=？",
        "answer": 8.582973528775891
    },
    {
        "question": "560545729÷1102595=？",
        "answer": 2.7061950291437644
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1815=？",
        "answer": 3.258876629372131
    },
    {
        "question": "1×4063645=？",
        "answer": 6.608915760969952
    },
    {
        "question": "5307452÷716=？",
        "answer": 3.8699730528374072
    },
    {
        "question": "15×203902=？",
        "answer": 6.485512744690142
    },
    {
        "question": "28288÷4971=？",
        "answer": 0.7551584801939799
    },
    {
        "question": "209637093÷37809=？",
        "answer": 3.743872937811242
    },
    {
        "question": "1549897÷201374=？",
        "answer": 0.8862994408661213
    },
    {
        "question": "222168505÷11744173=？",
        "answer": 1.2768600525299125
    },
    {
        "question": "5779705÷2345276=？",
        "answer": 0.39171171300605484
    },
    {
        "question": "465×950=？",
        "answer": 5.645176558178802
    },
    {
        "question": "16103381÷5228=？",
        "answer": 3.48858148938969
    },
    {
        "question": "2×53274597=？",
        "answer": 8.027550168806895
    },
    {
        "question": "5×19908=？",
        "answer": 4.997997636408004
    },
    {
        "question": "22×1307=？",
        "answer": 4.458698268402751
    },
    {
        "question": "97411×9256=？",
        "answer": 8.955031347684313
    },
    {
        "question": "157227764÷4396=？",
        "answer": 4.5534715544362
    },
    {
        "question": "5×18316625=？",
        "answer": 7.961815458443709
    },
    {
        "question": "235955÷1788=？",
        "answer": 2.120461670225647
    },
    {
        "question": "57479609÷46644005=？",
        "answer": 0.09071797198905253
    },
    {
        "question": "48651×1524=？",
        "answer": 7.870076738432588
    },
    {
        "question": "1014761÷4869=？",
        "answer": 2.318923993217174
    },
    {
        "question": "306014÷287=？",
        "answer": 3.0278593989752447
    },
    {
        "question": "13×36197278=？",
        "answer": 8.672619265546443
    },
    {
        "question": "652966883÷64281=？",
        "answer": 4.00680853107081
    },
    {
        "question": "1×11787=？",
        "answer": 4.071403283531469
    },
    {
        "question": "12038÷354=？",
        "answer": 1.5315510769629832
    },
    {
        "question": "6×957=？",
        "answer": 3.759063188160487
    },
    {
        "question": "9507220÷218=？",
        "answer": 4.639597050129755
    },
    {
        "question": "17317646÷9322=？",
        "answer": 3.2689797591372884
    },
    {
        "question": "13788×30516=？",
        "answer": 8.624028880959244
    },
    {
        "question": "3137819÷225=？",
        "answer": 4.144445370289222
    },
    {
        "question": "101100393÷513=？",
        "answer": 5.29463547868294
    },
    {
        "question": "10622263÷5497=？",
        "answer": 3.286091313086201
    },
    {
        "question": "4×481=？",
        "answer": 3.284205067701794
    },
    {
        "question": "8577549÷1317=？",
        "answer": 3.8137774327187826
    },
    {
        "question": "14925883÷1641=？",
        "answer": 3.958831451926477
    },
    {
        "question": "423407737÷457=？",
        "answer": 5.9668425896213515
    },
    {
        "question": "94657185÷3742=？",
        "answer": 4.403049801722423
    },
    {
        "question": "4080626÷556=？",
        "answer": 3.8656520007948907
    },
    {
        "question": "65491×4650=？",
        "answer": 8.483634574730669
    },
    {
        "question": "545080472÷22635569=？",
        "answer": 1.3816692072994834
    },
    {
        "question": "671×1120=？",
        "answer": 5.8759405428391736
    },
    {
        "question": "231978774÷410=？",
        "answer": 5.752664392152209
    },
    {
        "question": "16453×48388=？",
        "answer": 8.900982769681898
    },
    {
        "question": "10×51050506=？",
        "answer": 8.708000051063845
    },
    {
        "question": "765×267293=？",
        "answer": 8.310649020542478
    },
    {
        "question": "1×772=？",
        "answer": 2.887617300335736
    },
    {
        "question": "16×14156741=？",
        "answer": 8.355083269299326
    },
    {
        "question": "823012÷8727=？",
        "answer": 1.9745411915612092
    },
    {
        "question": "111864÷844=？",
        "answer": 2.1223478980185364
    },
    {
        "question": "8×12815=？",
        "answer": 5.010808597512207
    },
    {
        "question": "1128×136379=？",
        "answer": 8.187056601300196
    },
    {
        "question": "44×2180516=？",
        "answer": 7.98201195423547
    },
    {
        "question": "9664×1208=？",
        "answer": 7.06722385556217
    },
    {
        "question": "10370÷245=？",
        "answer": 1.6266126720245084
    },
    {
        "question": "2778÷1869=？",
        "answer": 0.17212294002276474
    },
    {
        "question": "81×1434=？",
        "answer": 5.065034170210431
    },
    {
        "question": "2×158120=？",
        "answer": 5.500016801334914
    },
    {
        "question": "2211×10493=？",
        "answer": 7.36548841544125
    },
    {
        "question": "939081×669=？",
        "answer": 8.798129171520479
    },
    {
        "question": "11665499÷457722=？",
        "answer": 1.406301533875658
    },
    {
        "question": "104463384÷3114988=？",
        "answer": 1.5255077123715062
    },
    {
        "question": "2234×57977=？",
        "answer": 8.112338907960801
    },
    {
        "question": "487×337295=？",
        "answer": 8.215538864548797
    },
    {
        "question": "17221401÷805=？",
        "answer": 4.330272599027307
    },
    {
        "question": "32762×5803=？",
        "answer": 8.279022976548246
    },
    {
        "question": "7×2641311=？",
        "answer": 7.266917580044332
    },
    {
        "question": "1×241865=？",
        "answer": 5.38357302666439
    },
    {
        "question": "209194963÷363997=？",
        "answer": 2.759453419086769
    },
    {
        "question": "11×62309178=？",
        "answer": 8.835944707117225
    },
    {
        "question": "5430647÷375037=？",
        "answer": 1.160777457930596
    },
    {
        "question": "3×1361093=？",
        "answer": 6.611009055166887
    },
    {
        "question": "61×1240672=？",
        "answer": 7.87898681601137
    },
    {
        "question": "5×6258561=？",
        "answer": 7.4954444938404166
    },
    {
        "question": "2609063÷278=？",
        "answer": 3.972439770043787
    },
    {
        "question": "10481019÷162369=？",
        "answer": 1.8099003923224597
    },
    {
        "question": "188×84325=？",
        "answer": 7.200114199124919
    },
    {
        "question": "42531326÷1539=？",
        "answer": 4.441470303101352
    },
    {
        "question": "1×58572632=？",
        "answer": 7.767694739776531
    },
    {
        "question": "1×629603=？",
        "answer": 5.7990667887289336
    },
    {
        "question": "57×274820=？",
        "answer": 7.194923190950735
    },
    {
        "question": "345380×397=？",
        "answer": 8.13708769193109
    },
    {
        "question": "29227×30464=？",
        "answer": 8.949571166272882
    },
    {
        "question": "9654×14648=？",
        "answer": 8.150485625776314
    },
    {
        "question": "364×28168=？",
        "answer": 7.0108573957111835
    },
    {
        "question": "1402×98232=？",
        "answer": 8.139000999987516
    },
    {
        "question": "476194×1391=？",
        "answer": 8.821111049025403
    },
    {
        "question": "1576÷406=？",
        "answer": 0.5890301795763424
    },
    {
        "question": "29×1175=？",
        "answer": 4.532435864506711
    },
    {
        "question": "7984394÷69615=？",
        "answer": 2.0595391321427714
    },
    {
        "question": "333415×654=？",
        "answer": 8.338562882720536
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1015=？",
        "answer": 3.0064660422492318
    },
    {
        "question": "113452896÷82037978=？",
        "answer": 0.14080063844922322
    },
    {
        "question": "326379287÷98111343=？",
        "answer": 0.5220033687306692
    },
    {
        "question": "477×16584=？",
        "answer": 6.898207668125918
    },
    {
        "question": "2×2313223=？",
        "answer": 6.665247497436393
    },
    {
        "question": "735572÷127811=？",
        "answer": 0.7600569563914882
    },
    {
        "question": "8556162÷240=？",
        "answer": 4.552067757077086
    },
    {
        "question": "47×2368408=？",
        "answer": 8.046554377306492
    },
    {
        "question": "55748×262=？",
        "answer": 7.164530582689374
    },
    {
        "question": "463556220÷23882=？",
        "answer": 4.288031718810917
    },
    {
        "question": "55683166÷876=？",
        "answer": 4.803219813991181
    },
    {
        "question": "32703÷7318=？",
        "answer": 0.6501951892125741
    },
    {
        "question": "8880÷7592=？",
        "answer": 0.06805676635936474
    },
    {
        "question": "8578172÷242306=？",
        "answer": 1.5490305816777317
    },
    {
        "question": "16×1805729=？",
        "answer": 7.460772555523903
    },
    {
        "question": "325607652÷264544=？",
        "answer": 3.0901966866034116
    },
    {
        "question": "659×45646=？",
        "answer": 7.478288140516011
    },
    {
        "question": "3610167÷434=？",
        "answer": 3.9200375625596187
    },
    {
        "question": "11523292÷380=？",
        "answer": 4.481792970421371
    },
    {
        "question": "888778338÷5613712=？",
        "answer": 2.1995433328166407
    },
    {
        "question": "4×3678770=？",
        "answer": 7.1677626275273125
    },
    {
        "question": "11×4759530=？",
        "answer": 7.718956753743333
    },
    {
        "question": "1×126726=？",
        "answer": 5.102865726944312
    },
    {
        "question": "1×3172982=？",
        "answer": 6.501467608399547
    },
    {
        "question": "336×19455=？",
        "answer": 6.815370512529605
    },
    {
        "question": "1818÷679=？",
        "answer": 0.4277241046054469
    },
    {
        "question": "328÷230=？",
        "answer": 0.1541460076940862
    },
    {
        "question": "1×225057=？",
        "answer": 5.352292525446437
    },
    {
        "question": "157049376÷20848511=？",
        "answer": 0.8769611720484275
    },
    {
        "question": "190×4008873=？",
        "answer": 8.881775899090892
    },
    {
        "question": "420176190÷456=？",
        "answer": 5.964466596065682
    },
    {
        "question": "32377225÷4336108=？",
        "answer": 0.8731395326356708
    },
    {
        "question": "2173×153266=？",
        "answer": 8.522505549471806
    },
    {
        "question": "392060÷7052=？",
        "answer": 1.7450402319516123
    },
    {
        "question": "14737070÷851=？",
        "answer": 4.2384815863068255
    },
    {
        "question": "416921809÷1758=？",
        "answer": 5.37503574273977
    },
    {
        "question": "2×235060024=？",
        "answer": 8.672208771822424
    },
    {
        "question": "5×132454=？",
        "answer": 5.821035082497367
    },
    {
        "question": "319×412=？",
        "answer": 5.1186878990903155
    },
    {
        "question": "346×459=？",
        "answer": 5.200888784330038
    },
    {
        "question": "3402÷1546=？",
        "answer": 0.3425248196942441
    },
    {
        "question": "6488114÷1454612=？",
        "answer": 0.6493713060652668
    },
    {
        "question": "70970÷14480=？",
        "answer": 0.6903062433677588
    },
    {
        "question": "26058×23187=？",
        "answer": 8.781185641763443
    },
    {
        "question": "676980÷810=？",
        "answer": 2.9220908196470554
    },
    {
        "question": "15571438÷98882=？",
        "answer": 2.197211478964183
    },
    {
        "question": "4933937÷797=？",
        "answer": 3.791735278413657
    },
    {
        "question": "93×2498633=？",
        "answer": 8.366185420054686
    },
    {
        "question": "3921×910=？",
        "answer": 6.552438234621301
    },
    {
        "question": "5871106÷1242=？",
        "answer": 3.6745983255862433
    },
    {
        "question": "109803330÷23298=？",
        "answer": 3.673296870210749
    },
    {
        "question": "100029511÷779=？",
        "answer": 5.108590688064376
    },
    {
        "question": "95743532÷473=？",
        "answer": 5.306248303922806
    },
    {
        "question": "1470×68520=？",
        "answer": 8.00313468904165
    },
    {
        "question": "12×2780=？",
        "answer": 4.523226041965701
    },
    {
        "question": "9×90670=？",
        "answer": 5.911706125169256
    },
    {
        "question": "354×7044=？",
        "answer": 6.396822609321027
    },
    {
        "question": "2×57642=？",
        "answer": 5.061769036749287
    },
    {
        "question": "3×26564=？",
        "answer": 4.901414726286469
    },
    {
        "question": "130031×7514=？",
        "answer": 8.989918093218625
    },
    {
        "question": "97339030÷62147=？",
        "answer": 3.194866845169842
    },
    {
        "question": "15012111÷234=？",
        "answer": 4.807225909529228
    },
    {
        "question": "7×297599=？",
        "answer": 6.31872950756279
    },
    {
        "question": "257656479÷7030=？",
        "answer": 4.564085742633354
    },
    {
        "question": "39×79783=？",
        "answer": 6.492974969646471
    },
    {
        "question": "520406÷134749=？",
        "answer": 0.5868167442169351
    },
    {
        "question": "30×1665=？",
        "answer": 4.6985354925620015
    },
    {
        "question": "4×2403536=？",
        "answer": 6.982910622674783
    },
    {
        "question": "4596÷373=？",
        "answer": 1.09067118820756
    },
    {
        "question": "246271÷167142=？",
        "answer": 0.16832767929621248
    },
    {
        "question": "139×20273=？",
        "answer": 6.4499328206313935
    },
    {
        "question": "4413575÷22324=？",
        "answer": 2.2960184971193804
    },
    {
        "question": "838086÷785644=？",
        "answer": 0.028062787817442814
    },
    {
        "question": "37126×351=？",
        "answer": 7.1149852768014075
    },
    {
        "question": "1683÷393=？",
        "answer": 0.6316915656003972
    },
    {
        "question": "41335328÷7280413=？",
        "answer": 0.754165371673782
    },
    {
        "question": "103635261÷102765=？",
        "answer": 3.0036623189138907
    },
    {
        "question": "82×14397=？",
        "answer": 6.072085857035801
    },
    {
        "question": "74×48057=？",
        "answer": 6.5509883758344865
    },
    {
        "question": "41×181057=？",
        "answer": 6.870599176828885
    },
    {
        "question": "1243×5396=？",
        "answer": 6.826543069641511
    },
    {
        "question": "330085÷16333=？",
        "answer": 1.305559827138138
    },
    {
        "question": "8×4490=？",
        "answer": 4.555336327995267
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1732=？",
        "answer": 3.2385478876813276
    },
    {
        "question": "274234÷4963=？",
        "answer": 1.7423770231664153
    },
    {
        "question": "26×10313589=？",
        "answer": 8.428383168604771
    },
    {
        "question": "147105394÷19476471=？",
        "answer": 0.8781183289951913
    },
    {
        "question": "1865×386793=？",
        "answer": 8.858157441967041
    },
    {
        "question": "4248÷2056=？",
        "answer": 0.3151613977501746
    },
    {
        "question": "7×135760=？",
        "answer": 5.977869869323876
    },
    {
        "question": "1372×5734=？",
        "answer": 6.895811799981199
    },
    {
        "question": "3×54261819=？",
        "answer": 8.211615603091449
    },
    {
        "question": "1×11010354=？",
        "answer": 7.041801282439061
    },
    {
        "question": "92491×485=？",
        "answer": 7.651841213606161
    },
    {
        "question": "64186574÷126103=？",
        "answer": 2.7067187769584993
    },
    {
        "question": "84281÷377=？",
        "answer": 2.3493883296954503
    },
    {
        "question": "6956913÷991064=？",
        "answer": 0.8463148714497664
    },
    {
        "question": "5954790÷1083265=？",
        "answer": 0.7401317389425182
    },
    {
        "question": "12×5765342=？",
        "answer": 7.840006320784563
    },
    {
        "question": "5×136350=？",
        "answer": 5.8336251466136675
    },
    {
        "question": "332261453÷1613255=？",
        "answer": 2.313776940134658
    },
    {
        "question": "81339507÷4312=？",
        "answer": 4.275622783632345
    },
    {
        "question": "11×461894=？",
        "answer": 6.70593500595897
    },
    {
        "question": "15×3038804=？",
        "answer": 7.658793948453318
    },
    {
        "question": "12×2599877=？",
        "answer": 7.494134048062727
    },
    {
        "question": "4620×125420=？",
        "answer": 8.763008771995457
    },
    {
        "question": "3×35868655=？",
        "answer": 8.031836346560675
    },
    {
        "question": "1362×11114=？",
        "answer": 7.180047500026126
    },
    {
        "question": "1369÷995=？",
        "answer": 0.1385803673882645
    },
    {
        "question": "303×249212=？",
        "answer": 7.878011579042842
    },
    {
        "question": "8×1382531=？",
        "answer": 7.0437648651082805
    },
    {
        "question": "544×4918=？",
        "answer": 6.427387424100878
    },
    {
        "question": "1117×29356=？",
        "answer": 7.5157500521432
    },
    {
        "question": "615×317816=？",
        "answer": 8.291050873142675
    },
    {
        "question": "4657827÷2095863=？",
        "answer": 0.3468204632573539
    },
    {
        "question": "161×3134=？",
        "answer": 5.702924868164421
    },
    {
        "question": "11×39670537=？",
        "answer": 8.639860764496966
    },
    {
        "question": "3×47146411=？",
        "answer": 8.150569892573051
    },
    {
        "question": "218573÷17496=？",
        "answer": 1.0966577431411653
    },
    {
        "question": "131710616÷88156=？",
        "answer": 3.1743689046884564
    },
    {
        "question": "69062462÷615480=？",
        "answer": 2.050028111291539
    },
    {
        "question": "3860083÷10685=？",
        "answer": 2.5578221165277437
    },
    {
        "question": "235×509=？",
        "answer": 5.077785644608495
    },
    {
        "question": "17140÷10470=？",
        "answer": 0.21406413590833703
    },
    {
        "question": "14237×406=？",
        "answer": 6.7619445186149045
    },
    {
        "question": "1997÷484=？",
        "answer": 0.6155327032262902
    },
    {
        "question": "1986449÷27633=？",
        "answer": 1.856649382454417
    },
    {
        "question": "330680÷7638=？",
        "answer": 1.6364282749184351
    },
    {
        "question": "1×7848007=？",
        "answer": 6.894759381739377
    },
    {
        "question": "4496847÷906=？",
        "answer": 3.6957799137768057
    },
    {
        "question": "7×324=？",
        "answer": 3.355643050220869
    },
    {
        "question": "61×10411=？",
        "answer": 5.802822281488043
    },
    {
        "question": "222702×256=？",
        "answer": 7.755964082593143
    },
    {
        "question": "480337×1207=？",
        "answer": 8.763253311404075
    },
    {
        "question": "13×408283=？",
        "answer": 6.724904649545787
    },
    {
        "question": "304188717÷123250638=？",
        "answer": 0.3923539250629022
    },
    {
        "question": "19526÷3547=？",
        "answer": 0.7407520965030435
    },
    {
        "question": "4615×1729=？",
        "answer": 6.901966698635853
    },
    {
        "question": "24417×523=？",
        "answer": 7.106193992068195
    },
    {
        "question": "2433×200050=？",
        "answer": 8.687280664645835
    },
    {
        "question": "685007÷40088=？",
        "answer": 1.2326806197811297
    },
    {
        "question": "18434673÷1539=？",
        "answer": 4.07839681852752
    },
    {
        "question": "228572601÷2548=？",
        "answer": 4.9528247466319
    },
    {
        "question": "24213136÷2046=？",
        "answer": 4.073145411998434
    },
    {
        "question": "2768×37582=？",
        "answer": 8.01714597399871
    },
    {
        "question": "4×23121764=？",
        "answer": 7.966080955429479
    },
    {
        "question": "11×2080=？",
        "answer": 4.359456020120986
    },
    {
        "question": "18×139084=？",
        "answer": 6.398549677429073
    },
    {
        "question": "886×85926=？",
        "answer": 7.8815583170105965
    },
    {
        "question": "111×498821=？",
        "answer": 7.743267707458721
    },
    {
        "question": "56×309856=？",
        "answer": 7.239347937179367
    },
    {
        "question": "954097200÷4897849=？",
        "answer": 2.289587229564883
    },
    {
        "question": "104174×4298=？",
        "answer": 8.651025751371217
    },
    {
        "question": "290391×2444=？",
        "answer": 8.851084353850272
    },
    {
        "question": "5×14137924=？",
        "answer": 7.849355647068759
    },
    {
        "question": "520889÷89650=？",
        "answer": 0.7641948923121057
    },
    {
        "question": "32773÷17036=？",
        "answer": 0.28414856658157145
    },
    {
        "question": "698678÷940=？",
        "answer": 2.871149214788427
    },
    {
        "question": "20×19109520=？",
        "answer": 8.582279774086373
    },
    {
        "question": "22×810=？",
        "answer": 4.250907699700856
    },
    {
        "question": "3908×1342=？",
        "answer": 6.719707070879709
    },
    {
        "question": "2219148÷3216=？",
        "answer": 2.8388702272028827
    },
    {
        "question": "111435643÷2217246=？",
        "answer": 1.70121024326853
    },
    {
        "question": "103099÷10047=？",
        "answer": 1.0112180506419495
    },
    {
        "question": "12224121÷1128=？",
        "answer": 4.034908540453093
    },
    {
        "question": "676398307÷418332=？",
        "answer": 3.208681425014335
    },
    {
        "question": "196742÷10765=？",
        "answer": 1.2618830477788792
    },
    {
        "question": "39907223÷14912601=？",
        "answer": 0.42749810976957353
    },
    {
        "question": "363141÷102477=？",
        "answer": 0.5494488821680124
    },
    {
        "question": "5×10192631=？",
        "answer": 7.707256306232254
    },
    {
        "question": "81076685÷560=？",
        "answer": 5.160707956285127
    },
    {
        "question": "13×27261802=？",
        "answer": 8.549497911538104
    },
    {
        "question": "3058496÷2775137=？",
        "answer": 0.042223489075677224
    },
    {
        "question": "116706×2503=？",
        "answer": 8.465554033844745
    },
    {
        "question": "1180×2068=？",
        "answer": 6.38743254172803
    },
    {
        "question": "725427158÷176990=？",
        "answer": 3.612645081083878
    },
    {
        "question": "302520237÷2050=？",
        "answer": 5.169000570902853
    },
    {
        "question": "30×7098416=？",
        "answer": 8.328282702141834
    },
    {
        "question": "1×152894=？",
        "answer": 5.184390442783022
    },
    {
        "question": "145873719÷2547693=？",
        "answer": 1.7578299614628015
    },
    {
        "question": "27×4183924=？",
        "answer": 8.05294755123226
    },
    {
        "question": "1604×1298=？",
        "answer": 6.318479056412495
    },
    {
        "question": "24×47415=？",
        "answer": 6.056126996606867
    },
    {
        "question": "245×163737=？",
        "answer": 7.603312913319127
    },
    {
        "question": "946437699÷23201=？",
        "answer": 4.610585326931497
    },
    {
        "question": "91479995÷85902671=？",
        "answer": 0.02731946449524814
    },
    {
        "question": "1019×942588=？",
        "answer": 8.982496090502655
    },
    {
        "question": "160790×2089=？",
        "answer": 8.526197475189592
    },
    {
        "question": "4811056÷59536=？",
        "answer": 1.907460759379843
    },
    {
        "question": "70×265141=？",
        "answer": 7.268574929938858
    },
    {
        "question": "89×681=？",
        "answer": 4.782537118557698
    },
    {
        "question": "322×1974=？",
        "answer": 5.803203020029449
    },
    {
        "question": "22×1532=？",
        "answer": 4.527681446118791
    },
    {
        "question": "8×1707333=？",
        "answer": 7.1354082216146635
    },
    {
        "question": "24738437÷676=？",
        "answer": 4.563425561044332
    },
    {
        "question": "75×569075=？",
        "answer": 7.630230770454021
    },
    {
        "question": "4517867÷1349=？",
        "answer": 3.5249214920482763
    },
    {
        "question": "6×78117938=？",
        "answer": 8.670902021519678
    },
    {
        "question": "6291×554=？",
        "answer": 6.542229449913436
    },
    {
        "question": "5962596÷801=？",
        "answer": 3.871802868321942
    },
    {
        "question": "553×5961=？",
        "answer": 6.518044253134176
    },
    {
        "question": "141757÷1246=？",
        "answer": 2.056026471353346
    },
    {
        "question": "14265÷637=？",
        "answer": 1.3501323436577448
    },
    {
        "question": "239×529868=？",
        "answer": 8.10256559316852
    },
    {
        "question": "10297166÷135086=？",
        "answer": 1.8821073719532053
    },
    {
        "question": "2×14051=？",
        "answer": 4.448737229444391
    },
    {
        "question": "1×3542=？",
        "answer": 3.549248556854056
    },
    {
        "question": "5668042÷765876=？",
        "answer": 0.8692745992985541
    },
    {
        "question": "10×20740=？",
        "answer": 5.3168087520530225
    },
    {
        "question": "3598÷3395=？",
        "answer": 0.02522138039301208
    },
    {
        "question": "10754675÷4434=？",
        "answer": 3.3848016020176046
    },
    {
        "question": "308757289÷47518160=？",
        "answer": 0.8127576034817646
    },
    {
        "question": "1755594÷18279=？",
        "answer": 1.9824716550662476
    },
    {
        "question": "333173691÷865420=？",
        "answer": 2.585443772507478
    },
    {
        "question": "404124÷212358=？",
        "answer": 0.2794460164867656
    },
    {
        "question": "22×209528=？",
        "answer": 6.663664748377255
    },
    {
        "question": "1666505÷6096=？",
        "answer": 2.436761662676797
    },
    {
        "question": "51×988=？",
        "answer": 4.702327120685564
    },
    {
        "question": "46431635÷75951=？",
        "answer": 2.7862804804493706
    },
    {
        "question": "52192×230=？",
        "answer": 7.079331775377774
    },
    {
        "question": "11×522=？",
        "answer": 3.759063188160487
    },
    {
        "question": "132905827÷11433=？",
        "answer": 4.065383818673399
    },
    {
        "question": "519587443÷20384=？",
        "answer": 4.406369236168932
    },
    {
        "question": "2594450÷1899550=？",
        "answer": 0.13539457587777087
    },
    {
        "question": "305395×374=？",
        "answer": 8.057733524605935
    },
    {
        "question": "29573×1798=？",
        "answer": 7.725685070677426
    },
    {
        "question": "79120×7762=？",
        "answer": 8.78825991699312
    },
    {
        "question": "6×56781=？",
        "answer": 5.532354287228952
    },
    {
        "question": "12×32040332=？",
        "answer": 8.584878253616534
    },
    {
        "question": "247×445930=？",
        "answer": 8.041963643811087
    },
    {
        "question": "51749828÷24152=？",
        "answer": 3.330955810659324
    },
    {
        "question": "91×3094=？",
        "answer": 5.449561701684442
    },
    {
        "question": "4×84446=？",
        "answer": 5.528639074257253
    },
    {
        "question": "64948022÷330=？",
        "answer": 5.294051989240688
    },
    {
        "question": "1×253=？",
        "answer": 2.403120521175818
    },
    {
        "question": "13×216=？",
        "answer": 3.4483971034577676
    },
    {
        "question": "7994÷5533=？",
        "answer": 0.15980347370993364
    },
    {
        "question": "78×327=？",
        "answer": 4.406642355350766
    },
    {
        "question": "3329×107114=？",
        "answer": 8.552160032798865
    },
    {
        "question": "18216×1682=？",
        "answer": 7.48627900906898
    },
    {
        "question": "269183×848=？",
        "answer": 8.35844348121385
    },
    {
        "question": "820159252÷1046=？",
        "answer": 5.8943665038886905
    },
    {
        "question": "5874×17812=？",
        "answer": 8.019646628645967
    },
    {
        "question": "288208×1506=？",
        "answer": 8.637531003539165
    },
    {
        "question": "86559÷2125=？",
        "answer": 1.6099532960819107
    },
    {
        "question": "18343×1053=？",
        "answer": 7.285898737246671
    },
    {
        "question": "3×53882388=？",
        "answer": 8.208568089585032
    },
    {
        "question": "12×1313=？",
        "answer": 4.197445972137104
    },
    {
        "question": "40831×5909=？",
        "answer": 8.38250400642394
    },
    {
        "question": "90×1643380=？",
        "answer": 8.169980506727963
    },
    {
        "question": "4268231÷1084=？",
        "answer": 3.595218633543156
    },
    {
        "question": "611×1652=？",
        "answer": 6.004051253226917
    },
    {
        "question": "1365849×549=？",
        "answer": 8.874975033479638
    },
    {
        "question": "3918×325=？",
        "answer": 6.104947792637592
    },
    {
        "question": "1985×399129=？",
        "answer": 8.898873795090664
    },
    {
        "question": "220×513=？",
        "answer": 5.052540045934022
    },
    {
        "question": "5404752÷4100154=？",
        "answer": 0.1199756019689799
    },
    {
        "question": "28138÷10632=？",
        "answer": 0.4226782573661846
    },
    {
        "question": "932156÷1649=？",
        "answer": 2.7522679436941733
    },
    {
        "question": "18×3088=？",
        "answer": 4.7449497967670045
    },
    {
        "question": "512651016÷311199211=？",
        "answer": 0.2167833351904778
    },
    {
        "question": "102981851÷5377033=？",
        "answer": 1.282217991744848
    },
    {
        "question": "789822488÷9452293=？",
        "answer": 1.92199231957555
    },
    {
        "question": "285134388÷4539=？",
        "answer": 4.798089414847338
    },
    {
        "question": "112655980÷769=？",
        "answer": 5.165827910071747
    },
    {
        "question": "226160÷361=？",
        "answer": 2.796908593575805
    },
    {
        "question": "314732÷4058=？",
        "answer": 1.8896288588332906
    },
    {
        "question": "27764058÷10197260=？",
        "answer": 0.43499945031628795
    },
    {
        "question": "814892÷4262=？",
        "answer": 2.281486608868472
    },
    {
        "question": "1×346786877=？",
        "answer": 8.540062654679838
    },
    {
        "question": "473240846÷4846791=？",
        "answer": 1.9896279292875276
    },
    {
        "question": "42838×13711=？",
        "answer": 8.768898317340039
    },
    {
        "question": "5×4554215=？",
        "answer": 7.357383533713418
    },
    {
        "question": "5762×84254=？",
        "answer": 8.68616378232089
    },
    {
        "question": "440×97810=？",
        "answer": 7.633835935392421
    },
    {
        "question": "61653381÷4369335=？",
        "answer": 1.1495415541404084
    },
    {
        "question": "1731×411715=？",
        "answer": 8.852893757798693
    },
    {
        "question": "77×5080=？",
        "answer": 5.592354437456401
    },
    {
        "question": "9×2721370=？",
        "answer": 7.3890301023157745
    },
    {
        "question": "13114÷11791=？",
        "answer": 0.04618453996356451
    },
    {
        "question": "14728÷790=？",
        "answer": 1.2705166842055169
    },
    {
        "question": "108048÷73486=？",
        "answer": 0.16741212392972857
    },
    {
        "question": "193×4829315=？",
        "answer": 8.969442842902655
    },
    {
        "question": "812526÷2516=？",
        "answer": 2.5091266300787476
    },
    {
        "question": "4386×92162=？",
        "answer": 8.606620518111821
    },
    {
        "question": "261091×3393=？",
        "answer": 8.947375761273872
    },
    {
        "question": "50×3024919=？",
        "answer": 8.179683754126485
    },
    {
        "question": "7367643÷216=？",
        "answer": 4.532874822757963
    },
    {
        "question": "54175041÷19282=？",
        "answer": 3.4486471701435897
    },
    {
        "question": "90586÷11559=？",
        "answer": 0.8941408192359631
    },
    {
        "question": "22082145÷1454526=？",
        "answer": 1.1813197685305503
    },
    {
        "question": "72937999÷34025640=？",
        "answer": 0.3311475418467098
    },
    {
        "question": "2×26719=？",
        "answer": 4.727850195627337
    },
    {
        "question": "411607168÷5758951=？",
        "answer": 1.8541395458945347
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1311716=？",
        "answer": 6.117839815996923
    },
    {
        "question": "110×1084=？",
        "answer": 5.076421967360593
    },
    {
        "question": "1222×279247=？",
        "answer": 8.533059722016674
    },
    {
        "question": "36828×1595=？",
        "answer": 7.768938821872648
    },
    {
        "question": "163957÷56513=？",
        "answer": 0.46258160073312815
    },
    {
        "question": "11745÷1398=？",
        "answer": 0.9243458497039619
    },
    {
        "question": "10×19588=？",
        "answer": 5.291990095346181
    },
    {
        "question": "1×225070937=？",
        "answer": 8.352319418965807
    },
    {
        "question": "4917×222=？",
        "answer": 6.0380531827408
    },
    {
        "question": "7×19823034=？",
        "answer": 8.142268165875775
    },
    {
        "question": "238×12935=？",
        "answer": 6.488343390109074
    },
    {
        "question": "41071615÷6757=？",
        "answer": 3.783787861401244
    },
    {
        "question": "5×1345=？",
        "answer": 3.8276922886744456
    },
    {
        "question": "82×35076=？",
        "answer": 6.458823913788778
    },
    {
        "question": "16855287÷7630400=？",
        "answer": 0.34418884669185845
    },
    {
        "question": "518047÷12707=？",
        "answer": 1.6103261331334278
    },
    {
        "question": "520×1540=？",
        "answer": 5.903524064471262
    },
    {
        "question": "216653459÷66825447=？",
        "answer": 0.510823754728906
    },
    {
        "question": "5164÷4131=？",
        "answer": 0.09693103861779657
    },
    {
        "question": "1471661÷741=？",
        "answer": 3.2979895729562942
    },
    {
        "question": "80947÷1361=？",
        "answer": 1.7743426326718679
    },
    {
        "question": "665919592÷291019842=？",
        "answer": 0.3594991918533372
    },
    {
        "question": "3×29098912=？",
        "answer": 7.940998005862623
    },
    {
        "question": "81×13128=？",
        "answer": 6.026683586923687
    },
    {
        "question": "11154×5412=？",
        "answer": 7.780788428081127
    },
    {
        "question": "87250×327=？",
        "answer": 7.455313188291504
    },
    {
        "question": "316036701÷31239=？",
        "answer": 4.005040396584416
    },
    {
        "question": "618×618234=？",
        "answer": 8.582141360653285
    },
    {
        "question": "166×1727=？",
        "answer": 5.4574004256075135
    },
    {
        "question": "665984÷472508=？",
        "answer": 0.14905462962678614
    },
    {
        "question": "236277343÷426894=？",
        "answer": 2.7431020276261346
    },
    {
        "question": "1×3440519=？",
        "answer": 6.53662396054671
    },
    {
        "question": "1×396999917=？",
        "answer": 8.598790415966022
    },
    {
        "question": "1×247069394=？",
        "answer": 8.392818950014945
    },
    {
        "question": "64×12621134=？",
        "answer": 8.90727835169841
    },
    {
        "question": "4515×137133=？",
        "answer": 8.79179973163711
    },
    {
        "question": "72743729÷1530=？",
        "answer": 4.677104129340924
    },
    {
        "question": "131×2069=？",
        "answer": 5.433031786321499
    },
    {
        "question": "53941531÷5744=？",
        "answer": 3.9727088374568935
    },
    {
        "question": "1×17760239=？",
        "answer": 7.24944880579409
    },
    {
        "question": "72396÷353=？",
        "answer": 2.3119398659762065
    },
    {
        "question": "32×8550126=？",
        "answer": 8.437122493130127
    },
    {
        "question": "33008960÷9451=？",
        "answer": 3.543154078238768
    },
    {
        "question": "12224×3789=？",
        "answer": 7.665737946506608
    },
    {
        "question": "815247376÷3951301=？",
        "answer": 2.3145492952521414
    },
    {
        "question": "267×314530=？",
        "answer": 7.92417333630672
    },
    {
        "question": "6101672÷9016=？",
        "answer": 2.830434955066976
    },
    {
        "question": "90844063÷2438062=？",
        "answer": 1.571251804253036
    },
    {
        "question": "7×26847892=？",
        "answer": 8.274008232146386
    },
    {
        "question": "11387×36245=？",
        "answer": 8.615657424738172
    },
    {
        "question": "18×5786823=？",
        "answer": 8.017712704021392
    },
    {
        "question": "122×6651518=？",
        "answer": 8.909280601359841
    },
    {
        "question": "1921×21539=？",
        "answer": 7.616752901123409
    },
    {
        "question": "14×29036=？",
        "answer": 5.609064823409498
    },
    {
        "question": "175031460÷1673681=？",
        "answer": 2.019443429458659
    },
    {
        "question": "5818×66508=？",
        "answer": 8.587647605024493
    },
    {
        "question": "160221÷1367=？",
        "answer": 2.0689509234376207
    },
    {
        "question": "529077735÷5649399=？",
        "answer": 1.9715172369203093
    },
    {
        "question": "92×2313202=？",
        "answer": 8.328001386469326
    },
    {
        "question": "187697385÷1312=？",
        "answer": 5.155524387033057
    },
    {
        "question": "28917÷886=？",
        "answer": 1.5137195131037922
    },
    {
        "question": "119156÷256=？",
        "answer": 2.6678759504540053
    },
    {
        "question": "969119571÷6961653=？",
        "answer": 2.143664991766711
    },
    {
        "question": "16441÷15433=？",
        "answer": 0.027477873153332867
    },
    {
        "question": "6159707÷2515=？",
        "answer": 3.389022065092354
    },
    {
        "question": "17×1202145=？",
        "answer": 7.310405775818631
    },
    {
        "question": "223×227=？",
        "answer": 4.704330720241283
    },
    {
        "question": "10437÷7477=？",
        "answer": 0.14484830282057184
    },
    {
        "question": "10×10059=？",
        "answer": 5.002554808148482
    },
    {
        "question": "36038914÷7548=？",
        "answer": 3.6789398039408363
    },
    {
        "question": "97672÷611=？",
        "answer": 2.2037288704840137
    },
    {
        "question": "1255÷225=？",
        "answer": 0.7464612077056945
    },
    {
        "question": "5×22569055=？",
        "answer": 8.052483379236666
    },
    {
        "question": "46×346=？",
        "answer": 4.201833930474351
    },
    {
        "question": "1114÷638=？",
        "answer": 0.24206451211654775
    },
    {
        "question": "3×145710=？",
        "answer": 5.640610612912361
    },
    {
        "question": "26549880÷1504=？",
        "answer": 4.246814726244516
    },
    {
        "question": "126×1980=？",
        "answer": 5.397035735379094
    },
    {
        "question": "24×5213=？",
        "answer": 5.0972989666386255
    },
    {
        "question": "5645240÷4117=？",
        "answer": 3.137101543118241
    },
    {
        "question": "22×37876373=？",
        "answer": 8.920791065580515
    },
    {
        "question": "1852830÷813811=？",
        "answer": 0.35731201819637715
    },
    {
        "question": "41203215÷5146883=？",
        "answer": 0.9033868085469547
    },
    {
        "question": "63125069÷91837=？",
        "answer": 2.8371841774669058
    },
    {
        "question": "1575968÷435=？",
        "answer": 3.5590581379473045
    },
    {
        "question": "48180÷341=？",
        "answer": 2.1501124166698267
    },
    {
        "question": "428×450962=？",
        "answer": 8.285583716909741
    },
    {
        "question": "2×58933283=？",
        "answer": 8.071390630702284
    },
    {
        "question": "72×8951=？",
        "answer": 5.8092040535596325
    },
    {
        "question": "101×7785=？",
        "answer": 5.895579990686782
    },
    {
        "question": "2×277=？",
        "answer": 2.74350976472843
    },
    {
        "question": "8179365÷1339=？",
        "answer": 3.7859390117814873
    },
    {
        "question": "260×9573=？",
        "answer": 6.396021406883991
    },
    {
        "question": "138906÷30243=？",
        "answer": 0.6620961358910609
    },
    {
        "question": "11916÷681=？",
        "answer": 1.2429833826302208
    },
    {
        "question": "9×23892831=？",
        "answer": 8.3325101206725
    },
    {
        "question": "29×1100=？",
        "answer": 4.503790683057181
    },
    {
        "question": "7×5370=？",
        "answer": 4.575072325713813
    },
    {
        "question": "870×531=？",
        "answer": 5.664613773700087
    },
    {
        "question": "68820÷16508=？",
        "answer": 0.620020208079533
    },
    {
        "question": "45786×11143=？",
        "answer": 8.7077348344566
    },
    {
        "question": "51248701÷19949=？",
        "answer": 3.4097617314818587
    },
    {
        "question": "199392÷95878=？",
        "answer": 0.31798876343314997
    },
    {
        "question": "311÷256=？",
        "answer": 0.08452042371498794
    },
    {
        "question": "28132464÷457=？",
        "answer": 4.78929157172348
    },
    {
        "question": "834×15820=？",
        "answer": 7.120372529799396
    },
    {
        "question": "1386×180863=？",
        "answer": 8.399112960544317
    },
    {
        "question": "28569802÷22613=？",
        "answer": 3.101549047825742
    },
    {
        "question": "120096×370=？",
        "answer": 7.647730266799983
    },
    {
        "question": "224×322=？",
        "answer": 4.8581038900299935
    },
    {
        "question": "505176÷109391=？",
        "answer": 0.6644611173639066
    },
    {
        "question": "1083×1218=？",
        "answer": 6.120275744922177
    },
    {
        "question": "1060×1812=？",
        "answer": 6.283464058605564
    },
    {
        "question": "45671514÷19207493=？",
        "answer": 0.3761747250206649
    },
    {
        "question": "1003×460617=？",
        "answer": 8.664640895458765
    },
    {
        "question": "2382883÷627=？",
        "answer": 3.5798351780991164
    },
    {
        "question": "4551÷2551=？",
        "answer": 0.2513963768966029
    },
    {
        "question": "30499÷6347=？",
        "answer": 0.6817171016360543
    },
    {
        "question": "2193×4809=？",
        "answer": 7.02309340875133
    },
    {
        "question": "228225÷31393=？",
        "answer": 0.8615303957111756
    },
    {
        "question": "32263915÷40742=？",
        "answer": 2.898674720403212
    },
    {
        "question": "7227413÷5141711=？",
        "answer": 0.14787520993779893
    },
    {
        "question": "54×7006350=？",
        "answer": 8.577885588390137
    },
    {
        "question": "459844÷114235=？",
        "answer": 0.6048113381961266
    },
    {
        "question": "1×33082350=？",
        "answer": 7.519596352022674
    },
    {
        "question": "256359÷31744=？",
        "answer": 0.9071869183541212
    },
    {
        "question": "108127593÷191762=？",
        "answer": 2.7511739848175782
    },
    {
        "question": "318386×1635=？",
        "answer": 8.716471719779205
    },
    {
        "question": "158706989÷1541=？",
        "answer": 5.012793413539267
    },
    {
        "question": "117578÷7608=？",
        "answer": 1.1890555646439716
    },
    {
        "question": "555561343÷2624=？",
        "answer": 5.3257681883888415
    },
    {
        "question": "36426×3591=？",
        "answer": 8.116626888382665
    },
    {
        "question": "7797÷2307=？",
        "answer": 0.5288799396995816
    },
    {
        "question": "76×5606=？",
        "answer": 5.629466685705059
    },
    {
        "question": "50502×1561=？",
        "answer": 7.89671148062196
    },
    {
        "question": "136×333681=？",
        "answer": 7.656870386735897
    },
    {
        "question": "4×30609669=？",
        "answer": 8.087918624674048
    },
    {
        "question": "154345522÷400=？",
        "answer": 5.5864340425620576
    },
    {
        "question": "18×3415784=？",
        "answer": 7.788762905008438
    },
    {
        "question": "368884076÷32215778=？",
        "answer": 1.0588212841209383
    },
    {
        "question": "222288×2914=？",
        "answer": 8.811405565803453
    },
    {
        "question": "3004305÷516227=？",
        "answer": 0.7649033050530478
    },
    {
        "question": "32×612=？",
        "answer": 4.291901400465467
    },
    {
        "question": "4×36650=？",
        "answer": 5.1661339703051095
    },
    {
        "question": "3577×225=？",
        "answer": 5.905701458260332
    },
    {
        "question": "1803037÷1601359=？",
        "answer": 0.05151593397956109
    },
    {
        "question": "6×11251764=？",
        "answer": 7.829371864867511
    },
    {
        "question": "1×98754=？",
        "answer": 4.9945546956174365
    },
    {
        "question": "352898798÷4869888=？",
        "answer": 1.8601312059041586
    },
    {
        "question": "34079835÷14080=？",
        "answer": 3.383894828625336
    },
    {
        "question": "40268375÷4938625=？",
        "answer": 0.911358053797543
    },
    {
        "question": "1269÷796=？",
        "answer": 0.20254855435703575
    },
    {
        "question": "3138×14226=？",
        "answer": 7.64973574361275
    },
    {
        "question": "9×63113=？",
        "answer": 5.7543613337668456
    },
    {
        "question": "418571353÷692=？",
        "answer": 5.781663407472924
    },
    {
        "question": "337513÷57311=？",
        "answer": 0.7700525188454643
    },
    {
        "question": "346×2218506=？",
        "answer": 8.885136706406255
    },
    {
        "question": "1×65759=？",
        "answer": 4.817955200246956
    },
    {
        "question": "6×251743=？",
        "answer": 6.179108653725926
    },
    {
        "question": "5610×1819=？",
        "answer": 7.008795560319645
    },
    {
        "question": "6005769÷2121=？",
        "answer": 3.452027955391249
    },
    {
        "question": "63×2620=？",
        "answer": 5.217641840773327
    },
    {
        "question": "2097297÷2443=？",
        "answer": 2.93373646865539
    },
    {
        "question": "4236062÷6503=？",
        "answer": 2.8138485539102747
    },
    {
        "question": "275×9608=？",
        "answer": 6.421965688225113
    },
    {
        "question": "4479548÷74926=？",
        "answer": 1.77660164660797
    },
    {
        "question": "1877×4467=？",
        "answer": 6.923480225093185
    },
    {
        "question": "1137×3931=？",
        "answer": 6.650263508507824
    },
    {
        "question": "3210828÷453964=？",
        "answer": 0.8495956275390528
    },
    {
        "question": "52077203÷10356477=？",
        "answer": 0.7014356057683518
    },
    {
        "question": "16907÷3071=？",
        "answer": 0.7407867362149012
    },
    {
        "question": "810559273÷304009=？",
        "answer": 3.425898337766019
    },
    {
        "question": "25×115255=？",
        "answer": 6.459599783734221
    },
    {
        "question": "2908936÷1522123=？",
        "answer": 0.28128441796246856
    },
    {
        "question": "605967922÷77186=？",
        "answer": 3.894911099489647
    },
    {
        "question": "339779÷455=？",
        "answer": 2.873185137187421
    },
    {
        "question": "13180×841=？",
        "answer": 7.044711406055903
    },
    {
        "question": "4862883÷239215=？",
        "answer": 1.3081054120065898
    },
    {
        "question": "190360146÷2718=？",
        "answer": 4.845326576820022
    },
    {
        "question": "773473465÷988354=？",
        "answer": 2.8935328950070454
    },
    {
        "question": "29663390÷1750=？",
        "answer": 4.229182733008224
    },
    {
        "question": "3×932743=？",
        "answer": 6.446883253174656
    },
    {
        "question": "2×20523129=？",
        "answer": 7.613273570614367
    },
    {
        "question": "264051÷136093=？",
        "answer": 0.2878520289040711
    },
    {
        "question": "750242÷7172=？",
        "answer": 2.019561092251225
    },
    {
        "question": "2338÷220=？",
        "answer": 1.026421826003615
    },
    {
        "question": "1×9893=？",
        "answer": 3.9953280090774097
    },
    {
        "question": "4×29497=？",
        "answer": 5.071837839519735
    },
    {
        "question": "14518446÷12870=？",
        "answer": 3.0523415866950443
    },
    {
        "question": "6564×99134=？",
        "answer": 8.813391202445993
    },
    {
        "question": "12×48579=？",
        "answer": 5.765629816645352
    },
    {
        "question": "42919÷10149=？",
        "answer": 0.6262263419712348
    },
    {
        "question": "1168494÷489=？",
        "answer": 3.3783176275887237
    },
    {
        "question": "6553×251=？",
        "answer": 6.216113889437177
    },
    {
        "question": "71093497÷327624=？",
        "answer": 2.3364541687862546
    },
    {
        "question": "118635726÷28650=？",
        "answer": 3.61709086599835
    },
    {
        "question": "63189287÷66881=？",
        "answer": 2.9753406969845533
    },
    {
        "question": "231761×2247=？",
        "answer": 8.71664342850828
    },
    {
        "question": "69×28060=？",
        "answer": 6.286936757429596
    },
    {
        "question": "2292188÷101751=？",
        "answer": 1.3527115484662946
    },
    {
        "question": "606228÷40590=？",
        "answer": 1.1742169400423697
    },
    {
        "question": "1991×474=？",
        "answer": 5.974849601701495
    },
    {
        "question": "276197510÷4802=？",
        "answer": 4.759797603249575
    },
    {
        "question": "142973×1591=？",
        "answer": 8.35692420971202
    },
    {
        "question": "92570289÷131725=？",
        "answer": 2.8468034123331067
    },
    {
        "question": "316727080÷387958=？",
        "answer": 2.9119004851196237
    },
    {
        "question": "294664÷1796=？",
        "answer": 2.2150207476775363
    },
    {
        "question": "11404903÷9606621=？",
        "answer": 0.07452093863195788
    },
    {
        "question": "15438÷2088=？",
        "answer": 0.8688605422637656
    },
    {
        "question": "1×661925=？",
        "answer": 5.820808784105292
    },
    {
        "question": "299333369÷2817331=？",
        "answer": 2.026317259720402
    },
    {
        "question": "109709÷920=？",
        "answer": 2.0764544291262323
    },
    {
        "question": "2260×113552=？",
        "answer": 8.409303227032213
    },
    {
        "question": "104×2461=？",
        "answer": 5.408144953001583
    },
    {
        "question": "43391×2703=？",
        "answer": 8.06924570480414
    },
    {
        "question": "220054÷3212=？",
        "answer": 1.8357537306896796
    },
    {
        "question": "16688640÷16194=？",
        "answer": 3.013066811411876
    },
    {
        "question": "201475829÷353194=？",
        "answer": 2.756209634165314
    },
    {
        "question": "2761×16349=？",
        "answer": 7.654557600469597
    },
    {
        "question": "196946636÷14248083=？",
        "answer": 1.1405921307470053
    },
    {
        "question": "557×118714=？",
        "answer": 7.8203571337089155
    },
    {
        "question": "2726×40562=？",
        "answer": 8.043645212211251
    },
    {
        "question": "239681025÷1828=？",
        "answer": 5.117657461893306
    },
    {
        "question": "604571÷1532=？",
        "answer": 2.59618854585147
    },
    {
        "question": "15403597÷31869=？",
        "answer": 2.6842537115768295
    },
    {
        "question": "23356÷2086=？",
        "answer": 1.0490841624887377
    },
    {
        "question": "7006÷307=？",
        "answer": 1.358331757504487
    },
    {
        "question": "62205507÷8901880=？",
        "answer": 0.8443470985428242
    },
    {
        "question": "242005359÷173764=？",
        "answer": 3.143865177799107
    },
    {
        "question": "6738768÷3712451=？",
        "answer": 0.2589197747019941
    },
    {
        "question": "184×2546687=？",
        "answer": 8.670793394386196
    },
    {
        "question": "963627÷127829=？",
        "answer": 0.877279568585791
    },
    {
        "question": "1996220÷298943=？",
        "answer": 0.824620013935546
    },
    {
        "question": "20×1152976=？",
        "answer": 7.3628502629100705
    },
    {
        "question": "145400555÷213=？",
        "answer": 5.834186460807648
    },
    {
        "question": "1773×174010=？",
        "answer": 8.489282942619303
    },
    {
        "question": "7012767÷402=？",
        "answer": 4.241663356569296
    },
    {
        "question": "1026×526=？",
        "answer": 5.732133104929536
    },
    {
        "question": "4446544÷53686=？",
        "answer": 1.9181615471076348
    },
    {
        "question": "1032×26902=？",
        "answer": 7.443464265645863
    },
    {
        "question": "5531232÷23156=？",
        "answer": 2.378158333847538
    },
    {
        "question": "385×99191=？",
        "answer": 7.581932998158087
    },
    {
        "question": "1×38289189=？",
        "answer": 7.583076167691253
    },
    {
        "question": "10×2082=？",
        "answer": 4.318480725174517
    },
    {
        "question": "41×2013897=？",
        "answer": 7.916821111678384
    },
    {
        "question": "27963÷6422=？",
        "answer": 0.6389134614638157
    },
    {
        "question": "49×186662=？",
        "answer": 6.961251994817284
    },
    {
        "question": "7306324÷3396=？",
        "answer": 3.332731245582953
    },
    {
        "question": "719313476÷311746=？",
        "answer": 3.3631173069082254
    },
    {
        "question": "159×9156=？",
        "answer": 6.163102908322957
    },
    {
        "question": "367471543÷1721=？",
        "answer": 5.329442842625745
    },
    {
        "question": "4799828÷924159=？",
        "answer": 0.7154789775948684
    },
    {
        "question": "712054÷251998=？",
        "answer": 0.45111583646623854
    },
    {
        "question": "175×274=？",
        "answer": 4.680788611506682
    },
    {
        "question": "6245529÷663=？",
        "answer": 3.9740557008627904
    },
    {
        "question": "36115÷227=？",
        "answer": 2.2016617620031878
    },
    {
        "question": "2310858÷31889=？",
        "answer": 1.8601323588078744
    },
    {
        "question": "4×460=？",
        "answer": 3.2648178230095364
    },
    {
        "question": "3136×1016=？",
        "answer": 6.5032697619603015
    },
    {
        "question": "265424971÷1180=？",
        "answer": 5.352059771272621
    },
    {
        "question": "3865041÷1649=？",
        "answer": 3.369933449590243
    },
    {
        "question": "3844×2487=？",
        "answer": 6.980459164266444
    },
    {
        "question": "21×479=？",
        "answer": 4.002554808148482
    },
    {
        "question": "805299575÷239666=？",
        "answer": 3.5263510422817466
    },
    {
        "question": "1428211÷6391=？",
        "answer": 2.349223556114507
    },
    {
        "question": "236×256388=？",
        "answer": 7.781809697546444
    },
    {
        "question": "21×804=？",
        "answer": 4.227475343482371
    },
    {
        "question": "2×218267255=？",
        "answer": 8.640018582314534
    },
    {
        "question": "18779214÷2125271=？",
        "answer": 0.9462630948326842
    },
    {
        "question": "10218283÷4734256=？",
        "answer": 0.3341261882429578
    },
    {
        "question": "5338×1262=？",
        "answer": 6.828437924359604
    },
    {
        "question": "4014×181485=？",
        "answer": 8.862418103934429
    },
    {
        "question": "66731245÷58650=？",
        "answer": 3.056061211075472
    },
    {
        "question": "17321×17070=？",
        "answer": 8.470806482811362
    },
    {
        "question": "3×635=？",
        "answer": 3.279894980011638
    },
    {
        "question": "27901780÷8460657=？",
        "answer": 0.5182278212122607
    },
    {
        "question": "8×2181678=？",
        "answer": 7.241880639228427
    },
    {
        "question": "3018834÷20993=？",
        "answer": 2.1577647268696896
    },
    {
        "question": "6131055÷2204820=？",
        "answer": 0.44416207233451704
    },
    {
        "question": "140937÷1489=？",
        "answer": 1.9761303250688416
    },
    {
        "question": "358165790÷2365=？",
        "answer": 5.180252957031749
    },
    {
        "question": "58×730672=？",
        "answer": 7.627150458676752
    },
    {
        "question": "404807912÷100841=？",
        "answer": 3.6036118484808215
    },
    {
        "question": "7120477÷327=？",
        "answer": 4.337961335292435
    },
    {
        "question": "1×370484960=？",
        "answer": 8.568770582297569
    },
    {
        "question": "96606÷32960=？",
        "answer": 0.4670168973652633
    },
    {
        "question": "89×549963=？",
        "answer": 7.68972347898215
    },
    {
        "question": "2×289566777=？",
        "answer": 8.76277872793612
    },
    {
        "question": "1280×8417=？",
        "answer": 7.032367296823767
    },
    {
        "question": "203565082÷714=？",
        "answer": 5.455005072717316
    },
    {
        "question": "855790081÷13541=？",
        "answer": 4.8007165104150795
    },
    {
        "question": "498169909÷13228862=？",
        "answer": 1.5758550052321645
    },
    {
        "question": "194872÷166930=？",
        "answer": 0.06721504902442471
    },
    {
        "question": "233620÷18198=？",
        "answer": 1.1084863589011567
    },
    {
        "question": "4512×72019=？",
        "answer": 8.511816177775936
    },
    {
        "question": "11159÷1909=？",
        "answer": 0.7668193491881169
    },
    {
        "question": "821×356=？",
        "answer": 5.465793155092316
    },
    {
        "question": "32×124925=？",
        "answer": 6.601799336434531
    },
    {
        "question": "79×5022662=？",
        "answer": 8.59856104458956
    },
    {
        "question": "640÷299=？",
        "answer": 0.3305087856594575
    },
    {
        "question": "36530466÷28909471=？",
        "answer": 0.10161506750912226
    },
    {
        "question": "16480162÷1143=？",
        "answer": 4.158915246101754
    },
    {
        "question": "1052167÷544821=？",
        "answer": 0.28583083752288085
    },
    {
        "question": "10566×199=？",
        "answer": 6.322763682760627
    },
    {
        "question": "1954×79118=？",
        "answer": 8.189199859711739
    },
    {
        "question": "57×8330=？",
        "answer": 5.676519857079279
    },
    {
        "question": "2519×270=？",
        "answer": 5.832591931657101
    },
    {
        "question": "8122×16655=？",
        "answer": 8.131207622181213
    },
    {
        "question": "4420277÷3576392=？",
        "answer": 0.09200437085409381
    },
    {
        "question": "1×4056021=？",
        "answer": 6.608100194885563
    },
    {
        "question": "20327325÷116636=？",
        "answer": 2.2412476136496906
    },
    {
        "question": "40×11005=？",
        "answer": 5.643650038217329
    },
    {
        "question": "114×1537=？",
        "answer": 5.2435787188362175
    },
    {
        "question": "2×4184=？",
        "answer": 3.922621671523199
    },
    {
        "question": "77×1679604=？",
        "answer": 8.111697625417891
    },
    {
        "question": "21×440495=？",
        "answer": 6.966160277891218
    },
    {
        "question": "4986×251=？",
        "answer": 6.097425995648793
    },
    {
        "question": "890×275973=？",
        "answer": 8.390256601302157
    },
    {
        "question": "1401675÷79127=？",
        "answer": 1.2483226271046295
    },
    {
        "question": "3127755÷4290=？",
        "answer": 2.8627754348388765
    },
    {
        "question": "4×11033=？",
        "answer": 4.644753609506606
    },
    {
        "question": "557×244917=？",
        "answer": 8.134874126276207
    },
    {
        "question": "710061÷1551=？",
        "answer": 2.6606838619271973
    },
    {
        "question": "20×475=？",
        "answer": 3.9777236052888476
    },
    {
        "question": "83296492÷2473=？",
        "answer": 4.5274025952841095
    },
    {
        "question": "1×18226=？",
        "answer": 4.260691365937476
    },
    {
        "question": "210750573÷26889364=？",
        "answer": 0.8941882338760329
    },
    {
        "question": "6643710÷212940=？",
        "answer": 1.494153417373152
    },
    {
        "question": "2×120132790=？",
        "answer": 8.38069155904045
    },
    {
        "question": "3336×49076=？",
        "answer": 8.214095199754956
    },
    {
        "question": "815×237245=？",
        "answer": 8.28635467706674
    },
    {
        "question": "2×236089657=？",
        "answer": 8.674106956879857
    },
    {
        "question": "486508894÷76321525=？",
        "answer": 0.8044437445988656
    },
    {
        "question": "3056÷815=？",
        "answer": 0.5739957411636757
    },
    {
        "question": "2×119451=？",
        "answer": 5.378219785519355
    },
    {
        "question": "7942×699=？",
        "answer": 6.744407058473546
    },
    {
        "question": "382641×257=？",
        "answer": 7.992724626188706
    },
    {
        "question": "1×913220=？",
        "answer": 5.960575414200726
    },
    {
        "question": "163×1079800=？",
        "answer": 8.245530927539182
    },
    {
        "question": "517774÷1909=？",
        "answer": 2.4333343101732634
    },
    {
        "question": "1×11080=？",
        "answer": 4.044539760392411
    },
    {
        "question": "1935÷259=？",
        "answer": 0.8733812052736784
    },
    {
        "question": "9006÷3063=？",
        "answer": 0.46838494582034135
    },
    {
        "question": "138358484÷3227831=？",
        "answer": 1.6320950065564146
    },
    {
        "question": "2087÷837=？",
        "answer": 0.396796991072194
    },
    {
        "question": "50×50884=？",
        "answer": 6.405551248282309
    },
    {
        "question": "13236×31572=？",
        "answer": 8.621058852621143
    },
    {
        "question": "96×7481=？",
        "answer": 5.856230887782922
    },
    {
        "question": "73788893÷26804=？",
        "answer": 3.439791385732142
    },
    {
        "question": "205×33676=？",
        "answer": 6.839074361903152
    },
    {
        "question": "39×6594=？",
        "answer": 5.4102135498336335
    },
    {
        "question": "79×449202=？",
        "answer": 7.550068772510828
    },
    {
        "question": "15302312÷1824936=？",
        "answer": 0.9235094141089689
    },
    {
        "question": "259672459÷10349=？",
        "answer": 4.399527503620357
    },
    {
        "question": "771×3362=？",
        "answer": 6.413652087154409
    },
    {
        "question": "5×1981=？",
        "answer": 3.995854479874566
    },
    {
        "question": "389037445÷3393=？",
        "answer": 5.0594075446991775
    },
    {
        "question": "855600÷94755=？",
        "answer": 0.9556686399494412
    },
    {
        "question": "362535409÷772541=？",
        "answer": 2.671428893301375
    },
    {
        "question": "1×202317863=？",
        "answer": 8.30603422908739
    },
    {
        "question": "2×681490=？",
        "answer": 6.134489483161625
    },
    {
        "question": "5989×361=？",
        "answer": 6.334861514989867
    },
    {
        "question": "215555÷858=？",
        "answer": 2.4000708133250783
    },
    {
        "question": "199904805÷594493=？",
        "answer": 2.526676487856577
    },
    {
        "question": "808130816÷1072=？",
        "answer": 5.877286882433215
    },
    {
        "question": "9800×19219=？",
        "answer": 8.274956862470376
    },
    {
        "question": "83×2765612=？",
        "answer": 8.360869343319767
    },
    {
        "question": "212×485357=？",
        "answer": 8.012397158491346
    },
    {
        "question": "18×1725=？",
        "answer": 4.492061604512599
    },
    {
        "question": "233128÷4830=？",
        "answer": 1.6836473071414657
    },
    {
        "question": "1673556÷751527=？",
        "answer": 0.34769566112393513
    },
    {
        "question": "37725069÷1750884=？",
        "answer": 1.3333726687316665
    },
    {
        "question": "138891÷39557=？",
        "answer": 0.5454507574825321
    },
    {
        "question": "725890÷16060=？",
        "answer": 1.6551252725776855
    },
    {
        "question": "8466×523=？",
        "answer": 6.646179953005266
    },
    {
        "question": "136×207=？",
        "answer": 4.449509253827135
    },
    {
        "question": "342008856÷37694818=？",
        "answer": 0.9577557010808083
    },
    {
        "question": "2376029÷959=？",
        "answer": 3.3940331298384567
    },
    {
        "question": "578×146092=？",
        "answer": 7.926554273033941
    },
    {
        "question": "655098136÷101432=？",
        "answer": 3.8101313748693846
    },
    {
        "question": "297046÷1260=？",
        "answer": 2.372453163456365
    },
    {
        "question": "1952÷465=？",
        "answer": 0.6230268604407191
    },
    {
        "question": "74660÷358=？",
        "answer": 2.319204958946411
    },
    {
        "question": "394389800÷6997805=？",
        "answer": 1.750963838052855
    },
    {
        "question": "131×207=？",
        "answer": 4.433241641112682
    },
    {
        "question": "1×247421060=？",
        "answer": 8.393436663169103
    },
    {
        "question": "14×15993=？",
        "answer": 5.350057972922865
    },
    {
        "question": "333871÷22228=？",
        "answer": 1.1766783098061397
    },
    {
        "question": "70664×844=？",
        "answer": 7.775540664054505
    },
    {
        "question": "21222954÷19886611=？",
        "answer": 0.028245054122027085
    },
    {
        "question": "15258÷752=？",
        "answer": 1.3072797699677103
    },
    {
        "question": "9599721÷970=？",
        "answer": 3.995486876906531
    },
    {
        "question": "50619857÷158551=？",
        "answer": 2.5041519284328038
    },
    {
        "question": "7×15314=？",
        "answer": 5.030186682772176
    },
    {
        "question": "184007674÷28220127=？",
        "answer": 0.8142769716510887
    },
    {
        "question": "148944÷949=？",
        "answer": 2.19575680053246
    },
    {
        "question": "82×5601=？",
        "answer": 5.6620794250524575
    },
    {
        "question": "189×2853=？",
        "answer": 5.73176357583032
    },
    {
        "question": "158803260÷333=？",
        "answer": 5.678415180110442
    },
    {
        "question": "869×15984=？",
        "answer": 7.142705247330573
    },
    {
        "question": "4×122761=？",
        "answer": 5.691120408825716
    },
    {
        "question": "15×7231542=？",
        "answer": 8.035322171936246
    },
    {
        "question": "118288489÷293795=？",
        "answer": 2.604898083810717
    },
    {
        "question": "151×121152=？",
        "answer": 7.262307535240853
    },
    {
        "question": "7559972÷5335=？",
        "answer": 3.151385763239658
    },
    {
        "question": "220087÷28775=？",
        "answer": 0.8835790582978426
    },
    {
        "question": "36786÷1034=？",
        "answer": 1.551162027752954
    },
    {
        "question": "54952÷19025=？",
        "answer": 0.46065883792576684
    },
    {
        "question": "690553102÷572448385=？",
        "answer": 0.08146074600992877
    },
    {
        "question": "755294÷185987=？",
        "answer": 0.6086334454657297
    },
    {
        "question": "297943÷5763=？",
        "answer": 1.7134845667994016
    },
    {
        "question": "14×1997=？",
        "answer": 4.446506100548941
    },
    {
        "question": "168349÷48493=？",
        "answer": 0.5405314886040355
    },
    {
        "question": "125672×3703=？",
        "answer": 8.667792238740512
    },
    {
        "question": "229190694÷23897=？",
        "answer": 3.981853596097116
    },
    {
        "question": "1804608÷86986=？",
        "answer": 1.3169335177783035
    },
    {
        "question": "3422274÷27564=？",
        "answer": 2.0939725365878705
    },
    {
        "question": "4221549÷732467=？",
        "answer": 0.7606837714437862
    },
    {
        "question": "2×2212228=？",
        "answer": 6.645859880520452
    },
    {
        "question": "241199483÷57931235=？",
        "answer": 0.6194635855269294
    },
    {
        "question": "1289261÷558478=？",
        "answer": 0.3633347757811764
    },
    {
        "question": "1×153933897=？",
        "answer": 8.187334264140024
    },
    {
        "question": "13167÷952=？",
        "answer": 1.1408498871801613
    },
    {
        "question": "1×63547=？",
        "answer": 4.803095052699637
    },
    {
        "question": "49447873÷1360=？",
        "answer": 4.560608706789873
    },
    {
        "question": "956×297282=？",
        "answer": 8.453626506367238
    },
    {
        "question": "10737÷1567=？",
        "answer": 0.8358139566410766
    },
    {
        "question": "1×6554=？",
        "answer": 3.816506437046357
    },
    {
        "question": "8×108714=？",
        "answer": 5.939375462368358
    },
    {
        "question": "199354420÷4221468=？",
        "answer": 1.6741623675559991
    },
    {
        "question": "39×1067=？",
        "answer": 4.619229026450969
    },
    {
        "question": "38849711÷16496934=？",
        "answer": 0.37198455556160614
    },
    {
        "question": "70447÷61324=？",
        "answer": 0.060232028349045175
    },
    {
        "question": "44×1110187=？",
        "answer": 7.688848814036776
    },
    {
        "question": "19×456647=？",
        "answer": 6.938334209793813
    },
    {
        "question": "1709÷434=？",
        "answer": 0.5952523332082261
    },
    {
        "question": "688×213146=？",
        "answer": 8.166265625116726
    },
    {
        "question": "258955÷15855=？",
        "answer": 1.2130580545920626
    },
    {
        "question": "8×1408=？",
        "answer": 4.051692641798037
    },
    {
        "question": "833714569÷3589=？",
        "answer": 5.366043932441739
    },
    {
        "question": "803×10453=？",
        "answer": 6.923956495674532
    },
    {
        "question": "10189×776=？",
        "answer": 6.897993283498851
    },
    {
        "question": "42×153218=？",
        "answer": 6.808559079463867
    },
    {
        "question": "5853×503=？",
        "answer": 6.468946509170108
    },
    {
        "question": "20086954÷2881316=？",
        "answer": 0.843323194132873
    },
    {
        "question": "8882×2077=？",
        "answer": 7.265947265372756
    },
    {
        "question": "419311310÷2192672=？",
        "answer": 2.281562905917664
    },
    {
        "question": "16714960÷939=？",
        "answer": 4.250439749368425
    },
    {
        "question": "17607032÷18964=？",
        "answer": 2.9677562068979992
    },
    {
        "question": "20×1017392=？",
        "answer": 7.3085183140099215
    },
    {
        "question": "2646×258984=？",
        "answer": 8.835862774101262
    },
    {
        "question": "4×4932839=？",
        "answer": 7.295156932341971
    },
    {
        "question": "126×61102=？",
        "answer": 6.886425970986112
    },
    {
        "question": "10375195÷8957882=？",
        "answer": 0.06379093065988779
    },
    {
        "question": "899×487503=？",
        "answer": 8.641736984340989
    },
    {
        "question": "4×21129237=？",
        "answer": 7.926943805811765
    },
    {
        "question": "259815641÷141003=？",
        "answer": 3.2654369393511056
    },
    {
        "question": "1×3526229=？",
        "answer": 6.5473105127865985
    },
    {
        "question": "20×507297=？",
        "answer": 7.006292289703644
    },
    {
        "question": "1×14808658=？",
        "answer": 7.170515703382626
    },
    {
        "question": "4451963÷318=？",
        "answer": 4.146124426297599
    },
    {
        "question": "23×1272=？",
        "answer": 4.466214947329988
    },
    {
        "question": "31169×340=？",
        "answer": 7.025201786003452
    },
    {
        "question": "1573×242=？",
        "answer": 5.580544088603718
    },
    {
        "question": "48×1597714=？",
        "answer": 7.884740278099396
    },
    {
        "question": "30×2215=？",
        "answer": 4.822494985278751
    },
    {
        "question": "7422×7406=？",
        "answer": 7.740104657726188
    },
    {
        "question": "339551436÷59273247=？",
        "answer": 0.7580468528584401
    },
    {
        "question": "31768256÷8938=？",
        "answer": 3.550753023446275
    },
    {
        "question": "24270068÷483919=？",
        "answer": 1.700298319094749
    },
    {
        "question": "355249÷3245=？",
        "answer": 2.039318162957579
    },
    {
        "question": "6030÷2781=？",
        "answer": 0.33611632327599184
    },
    {
        "question": "608÷343=？",
        "answer": 0.24860945922996447
    },
    {
        "question": "326267÷128793=？",
        "answer": 0.40368089023939213
    },
    {
        "question": "931728749÷832=？",
        "answer": 6.049166169798653
    },
    {
        "question": "295515429÷415244=？",
        "answer": 2.8522767946271066
    },
    {
        "question": "35472525÷17111433=？",
        "answer": 0.31660572232475837
    },
    {
        "question": "120547÷369=？",
        "answer": 2.514130040593751
    },
    {
        "question": "8727212÷96256=？",
        "answer": 1.957447715665549
    },
    {
        "question": "73×25115=？",
        "answer": 6.263256042616024
    },
    {
        "question": "544342÷1169=？",
        "answer": 2.6680573334703768
    },
    {
        "question": "204109014÷17499038=？",
        "answer": 1.0668480105035556
    },
    {
        "question": "287847387÷6238=？",
        "answer": 4.664116920981173
    },
    {
        "question": "8×3533338=？",
        "answer": 7.451275171133158
    },
    {
        "question": "121×2045182=？",
        "answer": 8.393517332087029
    },
    {
        "question": "149×483268=？",
        "answer": 7.8573743073261895
    },
    {
        "question": "19799×4833=？",
        "answer": 7.98086005078176
    },
    {
        "question": "2234×128434=？",
        "answer": 8.457763177385697
    },
    {
        "question": "43818×805=？",
        "answer": 7.547448431392962
    },
    {
        "question": "30×74773=？",
        "answer": 6.350866060233382
    },
    {
        "question": "191065225÷28713=？",
        "answer": 3.823103079136054
    },
    {
        "question": "1717364÷48176=？",
        "answer": 1.5520316166527721
    },
    {
        "question": "227062÷201004=？",
        "answer": 0.05293975886251922
    },
    {
        "question": "1875290÷3372=？",
        "answer": 2.745180871796888
    },
    {
        "question": "7×127316308=？",
        "answer": 8.949982076195743
    },
    {
        "question": "15224×13636=？",
        "answer": 8.317215767835817
    },
    {
        "question": "20731÷386=？",
        "answer": 1.730032946964181
    },
    {
        "question": "1×5332168=？",
        "answer": 6.726903824223358
    },
    {
        "question": "315320458÷853525=？",
        "answer": 2.567535902448924
    },
    {
        "question": "18725807÷45012=？",
        "answer": 2.619112232760329
    },
    {
        "question": "40×15225470=？",
        "answer": 8.784630699217832
    },
    {
        "question": "19×1367799=？",
        "answer": 7.414775882836578
    },
    {
        "question": "65610413÷176726=？",
        "answer": 2.569672323747889
    },
    {
        "question": "641212571÷629765300=？",
        "answer": 0.00782330074682392
    },
    {
        "question": "7×137429107=？",
        "answer": 8.983176764518936
    },
    {
        "question": "71×74453=？",
        "answer": 6.723140550568133
    },
    {
        "question": "517569×517=？",
        "answer": 8.427458799293767
    },
    {
        "question": "83038×203=？",
        "answer": 7.226772918405266
    },
    {
        "question": "304565245÷235788395=？",
        "answer": 0.11115791673233553
    },
    {
        "question": "2×8557484=？",
        "answer": 7.2333760914706
    },
    {
        "question": "2559560÷614985=？",
        "answer": 0.6193007914343892
    },
    {
        "question": "6639071÷383327=？",
        "answer": 1.2385379028584995
    },
    {
        "question": "4×31091=？",
        "answer": 5.094694682090922
    },
    {
        "question": "190443÷2219=？",
        "answer": 1.9336077119545418
    },
    {
        "question": "1×18428=？",
        "answer": 4.265478203580642
    },
    {
        "question": "3×725=？",
        "answer": 3.337459261290656
    },
    {
        "question": "4827113÷22200=？",
        "answer": 2.337334491076576
    },
    {
        "question": "2611683÷891797=？",
        "answer": 0.4666544550972583
    },
    {
        "question": "796÷735=？",
        "answer": 0.034625728653474123
    },
    {
        "question": "2333659÷2052460=？",
        "answer": 0.05576269417423982
    },
    {
        "question": "214042491÷10670=？",
        "answer": 4.302335577172549
    },
    {
        "question": "37199×6084=？",
        "answer": 8.354720470523093
    },
    {
        "question": "15×683=？",
        "answer": 4.010511962737214
    },
    {
        "question": "20095÷6119=？",
        "answer": 0.5164075573314049
    },
    {
        "question": "45×37898=？",
        "answer": 6.231828805224088
    },
    {
        "question": "22144504÷1236215=？",
        "answer": 1.2531719483215615
    },
    {
        "question": "7862471÷385=？",
        "answer": 4.310098327092589
    },
    {
        "question": "426556196÷65774861=？",
        "answer": 0.8119163157640338
    },
    {
        "question": "385901920÷75012907=？",
        "answer": 0.7113409432006472
    },
    {
        "question": "70570÷31070=？",
        "answer": 0.35627886417915944
    },
    {
        "question": "2×30293780=？",
        "answer": 7.782383462813852
    },
    {
        "question": "4×1549286=？",
        "answer": 6.792191587755101
    },
    {
        "question": "24799246÷243=？",
        "answer": 5.008832203073979
    },
    {
        "question": "7842×729=？",
        "answer": 6.757154366282163
    },
    {
        "question": "17089×10775=？",
        "answer": 8.265133928610938
    },
    {
        "question": "2×29343487=？",
        "answer": 7.768541717130166
    },
    {
        "question": "17×2959075=？",
        "answer": 7.701604894201414
    },
    {
        "question": "307×863080=？",
        "answer": 8.423189428374656
    },
    {
        "question": "7052115÷708=？",
        "answer": 3.998286128106857
    },
    {
        "question": "6270981÷138919=？",
        "answer": 1.6545738365318574
    },
    {
        "question": "3467092÷1893=？",
        "answer": 3.2628147519389863
    },
    {
        "question": "111386÷37670=？",
        "answer": 0.47083498800577955
    },
    {
        "question": "213533×248=？",
        "answer": 7.723916682484277
    },
    {
        "question": "14×17437426=？",
        "answer": 8.387610413264522
    },
    {
        "question": "79×2294=？",
        "answer": 5.25822050485569
    },
    {
        "question": "9×225731=？",
        "answer": 6.307833714970078
    },
    {
        "question": "4×7115825=？",
        "answer": 7.45428525023551
    },
    {
        "question": "10×1909=？",
        "answer": 4.280805928393667
    },
    {
        "question": "19×2016=？",
        "answer": 4.583244128726316
    },
    {
        "question": "293352405÷563291=？",
        "answer": 2.7166568407199034
    },
    {
        "question": "812922÷44796=？",
        "answer": 1.2588096409919827
    },
    {
        "question": "643112779÷558=？",
        "answer": 6.061652940398019
    },
    {
        "question": "24640207÷510656=？",
        "answer": 1.6835159129167534
    },
    {
        "question": "3×2826=？",
        "answer": 3.928293412232202
    },
    {
        "question": "567047721÷5432=？",
        "answer": 5.018659848052334
    },
    {
        "question": "1×331935=？",
        "answer": 5.521053047845363
    },
    {
        "question": "207567÷220=？",
        "answer": 2.974735627616713
    },
    {
        "question": "404752÷301110=？",
        "answer": 0.1284638245394417
    },
    {
        "question": "871907÷7661=？",
        "answer": 2.0561847020186237
    },
    {
        "question": "5×7021400=？",
        "answer": 7.5453937192656415
    },
    {
        "question": "3914×653=？",
        "answer": 6.407534002597056
    },
    {
        "question": "203363670÷1389=？",
        "answer": 5.1655711250331295
    },
    {
        "question": "203×829750=？",
        "answer": 8.226443298993855
    },
    {
        "question": "9×1972085=？",
        "answer": 7.249168139230827
    },
    {
        "question": "13759115÷12418103=？",
        "answer": 0.044535242831496395
    },
    {
        "question": "703412÷7433=？",
        "answer": 1.9760456401761675
    },
    {
        "question": "1356×4753=？",
        "answer": 6.809227503825803
    },
    {
        "question": "256621÷26273=？",
        "answer": 0.9897825271791421
    },
    {
        "question": "26056948÷45157=？",
        "answer": 2.761198464373078
    },
    {
        "question": "4879689÷2396859=？",
        "answer": 0.30874965719897596
    },
    {
        "question": "6990×532=？",
        "answer": 6.57038880804073
    },
    {
        "question": "188×311048=？",
        "answer": 7.766985262491778
    },
    {
        "question": "73×534=？",
        "answer": 4.590864117149012
    },
    {
        "question": "40×9410=？",
        "answer": 5.5756496147552195
    },
    {
        "question": "100394221÷6233648=？",
        "answer": 1.2069664391966581
    },
    {
        "question": "108614882÷42338986=？",
        "answer": 0.4091488820687422
    },
    {
        "question": "153219214÷73162109=？",
        "answer": 0.32102701398999317
    },
    {
        "question": "216138463÷439590=？",
        "answer": 2.6916842544668476
    },
    {
        "question": "1×27159751=？",
        "answer": 7.433925784024455
    },
    {
        "question": "961÷284=？",
        "answer": 0.5294050476215076
    },
    {
        "question": "2538167÷1134=？",
        "answer": 3.349907138770137
    },
    {
        "question": "66×256695=？",
        "answer": 7.2289613449474075
    },
    {
        "question": "1788575÷898=？",
        "answer": 3.299230819393425
    },
    {
        "question": "61550301÷9933239=？",
        "answer": 0.7921392961100108
    },
    {
        "question": "4104÷2534=？",
        "answer": 0.20940074155633728
    },
    {
        "question": "77×293253=？",
        "answer": 7.353733188847624
    },
    {
        "question": "2×5120054=？",
        "answer": 7.010304537065271
    },
    {
        "question": "32×11559578=？",
        "answer": 8.56809195811232
    },
    {
        "question": "337023411÷2657998=？",
        "answer": 2.1031054199348294
    },
    {
        "question": "25987453÷20054=？",
        "answer": 3.11256270628502
    },
    {
        "question": "41618÷1113=？",
        "answer": 1.5727860415304726
    },
    {
        "question": "1365×620=？",
        "answer": 5.927524340875029
    },
    {
        "question": "13×675095=？",
        "answer": 6.943308243764105
    },
    {
        "question": "4460×442=？",
        "answer": 6.294757128061233
    },
    {
        "question": "63×349=？",
        "answer": 4.342165976412762
    },
    {
        "question": "1×22393073=？",
        "answer": 7.350113695873182
    },
    {
        "question": "575741301÷1841624=？",
        "answer": 2.495026418798547
    },
    {
        "question": "769617476÷2860=？",
        "answer": 5.429908887704499
    },
    {
        "question": "18654×39801=？",
        "answer": 8.870665956285096
    },
    {
        "question": "154501÷6590=？",
        "answer": 1.370045880125267
    },
    {
        "question": "243524251÷70337=？",
        "answer": 3.539358375341224
    },
    {
        "question": "1418784÷570=？",
        "answer": 3.3960414265020322
    },
    {
        "question": "127×252=？",
        "answer": 4.505204261737501
    },
    {
        "question": "59889417÷2243=？",
        "answer": 4.426520811835265
    },
    {
        "question": "2599922÷308=？",
        "answer": 3.92640960244048
    },
    {
        "question": "14902497÷45273=？",
        "answer": 2.517419769248902
    },
    {
        "question": "32882235÷53659=？",
        "answer": 2.7873187539830333
    },
    {
        "question": "6565×21231=？",
        "answer": 8.144205180750419
    },
    {
        "question": "428129÷88253=？",
        "answer": 0.6858451690987002
    },
    {
        "question": "64×212299=？",
        "answer": 7.133127922480999
    },
    {
        "question": "6969517÷6293638=？",
        "answer": 0.04430092238508341
    },
    {
        "question": "882÷439=？",
        "answer": 0.30300406488969833
    },
    {
        "question": "38621746÷2920423=？",
        "answer": 1.1213861432389411
    },
    {
        "question": "12978911÷439058=？",
        "answer": 1.4707163595985164
    },
    {
        "question": "673554381÷14427=？",
        "answer": 4.669196633469384
    },
    {
        "question": "81×9703=？",
        "answer": 5.895391050259371
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1930=？",
        "answer": 3.285557309007774
    },
    {
        "question": "1981769÷2397=？",
        "answer": 2.917384996604005
    },
    {
        "question": "134239×904=？",
        "answer": 8.084047138738747
    },
    {
        "question": "34072705÷731092=？",
        "answer": 1.6684345815192538
    },
    {
        "question": "1×81671591=？",
        "answer": 7.912071015926331
    },
    {
        "question": "4598×1159=？",
        "answer": 6.726652402896856
    },
    {
        "question": "52×3300=？",
        "answer": 5.2345172835126865
    },
    {
        "question": "3683609÷135625=？",
        "answer": 1.4339337741990965
    },
    {
        "question": "2151190÷1280143=？",
        "answer": 0.22542028458852859
    },
    {
        "question": "22×20201=？",
        "answer": 5.647795549463503
    },
    {
        "question": "13608×4569=？",
        "answer": 7.793615458660217
    },
    {
        "question": "3×69593=？",
        "answer": 5.319686813090853
    },
    {
        "question": "73559528÷616=？",
        "answer": 5.077058221728788
    },
    {
        "question": "21×35826=？",
        "answer": 5.876417616299343
    },
    {
        "question": "981572275÷8106=？",
        "answer": 5.083115683621588
    },
    {
        "question": "870507÷203051=？",
        "answer": 0.6321671350799861
    },
    {
        "question": "2×29194795=？",
        "answer": 7.766335425733172
    },
    {
        "question": "110076×504=？",
        "answer": 7.744123176000747
    },
    {
        "question": "2775×644=？",
        "answer": 6.252148854818508
    },
    {
        "question": "5×173282=？",
        "answer": 5.93772345622086
    },
    {
        "question": "291205÷1401=？",
        "answer": 2.3177606922706344
    },
    {
        "question": "10247×266=？",
        "answer": 6.435478372837593
    },
    {
        "question": "2098×17599=？",
        "answer": 7.567293475147809
    },
    {
        "question": "14954340÷103540=？",
        "answer": 2.159659089841983
    },
    {
        "question": "141739148÷508617=？",
        "answer": 2.4450989459423123
    },
    {
        "question": "24624054÷750=？",
        "answer": 4.516298291494839
    },
    {
        "question": "264×2277=？",
        "answer": 5.778966957484974
    },
    {
        "question": "5076×230=？",
        "answer": 6.0672494494402605
    },
    {
        "question": "653581706÷206046600=？",
        "answer": 0.5013344350534287
    },
    {
        "question": "93252÷86603=？",
        "answer": 0.032125218407550976
    },
    {
        "question": "366743÷10399=？",
        "answer": 1.5473702550374429
    },
    {
        "question": "148×297677=？",
        "answer": 7.64400699559437
    },
    {
        "question": "384292÷43230=？",
        "answer": 0.9488761080979655
    },
    {
        "question": "19×46961=？",
        "answer": 5.950490937272836
    },
    {
        "question": "1180889÷547961=？",
        "answer": 0.3334594275966226
    },
    {
        "question": "119×25036=？",
        "answer": 6.47411190427379
    },
    {
        "question": "12546×9777=？",
        "answer": 8.088710898386122
    },
    {
        "question": "729841714÷1081926=？",
        "answer": 2.82903112423333
    },
    {
        "question": "143×15340=？",
        "answer": 6.341161397078024
    },
    {
        "question": "201020940÷11702144=？",
        "answer": 1.2349758614829707
    },
    {
        "question": "836690÷903=？",
        "answer": 2.9668768280772837
    },
    {
        "question": "58299782÷8636=？",
        "answer": 3.829354297145293
    },
    {
        "question": "340×1372766=？",
        "answer": 8.669075431285783
    },
    {
        "question": "775464742÷6272=？",
        "answer": 5.092156006885955
    },
    {
        "question": "1×17334=？",
        "answer": 4.2388987922278405
    },
    {
        "question": "971398977÷165560180=？",
        "answer": 0.7684417518711785
    },
    {
        "question": "1×820=？",
        "answer": 2.9138138523837167
    },
    {
        "question": "447002855÷166268938=？",
        "answer": 0.4294991741223731
    },
    {
        "question": "36911364÷53620=？",
        "answer": 2.837833284498349
    },
    {
        "question": "13953788÷1670=？",
        "answer": 3.9219756493065225
    },
    {
        "question": "414133×1289=？",
        "answer": 8.727392755793186
    },
    {
        "question": "1702×247749=？",
        "answer": 8.624971465947826
    },
    {
        "question": "17064÷1881=？",
        "answer": 0.9576920468909934
    },
    {
        "question": "369×4016=？",
        "answer": 6.170820070296023
    },
    {
        "question": "634801÷7351=？",
        "answer": 1.9362911794764663
    },
    {
        "question": "177×2500=？",
        "answer": 5.645913275033844
    },
    {
        "question": "105309÷23980=？",
        "answer": 0.6426163100229445
    },
    {
        "question": "29063453÷261349=？",
        "answer": 2.0461263684282427
    },
    {
        "question": "1×908=？",
        "answer": 2.958085848521085
    },
    {
        "question": "210857×249=？",
        "answer": 7.720187370330949
    },
    {
        "question": "2487×7964=？",
        "answer": 7.2968070366253075
    },
    {
        "question": "87243849÷127677=？",
        "answer": 2.8346221478140263
    },
    {
        "question": "215608÷63740=？",
        "answer": 0.5292528119010945
    },
    {
        "question": "2×859060=？",
        "answer": 6.235053493323989
    },
    {
        "question": "1144×228=？",
        "answer": 5.416360871457459
    },
    {
        "question": "15622390÷446628=？",
        "answer": 1.5438015290301998
    },
    {
        "question": "4767725÷3730=？",
        "answer": 3.1066023657567943
    },
    {
        "question": "2×247=？",
        "answer": 2.693726948923647
    },
    {
        "question": "211108530÷1826=？",
        "answer": 5.063005008461283
    },
    {
        "question": "3×94843=？",
        "answer": 5.454126537508306
    },
    {
        "question": "12372233÷242=？",
        "answer": 4.708632724275819
    },
    {
        "question": "769809÷6283=？",
        "answer": 2.088215924501049
    },
    {
        "question": "931822÷41437=？",
        "answer": 1.3519446544165303
    },
    {
        "question": "140275÷70825=？",
        "answer": 0.29679369418302
    },
    {
        "question": "16×6201081=？",
        "answer": 7.996587386898099
    },
    {
        "question": "465÷264=？",
        "answer": 0.24584902602012287
    },
    {
        "question": "21870÷1372=？",
        "answer": 1.2024946716669043
    },
    {
        "question": "795927564÷91989=？",
        "answer": 3.937137647414646
    },
    {
        "question": "69×510265=？",
        "answer": 7.5466448710464356
    },
    {
        "question": "1601604÷3612=？",
        "answer": 2.646807403143974
    },
    {
        "question": "6009÷2266=？",
        "answer": 0.4235422984858602
    },
    {
        "question": "36×3842713=？",
        "answer": 8.140940450370652
    },
    {
        "question": "163264349÷2080=？",
        "answer": 4.894828025996092
    },
    {
        "question": "59×4828=？",
        "answer": 5.454619273067456
    },
    {
        "question": "302×311495=？",
        "answer": 7.97345802287742
    },
    {
        "question": "7526857÷19472=？",
        "answer": 2.587203104224827
    },
    {
        "question": "54584÷6026=？",
        "answer": 0.9570362309345114
    },
    {
        "question": "80831÷333=？",
        "answer": 2.3851337181958
    },
    {
        "question": "4×39908=？",
        "answer": 5.2031199548742455
    },
    {
        "question": "16×2009051=？",
        "answer": 7.507110944161489
    },
    {
        "question": "2104×112381=？",
        "answer": 8.373738627740936
    },
    {
        "question": "285028349÷1210436=？",
        "answer": 2.371946225497297
    },
    {
        "question": "32666÷386=？",
        "answer": 1.927508653057944
    },
    {
        "question": "1436×510564=？",
        "answer": 8.865204629237546
    },
    {
        "question": "1250899÷519=？",
        "answer": 3.3820548874856926
    },
    {
        "question": "10×6117945=？",
        "answer": 7.786605568381927
    },
    {
        "question": "426545069÷375=？",
        "answer": 6.055933658007733
    },
    {
        "question": "4×81334371=？",
        "answer": 8.51233410372612
    },
    {
        "question": "28767703÷27196=？",
        "answer": 3.0244001538842458
    },
    {
        "question": "1994624÷2715=？",
        "answer": 2.866091206390982
    },
    {
        "question": "181717×1241=？",
        "answer": 8.35316733985153
    },
    {
        "question": "361×49591=？",
        "answer": 7.252910067811269
    },
    {
        "question": "3×279678=？",
        "answer": 5.923779560010107
    },
    {
        "question": "2×2905368=？",
        "answer": 6.76423114452366
    },
    {
        "question": "30×443=？",
        "answer": 4.123524980942732
    },
    {
        "question": "71824663÷70567829=？",
        "answer": 0.0076668402785872
    },
    {
        "question": "309821×2160=？",
        "answer": 8.825564602518034
    },
    {
        "question": "59×4609404=？",
        "answer": 8.4344967860026
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1327=？",
        "answer": 3.1228709228644354
    },
    {
        "question": "1167×55021=？",
        "answer": 7.807599335420286
    },
    {
        "question": "90935÷429=？",
        "answer": 2.326273778949959
    },
    {
        "question": "90469÷7081=？",
        "answer": 1.1064051954781107
    },
    {
        "question": "469×835=？",
        "answer": 5.592859318198685
    },
    {
        "question": "21895984÷189317=？",
        "answer": 2.0631748532210774
    },
    {
        "question": "30×4615=？",
        "answer": 5.141292960081593
    },
    {
        "question": "17×704=？",
        "answer": 4.078021580520386
    },
    {
        "question": "790878728÷150678=？",
        "answer": 3.720060047593012
    },
    {
        "question": "66494508÷5251337=？",
        "answer": 1.1025158873221323
    },
    {
        "question": "5×11786=？",
        "answer": 4.770336441095149
    },
    {
        "question": "169×2072=？",
        "answer": 5.544276455686869
    },
    {
        "question": "8561×591=？",
        "answer": 6.704111977931798
    },
    {
        "question": "100×2088=？",
        "answer": 5.319730494330225
    },
    {
        "question": "1608606÷489=？",
        "answer": 3.5171408251372407
    },
    {
        "question": "2×22713593=？",
        "answer": 7.65731583515222
    },
    {
        "question": "1869×635=？",
        "answer": 6.074383026670808
    },
    {
        "question": "12459÷1430=？",
        "answer": 0.9401471483644788
    },
    {
        "question": "78×8762=？",
        "answer": 5.834697851532637
    },
    {
        "question": "2425×271=？",
        "answer": 5.817681033812688
    },
    {
        "question": "281334×326=？",
        "answer": 7.962439821106556
    },
    {
        "question": "17×212=？",
        "answer": 3.5567847823070253
    },
    {
        "question": "177539÷101379=？",
        "answer": 0.24334576632090094
    },
    {
        "question": "120052×4028=？",
        "answer": 8.684458861441046
    },
    {
        "question": "73940872÷51761949=？",
        "answer": 0.15487394747178096
    },
    {
        "question": "47×1035=？",
        "answer": 4.687038207728654
    },
    {
        "question": "245015÷2267=？",
        "answer": 2.033741152882161
    },
    {
        "question": "236507693÷26507=？",
        "answer": 3.950484693725053
    },
    {
        "question": "286915358÷4895=？",
        "answer": 4.768001099636074
    },
    {
        "question": "6×1952305=？",
        "answer": 7.06869891692622
    },
    {
        "question": "188×15237=？",
        "answer": 6.45705731681194
    },
    {
        "question": "5×67536651=？",
        "answer": 8.528509525422487
    },
    {
        "question": "13453×9265=？",
        "answer": 8.095664565849427
    },
    {
        "question": "2468×6904=？",
        "answer": 7.231445938068357
    },
    {
        "question": "811×5874=？",
        "answer": 6.6779547963979375
    },
    {
        "question": "2×87565415=？",
        "answer": 8.243362605936577
    },
    {
        "question": "13×361=？",
        "answer": 3.6714505542124947
    },
    {
        "question": "1×16182=？",
        "answer": 4.209032196836535
    },
    {
        "question": "1792083÷12956=？",
        "answer": 2.140887180724152
    },
    {
        "question": "219207166÷5764=？",
        "answer": 4.580130775222331
    },
    {
        "question": "142479578÷25523=？",
        "answer": 3.7468208996764196
    },
    {
        "question": "130×6147=？",
        "answer": 5.9026065654276945
    },
    {
        "question": "63718293÷30722=？",
        "answer": 3.316814647805389
    },
    {
        "question": "14263×263=？",
        "answer": 6.574166630696732
    },
    {
        "question": "2589859÷23669=？",
        "answer": 2.0390962107243573
    },
    {
        "question": "21933889÷45769=？",
        "answer": 2.6805442176256977
    },
    {
        "question": "14081284÷1479=？",
        "answer": 3.9786740836991226
    },
    {
        "question": "132499924÷561172=？",
        "answer": 2.373119635644281
    },
    {
        "question": "2×10319=？",
        "answer": 4.314667608117513
    },
    {
        "question": "10610969÷5912902=？",
        "answer": 0.25395436464856247
    },
    {
        "question": "123×2568=？",
        "answer": 5.499500130836213
    },
    {
        "question": "999355×261=？",
        "answer": 8.416360297019908
    },
    {
        "question": "2425560÷549106=？",
        "answer": 0.6451558328377541
    },
    {
        "question": "334447÷3592=？",
        "answer": 1.9689909766758367
    },
    {
        "question": "79×3641=？",
        "answer": 5.458847770224385
    },
    {
        "question": "300074200÷16023727=？",
        "answer": 1.272465119768523
    },
    {
        "question": "34472÷955=？",
        "answer": 1.557463109496565
    },
    {
        "question": "5×59950362=？",
        "answer": 8.4767618141917
    },
    {
        "question": "67314÷2190=？",
        "answer": 1.4876612835655716
    },
    {
        "question": "2×2735843=？",
        "answer": 6.738121166858974
    },
    {
        "question": "46×637962=？",
        "answer": 7.467552642562914
    },
    {
        "question": "87493763÷21331=？",
        "answer": 3.612965879700932
    },
    {
        "question": "797322÷108675=？",
        "answer": 0.8655040986078628
    },
    {
        "question": "13×12074354=？",
        "answer": 8.195807256803658
    },
    {
        "question": "324032266÷143745662=？",
        "answer": 0.35299351059638656
    },
    {
        "question": "570025÷353=？",
        "answer": 3.208119197870554
    },
    {
        "question": "4112÷1138=？",
        "answer": 0.5579108439281669
    },
    {
        "question": "5×10696708=？",
        "answer": 7.728220144879879
    },
    {
        "question": "282×35039=？",
        "answer": 6.99480081138963
    },
    {
        "question": "206463×4276=？",
        "answer": 8.945879930080789
    },
    {
        "question": "4×384=？",
        "answer": 3.186391215695493
    },
    {
        "question": "223809×309=？",
        "answer": 7.839836026191549
    },
    {
        "question": "193568÷65720=？",
        "answer": 0.4691360080642326
    },
    {
        "question": "43×2193548=？",
        "answer": 7.974615597811341
    },
    {
        "question": "437445192÷7775872=？",
        "answer": 1.750174544543788
    },
    {
        "question": "60×16946=？",
        "answer": 6.007218452454508
    },
    {
        "question": "1×140634=？",
        "answer": 5.148090329412883
    },
    {
        "question": "7×83190=？",
        "answer": 5.765169164311781
    },
    {
        "question": "4×651784=？",
        "answer": 6.416163686522755
    },
    {
        "question": "4×5710144=？",
        "answer": 7.3587070518709785
    },
    {
        "question": "1265183÷2263=？",
        "answer": 2.7474687938038205
    },
    {
        "question": "31803919÷1643400=？",
        "answer": 1.2867373560640227
    },
    {
        "question": "787×345950=？",
        "answer": 8.434988067298578
    },
    {
        "question": "20921374÷762899=？",
        "answer": 1.4381231575615934
    },
    {
        "question": "21716642÷910=？",
        "answer": 4.377751279718363
    },
    {
        "question": "18264461÷930221=？",
        "answer": 1.2930207207263225
    },
    {
        "question": "778065750÷104832=？",
        "answer": 3.870522426938272
    },
    {
        "question": "147598×1692=？",
        "answer": 8.397480831401081
    },
    {
        "question": "561696009÷940441=？",
        "answer": 2.776169783494398
    },
    {
        "question": "506348925÷63618=？",
        "answer": 3.9008698805001183
    },
    {
        "question": "981×4892=？",
        "answer": 6.681155455744197
    },
    {
        "question": "508232280÷263911=？",
        "answer": 3.2846047531822418
    },
    {
        "question": "220×1259=？",
        "answer": 5.442448410930069
    },
    {
        "question": "27775×409=？",
        "answer": 7.055377375620247
    },
    {
        "question": "42×16294841=？",
        "answer": 8.835299417509004
    },
    {
        "question": "649×236=？",
        "answer": 5.185156699770475
    },
    {
        "question": "20805÷1619=？",
        "answer": 1.1089208713755925
    },
    {
        "question": "40×259=？",
        "answer": 4.015359755409214
    },
    {
        "question": "851572734÷76980688=？",
        "answer": 1.0438399593738381
    },
    {
        "question": "16×2518=？",
        "answer": 4.605175708427769
    },
    {
        "question": "4655283÷285=？",
        "answer": 4.213101227371692
    },
    {
        "question": "1330208÷430839=？",
        "answer": 0.48960454619591554
    },
    {
        "question": "77955175÷56151816=？",
        "answer": 0.14248114452160282
    },
    {
        "question": "6556239÷404353=？",
        "answer": 1.209894107280567
    },
    {
        "question": "34×563812=？",
        "answer": 7.282613232065462
    },
    {
        "question": "9×1083=？",
        "answer": 3.988870966064645
    },
    {
        "question": "2×93930342=？",
        "answer": 8.273835899267912
    },
    {
        "question": "1121107÷517=？",
        "answer": 3.3361565211441495
    },
    {
        "question": "417334060÷228662510=？",
        "answer": 0.2612888639751307
    },
    {
        "question": "80×1313=？",
        "answer": 5.021354713081423
    },
    {
        "question": "168398753÷1482810=？",
        "answer": 2.055253364977544
    },
    {
        "question": "5822×8550=？",
        "answer": 7.697038315830965
    },
    {
        "question": "864×6900=？",
        "answer": 6.775362833216149
    },
    {
        "question": "23999×238=？",
        "answer": 6.756770102787703
    },
    {
        "question": "28×135321=？",
        "answer": 6.578523229835026
    },
    {
        "question": "18×259=？",
        "answer": 3.668572269184558
    },
    {
        "question": "569×776=？",
        "answer": 5.64497398765326
    },
    {
        "question": "4×934583=？",
        "answer": 6.572677868301577
    },
    {
        "question": "339830÷113474=？",
        "answer": 0.4763653513244697
    },
    {
        "question": "3×12280706=？",
        "answer": 7.566344589203209
    },
    {
        "question": "343×3300=？",
        "answer": 6.053808059920658
    },
    {
        "question": "17325311÷61006=？",
        "answer": 2.4533084888071017
    },
    {
        "question": "353232÷39801=？",
        "answer": 0.9481660564433738
    },
    {
        "question": "38×9560678=？",
        "answer": 8.560272288183485
    },
    {
        "question": "432130888÷2281721=？",
        "answer": 2.277352770588167
    },
    {
        "question": "4×1779=？",
        "answer": 3.8522359394118872
    },
    {
        "question": "132563089÷35244195=？",
        "answer": 0.5753350200551299
    },
    {
        "question": "50619÷3518=？",
        "answer": 1.1580177261122566
    },
    {
        "question": "2×14707=？",
        "answer": 4.468554088084191
    },
    {
        "question": "53162969÷1171976=？",
        "answer": 1.656690508865919
    },
    {
        "question": "118948391÷860877=？",
        "answer": 2.140417466813095
    },
    {
        "question": "347×87623=？",
        "answer": 7.482947593082262
    },
    {
        "question": "28296085÷491924=？",
        "answer": 1.759828339961291
    },
    {
        "question": "4348×126997=？",
        "answer": 8.742082997324275
    },
    {
        "question": "323341790÷783945=？",
        "answer": 2.6153762436851817
    },
    {
        "question": "181706540÷888=？",
        "answer": 5.310957592981261
    },
    {
        "question": "37762917÷3479972=？",
        "answer": 1.035489784429902
    },
    {
        "question": "723539116÷8971=？",
        "answer": 4.906621158259308
    },
    {
        "question": "42×127192=？",
        "answer": 6.7277090867329665
    },
    {
        "question": "748735285÷784=？",
        "answer": 5.980012237546187
    },
    {
        "question": "99731÷12215=？",
        "answer": 0.911936702411514
    },
    {
        "question": "83×1238=？",
        "answer": 5.011798737060173
    },
    {
        "question": "39817÷6412=？",
        "answer": 0.793075021453604
    },
    {
        "question": "2×48087=？",
        "answer": 4.983057679286212
    },
    {
        "question": "320760÷949=？",
        "answer": 2.5289139923768693
    },
    {
        "question": "153188÷4103=？",
        "answer": 1.5721232291527758
    },
    {
        "question": "60×2168686=？",
        "answer": 8.114347926261779
    },
    {
        "question": "5×8662=？",
        "answer": 4.636588183729843
    },
    {
        "question": "179×196540=？",
        "answer": 7.546303982695899
    },
    {
        "question": "801565444÷268174457=？",
        "answer": 0.47552157627799946
    },
    {
        "question": "590÷245=？",
        "answer": 0.38168592727761175
    },
    {
        "question": "29015÷2999=？",
        "answer": 0.985646109141022
    },
    {
        "question": "229479÷4271=？",
        "answer": 1.730213377263847
    },
    {
        "question": "5066761÷4394=？",
        "answer": 3.0618703664428715
    },
    {
        "question": "453599÷23037=？",
        "answer": 1.2942461661358304
    },
    {
        "question": "7842761÷3223755=？",
        "answer": 0.38610695180691335
    },
    {
        "question": "144504÷76815=？",
        "answer": 0.2744338340286767
    },
    {
        "question": "532218414÷12476557=？",
        "answer": 1.6299951414045346
    },
    {
        "question": "8×1038206=？",
        "answer": 6.919373521416648
    },
    {
        "question": "72092017÷464833=？",
        "answer": 2.1905902239936186
    },
    {
        "question": "5731÷312=？",
        "answer": 1.2640758144393067
    },
    {
        "question": "19401101÷20563=？",
        "answer": 2.9747399010442144
    },
    {
        "question": "63×2797=？",
        "answer": 5.246033015825109
    },
    {
        "question": "50067317÷97624=？",
        "answer": 2.709997720850282
    },
    {
        "question": "2329574÷108359=？",
        "answer": 1.3324115221122135
    },
    {
        "question": "2×2714=？",
        "answer": 3.7346398389876994
    },
    {
        "question": "70×1841=？",
        "answer": 5.110151828518272
    },
    {
        "question": "47×504=？",
        "answer": 4.374528394381243
    },
    {
        "question": "376×229=？",
        "answer": 4.935023327267549
    },
    {
        "question": "2409593÷17588=？",
        "answer": 2.136727235925449
    },
    {
        "question": "8670÷1713=？",
        "answer": 0.7042617345106997
    },
    {
        "question": "74×1960660=？",
        "answer": 8.161634008490013
    },
    {
        "question": "7989950÷83448=？",
        "answer": 1.9811281291729392
    },
    {
        "question": "5×4216390=？",
        "answer": 7.323910778982263
    },
    {
        "question": "938004÷1595=？",
        "answer": 2.769444002983971
    },
    {
        "question": "31576775÷17560=？",
        "answer": 3.254843260991845
    },
    {
        "question": "3784913÷16183=？",
        "answer": 2.368996867130235
    },
    {
        "question": "4×10102500=？",
        "answer": 7.606488850442648
    },
    {
        "question": "277176÷2545=？",
        "answer": 2.0370678363852934
    },
    {
        "question": "4×1708096=？",
        "answer": 6.834572266989278
    },
    {
        "question": "11483319÷3436=？",
        "answer": 3.524014274284244
    },
    {
        "question": "436×21888=？",
        "answer": 6.979692569308608
    },
    {
        "question": "189177324÷17542803=？",
        "answer": 1.0327700914629767
    },
    {
        "question": "65966340÷584=？",
        "answer": 5.052909541744491
    },
    {
        "question": "31183÷6441=？",
        "answer": 0.6849645955574288
    },
    {
        "question": "9417÷315=？",
        "answer": 1.4756020166301043
    },
    {
        "question": "27×7032=？",
        "answer": 5.278442626224702
    },
    {
        "question": "70200÷12400=？",
        "answer": 0.7529154269675702
    },
    {
        "question": "4×3256=？",
        "answer": 4.114744387545126
    },
    {
        "question": "3685×931=？",
        "answer": 6.535387173176413
    },
    {
        "question": "171206÷951=？",
        "answer": 2.255338463738012
    },
    {
        "question": "2×17522=？",
        "answer": 4.544613671662172
    },
    {
        "question": "1256×259509=？",
        "answer": 8.513142063560831
    },
    {
        "question": "2464×78072=？",
        "answer": 8.284136008485847
    },
    {
        "question": "165862÷93720=？",
        "answer": 0.24791461797008682
    },
    {
        "question": "11859122÷862=？",
        "answer": 4.1385452710391055
    },
    {
        "question": "10495283÷97158=？",
        "answer": 2.0335155873457365
    },
    {
        "question": "81394359÷3263229=？",
        "answer": 1.3969467554862467
    },
    {
        "question": "392344090÷211792048=？",
        "answer": 0.26775746514022525
    },
    {
        "question": "275×126010=？",
        "answer": 7.539737705396152
    },
    {
        "question": "27138×1003=？",
        "answer": 7.434878771149981
    },
    {
        "question": "5853×8919=？",
        "answer": 7.7176946880387804
    },
    {
        "question": "5497762÷78896=？",
        "answer": 1.8431309499704507
    },
    {
        "question": "23604×32988=？",
        "answer": 8.891341591858055
    },
    {
        "question": "989926140÷1769=？",
        "answer": 5.747874959478674
    },
    {
        "question": "31×7845=？",
        "answer": 5.385954641757229
    },
    {
        "question": "286×117478=？",
        "answer": 7.526322577411902
    },
    {
        "question": "579258022÷2716920=？",
        "answer": 2.3287952061810313
    },
    {
        "question": "2448814÷826=？",
        "answer": 3.4719757521606662
    },
    {
        "question": "27×1171295=？",
        "answer": 7.500030053541494
    },
    {
        "question": "653524÷1167=？",
        "answer": 2.748190685184391
    },
    {
        "question": "1227×1939=？",
        "answer": 6.37642237180571
    },
    {
        "question": "382610×1926=？",
        "answer": 8.867412599467938
    },
    {
        "question": "17812÷2827=？",
        "answer": 0.7993868779696658
    },
    {
        "question": "95×274=？",
        "answer": 4.4154741681092355
    },
    {
        "question": "35006008÷64224=？",
        "answer": 2.73644523689504
    },
    {
        "question": "470462496÷127477=？",
        "answer": 3.5670931739750156
    },
    {
        "question": "2×168659124=？",
        "answer": 8.528039835975271
    },
    {
        "question": "1264×173590=？",
        "answer": 8.341271777103033
    },
    {
        "question": "6493×917=？",
        "answer": 6.774814738542777
    },
    {
        "question": "4866515÷1583=？",
        "answer": 3.487737151471704
    },
    {
        "question": "4028659÷116189=？",
        "answer": 1.539995494823336
    },
    {
        "question": "147075×1512=？",
        "answer": 8.347090648224672
    },
    {
        "question": "2476078÷82788=？",
        "answer": 1.4757969304669578
    },
    {
        "question": "366063÷683=？",
        "answer": 2.729135130887273
    },
    {
        "question": "207×47635=？",
        "answer": 6.993896515010528
    },
    {
        "question": "19874660÷1004=？",
        "answer": 4.296565995015766
    },
    {
        "question": "4×356=？",
        "answer": 3.1535099893008374
    },
    {
        "question": "417×513827=？",
        "answer": 8.330952976318887
    },
    {
        "question": "742676÷934=？",
        "answer": 2.9004525134375205
    },
    {
        "question": "21890465÷199055=？",
        "answer": 2.0412818960399504
    },
    {
        "question": "11457446÷950027=？",
        "answer": 1.081351870831912
    },
    {
        "question": "1717÷1236=？",
        "answer": 0.14275182440811948
    },
    {
        "question": "1×552867=？",
        "answer": 5.742620668170575
    },
    {
        "question": "6×836=？",
        "answer": 3.70035752782266
    },
    {
        "question": "186×14446=？",
        "answer": 6.429260554742189
    },
    {
        "question": "1602×2746=？",
        "answer": 6.6433630446489556
    },
    {
        "question": "39×4426=？",
        "answer": 5.237076016617738
    },
    {
        "question": "260×3082=？",
        "answer": 5.9038059823532185
    },
    {
        "question": "1742587÷5009=？",
        "answer": 2.5414434381087805
    },
    {
        "question": "18612138÷1746=？",
        "answer": 4.027752024587119
    },
    {
        "question": "160×19587=？",
        "answer": 6.49608790598005
    },
    {
        "question": "23×379054=？",
        "answer": 6.9404289199473155
    },
    {
        "question": "192×682832=？",
        "answer": 8.117615094247848
    },
    {
        "question": "92544874÷1611=？",
        "answer": 4.759256828048778
    },
    {
        "question": "556×34503=？",
        "answer": 7.282931649751038
    },
    {
        "question": "334×363=？",
        "answer": 5.083653091847677
    },
    {
        "question": "28091084÷11712764=？",
        "answer": 0.37990910561653946
    },
    {
        "question": "28967÷352=？",
        "answer": 1.915360855857123
    },
    {
        "question": "137831÷17197=？",
        "answer": 0.9038942158207854
    },
    {
        "question": "4387×205=？",
        "answer": 5.953921495460699
    },
    {
        "question": "487×15300=？",
        "answer": 6.872220392032233
    },
    {
        "question": "1×20401=？",
        "answer": 4.309651455849319
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1307490=？",
        "answer": 6.116438375962694
    },
    {
        "question": "5191×28868=？",
        "answer": 8.175667725504585
    },
    {
        "question": "541077994÷99496908=？",
        "answer": 0.7354502865765196
    },
    {
        "question": "19327066÷68207=？",
        "answer": 2.4523369816793426
    },
    {
        "question": "337511327÷131271=？",
        "answer": 3.41011955885195
    },
    {
        "question": "20659÷13907=？",
        "answer": 0.17187584099157607
    },
    {
        "question": "84×6631808=？",
        "answer": 8.7459112303611
    },
    {
        "question": "150×549894=？",
        "answer": 7.9163702400921565
    },
    {
        "question": "92484×1877=？",
        "answer": 8.23953087765498
    },
    {
        "question": "3157×6660=？",
        "answer": 7.322748811062518
    },
    {
        "question": "3424×4631=？",
        "answer": 7.200208536999009
    },
    {
        "question": "152024÷130074=？",
        "answer": 0.06772165958994404
    },
    {
        "question": "128300746÷19256=？",
        "answer": 3.823663104304694
    },
    {
        "question": "276863926÷219=？",
        "answer": 6.1018222581689265
    },
    {
        "question": "134×6815=？",
        "answer": 5.9605706585355
    },
    {
        "question": "22461153÷6467=？",
        "answer": 3.540729185220758
    },
    {
        "question": "557569÷7258=？",
        "answer": 1.8854816557749186
    },
    {
        "question": "78275×2414=？",
        "answer": 8.276360342050284
    },
    {
        "question": "3517035÷80051=？",
        "answer": 1.6428099287362665
    },
    {
        "question": "19689713÷185054=？",
        "answer": 2.0269409089039376
    },
    {
        "question": "69159689÷11034789=？",
        "answer": 0.7970889983710875
    },
    {
        "question": "203060868÷2470742=？",
        "answer": 1.9147988404389025
    },
    {
        "question": "223551519÷679=？",
        "answer": 5.5175078509013025
    },
    {
        "question": "8×1402=？",
        "answer": 4.049838000622583
    },
    {
        "question": "4201444÷2631091=？",
        "answer": 0.20326271028112622
    },
    {
        "question": "94×18089=？",
        "answer": 6.230542412361886
    },
    {
        "question": "5434×2562=？",
        "answer": 7.1436987594905395
    },
    {
        "question": "12×922=？",
        "answer": 4.043912167101254
    },
    {
        "question": "13831×11939=？",
        "answer": 8.217821533520642
    },
    {
        "question": "204362719÷2020=？",
        "answer": 5.005050302792418
    },
    {
        "question": "32918466÷14511=？",
        "answer": 3.3557422467875937
    },
    {
        "question": "811494143÷6967816=？",
        "answer": 2.066188715949569
    },
    {
        "question": "6×764=？",
        "answer": 3.6612446089593336
    },
    {
        "question": "2624÷396=？",
        "answer": 0.8212686447781103
    },
    {
        "question": "26424÷9664=？",
        "answer": 0.43684163940630116
    },
    {
        "question": "6050÷2238=？",
        "answer": 0.43189529246013764
    },
    {
        "question": "39193313÷1781=？",
        "answer": 4.342548056359983
    },
    {
        "question": "59576×4373=？",
        "answer": 8.41585081818017
    },
    {
        "question": "25×7143327=？",
        "answer": 8.251840539945263
    },
    {
        "question": "1679×4259=？",
        "answer": 6.8543583362117975
    },
    {
        "question": "41508×436=？",
        "answer": 7.2576182973305725
    },
    {
        "question": "17747×1233=？",
        "answer": 7.340088025898904
    },
    {
        "question": "3×2293=？",
        "answer": 3.8375253094496014
    },
    {
        "question": "37461×535=？",
        "answer": 7.301933148458344
    },
    {
        "question": "155849667÷566340=？",
        "answer": 2.439628642194525
    },
    {
        "question": "21×11779=？",
        "answer": 5.393327716516369
    },
    {
        "question": "10650÷1644=？",
        "answer": 0.8114477945707249
    },
    {
        "question": "53×1229901=？",
        "answer": 7.8141460242238505
    },
    {
        "question": "18385949÷237719=？",
        "answer": 1.8884221564451278
    },
    {
        "question": "23628×19169=？",
        "answer": 8.65602641957034
    },
    {
        "question": "455848÷3390=？",
        "answer": 2.1286203555012175
    },
    {
        "question": "22×12535849=？",
        "answer": 8.440576433039782
    },
    {
        "question": "1700×4726=？",
        "answer": 6.904942638674624
    },
    {
        "question": "2×160958901=？",
        "answer": 8.507744993761081
    },
    {
        "question": "2707×873=？",
        "answer": 6.373502499476076
    },
    {
        "question": "593503502÷5756958=？",
        "answer": 2.013230224813825
    },
    {
        "question": "259×1070=？",
        "answer": 5.442683541766462
    },
    {
        "question": "5×578006=？",
        "answer": 6.460902350980366
    },
    {
        "question": "10×15311=？",
        "answer": 5.1850035564918056
    },
    {
        "question": "548×44309=？",
        "answer": 7.385272507130682
    },
    {
        "question": "21×2107=？",
        "answer": 4.64588383034202
    },
    {
        "question": "2933÷486=？",
        "answer": 0.7806757937182588
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1606=？",
        "answer": 3.205745540942662
    },
    {
        "question": "12297479÷4007=？",
        "answer": 3.4869967471689147
    },
    {
        "question": "779643431÷212153768=？",
        "answer": 0.5652452744835127
    },
    {
        "question": "326312×928=？",
        "answer": 8.481181021315212
    },
    {
        "question": "83662927÷60609=？",
        "answer": 3.139995936017678
    },
    {
        "question": "21872539÷9996146=？",
        "answer": 0.34006660893086066
    },
    {
        "question": "82782÷279=？",
        "answer": 2.472331711403746
    },
    {
        "question": "86262285÷3205437=？",
        "answer": 1.4299337123467828
    },
    {
        "question": "193867110÷6365=？",
        "answer": 4.48370572828298
    },
    {
        "question": "8505965÷282225=？",
        "answer": 1.4791281096527862
    },
    {
        "question": "166×531021=？",
        "answer": 7.94521978426989
    },
    {
        "question": "13×86656=？",
        "answer": 6.051741990639849
    },
    {
        "question": "27995×1073=？",
        "answer": 7.477680193796954
    },
    {
        "question": "497×277753=？",
        "answer": 8.140015147170393
    },
    {
        "question": "486293÷6661=？",
        "answer": 1.8633585844549057
    },
    {
        "question": "105134÷583=？",
        "answer": 2.2560746334337063
    },
    {
        "question": "2×5901=？",
        "answer": 4.071955610302981
    },
    {
        "question": "583904777÷33057943=？",
        "answer": 1.247066201782028
    },
    {
        "question": "3394×131745=？",
        "answer": 8.650445979789467
    },
    {
        "question": "28297134÷8126752=？",
        "answer": 0.5418254445805142
    },
    {
        "question": "658610226÷362866681=？",
        "answer": 0.25888137714361104
    },
    {
        "question": "599140501÷62815=？",
        "answer": 3.9794653141297043
    },
    {
        "question": "2×5384=？",
        "answer": 4.032135046879902
    },
    {
        "question": "302803÷1019=？",
        "answer": 2.4729859895857818
    },
    {
        "question": "603783259÷1663=？",
        "answer": 5.559988818022189
    },
    {
        "question": "107146×1807=？",
        "answer": 8.286934115056338
    },
    {
        "question": "62×1783=？",
        "answer": 5.043543032673608
    },
    {
        "question": "3327×6529=？",
        "answer": 7.336899469473286
    },
    {
        "question": "19×7983=？",
        "answer": 5.18091973022388
    },
    {
        "question": "322409317÷57834042=？",
        "answer": 0.7462240375307996
    },
    {
        "question": "40×44118=？",
        "answer": 6.246675807683347
    },
    {
        "question": "14852÷327=？",
        "answer": 1.6572371878938352
    },
    {
        "question": "2×323483919=？",
        "answer": 8.81088269160177
    },
    {
        "question": "20596×14164=？",
        "answer": 8.464968801241271
    },
    {
        "question": "66×1312=？",
        "answer": 4.93747777058151
    },
    {
        "question": "430567÷648=？",
        "answer": 2.8224657352065115
    },
    {
        "question": "289396×1676=？",
        "answer": 8.685766538347721
    },
    {
        "question": "209550180÷10515675=？",
        "answer": 1.2994508829902818
    },
    {
        "question": "17575×14528=？",
        "answer": 8.407101164868871
    },
    {
        "question": "928259÷19049=？",
        "answer": 1.6877969868484506
    },
    {
        "question": "37×4443=？",
        "answer": 5.215878037307866
    },
    {
        "question": "2×58991330=？",
        "answer": 8.071818183410507
    },
    {
        "question": "2250×2488=？",
        "answer": 6.7480328941301435
    },
    {
        "question": "340÷199=？",
        "answer": 0.2326258406325485
    },
    {
        "question": "64189124÷231=？",
        "answer": 5.443849468941189
    },
    {
        "question": "18673÷392=？",
        "answer": 1.6779280301883759
    },
    {
        "question": "10566×6661=？",
        "answer": 7.84745004000778
    },
    {
        "question": "3630×79908=？",
        "answer": 8.462496885976282
    },
    {
        "question": "516158535÷2338=？",
        "answer": 5.343938606237512
    },
    {
        "question": "108×7645329=？",
        "answer": 8.916819934549896
    },
    {
        "question": "269807020÷3082157=？",
        "answer": 1.942198488024497
    },
    {
        "question": "924508÷50037=？",
        "answer": 1.2666194101692894
    },
    {
        "question": "171626÷210=？",
        "answer": 2.912363785988484
    },
    {
        "question": "24942296÷1163=？",
        "answer": 4.331356714134783
    },
    {
        "question": "181580×1331=？",
        "answer": 8.383246067236993
    },
    {
        "question": "80×202873=？",
        "answer": 7.21031423840543
    },
    {
        "question": "2×565=？",
        "answer": 3.0530784434834195
    },
    {
        "question": "26×3632=？",
        "answer": 4.975119187819866
    },
    {
        "question": "1379233÷3157=？",
        "answer": 2.640363057790892
    },
    {
        "question": "56×2906317=？",
        "answer": 8.211531009247071
    },
    {
        "question": "983920623÷8240916=？",
        "answer": 2.0769845761076215
    },
    {
        "question": "4362×40442=？",
        "answer": 8.246518286091566
    },
    {
        "question": "17522×31427=？",
        "answer": 8.74088660153916
    },
    {
        "question": "7340907÷617780=？",
        "answer": 1.0749158777946322
    },
    {
        "question": "167064÷334=？",
        "answer": 2.69913640866083
    },
    {
        "question": "447426451÷8660=？",
        "answer": 4.7132037631651995
    },
    {
        "question": "46965195÷16963633=？",
        "answer": 0.4422572617336262
    },
    {
        "question": "779850÷66563=？",
        "answer": 1.0687781890767143
    },
    {
        "question": "2×1193263=？",
        "answer": 6.377766170147903
    },
    {
        "question": "3228060÷305645=？",
        "answer": 1.0237243027365204
    },
    {
        "question": "5055093÷10418=？",
        "answer": 2.685944796744345
    },
    {
        "question": "2297991÷3291=？",
        "answer": 2.844020441162335
    },
    {
        "question": "44×53067=？",
        "answer": 6.368277213140021
    },
    {
        "question": "1596×476=？",
        "answer": 5.8806398397352035
    },
    {
        "question": "162×32183=？",
        "answer": 6.717141539784772
    },
    {
        "question": "432271459÷1256=？",
        "answer": 5.536766922507678
    },
    {
        "question": "307×1290=？",
        "answer": 5.597728085776436
    },
    {
        "question": "1347×112477=？",
        "answer": 8.180431319998833
    },
    {
        "question": "4277×356=？",
        "answer": 6.182589248229686
    },
    {
        "question": "9×39551152=？",
        "answer": 8.551401647082297
    },
    {
        "question": "32479398÷629=？",
        "answer": 4.712957325625685
    },
    {
        "question": "3109985÷444=？",
        "answer": 3.845375324239247
    },
    {
        "question": "4172972÷28179=？",
        "answer": 2.170519893616099
    },
    {
        "question": "4×252=？",
        "answer": 3.0034605321095067
    },
    {
        "question": "302×1626727=？",
        "answer": 8.69132161799501
    },
    {
        "question": "228×3217=？",
        "answer": 5.865385907902423
    },
    {
        "question": "39347÷17177=？",
        "answer": 0.35996430965450804
    },
    {
        "question": "2097239÷5932=？",
        "answer": 2.5484467828475146
    },
    {
        "question": "389484÷19929=？",
        "answer": 1.291004114399528
    },
    {
        "question": "1×4326769=？",
        "answer": 6.636163709457264
    },
    {
        "question": "14×27019=？",
        "answer": 5.577797306991983
    },
    {
        "question": "165041814÷1042050=？",
        "answer": 2.1997054304588386
    },
    {
        "question": "183×8421=？",
        "answer": 6.187814757084531
    },
    {
        "question": "30×161774=？",
        "answer": 6.686029978646921
    },
    {
        "question": "28×21125=？",
        "answer": 5.7719547489639496
    },
    {
        "question": "37409446÷27227=？",
        "answer": 3.1379814853878742
    },
    {
        "question": "5×18732661=？",
        "answer": 7.971569478215852
    },
    {
        "question": "65788450÷324793=？",
        "answer": 2.3065429937071062
    },
    {
        "question": "125×2321=？",
        "answer": 5.462585153463974
    },
    {
        "question": "9462178÷555200=？",
        "answer": 1.2315416561759847
    },
    {
        "question": "226514705÷2394=？",
        "answer": 4.975972254949793
    },
    {
        "question": "477192×881=？",
        "answer": 8.623669062637136
    },
    {
        "question": "8468÷277=？",
        "answer": 1.4853010802829258
    },
    {
        "question": "62×3131=？",
        "answer": 5.288074757115169
    },
    {
        "question": "4×20984465=？",
        "answer": 7.923957892656761
    },
    {
        "question": "114155÷3960=？",
        "answer": 1.4597997524574957
    },
    {
        "question": "5642÷2976=？",
        "answer": 0.27780015494550636
    },
    {
        "question": "1423÷1367=？",
        "answer": 0.017436385516462087
    },
    {
        "question": "526136977÷2972=？",
        "answer": 5.248050020074394
    },
    {
        "question": "7×221071=？",
        "answer": 6.189629815763427
    },
    {
        "question": "2712277÷14641=？",
        "answer": 2.2677633005460076
    },
    {
        "question": "9×68498=？",
        "answer": 5.789920400615777
    },
    {
        "question": "12×10383296=？",
        "answer": 8.095516480812094
    },
    {
        "question": "2×3493=？",
        "answer": 3.844228581301628
    },
    {
        "question": "39×349=？",
        "answer": 4.133890033985679
    },
    {
        "question": "208946÷204396=？",
        "answer": 0.009561669089020999
    },
    {
        "question": "40524590÷1209=？",
        "answer": 4.525292328788384
    },
    {
        "question": "16×536=？",
        "answer": 3.933284772348695
    },
    {
        "question": "79125249÷316=？",
        "answer": 5.398628007094601
    },
    {
        "question": "48924×335=？",
        "answer": 7.2145667645366265
    },
    {
        "question": "956792871÷1285277=？",
        "answer": 2.8718211948351606
    },
    {
        "question": "37×644511=？",
        "answer": 7.377432058011705
    },
    {
        "question": "128998366÷125909327=？",
        "answer": 0.010526306618142519
    },
    {
        "question": "1243÷319=？",
        "answer": 0.5906804455844636
    },
    {
        "question": "29196871÷19511=？",
        "answer": 3.175056782108461
    },
    {
        "question": "548×167870=？",
        "answer": 7.963753648913202
    },
    {
        "question": "3×3232=？",
        "answer": 3.986592606822211
    },
    {
        "question": "672788÷342867=？",
        "answer": 0.29275254919942195
    },
    {
        "question": "150×76576=？",
        "answer": 7.060183935989024
    },
    {
        "question": "22068878÷11683=？",
        "answer": 3.2762258771389576
    },
    {
        "question": "740843÷366=？",
        "answer": 3.3062450963258416
    },
    {
        "question": "17431÷3213=？",
        "answer": 0.7344115773372549
    },
    {
        "question": "1×101163548=？",
        "answer": 8.00502405248139
    },
    {
        "question": "58×744202=？",
        "answer": 7.6351188263914205
    },
    {
        "question": "180578819÷413=？",
        "answer": 5.640716756719279
    },
    {
        "question": "2×10233075=？",
        "answer": 7.311036152823072
    },
    {
        "question": "19×40499=？",
        "answer": 5.886197900714568
    },
    {
        "question": "3×252=？",
        "answer": 2.8785217955012063
    },
    {
        "question": "8×58394=？",
        "answer": 5.669458212516013
    },
    {
        "question": "16×12767=？",
        "answer": 5.310208841038367
    },
    {
        "question": "287815÷404=？",
        "answer": 2.852732059123304
    },
    {
        "question": "925328669÷1255=？",
        "answer": 5.867652292089757
    },
    {
        "question": "17×90495=？",
        "answer": 6.18707350575036
    },
    {
        "question": "100688÷20033=？",
        "answer": 0.7012317233781543
    },
    {
        "question": "18×410=？",
        "answer": 3.8680563618230415
    },
    {
        "question": "8552890÷761=？",
        "answer": 4.050728229768054
    },
    {
        "question": "314590125÷145585=？",
        "answer": 3.334628455179792
    },
    {
        "question": "280648÷153796=？",
        "answer": 0.2612169113523672
    },
    {
        "question": "392194262÷390=？",
        "answer": 6.00243662840428
    },
    {
        "question": "646789÷6743=？",
        "answer": 1.9819094655343403
    },
    {
        "question": "2×210993=？",
        "answer": 5.625298042848868
    },
    {
        "question": "17×9470=？",
        "answer": 5.206798900381547
    },
    {
        "question": "18920065÷3943=？",
        "answer": 3.681095847016485
    },
    {
        "question": "27582681÷22421=？",
        "answer": 3.089981498060876
    },
    {
        "question": "873÷269=？",
        "answer": 0.5112619637031618
    },
    {
        "question": "186863590÷2522945=？",
        "answer": 1.869616905167572
    },
    {
        "question": "32681952÷5732=？",
        "answer": 3.7560018060834044
    },
    {
        "question": "156×23162=？",
        "answer": 6.557900655631887
    },
    {
        "question": "7143447÷2449079=？",
        "answer": 0.4649050324811574
    },
    {
        "question": "238×221304=？",
        "answer": 7.721566220790494
    },
    {
        "question": "22×26980454=？",
        "answer": 8.773471934091223
    },
    {
        "question": "10×14213=？",
        "answer": 5.152685756036786
    },
    {
        "question": "258426360÷3865116=？",
        "answer": 1.8251742779673634
    },
    {
        "question": "791053916÷185161=？",
        "answer": 3.6306565671777293
    },
    {
        "question": "58862267÷6475=？",
        "answer": 3.958597211592549
    },
    {
        "question": "378×969384=？",
        "answer": 8.563987647110643
    },
    {
        "question": "7×53330=？",
        "answer": 5.572069623697134
    },
    {
        "question": "11987×4857=？",
        "answer": 7.765078608801312
    },
    {
        "question": "534735÷2492=？",
        "answer": 2.331590572912167
    },
    {
        "question": "63061×350=？",
        "answer": 7.343828897711709
    },
    {
        "question": "1×101330=？",
        "answer": 5.005738042651425
    },
    {
        "question": "361934500÷14798=？",
        "answer": 4.388426959529823
    },
    {
        "question": "2×225239277=？",
        "answer": 8.653674120284762
    },
    {
        "question": "59171÷14767=？",
        "answer": 0.6028166341099719
    },
    {
        "question": "334×440830=？",
        "answer": 8.168017608896488
    },
    {
        "question": "56206794÷48220050=？",
        "answer": 0.06656115774938597
    },
    {
        "question": "7958225÷781803=？",
        "answer": 1.007718881023213
    },
    {
        "question": "36×652565=？",
        "answer": 7.370926277674721
    },
    {
        "question": "6369043÷5073706=？",
        "answer": 0.09874888292466083
    },
    {
        "question": "102086556÷293525=？",
        "answer": 2.5413234559462694
    },
    {
        "question": "1×4876=？",
        "answer": 3.6880636969463443
    },
    {
        "question": "1832×262=？",
        "answer": 5.681226760651577
    },
    {
        "question": "2487075÷45574=？",
        "answer": 1.736971734014681
    },
    {
        "question": "31642÷25971=？",
        "answer": 0.08577525396393089
    },
    {
        "question": "256093517÷394=？",
        "answer": 5.812902362629722
    },
    {
        "question": "26540÷22133=？",
        "answer": 0.07886063450886023
    },
    {
        "question": "2618×420=？",
        "answer": 6.0412189326126375
    },
    {
        "question": "10560÷729=？",
        "answer": 1.1609363898798188
    },
    {
        "question": "15723×972=？",
        "answer": 7.18420167934853
    },
    {
        "question": "83×207=？",
        "answer": 4.235048437832992
    },
    {
        "question": "8130830÷2736225=？",
        "answer": 0.4729830743116717
    },
    {
        "question": "5877×26189=？",
        "answer": 8.187274606368598
    },
    {
        "question": "5960÷5766=？",
        "answer": 0.014371621688047481
    },
    {
        "question": "7×86988021=？",
        "answer": 8.784557490658267
    },
    {
        "question": "21347÷5048=？",
        "answer": 0.6262175038513458
    },
    {
        "question": "33775786÷4135329=？",
        "answer": 0.9120953973054028
    },
    {
        "question": "5049÷552=？",
        "answer": 0.9612662929662874
    },
    {
        "question": "293×122288=？",
        "answer": 7.554251462595008
    },
    {
        "question": "2734÷271=？",
        "answer": 1.0038292193573977
    },
    {
        "question": "378213÷723=？",
        "answer": 2.7185981551130465
    },
    {
        "question": "342245284÷1724=？",
        "answer": 5.297800210958275
    },
    {
        "question": "89669÷2110=？",
        "answer": 1.6283598711814071
    },
    {
        "question": "19332×9417=？",
        "answer": 8.260189356886547
    },
    {
        "question": "17×849367=？",
        "answer": 7.159544304950393
    },
    {
        "question": "51142×1219=？",
        "answer": 7.794781413508536
    },
    {
        "question": "60×24117=？",
        "answer": 6.160474533765624
    },
    {
        "question": "6959161÷1616=？",
        "answer": 3.6341155275636705
    },
    {
        "question": "104435468÷4956339=？",
        "answer": 1.323687013983795
    },
    {
        "question": "32860983÷494=？",
        "answer": 4.822953601809308
    },
    {
        "question": "10752769÷2049=？",
        "answer": 3.7199783576242202
    },
    {
        "question": "262÷250=？",
        "answer": 0.020361282647707864
    },
    {
        "question": "5×1788=？",
        "answer": 3.951337518795918
    },
    {
        "question": "2×43761746=？",
        "answer": 7.942124636755315
    },
    {
        "question": "124×2455013=？",
        "answer": 8.483475481341515
    },
    {
        "question": "613843827÷7311=？",
        "answer": 4.9240811088990695
    },
    {
        "question": "7774975÷1153505=？",
        "answer": 0.8286795198908111
    },
    {
        "question": "604×608272=？",
        "answer": 8.565134764083941
    },
    {
        "question": "3219×36651=？",
        "answer": 8.071806805282327
    },
    {
        "question": "314092629÷15638910=？",
        "answer": 1.3028512643265135
    },
    {
        "question": "2121÷1061=？",
        "answer": 0.3008252846152212
    },
    {
        "question": "3297×80681=？",
        "answer": 8.424890219576673
    },
    {
        "question": "3564915÷99262=？",
        "answer": 1.5552661577994893
    },
    {
        "question": "1×2150910=？",
        "answer": 6.332622238690065
    },
    {
        "question": "7×44313=？",
        "answer": 5.49162919287462
    },
    {
        "question": "6×720=？",
        "answer": 3.635483746814912
    },
    {
        "question": "1×617490=？",
        "answer": 5.7906299287657355
    },
    {
        "question": "1664306÷4764=？",
        "answer": 2.543261426051255
    },
    {
        "question": "92×6696=？",
        "answer": 5.789603272330758
    },
    {
        "question": "2352×12498=？",
        "answer": 7.46827783773549
    },
    {
        "question": "103104861÷9606=？",
        "answer": 4.030736558787658
    },
    {
        "question": "11×752=？",
        "answer": 3.9176105257498675
    },
    {
        "question": "56107÷334=？",
        "answer": 2.225270581106343
    },
    {
        "question": "83×333=？",
        "answer": 4.441522325882394
    },
    {
        "question": "1527655÷96982=？",
        "answer": 1.1973341497814292
    },
    {
        "question": "3×19998206=？",
        "answer": 7.778112292421326
    },
    {
        "question": "8640×21270=？",
        "answer": 8.264281232381622
    },
    {
        "question": "2724756÷828757=？",
        "answer": 0.5169004079394741
    },
    {
        "question": "21×44531497=？",
        "answer": 8.970886589638589
    },
    {
        "question": "37900×2229=？",
        "answer": 7.92674927844831
    },
    {
        "question": "1747÷514=？",
        "answer": 0.5313297859876552
    },
    {
        "question": "21462×3914=？",
        "answer": 7.924291011854596
    },
    {
        "question": "6×469=？",
        "answer": 3.449324093098727
    },
    {
        "question": "1×544670=？",
        "answer": 5.7361334553295675
    },
    {
        "question": "4094760÷185712=？",
        "answer": 1.3433884850972475
    },
    {
        "question": "6797199÷1099292=？",
        "answer": 0.7912169174045937
    },
    {
        "question": "1626498÷420=？",
        "answer": 3.588004243196303
    },
    {
        "question": "8776847÷28642=？",
        "answer": 2.4863351872981685
    },
    {
        "question": "100×90736=？",
        "answer": 6.957779629941924
    },
    {
        "question": "962378258÷5992925=？",
        "answer": 2.2057069602434747
    },
    {
        "question": "177713÷81253=？",
        "answer": 0.33987979348385644
    },
    {
        "question": "746921÷356=？",
        "answer": 3.3218246720106497
    },
    {
        "question": "4×2019=？",
        "answer": 3.9071963102716016
    },
    {
        "question": "13133×3905=？",
        "answer": 7.70998498247676
    },
    {
        "question": "994×15559=？",
        "answer": 7.189368065197643
    },
    {
        "question": "2271283÷20941=？",
        "answer": 2.035273833533444
    },
    {
        "question": "46×81123=？",
        "answer": 6.571901834560314
    },
    {
        "question": "27275508÷695=？",
        "answer": 4.593788043379424
    },
    {
        "question": "40464÷16755=？",
        "answer": 0.3829243798290392
    },
    {
        "question": "4142×165563=？",
        "answer": 8.836173381769374
    },
    {
        "question": "417×6236=？",
        "answer": 6.415042161490562
    },
    {
        "question": "300335110÷5073=？",
        "answer": 4.772341243068236
    },
    {
        "question": "504568330÷366465=？",
        "answer": 3.138887485119767
    },
    {
        "question": "54956÷6183=？",
        "answer": 0.9488158683614476
    },
    {
        "question": "7×250697=？",
        "answer": 6.244247176959146
    },
    {
        "question": "476×5889=？",
        "answer": 6.447648507040162
    },
    {
        "question": "32×6609140=？",
        "answer": 8.325294929854959
    },
    {
        "question": "1×7914510=？",
        "answer": 6.898424032163185
    },
    {
        "question": "6792835÷3913=？",
        "answer": 3.239541217674912
    },
    {
        "question": "32603÷3138=？",
        "answer": 1.0166046247280873
    },
    {
        "question": "6×68234=？",
        "answer": 5.612152081534697
    },
    {
        "question": "192129088÷2562091=？",
        "answer": 1.874998570351659
    },
    {
        "question": "2947999÷904492=？",
        "answer": 0.5131226018792456
    },
    {
        "question": "522391÷44683=？",
        "answer": 1.0678533623076483
    },
    {
        "question": "1×287=？",
        "answer": 2.4578818967339924
    },
    {
        "question": "3×1901085=？",
        "answer": 6.7561227898942535
    },
    {
        "question": "181011727÷11456837=？",
        "answer": 1.1986419776275377
    },
    {
        "question": "240386÷79168=？",
        "answer": 0.4823594972892608
    },
    {
        "question": "29×188149=？",
        "answer": 6.736899912313351
    },
    {
        "question": "6470×4139=？",
        "answer": 7.42779970706946
    },
    {
        "question": "371912530÷1524341=？",
        "answer": 2.387358679349388
    },
    {
        "question": "64×15209=？",
        "answer": 5.988280633877836
    },
    {
        "question": "7609÷255=？",
        "answer": 1.4747874036665962
    },
    {
        "question": "3182×27483=？",
        "answer": 7.941764313171612
    },
    {
        "question": "5291508÷6019=？",
        "answer": 2.9440551137291555
    },
    {
        "question": "19093×40273=？",
        "answer": 8.885888154658254
    },
    {
        "question": "5×284=？",
        "answer": 3.1522883443830563
    },
    {
        "question": "1637×103696=？",
        "answer": 8.229810683521018
    },
    {
        "question": "17628052÷7272262=？",
        "answer": 0.3845348059851977
    },
    {
        "question": "8378831÷1086=？",
        "answer": 3.887353605589414
    },
    {
        "question": "18950÷12350=？",
        "answer": 0.18594225670840658
    },
    {
        "question": "12145×672=？",
        "answer": 6.911766792194975
    },
    {
        "question": "52888÷3476=？",
        "answer": 1.1822773763762793
    },
    {
        "question": "311043655÷64722719=？",
        "answer": 0.6817645928782351
    },
    {
        "question": "1207×261=？",
        "answer": 5.49834777743563
    },
    {
        "question": "21648÷18108=？",
        "answer": 0.07754729343033306
    },
    {
        "question": "4251748÷2376312=？",
        "answer": 0.252664054959353
    },
    {
        "question": "2787×13993=？",
        "answer": 7.591047802845678
    },
    {
        "question": "1614459÷7468=？",
        "answer": 2.334822711088928
    },
    {
        "question": "262×256033=？",
        "answer": 7.826597236296666
    },
    {
        "question": "1080465÷817=？",
        "answer": 3.1213886466136755
    },
    {
        "question": "179697416÷372=？",
        "answer": 5.683998892235369
    },
    {
        "question": "3321÷612=？",
        "answer": 0.734517453452824
    },
    {
        "question": "280×9267=？",
        "answer": 6.4140971943633325
    },
    {
        "question": "333948392÷11218=？",
        "answer": 4.4737639209543
    },
    {
        "question": "1170109×229=？",
        "answer": 8.428061802114767
    },
    {
        "question": "823×438001=？",
        "answer": 8.55687493725515
    },
    {
        "question": "16×248108=？",
        "answer": 6.598760750555063
    },
    {
        "question": "21×37939492=？",
        "answer": 8.901310806234537
    },
    {
        "question": "74×356366=？",
        "answer": 7.42112798210828
    },
    {
        "question": "3440÷826=？",
        "answer": 0.6195783952511479
    },
    {
        "question": "236×822=？",
        "answer": 5.287783820510157
    },
    {
        "question": "1×5080=？",
        "answer": 3.7058637122839193
    },
    {
        "question": "1316×1613=？",
        "answer": 6.326890256666898
    },
    {
        "question": "35333÷14064=？",
        "answer": 0.40007165567833114
    },
    {
        "question": "6078891÷3539=？",
        "answer": 3.2349437935248613
    },
    {
        "question": "35689732÷19573=？",
        "answer": 3.260885890677852
    },
    {
        "question": "1288×601=？",
        "answer": 5.888790335026533
    },
    {
        "question": "1495×1756=？",
        "answer": 6.419165704230532
    },
    {
        "question": "924383559÷1102698=？",
        "answer": 2.923395625673799
    },
    {
        "question": "34×791=？",
        "answer": 4.429655400539931
    },
    {
        "question": "5609÷247=？",
        "answer": 1.356188486749851
    },
    {
        "question": "64746895÷1223=？",
        "answer": 4.723792489204267
    },
    {
        "question": "752071647÷992=？",
        "answer": 5.879747543988729
    },
    {
        "question": "1324978÷10108=？",
        "answer": 2.1175434340378376
    },
    {
        "question": "30×20550160=？",
        "answer": 8.789936462286816
    },
    {
        "question": "251292427÷5450=？",
        "answer": 4.663782898525768
    },
    {
        "question": "12×1183314=？",
        "answer": 7.152281248809613
    },
    {
        "question": "9770399÷289=？",
        "answer": 4.529014456884434
    },
    {
        "question": "7×1171176=？",
        "answer": 6.913720204160301
    },
    {
        "question": "24397460÷1703=？",
        "answer": 4.156129966679248
    },
    {
        "question": "17925347÷16685195=？",
        "answer": 0.031136284897875215
    },
    {
        "question": "738754940÷5131301=？",
        "answer": 2.1582729070565416
    },
    {
        "question": "136695351÷399758=？",
        "answer": 2.5339565808388724
    },
    {
        "question": "9021421÷15576=？",
        "answer": 2.76281901187395
    },
    {
        "question": "108×2035=？",
        "answer": 5.3419881690481885
    },
    {
        "question": "66925×1505=？",
        "answer": 8.003124879788832
    },
    {
        "question": "10×43400329=？",
        "answer": 8.637493021732395
    },
    {
        "question": "162766÷47483=？",
        "answer": 0.535025540664106
    },
    {
        "question": "704855353÷18006789=？",
        "answer": 1.592663726702878
    },
    {
        "question": "10336×1345=？",
        "answer": 7.143074784989436
    },
    {
        "question": "1159×30136=？",
        "answer": 7.543169043158807
    },
    {
        "question": "28779987÷32917=？",
        "answer": 2.941670345953236
    },
    {
        "question": "173×2202=？",
        "answer": 5.580863417764529
    },
    {
        "question": "47×13438238=？",
        "answer": 8.80044018639738
    },
    {
        "question": "37681811÷6578=？",
        "answer": 3.758037897808772
    },
    {
        "question": "171×1593531=？",
        "answer": 8.435356626898475
    },
    {
        "question": "22052924÷7107=？",
        "answer": 3.491779865339878
    },
    {
        "question": "181×2315=？",
        "answer": 5.622229570223157
    },
    {
        "question": "624224÷15223=？",
        "answer": 1.6128402149110102
    },
    {
        "question": "579706÷189692=？",
        "answer": 0.48515877987346995
    },
    {
        "question": "3727÷1371=？",
        "answer": 0.434321937964327
    },
    {
        "question": "7×97646=？",
        "answer": 5.834752497433232
    },
    {
        "question": "8×2048469=？",
        "answer": 7.214519383042487
    },
    {
        "question": "4×140192388=？",
        "answer": 8.748784424792102
    },
    {
        "question": "20674÷1680=？",
        "answer": 1.0901152302116535
    },
    {
        "question": "16×126718=？",
        "answer": 6.30695829245202
    },
    {
        "question": "208241716÷1505996=？",
        "answer": 2.140743915527975
    },
    {
        "question": "1134×5642=？",
        "answer": 6.806046136376235
    },
    {
        "question": "1709×57594=？",
        "answer": 7.993119304779055
    },
    {
        "question": "15647×1550=？",
        "answer": 7.384762780733993
    },
    {
        "question": "5789×14141=？",
        "answer": 7.913083671837138
    },
    {
        "question": "1×28033=？",
        "answer": 4.4476695770227925
    },
    {
        "question": "3×820090=？",
        "answer": 6.390982770955254
    },
    {
        "question": "310276÷54290=？",
        "answer": 0.7570283423375418
    },
    {
        "question": "620310×690=？",
        "answer": 8.63145787320774
    },
    {
        "question": "9746÷285=？",
        "answer": 1.5339815470367655
    },
    {
        "question": "4636×203136=？",
        "answer": 8.973930323694274
    },
    {
        "question": "7218÷3743=？",
        "answer": 0.2851970506090665
    },
    {
        "question": "5457739÷4001543=？",
        "answer": 0.1347852748788215
    },
    {
        "question": "194831÷446=？",
        "answer": 2.64032320090339
    },
    {
        "question": "40188÷31948=？",
        "answer": 0.09965271782705787
    },
    {
        "question": "12648÷1314=？",
        "answer": 0.9834264917003906
    },
    {
        "question": "1×232=？",
        "answer": 2.3654879848909
    },
    {
        "question": "540903339÷661045=？",
        "answer": 2.91288863768372
    },
    {
        "question": "282676016÷98691=？",
        "answer": 3.4570114122508877
    },
    {
        "question": "540×390=？",
        "answer": 5.323458366849468
    },
    {
        "question": "4161×446=？",
        "answer": 6.268532574505089
    },
    {
        "question": "984305÷8366=？",
        "answer": 2.0706118309638053
    },
    {
        "question": "4236026÷161555=？",
        "answer": 1.4186382134347606
    },
    {
        "question": "3642046÷174190=？",
        "answer": 1.3203222075880634
    },
    {
        "question": "13×5262835=？",
        "answer": 7.835163106570206
    },
    {
        "question": "16742401÷36966=？",
        "answer": 2.6560152803988615
    },
    {
        "question": "1×5767175=？",
        "answer": 6.760963129905994
    },
    {
        "question": "44080÷7651=？",
        "answer": 0.760523383879769
    },
    {
        "question": "86764×314=？",
        "answer": 7.435269213751508
    },
    {
        "question": "206109÷16513=？",
        "answer": 1.0962709752898308
    },
    {
        "question": "13×445=？",
        "answer": 3.7623033632877685
    },
    {
        "question": "23438100÷1867=？",
        "answer": 4.098778084919146
    },
    {
        "question": "72604÷13786=？",
        "answer": 0.7215222739534027
    },
    {
        "question": "60×654105=？",
        "answer": 7.593798719289512
    },
    {
        "question": "826×570482=？",
        "answer": 8.673221993315632
    },
    {
        "question": "2616777÷11946=？",
        "answer": 2.3405442035180926
    },
    {
        "question": "38×490295=？",
        "answer": 7.27024106097561
    },
    {
        "question": "9220÷3221=？",
        "answer": 0.45674019623393797
    },
    {
        "question": "3×110057=？",
        "answer": 5.518738925095555
    },
    {
        "question": "435020÷237=？",
        "answer": 3.2637608780479095
    },
    {
        "question": "8×87848=？",
        "answer": 5.846821865528423
    },
    {
        "question": "231356÷4817=？",
        "answer": 1.6815041206859602
    },
    {
        "question": "367894834÷14957=？",
        "answer": 4.390879195830888
    },
    {
        "question": "13×2654=？",
        "answer": 4.5378442708352535
    },
    {
        "question": "3×1870136=？",
        "answer": 6.748994445160899
    },
    {
        "question": "803444686÷198764216=？",
        "answer": 0.606617782647023
    },
    {
        "question": "8150150÷149458=？",
        "answer": 1.7366464354496727
    },
    {
        "question": "11498506÷160543=？",
        "answer": 1.855050041974297
    },
    {
        "question": "125664345÷3407=？",
        "answer": 4.566839938339981
    },
    {
        "question": "14063÷13068=？",
        "answer": 0.03186885095910622
    },
    {
        "question": "200424909÷4571=？",
        "answer": 4.641940473795079
    },
    {
        "question": "1×705839762=？",
        "answer": 8.84870611978024
    },
    {
        "question": "8888240÷360=？",
        "answer": 4.392513272130919
    },
    {
        "question": "27×819=？",
        "answer": 4.344647665919406
    },
    {
        "question": "231×2388=？",
        "answer": 5.7416463023494755
    },
    {
        "question": "17017749÷3770=？",
        "answer": 3.6545607636196813
    },
    {
        "question": "1400249÷357583=？",
        "answer": 0.5928284075430609
    },
    {
        "question": "33×64314=？",
        "answer": 6.326819461183634
    },
    {
        "question": "12747321÷7242603=？",
        "answer": 0.24552424204903417
    },
    {
        "question": "55220903÷1279325=？",
        "answer": 1.635122617404119
    },
    {
        "question": "100×22433=？",
        "answer": 6.350887356343713
    },
    {
        "question": "217824×4019=？",
        "answer": 8.942223735116539
    },
    {
        "question": "35491244÷144899=？",
        "answer": 2.3890558337668533
    },
    {
        "question": "248106460÷52908291=？",
        "answer": 0.6711143386997686
    },
    {
        "question": "66×147140=？",
        "answer": 6.987274687248349
    },
    {
        "question": "8310÷4562=？",
        "answer": 0.2604457428434812
    },
    {
        "question": "866×373=？",
        "answer": 5.509226723826035
    },
    {
        "question": "1208725÷840=？",
        "answer": 3.15804821863056
    },
    {
        "question": "331945÷25059=？",
        "answer": 1.12210239524343
    },
    {
        "question": "17×2323=？",
        "answer": 4.596498131178509
    },
    {
        "question": "1×29234852=？",
        "answer": 7.465900899584419
    },
    {
        "question": "2654335÷239997=？",
        "answer": 1.0437499207051208
    },
    {
        "question": "230805118÷46131106=？",
        "answer": 0.699251567869187
    },
    {
        "question": "3×214130171=？",
        "answer": 8.807799118537478
    },
    {
        "question": "138×256=？",
        "answer": 4.548119051713086
    },
    {
        "question": "1×458329=？",
        "answer": 5.6611773373702885
    },
    {
        "question": "1641999×354=？",
        "answer": 8.764376150317972
    },
    {
        "question": "58940876÷20409=？",
        "answer": 3.4605948605187633
    },
    {
        "question": "13×105387=？",
        "answer": 6.136730394146642
    },
    {
        "question": "42393554÷164061=？",
        "answer": 2.41229447214529
    },
    {
        "question": "144372314÷417197=？",
        "answer": 2.5391427405832965
    },
    {
        "question": "1257224×521=？",
        "answer": 8.816250386265557
    },
    {
        "question": "303×2730239=？",
        "answer": 8.917643294531329
    },
    {
        "question": "20986×3102=？",
        "answer": 7.813571462004104
    },
    {
        "question": "259169567÷287394=？",
        "answer": 2.9551063061272496
    },
    {
        "question": "332048935÷1400459=？",
        "answer": 2.3749316927488544
    },
    {
        "question": "102627×3687=？",
        "answer": 8.577934771368207
    },
    {
        "question": "11189632÷21983=？",
        "answer": 2.706728843960915
    },
    {
        "question": "45182×2727=？",
        "answer": 8.090650589177132
    },
    {
        "question": "59×286129=？",
        "answer": 7.227413888677422
    },
    {
        "question": "39967871÷339237=？",
        "answer": 2.0712078010455297
    },
    {
        "question": "144570662÷1231182=？",
        "answer": 2.069757912250239
    },
    {
        "question": "7753×1240=？",
        "answer": 6.982891469131743
    },
    {
        "question": "88×2798=？",
        "answer": 5.391330382305977
    },
    {
        "question": "10478576÷4653=？",
        "answer": 3.3525692150989945
    },
    {
        "question": "22×4131=？",
        "answer": 4.958477875798792
    },
    {
        "question": "37×29655=？",
        "answer": 6.040299652436349
    },
    {
        "question": "220×1825=？",
        "answer": 5.6036855496147
    },
    {
        "question": "143698052÷8007615=？",
        "answer": 1.2539476963629272
    },
    {
        "question": "383322795÷2115064=？",
        "answer": 2.2582411328642675
    },
    {
        "question": "43739278÷122694=？",
        "answer": 2.552048284590323
    },
    {
        "question": "5819788÷2519=？",
        "answer": 3.3636789972021037
    },
    {
        "question": "18×119580=？",
        "answer": 6.332931054187437
    },
    {
        "question": "335063248÷314679=？",
        "answer": 3.0272590327154556
    },
    {
        "question": "43488÷42100=？",
        "answer": 0.014087339216732019
    },
    {
        "question": "765188039÷5847=？",
        "answer": 5.116835078917743
    },
    {
        "question": "106×4999=？",
        "answer": 5.7241890020173605
    },
    {
        "question": "11907365÷1013=？",
        "answer": 4.070206221028478
    },
    {
        "question": "2×325424=？",
        "answer": 5.813479574637304
    },
    {
        "question": "31×2924=？",
        "answer": 4.957339062120096
    },
    {
        "question": "120×13579=？",
        "answer": 6.212049034366709
    },
    {
        "question": "8×706=？",
        "answer": 3.7518946880437474
    },
    {
        "question": "18×506738=？",
        "answer": 6.960055978116129
    },
    {
        "question": "5199×93115=？",
        "answer": 8.68493946503676
    },
    {
        "question": "883289÷886=？",
        "answer": 2.998669100116653
    },
    {
        "question": "16×433510=？",
        "answer": 6.841119102679753
    },
    {
        "question": "82448281÷35312=？",
        "answer": 3.368259289463177
    },
    {
        "question": "6815×64316=？",
        "answer": 8.641784886707937
    },
    {
        "question": "220717101÷57604=？",
        "answer": 3.5833833415698777
    },
    {
        "question": "142133856÷13017=？",
        "answer": 4.038186633477408
    },
    {
        "question": "15×3312930=？",
        "answer": 7.696303518682011
    },
    {
        "question": "777×598437=？",
        "answer": 8.66743945592849
    },
    {
        "question": "27789×990=？",
        "answer": 7.43950811336859
    },
    {
        "question": "1893223÷5913=？",
        "answer": 2.505393892896792
    },
    {
        "question": "29043×1361=？",
        "answer": 7.596899600046565
    },
    {
        "question": "179428459÷614=？",
        "answer": 5.465722956120064
    },
    {
        "question": "76804×12856=？",
        "answer": 8.994489702702037
    },
    {
        "question": "9950×381=？",
        "answer": 6.578748056421345
    },
    {
        "question": "7263÷261=？",
        "answer": 1.4444755368231144
    },
    {
        "question": "184072669÷100492=？",
        "answer": 3.262857819829944
    },
    {
        "question": "36732÷3254=？",
        "answer": 1.0526270270441196
    },
    {
        "question": "80825387÷339=？",
        "answer": 5.377348094530708
    },
    {
        "question": "4971÷1781=？",
        "answer": 0.4457798436757556
    },
    {
        "question": "104105944÷1673=？",
        "answer": 4.7939795855962135
    },
    {
        "question": "496817261÷41934629=？",
        "answer": 1.0736238710696533
    },
    {
        "question": "1365×34906=？",
        "answer": 7.678032735726375
    },
    {
        "question": "41425÷7586=？",
        "answer": 0.7372496787246026
    },
    {
        "question": "65245÷21282=？",
        "answer": 0.48653479660895527
    },
    {
        "question": "20107175÷854=？",
        "answer": 4.371893187073623
    },
    {
        "question": "131883530÷5272316=？",
        "answer": 1.3981891308567593
    },
    {
        "question": "417×1082086=？",
        "answer": 8.65439783315763
    },
    {
        "question": "75657603÷1107=？",
        "answer": 4.834704956887365
    },
    {
        "question": "278182÷148204=？",
        "answer": 0.27346909984237766
    },
    {
        "question": "422400080÷1073133=？",
        "answer": 2.595070441679645
    },
    {
        "question": "2×2701464=？",
        "answer": 6.7326291801227525
    },
    {
        "question": "3×959509=？",
        "answer": 6.4591703074044995
    },
    {
        "question": "132470×571=？",
        "answer": 7.8787536445591115
    },
    {
        "question": "2370×475=？",
        "answer": 6.051441955634971
    },
    {
        "question": "5×411=？",
        "answer": 3.312811826212088
    },
    {
        "question": "1458589×609=？",
        "answer": 8.948550226625168
    },
    {
        "question": "229×1449=？",
        "answer": 5.520903867811063
    },
    {
        "question": "181064×1556=？",
        "answer": 8.449841703069781
    },
    {
        "question": "588545÷1042=？",
        "answer": 2.751911955530358
    },
    {
        "question": "315×83901=？",
        "answer": 7.422077690922159
    },
    {
        "question": "242880920÷1141=？",
        "answer": 5.3281077548489115
    },
    {
        "question": "25621023÷8775229=？",
        "answer": 0.4653380076143261
    },
    {
        "question": "48×236209=？",
        "answer": 7.054537678391749
    },
    {
        "question": "39237×214=？",
        "answer": 6.92410956784577
    },
    {
        "question": "233010450÷1572130=？",
        "answer": 2.1708869434470475
    },
    {
        "question": "267199433÷51526900=？",
        "answer": 0.7148015173303353
    },
    {
        "question": "2937×160446=？",
        "answer": 8.673232840908005
    },
    {
        "question": "117139÷268=？",
        "answer": 2.6405667181649823
    },
    {
        "question": "34716919÷63196=？",
        "answer": 2.739851585742566
    },
    {
        "question": "633×70999=？",
        "answer": 7.652655941869665
    },
    {
        "question": "2399×4726=？",
        "answer": 7.054523965264181
    },
    {
        "question": "611008642÷4907392=？",
        "answer": 2.095196602280728
    },
    {
        "question": "76472443÷2084=？",
        "answer": 4.564607249818955
    },
    {
        "question": "358×203349=？",
        "answer": 7.862125067679786
    },
    {
        "question": "880205÷381=？",
        "answer": 3.363658855565897
    },
    {
        "question": "83537÷4798=？",
        "answer": 1.2408186310937932
    },
    {
        "question": "74×1162492=？",
        "answer": 7.9346216925894755
    },
    {
        "question": "46979308÷10212=？",
        "answer": 3.6627958092469037
    },
    {
        "question": "21383÷326=？",
        "answer": 1.8168510358864491
    },
    {
        "question": "10751×292=？",
        "answer": 6.4968317133078015
    },
    {
        "question": "331444173÷57671=？",
        "answer": 3.759452906218131
    },
    {
        "question": "285676433÷110069328=？",
        "answer": 0.4142080995403645
    },
    {
        "question": "3158÷509=？",
        "answer": 0.7926943433355167
    },
    {
        "question": "10463÷3250=？",
        "answer": 0.5077728643404744
    },
    {
        "question": "376778÷28374=？",
        "answer": 1.12316497208499
    },
    {
        "question": "1×3457=？",
        "answer": 3.5386993795424067
    },
    {
        "question": "63×47931=？",
        "answer": 6.479957039366535
    },
    {
        "question": "16816933÷305855=？",
        "answer": 1.7402312093503736
    },
    {
        "question": "1162÷712=？",
        "answer": 0.21272613441745558
    },
    {
        "question": "2040×296=？",
        "answer": 5.780921878484837
    },
    {
        "question": "5×715710=？",
        "answer": 6.553707089615462
    },
    {
        "question": "2833840÷232330=？",
        "answer": 1.0862700337007523
    },
    {
        "question": "93621489÷5153626=？",
        "answer": 1.2592626455759872
    },
    {
        "question": "1×5795556=？",
        "answer": 6.763095106589329
    },
    {
        "question": "26×5135=？",
        "answer": 5.125513795904115
    },
    {
        "question": "19×3143=？",
        "answer": 4.776097981970409
    },
    {
        "question": "1×116305=？",
        "answer": 5.065598385628987
    },
    {
        "question": "1943÷1309=？",
        "answer": 0.17153315404902675
    },
    {
        "question": "59×4704=？",
        "answer": 5.4433193247102265
    },
    {
        "question": "506980÷8474=？",
        "answer": 1.7769023673982234
    },
    {
        "question": "6593439÷3703159=？",
        "answer": 0.25053963316038896
    },
    {
        "question": "417467×2096=？",
        "answer": 8.942013429306554
    },
    {
        "question": "31×2537321=？",
        "answer": 7.895737107729214
    },
    {
        "question": "6789×34688=？",
        "answer": 8.371985069196665
    },
    {
        "question": "4×69343376=？",
        "answer": 8.443064972901004
    },
    {
        "question": "1452291÷32435=？",
        "answer": 1.651039743734086
    },
    {
        "question": "73679÷327=？",
        "answer": 2.3527959701551473
    },
    {
        "question": "231969769÷76943408=？",
        "answer": 0.4792599717163463
    },
    {
        "question": "520263586÷251735=？",
        "answer": 3.3152798281399987
    },
    {
        "question": "21×19658441=？",
        "answer": 8.615768368151517
    },
    {
        "question": "7644871÷546=？",
        "answer": 4.146177518794963
    },
    {
        "question": "1835655×335=？",
        "answer": 8.788835868610493
    },
    {
        "question": "188416÷727=？",
        "answer": 2.4135833687903108
    },
    {
        "question": "36444836÷67805=？",
        "answer": 2.7303742799620103
    },
    {
        "question": "78145231÷110357=？",
        "answer": 2.8501025934135935
    },
    {
        "question": "3833×21841=？",
        "answer": 7.922811338110292
    },
    {
        "question": "1036×3876=？",
        "answer": 6.603743523787942
    },
    {
        "question": "480653÷49636=？",
        "answer": 0.9860348814191462
    },
    {
        "question": "1014698÷2971=？",
        "answer": 2.533434152564363
    },
    {
        "question": "2×1845=？",
        "answer": 3.56702636615906
    },
    {
        "question": "13436052÷1144=？",
        "answer": 4.06984565151564
    },
    {
        "question": "1243×37485=？",
        "answer": 7.668328643823776
    },
    {
        "question": "5063979÷578=？",
        "answer": 3.9425640576008094
    },
    {
        "question": "19837÷459=？",
        "answer": 1.6356633077869505
    },
    {
        "question": "68189÷520=？",
        "answer": 2.1177109778749994
    },
    {
        "question": "336×239352=？",
        "answer": 7.905376338141736
    },
    {
        "question": "370571938÷43181915=？",
        "answer": 0.9335706305632461
    },
    {
        "question": "77×953888=？",
        "answer": 7.865988110529163
    },
    {
        "question": "1391×76175=？",
        "answer": 8.025139592886758
    },
    {
        "question": "5×841=？",
        "answer": 3.623766000133931
    },
    {
        "question": "1643×3236=？",
        "answer": 6.7256460763752965
    },
    {
        "question": "581×2206=？",
        "answer": 6.107781640494503
    },
    {
        "question": "79906÷38998=？",
        "answer": 0.3115370559982253
    },
    {
        "question": "1150274÷100488=？",
        "answer": 1.0586871008065715
    },
    {
        "question": "8×483009=？",
        "answer": 6.587045210111824
    },
    {
        "question": "47076168÷5833=？",
        "answer": 3.906909127609979
    },
    {
        "question": "6575×565=？",
        "answer": 6.569944204981234
    },
    {
        "question": "12568÷499=？",
        "answer": 1.401165626408527
    },
    {
        "question": "260×13352=？",
        "answer": 6.540519671642008
    },
    {
        "question": "10×717=？",
        "answer": 3.8555191556678
    },
    {
        "question": "5890×2298=？",
        "answer": 7.131465319139368
    },
    {
        "question": "13991161÷1829=？",
        "answer": 3.883640048684657
    },
    {
        "question": "10005277÷221=？",
        "answer": 4.65583684306585
    },
    {
        "question": "576069÷7844=？",
        "answer": 1.8659369201714535
    },
    {
        "question": "6790769÷55552=？",
        "answer": 2.0872192582638665
    },
    {
        "question": "194×2649=？",
        "answer": 5.710883688227457
    },
    {
        "question": "22512539÷1000737=？",
        "answer": 1.3521045210426301
    },
    {
        "question": "3×20020969=？",
        "answer": 7.778606347901365
    },
    {
        "question": "26537÷1302=？",
        "answer": 1.3092408402085183
    },
    {
        "question": "2243166÷2318=？",
        "answer": 2.9857479820429527
    },
    {
        "question": "1114355÷1102288=？",
        "answer": 0.004728486529416516
    },
    {
        "question": "106219×1196=？",
        "answer": 8.10393338808435
    },
    {
        "question": "78×2588597=？",
        "answer": 8.305159046211736
    },
    {
        "question": "1×6196=？",
        "answer": 3.7921114090871684
    },
    {
        "question": "44666÷410=？",
        "answer": 2.0371932048698436
    },
    {
        "question": "183864228÷327=？",
        "answer": 5.749949489936227
    },
    {
        "question": "631424846÷1622=？",
        "answer": 5.590270817114695
    },
    {
        "question": "343×1055=？",
        "answer": 5.558546579676482
    },
    {
        "question": "702601÷48118=？",
        "answer": 1.1644011957648999
    },
    {
        "question": "8×6767313=？",
        "answer": 7.733506250815325
    },
    {
        "question": "2156×14833=？",
        "answer": 7.504877753239753
    },
    {
        "question": "162×212=？",
        "answer": 4.535850875471382
    },
    {
        "question": "40×3954=？",
        "answer": 5.199096656305616
    },
    {
        "question": "3865×574=？",
        "answer": 6.346061390652317
    },
    {
        "question": "3×656140=？",
        "answer": 6.294117769004551
    },
    {
        "question": "2192923÷2269=？",
        "answer": 2.9851888866990164
    },
    {
        "question": "792848172÷277=？",
        "answer": 6.4567102601501745
    },
    {
        "question": "13134258÷915=？",
        "answer": 4.156984448940086
    },
    {
        "question": "2368÷766=？",
        "answer": 0.49015292841827823
    },
    {
        "question": "46×7709330=？",
        "answer": 8.549774467845813
    },
    {
        "question": "10846÷1438=？",
        "answer": 0.8775107140525724
    },
    {
        "question": "1×9460=？",
        "answer": 3.975891136401793
    },
    {
        "question": "1692950÷111898=？",
        "answer": 1.1798218074688802
    },
    {
        "question": "2470895÷26618=？",
        "answer": 1.9676788698446008
    },
    {
        "question": "53×231439=？",
        "answer": 7.088712413748233
    },
    {
        "question": "38×3861=？",
        "answer": 5.166483398240859
    },
    {
        "question": "142696324÷4967=？",
        "answer": 4.458318625403386
    },
    {
        "question": "678526275÷2889=？",
        "answer": 5.370819127935745
    },
    {
        "question": "74×130182=？",
        "answer": 6.9837826591007035
    },
    {
        "question": "39648÷472=？",
        "answer": 1.9242792860618816
    },
    {
        "question": "49450÷453=？",
        "answer": 2.038068093920366
    },
    {
        "question": "10×32388=？",
        "answer": 5.510384130604142
    },
    {
        "question": "963246÷3411=？",
        "answer": 2.4508554948190016
    },
    {
        "question": "278×474=？",
        "answer": 5.119823137592161
    },
    {
        "question": "59471199÷268=？",
        "answer": 5.346171900378251
    },
    {
        "question": "1×449373=？",
        "answer": 5.652606974840401
    },
    {
        "question": "4×10770212=？",
        "answer": 7.634284243328266
    },
    {
        "question": "759814518÷64919209=？",
        "answer": 1.0683343679111652
    },
    {
        "question": "173×588796=？",
        "answer": 8.008010954078095
    },
    {
        "question": "3879÷840=？",
        "answer": 0.6644404935381748
    },
    {
        "question": "433×3866=？",
        "answer": 6.2237497460458995
    },
    {
        "question": "9173682÷3152583=？",
        "answer": 0.4638771521731529
    },
    {
        "question": "879×2979=？",
        "answer": 6.418059378288816
    },
    {
        "question": "884605÷32797=？",
        "answer": 1.4309152699385408
    },
    {
        "question": "2352254÷1018=？",
        "answer": 3.363736437720718
    },
    {
        "question": "4118×7449=？",
        "answer": 7.486784316556239
    },
    {
        "question": "12991077÷1981=？",
        "answer": 3.8167606813672856
    },
    {
        "question": "1×5787=？",
        "answer": 3.762453482363547
    },
    {
        "question": "4×1699623=？",
        "answer": 6.8324125908374
    },
    {
        "question": "10933×9075=？",
        "answer": 7.996585981812899
    },
    {
        "question": "61712660÷396337=？",
        "answer": 2.1923096484637585
    },
    {
        "question": "143×4159512=？",
        "answer": 8.774378419019934
    },
    {
        "question": "465÷343=？",
        "answer": 0.13215883284718344
    },
    {
        "question": "508510÷742=？",
        "answer": 2.835895592593534
    },
    {
        "question": "2093÷533=？",
        "answer": 0.5940420193121142
    },
    {
        "question": "5743161÷341482=？",
        "answer": 1.2257831748343622
    },
    {
        "question": "609×3859=？",
        "answer": 6.371092071204272
    },
    {
        "question": "3037139÷1075036=？",
        "answer": 0.4510416607994513
    },
    {
        "question": "4×201=？",
        "answer": 2.905256048748451
    },
    {
        "question": "316×666=？",
        "answer": 5.323161311788705
    },
    {
        "question": "543869888÷2458=？",
        "answer": 5.344913135702395
    },
    {
        "question": "45139141÷4345295=？",
        "answer": 1.0165340243454422
    },
    {
        "question": "151×4341=？",
        "answer": 5.81656673313187
    },
    {
        "question": "4504097÷26221=？",
        "answer": 2.234958484367898
    },
    {
        "question": "7640680÷71576=？",
        "answer": 2.0283645870030047
    },
    {
        "question": "1×2126=？",
        "answer": 3.327563260187278
    },
    {
        "question": "1901÷549=？",
        "answer": 0.5394097724153513
    },
    {
        "question": "69798110÷77928=？",
        "answer": 2.952150132576617
    },
    {
        "question": "796×419=？",
        "answer": 5.523127090703964
    },
    {
        "question": "1×127770171=？",
        "answer": 8.106429476027714
    },
    {
        "question": "16×13728=？",
        "answer": 5.341727253160555
    },
    {
        "question": "5×7581586=？",
        "answer": 7.5787300699943
    },
    {
        "question": "29×47807=？",
        "answer": 6.141889489464975
    },
    {
        "question": "118109÷627=？",
        "answer": 2.275015451629642
    },
    {
        "question": "103852536÷1332202=？",
        "answer": 1.891847024825514
    },
    {
        "question": "29546÷486=？",
        "answer": 1.7838624242286283
    },
    {
        "question": "29437×2574=？",
        "answer": 7.879502090426983
    },
    {
        "question": "1×8397=？",
        "answer": 3.924124153185825
    },
    {
        "question": "11×4424849=？",
        "answer": 7.687291139946713
    },
    {
        "question": "546406471÷3743=？",
        "answer": 5.164296006866066
    },
    {
        "question": "3015937÷282=？",
        "answer": 4.029173156982445
    },
    {
        "question": "2×7568=？",
        "answer": 4.180011119057718
    },
    {
        "question": "116×624=？",
        "answer": 4.859642578909343
    },
    {
        "question": "47277×1091=？",
        "answer": 7.712474660830775
    },
    {
        "question": "313723549÷36357136=？",
        "answer": 0.9359574545770691
    },
    {
        "question": "105492079÷161965=？",
        "answer": 2.813798675982294
    },
    {
        "question": "3072399÷84195=？",
        "answer": 1.5621913138100256
    },
    {
        "question": "14×202701=？",
        "answer": 6.452983926913973
    },
    {
        "question": "52×4196598=？",
        "answer": 8.338900712955072
    },
    {
        "question": "197×194344=？",
        "answer": 7.583037363322781
    },
    {
        "question": "38209904÷5030396=？",
        "answer": 0.8805737718647733
    },
    {
        "question": "362524×1871=？",
        "answer": 8.831410550745067
    },
    {
        "question": "10×2073429=？",
        "answer": 7.316689168498616
    },
    {
        "question": "884399057÷454=？",
        "answer": 6.28959241797866
    },
    {
        "question": "3153110÷214=？",
        "answer": 4.1683253485435605
    },
    {
        "question": "82236×1935=？",
        "answer": 8.20174294721995
    },
    {
        "question": "455069005÷49838961=？",
        "answer": 0.9605082765320335
    },
    {
        "question": "348982×1092=？",
        "answer": 8.581025665607918
    },
    {
        "question": "28849÷525=？",
        "answer": 1.7399714602899927
    },
    {
        "question": "109496124÷242815=？",
        "answer": 2.654123234110795
    },
    {
        "question": "82173÷4155=？",
        "answer": 1.2961581145144696
    },
    {
        "question": "31066×9566=？",
        "answer": 8.473015714446191
    },
    {
        "question": "4×13625=？",
        "answer": 4.7363965022766426
    },
    {
        "question": "868×118505=？",
        "answer": 8.012256399797712
    },
    {
        "question": "4204680÷399491=？",
        "answer": 1.0222259494337531
    },
    {
        "question": "569462÷40808=？",
        "answer": 1.1447194385400552
    },
    {
        "question": "358724÷19343=？",
        "answer": 1.268236601785152
    },
    {
        "question": "20347×231=？",
        "answer": 6.672112364977178
    },
    {
        "question": "118428÷4389=？",
        "answer": 1.431088814175822
    },
    {
        "question": "6696÷4457=？",
        "answer": 0.17677281089902722
    },
    {
        "question": "1×684057=？",
        "answer": 5.835092291419058
    },
    {
        "question": "4×608092=？",
        "answer": 6.3860292812416874
    },
    {
        "question": "88690×3663=？",
        "answer": 8.511711573562243
    },
    {
        "question": "59360129÷239243=？",
        "answer": 2.394655596437903
    },
    {
        "question": "63291992÷198323=？",
        "answer": 2.503975681204328
    },
    {
        "question": "129762255÷19011961=？",
        "answer": 0.8341214693359233
    },
    {
        "question": "616275÷2700=？",
        "answer": 2.3584107862063366
    },
    {
        "question": "30454÷690=？",
        "answer": 1.6447952526630756
    },
    {
        "question": "10×74851=？",
        "answer": 5.8741976068378
    },
    {
        "question": "2×1417=？",
        "answer": 3.4523998459114416
    },
    {
        "question": "1912852÷3519=？",
        "answer": 2.7352621025283286
    },
    {
        "question": "2208×254209=？",
        "answer": 8.749189991282805
    },
    {
        "question": "10×15975=？",
        "answer": 5.203440866830438
    },
    {
        "question": "51395350÷8292838=？",
        "answer": 0.7922206463777931
    },
    {
        "question": "530634465÷78948=？",
        "answer": 3.827454321782766
    },
    {
        "question": "2×19910=？",
        "answer": 4.600101255691391
    },
    {
        "question": "5724719÷231=？",
        "answer": 4.394142194133846
    },
    {
        "question": "1002103÷746=？",
        "answer": 3.1281735348097324
    },
    {
        "question": "28×616009=？",
        "answer": 7.236745088671879
    },
    {
        "question": "4×1692347=？",
        "answer": 6.8305494072025565
    },
    {
        "question": "125133706÷71696=？",
        "answer": 3.241879380391763
    },
    {
        "question": "261×1296=？",
        "answer": 5.529245508872855
    },
    {
        "question": "248164÷2445=？",
        "answer": 2.0064599171869024
    },
    {
        "question": "176×11702=？",
        "answer": 6.313772761588849
    },
    {
        "question": "32745196÷389804=？",
        "answer": 1.9243013029438123
    },
    {
        "question": "2812×6308=？",
        "answer": 7.2489070010046515
    },
    {
        "question": "30885452÷11187113=？",
        "answer": 0.44103593662741236
    },
    {
        "question": "134×160989=？",
        "answer": 7.333901001089167
    },
    {
        "question": "281813155÷49267=？",
        "answer": 3.757405144332076
    },
    {
        "question": "102126674÷8282167=？",
        "answer": 1.0909952050130658
    },
    {
        "question": "3049442÷7916=？",
        "answer": 2.5857145920119615
    },
    {
        "question": "121853168÷181525=？",
        "answer": 2.826900379244842
    },
    {
        "question": "10065×71859=？",
        "answer": 8.859294948431966
    },
    {
        "question": "8689855÷1339302=？",
        "answer": 0.8121340124431603
    },
    {
        "question": "53338840÷1270=？",
        "answer": 4.62323984557081
    },
    {
        "question": "6240÷5065=？",
        "answer": 0.09060513998612474
    },
    {
        "question": "94215÷1488=？",
        "answer": 1.8015171212498944
    },
    {
        "question": "128303×4731=？",
        "answer": 8.783189759280964
    },
    {
        "question": "297×1979439=？",
        "answer": 8.769298572040146
    },
    {
        "question": "20630×2090=？",
        "answer": 7.634645514084205
    },
    {
        "question": "173785141÷5817520=？",
        "answer": 1.475274755577631
    },
    {
        "question": "58×250=？",
        "answer": 4.161368002234975
    },
    {
        "question": "12573688÷11920555=？",
        "answer": 0.023166203825832118
    },
    {
        "question": "61×307=？",
        "answer": 4.272468210487953
    },
    {
        "question": "26142520÷51242=？",
        "answer": 2.7077213768157136
    },
    {
        "question": "1×104171943=？",
        "answer": 8.017750764634847
    },
    {
        "question": "1604×522291=？",
        "answer": 8.92311690618565
    },
    {
        "question": "128616151÷55368500=？",
        "answer": 0.36603275052727113
    },
    {
        "question": "59350×9626=？",
        "answer": 8.75686658063195
    },
    {
        "question": "6×497=？",
        "answer": 3.474507639116976
    },
    {
        "question": "24184×972=？",
        "answer": 7.371194399096035
    },
    {
        "question": "51821614÷254=？",
        "answer": 5.309677218474832
    },
    {
        "question": "5565÷1905=？",
        "answer": 0.46557018865908906
    },
    {
        "question": "1×6774=？",
        "answer": 3.8308451923086113
    },
    {
        "question": "1912×120992=？",
        "answer": 8.364244543622522
    },
    {
        "question": "17028×1309=？",
        "answer": 7.348103288055855
    },
    {
        "question": "475839432÷7159=？",
        "answer": 4.82260806601571
    },
    {
        "question": "2011960÷18022=？",
        "answer": 2.0478163568592374
    },
    {
        "question": "184315÷48515=？",
        "answer": 0.5796846448747801
    },
    {
        "question": "1861×512=？",
        "answer": 5.979016334106598
    },
    {
        "question": "44872÷33228=？",
        "answer": 0.13047122520826102
    },
    {
        "question": "192343368÷870603=？",
        "answer": 2.3442570570718497
    },
    {
        "question": "2052597×216=？",
        "answer": 8.646757440971319
    },
    {
        "question": "3373507÷2030=？",
        "answer": 3.2205855777366064
    },
    {
        "question": "23639÷220=？",
        "answer": 2.031206419827462
    },
    {
        "question": "176×14477=？",
        "answer": 6.406191242214534
    },
    {
        "question": "1×38515368=？",
        "answer": 7.58563405173911
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1851=？",
        "answer": 3.267406418752904
    },
    {
        "question": "228703÷16332=？",
        "answer": 1.146232490228987
    },
    {
        "question": "415165÷857=？",
        "answer": 2.6852399117718018
    },
    {
        "question": "2×96086=？",
        "answer": 5.2836901100164955
    },
    {
        "question": "13603÷13328=？",
        "answer": 0.008869713996215318
    },
    {
        "question": "43345×646=？",
        "answer": 7.447171525282556
    },
    {
        "question": "28711674÷949682=？",
        "answer": 1.4804803076689412
    },
    {
        "question": "86×15340=？",
        "answer": 6.120323810856529
    },
    {
        "question": "653323031÷2357413=？",
        "answer": 2.4426922941188614
    },
    {
        "question": "76×7279=？",
        "answer": 5.742885311660785
    },
    {
        "question": "415558589÷2478198=？",
        "answer": 2.224496260833309
    },
    {
        "question": "81436028÷2599=？",
        "answer": 4.496010303520283
    },
    {
        "question": "59890675÷63391=？",
        "answer": 2.9753316049740697
    },
    {
        "question": "3838514÷91488=？",
        "answer": 1.6227989952461257
    },
    {
        "question": "534086415÷52484=？",
        "answer": 4.007584604593387
    },
    {
        "question": "3×415=？",
        "answer": 3.095169351431755
    },
    {
        "question": "13123÷3798=？",
        "answer": 0.5384781684275681
    },
    {
        "question": "222×40341=？",
        "answer": 6.9520996340462515
    },
    {
        "question": "97×174034=？",
        "answer": 7.227405836398938
    },
    {
        "question": "209×242=？",
        "answer": 4.703961652091485
    },
    {
        "question": "20×10517=？",
        "answer": 5.32292186958309
    },
    {
        "question": "6499798÷130752=？",
        "answer": 1.6964515192805942
    },
    {
        "question": "265984×240=？",
        "answer": 7.805066754580633
    },
    {
        "question": "13007×30756=？",
        "answer": 8.602106992476317
    },
    {
        "question": "3352×212751=？",
        "answer": 8.853175620047232
    },
    {
        "question": "283×439=？",
        "answer": 5.0942509557664115
    },
    {
        "question": "11×6781017=？",
        "answer": 7.872687518312249
    },
    {
        "question": "5×846240=？",
        "answer": 6.626463554010928
    },
    {
        "question": "1816×73016=？",
        "answer": 8.122533881707152
    },
    {
        "question": "670068971÷2631=？",
        "answer": 5.405998659365977
    },
    {
        "question": "25528×2046=？",
        "answer": 7.717922420561595
    },
    {
        "question": "1×296012388=？",
        "answer": 8.47130988648956
    },
    {
        "question": "2×67879989=？",
        "answer": 8.132771758931899
    },
    {
        "question": "60×297=？",
        "answer": 4.250907699700856
    },
    {
        "question": "57×1619307=？",
        "answer": 7.965204048938812
    },
    {
        "question": "1511×73475=？",
        "answer": 8.045404059083676
    },
    {
        "question": "4756113÷969=？",
        "answer": 3.690928387376432
    },
    {
        "question": "8×1270508=？",
        "answer": 7.007067391006365
    },
    {
        "question": "113848318÷7382367=？",
        "answer": 1.188130987212207
    },
    {
        "question": "1312274÷800048=？",
        "answer": 0.21490848038613036
    },
    {
        "question": "588×119222=？",
        "answer": 7.845733729106238
    },
    {
        "question": "412×194131=？",
        "answer": 7.9029921077014835
    },
    {
        "question": "5×1567=？",
        "answer": 3.894039000804609
    },
    {
        "question": "28684×2127=？",
        "answer": 7.785407203732409
    },
    {
        "question": "596086÷1677=？",
        "answer": 2.550775859266763
    },
    {
        "question": "2663×459=？",
        "answer": 6.087183851976202
    },
    {
        "question": "71430692÷6226302=？",
        "answer": 1.059654675626543
    },
    {
        "question": "4713167÷13183=？",
        "answer": 2.5532985761588756
    },
    {
        "question": "6×1336=？",
        "answer": 3.9039577085231705
    },
    {
        "question": "896515461÷233=？",
        "answer": 6.585201862631341
    },
    {
        "question": "2412×42934=？",
        "answer": 8.015178655423023
    },
    {
        "question": "2165378÷6312=？",
        "answer": 2.5353667298804967
    },
    {
        "question": "668011505÷606=？",
        "answer": 6.042311318122114
    },
    {
        "question": "139298÷1752=？",
        "answer": 1.9004107791633356
    },
    {
        "question": "18634÷2391=？",
        "answer": 0.8917265150371384
    },
    {
        "question": "3099×221=？",
        "answer": 5.8356138499243935
    },
    {
        "question": "634062÷419=？",
        "answer": 3.179917703277236
    },
    {
        "question": "20913876÷1635232=？",
        "answer": 1.106855151439683
    },
    {
        "question": "442×59349=？",
        "answer": 7.418835675063616
    },
    {
        "question": "7×40478782=？",
        "answer": 8.452325476191918
    },
    {
        "question": "27009813÷1007=？",
        "answer": 4.428492106845634
    },
    {
        "question": "3×2090=？",
        "answer": 3.7972675408307164
    },
    {
        "question": "9×64810=？",
        "answer": 5.7658845308924755
    },
    {
        "question": "434001264÷23267=？",
        "answer": 4.2707506045254195
    },
    {
        "question": "693053544÷54536=？",
        "answer": 4.104083507684092
    },
    {
        "question": "618273655÷2232=？",
        "answer": 5.442486551087149
    },
    {
        "question": "343033×227=？",
        "answer": 7.8913617586601505
    },
    {
        "question": "1323368×434=？",
        "answer": 8.759170358390856
    },
    {
        "question": "10795÷269=？",
        "answer": 1.6034703666678416
    },
    {
        "question": "864×3535=？",
        "answer": 6.484903160611812
    },
    {
        "question": "18821÷1940=？",
        "answer": 0.9868409647690993
    },
    {
        "question": "146775×260=？",
        "answer": 7.581625437020519
    },
    {
        "question": "2097÷402=？",
        "answer": 0.7173723773808738
    },
    {
        "question": "2×1390654=？",
        "answer": 6.444249084978421
    },
    {
        "question": "10×94383=？",
        "answer": 5.974893777443667
    },
    {
        "question": "3×230=？",
        "answer": 2.838849090737255
    },
    {
        "question": "975229737÷6826=？",
        "answer": 5.15494065150826
    },
    {
        "question": "3×518=？",
        "answer": 3.1914510144648953
    },
    {
        "question": "2×685046=？",
        "answer": 6.1367497304781855
    },
    {
        "question": "684810256÷15853=？",
        "answer": 4.635458796266751
    },
    {
        "question": "103471159÷17770=？",
        "answer": 3.7651318859235365
    },
    {
        "question": "11490317÷9604=？",
        "answer": 3.0778798589788114
    },
    {
        "question": "4×1016149=？",
        "answer": 6.609017385430687
    },
    {
        "question": "22212474÷1831768=？",
        "answer": 1.0837264646081408
    },
    {
        "question": "169×6133=？",
        "answer": 6.015559669301166
    },
    {
        "question": "208850401÷83376454=？",
        "answer": 0.3987918928205862
    },
    {
        "question": "52390729÷15267=？",
        "answer": 3.5355007359638764
    },
    {
        "question": "66620028÷1181343=？",
        "answer": 1.751228798641662
    },
    {
        "question": "5127×245=？",
        "answer": 6.099029401804931
    },
    {
        "question": "85970736÷744=？",
        "answer": 5.062777709226231
    },
    {
        "question": "46802397÷214=？",
        "answer": 5.339854322827818
    },
    {
        "question": "196492÷31070=？",
        "answer": 0.8010036198962576
    },
    {
        "question": "166579208÷1537015=？",
        "answer": 2.034942687026046
    },
    {
        "question": "14552×5109=？",
        "answer": 7.871258588737691
    },
    {
        "question": "21×1882=？",
        "answer": 4.596838913825158
    },
    {
        "question": "145×918=？",
        "answer": 5.1242106834362176
    },
    {
        "question": "21×4791390=？",
        "answer": 8.002680816866233
    },
    {
        "question": "12822700÷93529=？",
        "answer": 2.1370331906792357
    },
    {
        "question": "64535568÷22668799=？",
        "answer": 0.45437062510503073
    },
    {
        "question": "29×415=？",
        "answer": 4.080446094611049
    },
    {
        "question": "2×14978540=？",
        "answer": 7.476499479197999
    },
    {
        "question": "1933×469=？",
        "answer": 5.9574046967436365
    },
    {
        "question": "1×169942=？",
        "answer": 5.230300725037752
    },
    {
        "question": "24×877010=？",
        "answer": 7.3232157870959576
    },
    {
        "question": "36391÷1491=？",
        "answer": 1.3875163464150433
    },
    {
        "question": "318×781898=？",
        "answer": 8.395577222243247
    },
    {
        "question": "1×9680897=？",
        "answer": 6.985915599467685
    },
    {
        "question": "897×89091=？",
        "answer": 7.90262627673577
    },
    {
        "question": "8438586÷34400=？",
        "answer": 2.3897112381957943
    },
    {
        "question": "1×3901522=？",
        "answer": 6.5912340601690635
    },
    {
        "question": "89179246÷7786=？",
        "answer": 4.058949396738379
    },
    {
        "question": "48082536÷368=？",
        "answer": 5.116139546763781
    },
    {
        "question": "968865198÷22176879=？",
        "answer": 1.6403629292514863
    },
    {
        "question": "413419710÷3695749=？",
        "answer": 2.0486887099374043
    },
    {
        "question": "850755636÷340056732=？",
        "answer": 0.3982534579841326
    },
    {
        "question": "6254656÷1956=？",
        "answer": 3.5048345784603416
    },
    {
        "question": "1×26579009=？",
        "answer": 7.42453878421187
    },
    {
        "question": "2×4128871=？",
        "answer": 6.916861309911087
    },
    {
        "question": "1×347439=？",
        "answer": 5.540878566368256
    },
    {
        "question": "84×9121=？",
        "answer": 5.884321741788723
    },
    {
        "question": "194310077÷32560=？",
        "answer": 3.7758109276559675
    },
    {
        "question": "2×52786609=？",
        "answer": 8.023553759580267
    },
    {
        "question": "13×56681448=？",
        "answer": 8.867384288631328
    },
    {
        "question": "17903346÷209=？",
        "answer": 4.932787918809436
    },
    {
        "question": "399282160÷3201705=？",
        "answer": 2.0958985920461823
    },
    {
        "question": "1195÷1141=？",
        "answer": 0.020082260865941882
    },
    {
        "question": "145042716÷93828=？",
        "answer": 3.1891634643752744
    },
    {
        "question": "643229×490=？",
        "answer": 8.49856169639089
    },
    {
        "question": "181162233÷23492=？",
        "answer": 3.8871476729731493
    },
    {
        "question": "881448623÷644=？",
        "answer": 6.136311136288739
    },
    {
        "question": "264725÷204141=？",
        "answer": 0.11286471911283028
    },
    {
        "question": "17049252÷10049=？",
        "answer": 3.2295824837662015
    },
    {
        "question": "32597×330=？",
        "answer": 7.03169157235693
    },
    {
        "question": "83723863÷483=？",
        "answer": 5.238902127626067
    },
    {
        "question": "38588460÷28546=？",
        "answer": 3.130912185504561
    },
    {
        "question": "91373×205=？",
        "answer": 7.272571745156066
    },
    {
        "question": "10853×2230=？",
        "answer": 7.383854666058218
    },
    {
        "question": "718237643÷1208=？",
        "answer": 5.774201228575075
    },
    {
        "question": "8422×3430=？",
        "answer": 7.460709357127016
    },
    {
        "question": "452×845553=？",
        "answer": 8.582279269555485
    },
    {
        "question": "269412÷1099=？",
        "answer": 2.3894192434984296
    },
    {
        "question": "24191751÷16684=？",
        "answer": 3.1613671225794238
    },
    {
        "question": "49605576÷5260=？",
        "answer": 3.9745447526977986
    },
    {
        "question": "60693701÷92922=？",
        "answer": 2.815025072111468
    },
    {
        "question": "4042919÷12888=？",
        "answer": 2.496509512907072
    },
    {
        "question": "7×548578=？",
        "answer": 6.584336426822351
    },
    {
        "question": "49×568378=？",
        "answer": 7.444833339531113
    },
    {
        "question": "395600100÷541137=？",
        "answer": 2.8639491630678533
    },
    {
        "question": "3795×482=？",
        "answer": 6.2622588184703485
    },
    {
        "question": "3606×261=？",
        "answer": 5.973666229724664
    },
    {
        "question": "3648÷2010=？",
        "answer": 0.2588587722358897
    },
    {
        "question": "449276045÷1082=？",
        "answer": 5.618286002243435
    },
    {
        "question": "1470×288720=？",
        "answer": 8.627794203799628
    },
    {
        "question": "5321786÷42487=？",
        "answer": 2.0978013399779196
    },
    {
        "question": "1111×8423=？",
        "answer": 6.971180859632406
    },
    {
        "question": "3×248102=？",
        "answer": 5.871751519940936
    },
    {
        "question": "87690÷12801=？",
        "answer": 0.8357061724981244
    },
    {
        "question": "1×14173=？",
        "answer": 4.151461787124331
    },
    {
        "question": "6076×140414=？",
        "answer": 8.93102817654313
    },
    {
        "question": "780268÷89760=？",
        "answer": 0.939160952278863
    },
    {
        "question": "227×60220=？",
        "answer": 7.135766608369863
    },
    {
        "question": "212439777÷1796=？",
        "answer": 5.072929504533116
    },
    {
        "question": "2×68959159=？",
        "answer": 8.139621952020567
    },
    {
        "question": "25716×12647=？",
        "answer": 8.512190935647753
    },
    {
        "question": "1077÷1048=？",
        "answer": 0.011854420650273752
    },
    {
        "question": "2×14430530=？",
        "answer": 7.460312277682523
    },
    {
        "question": "56557×364=？",
        "answer": 7.313587748405366
    },
    {
        "question": "3710588÷523009=？",
        "answer": 0.8509335734175278
    },
    {
        "question": "1621×1026=？",
        "answer": 6.220930375624312
    },
    {
        "question": "57879×3302=？",
        "answer": 8.281298087948867
    },
    {
        "question": "3010×1023=？",
        "answer": 6.488442129306003
    },
    {
        "question": "2785×114969=？",
        "answer": 8.505405953395005
    },
    {
        "question": "1849×445810=？",
        "answer": 8.916086717107138
    },
    {
        "question": "141518860÷4736=？",
        "answer": 4.475402627757582
    },
    {
        "question": "292×216=？",
        "answer": 4.799836602599349
    },
    {
        "question": "882135013÷260162029=？",
        "answer": 0.5302911491067158
    },
    {
        "question": "23452×1423=？",
        "answer": 7.523384785597044
    },
    {
        "question": "630×3220=？",
        "answer": 6.3071964211494125
    },
    {
        "question": "70262450÷264=？",
        "answer": 5.425119362379652
    },
    {
        "question": "43610×1360=？",
        "answer": 7.773124995043644
    },
    {
        "question": "89961419÷65623=？",
        "answer": 3.1370002165595596
    },
    {
        "question": "1909560÷2210=？",
        "answer": 2.936541035140766
    },
    {
        "question": "18983178÷198288=？",
        "answer": 1.9810724876636245
    },
    {
        "question": "226234÷4818=？",
        "answer": 1.6716910785909502
    },
    {
        "question": "436548×281=？",
        "answer": 8.08873832278982
    },
    {
        "question": "5462408÷68130=？",
        "answer": 1.9040457465441052
    },
    {
        "question": "257300×871=？",
        "answer": 8.35045794121801
    },
    {
        "question": "4031÷246=？",
        "answer": 1.214477691049672
    },
    {
        "question": "59628×1066=？",
        "answer": 7.803207447483711
    },
    {
        "question": "468979×1549=？",
        "answer": 8.86120481401734
    },
    {
        "question": "2405051÷941=？",
        "answer": 3.4075346667560806
    },
    {
        "question": "454526824÷368=？",
        "answer": 6.091711699624681
    },
    {
        "question": "3×12857187=？",
        "answer": 7.586267215219892
    },
    {
        "question": "795109÷462911=？",
        "answer": 0.23492916845223058
    },
    {
        "question": "1×347818=？",
        "answer": 5.541352053510263
    },
    {
        "question": "7×4523=？",
        "answer": 4.500524627760176
    },
    {
        "question": "946×1016=？",
        "answer": 5.982784844349693
    },
    {
        "question": "3233068÷12913=？",
        "answer": 2.3985876880469337
    },
    {
        "question": "666428÷835=？",
        "answer": 2.902066760199092
    },
    {
        "question": "159×64966=？",
        "answer": 7.014083252107736
    },
    {
        "question": "4×50474258=？",
        "answer": 8.305129934617257
    },
    {
        "question": "98×766168=？",
        "answer": 7.875550084846159
    },
    {
        "question": "805×228=？",
        "answer": 5.263730727368323
    },
    {
        "question": "143628888÷21897=？",
        "answer": 3.8168571797341446
    },
    {
        "question": "21186×28215=？",
        "answer": 8.7765290225528
    },
    {
        "question": "16×68809=？",
        "answer": 6.04176522895403
    },
    {
        "question": "2×9717402=？",
        "answer": 7.288580165129483
    },
    {
        "question": "1998×29300=？",
        "answer": 7.767463104244073
    },
    {
        "question": "31×7276=？",
        "answer": 5.3532543842257185
    },
    {
        "question": "48846×1418=？",
        "answer": 7.840505235973397
    },
    {
        "question": "870417939÷37686399=？",
        "answer": 1.3635431912489282
    },
    {
        "question": "50×1356=？",
        "answer": 4.831229693867063
    },
    {
        "question": "6953957÷239=？",
        "answer": 4.463834099934555
    },
    {
        "question": "236872×1264=？",
        "answer": 8.476260800924177
    },
    {
        "question": "392711×1852=？",
        "answer": 8.861714048557495
    },
    {
        "question": "2796278÷7655=？",
        "answer": 2.5626351508176968
    },
    {
        "question": "1400430÷39413=？",
        "answer": 1.5506219123211473
    },
    {
        "question": "61×768=？",
        "answer": 4.670691055042279
    },
    {
        "question": "14644354÷3429=？",
        "answer": 3.630502733482175
    },
    {
        "question": "9868×16274=？",
        "answer": 8.205723452477294
    },
    {
        "question": "23×16864=？",
        "answer": 5.588688429550046
    },
    {
        "question": "393898÷678=？",
        "answer": 2.764154081836293
    },
    {
        "question": "153931546÷551835=？",
        "answer": 2.445518389163095
    },
    {
        "question": "524047÷17986=？",
        "answer": 1.4644356500537814
    },
    {
        "question": "19×743693=？",
        "answer": 7.150147294668791
    },
    {
        "question": "323×1316=？",
        "answer": 5.6284584116090395
    },
    {
        "question": "5×132768021=？",
        "answer": 8.82206348617753
    },
    {
        "question": "218246÷50670=？",
        "answer": 0.634195388435862
    },
    {
        "question": "1×32516=？",
        "answer": 4.512097114881013
    },
    {
        "question": "103110÷11609=？",
        "answer": 0.9485059756615046
    },
    {
        "question": "1×211249=？",
        "answer": 5.324794661784997
    },
    {
        "question": "9513×7365=？",
        "answer": 7.845490247925401
    },
    {
        "question": "2594800÷448300=？",
        "answer": 0.7625351503923972
    },
    {
        "question": "30079766÷313=？",
        "answer": 4.982730115872356
    },
    {
        "question": "1003×41500=？",
        "answer": 7.619349029732511
    },
    {
        "question": "9334÷1490=？",
        "answer": 0.7968815281368631
    },
    {
        "question": "13×1628=？",
        "answer": 4.325597752860019
    },
    {
        "question": "766606900÷4802352=？",
        "answer": 2.203118734339298
    },
    {
        "question": "4351×12897=？",
        "answer": 7.749077783129386
    },
    {
        "question": "2×849=？",
        "answer": 3.229937685907934
    },
    {
        "question": "21613×620=？",
        "answer": 7.127106742962612
    },
    {
        "question": "113×179574=？",
        "answer": 7.307321900124654
    },
    {
        "question": "1247÷558=？",
        "answer": 0.34923225454096385
    },
    {
        "question": "7×16005619=？",
        "answer": 8.049370514688468
    },
    {
        "question": "29×43080=？",
        "answer": 6.0966736925249
    },
    {
        "question": "4491×13392=？",
        "answer": 7.7791884957118995
    },
    {
        "question": "11209×74036=？",
        "answer": 8.919009815916848
    },
    {
        "question": "306483×838=？",
        "answer": 8.409650408705106
    },
    {
        "question": "459÷356=？",
        "answer": 0.11036268756438607
    },
    {
        "question": "3×464=？",
        "answer": 3.1436392352745433
    },
    {
        "question": "55661÷218=？",
        "answer": 2.407094510955055
    },
    {
        "question": "38×3690844=？",
        "answer": 8.146909285981813
    },
    {
        "question": "28×95745=？",
        "answer": 6.4282741348277055
    },
    {
        "question": "959784505÷10110=？",
        "answer": 4.9774225787037585
    },
    {
        "question": "19417272÷157121=？",
        "answer": 2.0919539797889146
    },
    {
        "question": "29512÷29225=？",
        "answer": 0.00424412238486934
    },
    {
        "question": "121918÷90366=？",
        "answer": 0.13006277077783485
    },
    {
        "question": "1566×391929=？",
        "answer": 8.787999157137792
    },
    {
        "question": "18×1294313=？",
        "answer": 7.367311818325652
    },
    {
        "question": "1128637÷4192=？",
        "answer": 2.430133009626645
    },
    {
        "question": "1661895×402=？",
        "answer": 8.824829634288806
    },
    {
        "question": "338704131÷2811048=？",
        "answer": 2.080952232084817
    },
    {
        "question": "476×7240=？",
        "answer": 6.53734551891764
    },
    {
        "question": "734166÷43561=？",
        "answer": 1.2266964270004934
    },
    {
        "question": "37×1243303=？",
        "answer": 7.662778705638607
    },
    {
        "question": "58×458=？",
        "answer": 4.4242934715668065
    },
    {
        "question": "8191÷251=？",
        "answer": 1.513663204451585
    },
    {
        "question": "4990×862=？",
        "answer": 6.633607811448103
    },
    {
        "question": "1185066÷61951=？",
        "answer": 1.2816942171672039
    },
    {
        "question": "31×1612=？",
        "answer": 4.698726731303345
    },
    {
        "question": "17098×380=？",
        "answer": 6.812728909362037
    },
    {
        "question": "35×273178=？",
        "answer": 6.9805137654823195
    },
    {
        "question": "684910÷29934=？",
        "answer": 1.359468752831903
    },
    {
        "question": "19×907=？",
        "answer": 4.236360888012924
    },
    {
        "question": "69×432=？",
        "answer": 4.474332837552168
    },
    {
        "question": "264371÷119047=？",
        "answer": 0.3464953581826893
    },
    {
        "question": "253×5592=？",
        "answer": 6.150687683913443
    },
    {
        "question": "2188943÷2831=？",
        "answer": 2.8882945833367835
    },
    {
        "question": "244441×738=？",
        "answer": 8.256230413558743
    },
    {
        "question": "15587557÷3353880=？",
        "answer": 0.6672305348734641
    },
    {
        "question": "6×141001=？",
        "answer": 5.92737344313081
    },
    {
        "question": "1×435361=？",
        "answer": 5.638849521987096
    },
    {
        "question": "48491272÷886=？",
        "answer": 4.73822985458433
    },
    {
        "question": "315×6798=？",
        "answer": 6.330691714036641
    },
    {
        "question": "13369÷2238=？",
        "answer": 0.7762388410962731
    },
    {
        "question": "12566344÷2699913=？",
        "answer": 0.6678591742271393
    },
    {
        "question": "615128÷2878=？",
        "answer": 2.32987470651555
    },
    {
        "question": "2×17237645=？",
        "answer": 7.5375079280710935
    },
    {
        "question": "635305414÷49892459=？",
        "answer": 1.104947647252061
    },
    {
        "question": "412496415÷2285=？",
        "answer": 5.2565339740498125
    },
    {
        "question": "387593339÷7352=？",
        "answer": 4.721970806480546
    },
    {
        "question": "610788÷241543=？",
        "answer": 0.4028960399924331
    },
    {
        "question": "216799÷11437=？",
        "answer": 1.277745153550013
    },
    {
        "question": "110076958÷36472=？",
        "answer": 3.4797368400435644
    },
    {
        "question": "60×313246=？",
        "answer": 7.274036784354639
    },
    {
        "question": "6×139437=？",
        "answer": 5.922529280699999
    },
    {
        "question": "4309×19378=？",
        "answer": 7.9216854456583405
    },
    {
        "question": "224870649÷26151208=？",
        "answer": 0.9344410183278562
    },
    {
        "question": "1×408096=？",
        "answer": 5.610762338006691
    },
    {
        "question": "16199445÷4042356=？",
        "answer": 0.6028655776077672
    },
    {
        "question": "11636÷2962=？",
        "answer": 0.5942186583898319
    },
    {
        "question": "7163549÷314=？",
        "answer": 4.358198587817227
    },
    {
        "question": "128340195÷241=？",
        "answer": 5.726345652247528
    },
    {
        "question": "122946÷118127=？",
        "answer": 0.017365229114400072
    },
    {
        "question": "1164×4634=？",
        "answer": 6.7319090097678265
    },
    {
        "question": "2180×50764=？",
        "answer": 8.044012329042333
    },
    {
        "question": "3946×26508=？",
        "answer": 8.019534042835232
    },
    {
        "question": "396333183÷13134205=？",
        "answer": 1.4796566446499355
    },
    {
        "question": "589536418÷199979178=？",
        "answer": 0.46952585943872277
    },
    {
        "question": "216×16349=？",
        "answer": 6.547944944981265
    },
    {
        "question": "4756366÷65509=？",
        "answer": 1.8609742960336924
    },
    {
        "question": "127×1541148=？",
        "answer": 8.291648067978695
    },
    {
        "question": "2888727÷731882=？",
        "answer": 0.5962654344597322
    },
    {
        "question": "39×6064780=？",
        "answer": 8.373879658474937
    },
    {
        "question": "4089325÷5024=？",
        "answer": 2.9106019968459047
    },
    {
        "question": "38525÷11986=？",
        "answer": 0.5070683740299908
    },
    {
        "question": "691576880÷3411=？",
        "answer": 5.306958746605336
    },
    {
        "question": "1×2923400=？",
        "answer": 6.465888242626536
    },
    {
        "question": "250753÷256=？",
        "answer": 2.991006172295469
    },
    {
        "question": "86×12130=？",
        "answer": 6.018359252110141
    },
    {
        "question": "89×69923=？",
        "answer": 6.794010059788073
    },
    {
        "question": "52886363÷960=？",
        "answer": 4.741072468535256
    },
    {
        "question": "34232573÷11937=？",
        "answer": 3.4575443490844524
    },
    {
        "question": "341399÷2108=？",
        "answer": 2.2093916381376846
    },
    {
        "question": "395608571÷58774763=？",
        "answer": 0.8280748055948254
    },
    {
        "question": "232630664÷226=？",
        "answer": 6.01255852115155
    },
    {
        "question": "7×3177=？",
        "answer": 4.3471152548414045
    },
    {
        "question": "5×93395=？",
        "answer": 5.669293630774522
    },
    {
        "question": "12×760=？",
        "answer": 3.959994838328416
    },
    {
        "question": "15×945=？",
        "answer": 4.151523067564944
    },
    {
        "question": "2679×85383=？",
        "answer": 8.359344123628215
    },
    {
        "question": "586148÷117700=？",
        "answer": 0.6972308246217143
    },
    {
        "question": "15×977102=？",
        "answer": 7.16603116128513
    },
    {
        "question": "741×2263=？",
        "answer": 6.2245027619340565
    },
    {
        "question": "6828962÷57599=？",
        "answer": 2.073939752555155
    },
    {
        "question": "102×4373587=？",
        "answer": 8.649437941755384
    },
    {
        "question": "279×9949=？",
        "answer": 6.4433836341392015
    },
    {
        "question": "4348449÷165494=？",
        "answer": 1.419552127884755
    },
    {
        "question": "244885×2054=？",
        "answer": 8.701562623255965
    },
    {
        "question": "44599÷35865=？",
        "answer": 0.09465428588708161
    },
    {
        "question": "1629363÷13980=？",
        "answer": 2.0665106786045606
    },
    {
        "question": "603925393÷10790154=？",
        "answer": 1.747955647496206
    },
    {
        "question": "131633÷22300=？",
        "answer": 0.7710599162092079
    },
    {
        "question": "4×487=？",
        "answer": 3.2895889525425965
    },
    {
        "question": "967×2134=？",
        "answer": 6.314620889171453
    },
    {
        "question": "23179188÷18522431=？",
        "answer": 0.09740023232119172
    },
    {
        "question": "11×646=？",
        "answer": 3.851625203153309
    },
    {
        "question": "1×77004392=？",
        "answer": 7.886515496172065
    },
    {
        "question": "572970÷813=？",
        "answer": 2.8480413378470777
    },
    {
        "question": "2467×327=？",
        "answer": 5.9067169021500225
    },
    {
        "question": "5182192÷4693976=？",
        "answer": 0.04297263479228991
    },
    {
        "question": "17183×11307=？",
        "answer": 8.288446382264206
    },
    {
        "question": "19847÷4696=？",
        "answer": 0.6259667814535154
    },
    {
        "question": "499613187÷154471788=？",
        "answer": 0.5097847193002382
    },
    {
        "question": "20964÷15231=？",
        "answer": 0.13874573290628828
    },
    {
        "question": "65417×6179=？",
        "answer": 8.60660881887208
    },
    {
        "question": "166980295÷1258672=？",
        "answer": 2.1227526528424696
    },
    {
        "question": "851674238÷21027=？",
        "answer": 4.607496195917144
    },
    {
        "question": "64402×593=？",
        "answer": 7.5819540479209175
    },
    {
        "question": "211×2526115=？",
        "answer": 8.726735572985163
    },
    {
        "question": "5017×2289=？",
        "answer": 7.060089893702294
    },
    {
        "question": "939605÷1892=？",
        "answer": 2.696024187094107
    },
    {
        "question": "35×2259169=？",
        "answer": 7.898016764434933
    },
    {
        "question": "245×29672=？",
        "answer": 6.861512904685086
    },
    {
        "question": "2×13182847=？",
        "answer": 7.421039207353569
    },
    {
        "question": "3×22226=？",
        "answer": 4.8239825647313985
    },
    {
        "question": "160×500111=？",
        "answer": 7.903186389666625
    },
    {
        "question": "21567÷430=？",
        "answer": 1.700321282751611
    },
    {
        "question": "845470÷6194=？",
        "answer": 2.135127001018721
    },
    {
        "question": "200225899÷7108=？",
        "answer": 4.449772833157442
    },
    {
        "question": "1706×111207=？",
        "answer": 8.278111151898514
    },
    {
        "question": "2×8481564=？",
        "answer": 7.229505939187234
    },
    {
        "question": "36877÷6008=？",
        "answer": 0.7880256593063028
    },
    {
        "question": "65574218÷883=？",
        "answer": 4.870772416572205
    },
    {
        "question": "1211×149025=？",
        "answer": 8.256403273644567
    },
    {
        "question": "269186779÷1219=？",
        "answer": 5.344050020259166
    },
    {
        "question": "13042119÷219=？",
        "answer": 4.774904043675669
    },
    {
        "question": "306357÷531=？",
        "answer": 2.7611332869638225
    },
    {
        "question": "1286×88665=？",
        "answer": 8.056993186992772
    },
    {
        "question": "111272÷1806=？",
        "answer": 1.7896681481385286
    },
    {
        "question": "106×1103856=？",
        "answer": 8.068218287856917
    },
    {
        "question": "180×222=？",
        "answer": 4.601625479553944
    },
    {
        "question": "7×324=？",
        "answer": 3.355643050220869
    },
    {
        "question": "1085×4470=？",
        "answer": 6.6857372613164845
    },
    {
        "question": "13108÷762=？",
        "answer": 1.2355814613707377
    },
    {
        "question": "47378713÷895086=？",
        "answer": 1.7237184949281703
    },
    {
        "question": "5×218=？",
        "answer": 3.037426497940624
    },
    {
        "question": "6×3039=？",
        "answer": 4.260881950463586
    },
    {
        "question": "1437737÷492348=？",
        "answer": 0.46540727132004817
    },
    {
        "question": "312745780÷6478709=？",
        "answer": 1.6837029848434215
    },
    {
        "question": "10166×43059=？",
        "answer": 8.641214044938573
    },
    {
        "question": "272×1380434=？",
        "answer": 8.574584551430336
    },
    {
        "question": "1737×468=？",
        "answer": 5.910045671521223
    },
    {
        "question": "273120÷3263=？",
        "answer": 1.9227364299827836
    },
    {
        "question": "1056760×273=？",
        "answer": 8.460139013240672
    },
    {
        "question": "462×1440=？",
        "answer": 5.8230044676513755
    },
    {
        "question": "12314020÷42564=？",
        "answer": 2.461357420102355
    },
    {
        "question": "518×18521=？",
        "answer": 6.981994191484092
    },
    {
        "question": "1×2144=？",
        "answer": 3.3312247810207323
    },
    {
        "question": "134446×2311=？",
        "answer": 8.492347831221997
    },
    {
        "question": "765×280122=？",
        "answer": 8.331008653593042
    },
    {
        "question": "4887÷3983=？",
        "answer": 0.08883203261884383
    },
    {
        "question": "13422×8498=？",
        "answer": 8.057133961233768
    },
    {
        "question": "43×18854778=？",
        "answer": 8.908889878879561
    },
    {
        "question": "450915999÷11582453=？",
        "answer": 1.5902950982585355
    },
    {
        "question": "4×316796=？",
        "answer": 6.102839680694614
    },
    {
        "question": "1910645×203=？",
        "answer": 8.588676040058184
    },
    {
        "question": "349087332÷4899271=？",
        "answer": 1.8528026261866934
    },
    {
        "question": "73×1788610=？",
        "answer": 8.115838514655191
    },
    {
        "question": "1254500×401=？",
        "answer": 8.70161503827081
    },
    {
        "question": "4371806÷55104=？",
        "answer": 1.8994777563399314
    },
    {
        "question": "593378217÷5082=？",
        "answer": 5.067296938545979
    },
    {
        "question": "25×23850=？",
        "answer": 5.775428392048171
    },
    {
        "question": "162×5532=？",
        "answer": 5.952397185979904
    },
    {
        "question": "3×11951044=？",
        "answer": 7.554527100056931
    },
    {
        "question": "13190006÷28966=？",
        "answer": 2.6583564667585944
    },
    {
        "question": "10676693÷1572=？",
        "answer": 3.8319842133997386
    },
    {
        "question": "43123÷838=？",
        "answer": 1.7114649477906339
    },
    {
        "question": "6×51715=？",
        "answer": 5.491767779403694
    },
    {
        "question": "143591÷27976=？",
        "answer": 0.7103416007386043
    },
    {
        "question": "4063×32018=？",
        "answer": 8.114241022611399
    },
    {
        "question": "74×4508557=？",
        "answer": 8.523269284399449
    },
    {
        "question": "61472848÷179470=？",
        "answer": 2.534691471376399
    },
    {
        "question": "325767662÷4893895=？",
        "answer": 1.8232533237770798
    },
    {
        "question": "3365453÷8760=？",
        "answer": 2.5845394236576276
    },
    {
        "question": "470434÷366=？",
        "answer": 3.109017616871747
    },
    {
        "question": "47×13484=？",
        "answer": 5.801916601784652
    },
    {
        "question": "83912÷17189=？",
        "answer": 0.6885734608190581
    },
    {
        "question": "335996062÷20220=？",
        "answer": 4.220553036070302
    },
    {
        "question": "52753508÷1605969=？",
        "answer": 1.516514186779116
    },
    {
        "question": "251220187÷14062=？",
        "answer": 4.25200744095011
    },
    {
        "question": "2×237145=？",
        "answer": 5.676043968019777
    },
    {
        "question": "35×616319=？",
        "answer": 7.333873600800672
    },
    {
        "question": "243×2703=？",
        "answer": 5.817452319297038
    },
    {
        "question": "2×2154=？",
        "answer": 3.634275694625944
    },
    {
        "question": "22×2871400=？",
        "answer": 7.800516376868811
    },
    {
        "question": "1565×209=？",
        "answer": 5.514660627993521
    },
    {
        "question": "22122151÷7732=？",
        "answer": 3.4565355070235784
    },
    {
        "question": "132791455÷21897=？",
        "answer": 3.7827855111366566
    },
    {
        "question": "5296×224=？",
        "answer": 6.074195994765806
    },
    {
        "question": "3793×384=？",
        "answer": 6.1633140670703215
    },
    {
        "question": "50×1245915=？",
        "answer": 7.794458418817951
    },
    {
        "question": "22687413÷259931=？",
        "answer": 1.9409268993826725
    },
    {
        "question": "99544220÷70424=？",
        "answer": 3.150295359091484
    },
    {
        "question": "6×486=？",
        "answer": 3.4647875196459372
    },
    {
        "question": "9587956÷2361873=？",
        "answer": 0.6084694908424678
    },
    {
        "question": "19×216=？",
        "answer": 3.61320735210376
    },
    {
        "question": "3131233÷7477=？",
        "answer": 2.6219880047119517
    },
    {
        "question": "182305307÷71859=？",
        "answer": 3.404318142164459
    },
    {
        "question": "8×378459=？",
        "answer": 6.481108824491905
    },
    {
        "question": "466679÷22390=？",
        "answer": 1.3189641650106134
    },
    {
        "question": "8386×902=？",
        "answer": 6.878761395609491
    },
    {
        "question": "3×363937=？",
        "answer": 6.0381474655105505
    },
    {
        "question": "11164÷4197=？",
        "answer": 0.42488085860510333
    },
    {
        "question": "61×6086595=？",
        "answer": 8.569704239915271
    },
    {
        "question": "981209582÷212=？",
        "answer": 6.665425919728106
    },
    {
        "question": "41058408÷485=？",
        "answer": 4.9276603674108985
    },
    {
        "question": "9336111÷258=？",
        "answer": 4.558546300570326
    },
    {
        "question": "9449259÷5438=？",
        "answer": 3.239958549720339
    },
    {
        "question": "2×1584=？",
        "answer": 3.500785172917456
    },
    {
        "question": "104×22802=？",
        "answer": 6.375006280635639
    },
    {
        "question": "387202713÷287439154=？",
        "answer": 0.1293924656340694
    },
    {
        "question": "25470÷753=？",
        "answer": 1.5292339687629144
    },
    {
        "question": "5×6051=？",
        "answer": 4.480797157268447
    },
    {
        "question": "2080373÷4176=？",
        "answer": 2.697380718679487
    },
    {
        "question": "382518÷45472=？",
        "answer": 0.9249078201487797
    },
    {
        "question": "750214072÷297=？",
        "answer": 6.402428756771329
    },
    {
        "question": "187×3837799=？",
        "answer": 8.855923831892502
    },
    {
        "question": "68625×8857=？",
        "answer": 8.783769002135946
    },
    {
        "question": "248×7587=？",
        "answer": 6.274521764890284
    },
    {
        "question": "243434561÷1053508=？",
        "answer": 2.3637443982722024
    },
    {
        "question": "1101÷888=？",
        "answer": 0.09337435319315077
    },
    {
        "question": "2×188248842=？",
        "answer": 8.575762309011848
    },
    {
        "question": "29409835÷433356=？",
        "answer": 1.8316477740268087
    },
    {
        "question": "432881198÷2754=？",
        "answer": 5.196404786916551
    },
    {
        "question": "53269÷727=？",
        "answer": 1.8649401331463982
    },
    {
        "question": "135×34174=？",
        "answer": 6.664029583590433
    },
    {
        "question": "1×2914893=？",
        "answer": 6.464622617289731
    },
    {
        "question": "13×24477852=？",
        "answer": 8.50271665689651
    },
    {
        "question": "62106÷28080=？",
        "answer": 0.34473645551135795
    },
    {
        "question": "65410825÷459=？",
        "answer": 5.153836941208036
    },
    {
        "question": "96×5221=？",
        "answer": 5.7000249262502845
    },
    {
        "question": "26599815÷1408728=？",
        "answer": 1.2760514693887997
    },
    {
        "question": "21×46015=？",
        "answer": 5.985118721096496
    },
    {
        "question": "3392394÷2182=？",
        "answer": 3.1916515401651435
    },
    {
        "question": "1×4304=？",
        "answer": 3.6338722626583326
    },
    {
        "question": "15381204÷874879=？",
        "answer": 1.2450423400735202
    },
    {
        "question": "12348÷1093=？",
        "answer": 1.052976458860355
    },
    {
        "question": "5237526÷3332719=？",
        "answer": 0.19632749446318806
    },
    {
        "question": "2×248626=？",
        "answer": 5.696576538578206
    },
    {
        "question": "2×300256=？",
        "answer": 5.778521690309635
    },
    {
        "question": "483785÷21405=？",
        "answer": 1.3541371665429678
    },
    {
        "question": "106517710÷628873=？",
        "answer": 2.2288588719164855
    },
    {
        "question": "525238÷352=？",
        "answer": 3.173813475480267
    },
    {
        "question": "1903×1192=？",
        "answer": 6.355715043691238
    },
    {
        "question": "29258÷530=？",
        "answer": 1.7419687659735215
    },
    {
        "question": "32×14605=？",
        "answer": 5.669651539629474
    },
    {
        "question": "43174÷7263=？",
        "answer": 0.7741062430274596
    },
    {
        "question": "72×767368=？",
        "answer": 7.742336181164318
    },
    {
        "question": "1689×3031=？",
        "answer": 6.709215585938631
    },
    {
        "question": "1826124÷764445=？",
        "answer": 0.37818401984766475
    },
    {
        "question": "6456×7882=？",
        "answer": 7.706599952243598
    },
    {
        "question": "12×60467=？",
        "answer": 5.860699668171581
    },
    {
        "question": "280×65037=？",
        "answer": 7.260318531432925
    },
    {
        "question": "34442×12082=？",
        "answer": 8.619227193795982
    },
    {
        "question": "1×979979=？",
        "answer": 5.991216769282456
    },
    {
        "question": "475643155÷82448=？",
        "answer": 3.761101126061179
    },
    {
        "question": "84483864÷10536867=？",
        "answer": 0.9040622705032284
    },
    {
        "question": "52906×6894=？",
        "answer": 8.56197620666718
    },
    {
        "question": "69×411426=？",
        "answer": 7.453140824133235
    },
    {
        "question": "16×168520=？",
        "answer": 6.430771433110735
    },
    {
        "question": "2870655÷10806=？",
        "answer": 2.424316038210292
    },
    {
        "question": "134970984÷38616=？",
        "answer": 3.543473128290882
    },
    {
        "question": "1172853÷47804=？",
        "answer": 1.3897793453276963
    },
    {
        "question": "198551506÷383588=？",
        "answer": 2.7140081730755963
    },
    {
        "question": "5460×64317=？",
        "answer": 8.545518421700246
    },
    {
        "question": "30×2821=？",
        "answer": 4.927524340875029
    },
    {
        "question": "1498×168036=？",
        "answer": 8.400914148222952
    },
    {
        "question": "172226288÷1142=？",
        "answer": 5.17843333741217
    },
    {
        "question": "218103267÷121319=？",
        "answer": 3.254733349106153
    },
    {
        "question": "37411765÷604=？",
        "answer": 4.791971259063273
    },
    {
        "question": "3768206÷62220=？",
        "answer": 1.7822046299749608
    },
    {
        "question": "339×2880840=？",
        "answer": 8.989718836717197
    },
    {
        "question": "3×2316140=？",
        "answer": 6.841886061670507
    },
    {
        "question": "2086725×351=？",
        "answer": 8.864772335607075
    },
    {
        "question": "36949÷11456=？",
        "answer": 0.508569684036109
    },
    {
        "question": "1×703584=？",
        "answer": 5.847315954732667
    },
    {
        "question": "89583477÷31055827=？",
        "answer": 0.46008481592614137
    },
    {
        "question": "4084064÷47081=？",
        "answer": 1.9382468604715661
    },
    {
        "question": "365627969÷223=？",
        "answer": 6.214734546983446
    },
    {
        "question": "2155101÷761758=？",
        "answer": 0.45165060453545697
    },
    {
        "question": "10×2238=？",
        "answer": 4.349860082192332
    },
    {
        "question": "88758102÷12259=？",
        "answer": 3.859752961677817
    },
    {
        "question": "50214×941=？",
        "answer": 7.674414441669454
    },
    {
        "question": "61×8879=？",
        "answer": 5.733693890999136
    },
    {
        "question": "23784×1201=？",
        "answer": 7.455827903599787
    },
    {
        "question": "6779886÷85157=？",
        "answer": 1.9010020382542387
    },
    {
        "question": "2827×1156=？",
        "answer": 6.51428364257403
    },
    {
        "question": "1710319÷2321=？",
        "answer": 2.867401979888892
    },
    {
        "question": "1×212103210=？",
        "answer": 8.326547241240455
    },
    {
        "question": "1×2951336=？",
        "answer": 6.4700186553282135
    },
    {
        "question": "439316424÷448452=？",
        "answer": 2.9910614746060107
    },
    {
        "question": "49905101÷723823=？",
        "answer": 1.8385125598553569
    },
    {
        "question": "44766150÷1558501=？",
        "answer": 1.458242660311585
    },
    {
        "question": "10×79249=？",
        "answer": 5.89899379079866
    },
    {
        "question": "37×1848=？",
        "answer": 4.834903690951083
    },
    {
        "question": "1312×359=？",
        "answer": 5.673028283617961
    },
    {
        "question": "504817737÷385441=？",
        "answer": 3.117176696234912
    },
    {
        "question": "7760×19280=？",
        "answer": 8.174968750825
    },
    {
        "question": "18255473÷205041=？",
        "answer": 1.9495523787506728
    },
    {
        "question": "1252693÷105929=？",
        "answer": 1.0728297781711387
    },
    {
        "question": "806×41330=？",
        "answer": 7.522600447086798
    },
    {
        "question": "98606×453=？",
        "answer": 7.650001543806089
    },
    {
        "question": "105598904÷2161268=？",
        "answer": 1.6889507874296856
    },
    {
        "question": "25845×399=？",
        "answer": 7.013349432190458
    },
    {
        "question": "1×28692566=？",
        "answer": 7.457769389298917
    },
    {
        "question": "89542×3886=？",
        "answer": 8.541529586772027
    },
    {
        "question": "530947÷998=？",
        "answer": 2.7259206299705006
    },
    {
        "question": "10×19671846=？",
        "answer": 8.293845115892719
    },
    {
        "question": "912026671÷475458=？",
        "answer": 3.2828953796919964
    },
    {
        "question": "43×2450766=？",
        "answer": 8.022770302221218
    },
    {
        "question": "13880×619=？",
        "answer": 6.934080115138954
    },
    {
        "question": "6×3331048=？",
        "answer": 7.300732141251024
    },
    {
        "question": "92×9822=？",
        "answer": 5.95598775714114
    },
    {
        "question": "1435×414392=？",
        "answer": 8.774263263662903
    },
    {
        "question": "182637×432=？",
        "answer": 7.897072511623492
    },
    {
        "question": "11587059÷3877505=？",
        "answer": 0.475420851845047
    },
    {
        "question": "3×39830=？",
        "answer": 5.07733156112899
    },
    {
        "question": "283×12846=？",
        "answer": 6.560554353202372
    },
    {
        "question": "3404×11081=？",
        "answer": 7.5765685062891635
    },
    {
        "question": "41×150056=？",
        "answer": 6.7890372221240245
    },
    {
        "question": "3×676202=？",
        "answer": 6.307197705662396
    },
    {
        "question": "4545033÷204=？",
        "answer": 4.347906873413908
    },
    {
        "question": "1752×4470=？",
        "answer": 6.893841624963998
    },
    {
        "question": "287737202÷43186=？",
        "answer": 3.8236530357218954
    },
    {
        "question": "9459×2503=？",
        "answer": 7.374306075075791
    },
    {
        "question": "4×48059=？",
        "answer": 5.283834721195756
    },
    {
        "question": "1577354÷485=？",
        "answer": 3.512187432845607
    },
    {
        "question": "46×322691=？",
        "answer": 7.17154468458209
    },
    {
        "question": "4×820=？",
        "answer": 3.515873843711679
    },
    {
        "question": "20×1903=？",
        "answer": 4.580468783951002
    },
    {
        "question": "1594024×229=？",
        "answer": 8.562330338289003
    },
    {
        "question": "3020609÷348073=？",
        "answer": 0.9384241756589605
    },
    {
        "question": "3×423=？",
        "answer": 3.103461622094705
    },
    {
        "question": "24407639÷3618154=？",
        "answer": 0.8290387234157967
    },
    {
        "question": "15403÷824=？",
        "answer": 1.2716781037210327
    },
    {
        "question": "4×49583=？",
        "answer": 5.297392791372304
    },
    {
        "question": "7×418873=？",
        "answer": 6.467180407229325
    },
    {
        "question": "352805081÷664=？",
        "answer": 5.725366751724341
    },
    {
        "question": "416×17055=？",
        "answer": 6.850945054370158
    },
    {
        "question": "2×829685=？",
        "answer": 6.219943234150983
    },
    {
        "question": "915068190÷485417038=？",
        "answer": 0.27533844260250157
    },
    {
        "question": "32237562÷17451936=？",
        "answer": 0.2665185787251534
    },
    {
        "question": "538×5246=？",
        "answer": 6.450610561920724
    },
    {
        "question": "76×48310=？",
        "answer": 6.564850629767311
    },
    {
        "question": "75140786÷55024=？",
        "answer": 3.135323575151709
    },
    {
        "question": "1138×206=？",
        "answer": 5.370009482428205
    },
    {
        "question": "150971933÷9663430=？",
        "answer": 1.1937649106061579
    },
    {
        "question": "248140375÷1817552=？",
        "answer": 2.1352105893811015
    },
    {
        "question": "123166351÷60663688=？",
        "answer": 0.30756326558639313
    },
    {
        "question": "903790648÷207120221=？",
        "answer": 0.6398453423186711
    },
    {
        "question": "1×395=？",
        "answer": 2.59659709562646
    },
    {
        "question": "5476654÷7686=？",
        "answer": 2.852814924131233
    },
    {
        "question": "8845×53228=？",
        "answer": 8.672837985453404
    },
    {
        "question": "49331167÷36441=？",
        "answer": 3.1315311032391087
    },
    {
        "question": "6×1536994=？",
        "answer": 6.964823422521009
    },
    {
        "question": "36834629÷78977=？",
        "answer": 2.668755667264444
    },
    {
        "question": "12×56057177=？",
        "answer": 8.82781246925797
    },
    {
        "question": "3662÷396=？",
        "answer": 0.9660231540401654
    },
    {
        "question": "13352÷11998=？",
        "answer": 0.04643746606975408
    },
    {
        "question": "33×3767118=？",
        "answer": 8.094523163995738
    },
    {
        "question": "850013÷131034=？",
        "answer": 0.8120415691317951
    },
    {
        "question": "174185912÷94290091=？",
        "answer": 0.26654697186671367
    },
    {
        "question": "4×430=？",
        "answer": 3.2355284469075487
    },
    {
        "question": "1258398÷1360=？",
        "answer": 2.9662791110116578
    },
    {
        "question": "264×136154=？",
        "answer": 7.555634331652752
    },
    {
        "question": "317191404÷661220=？",
        "answer": 2.6809754280149933
    },
    {
        "question": "6010437÷1109298=？",
        "answer": 0.7338578193567968
    },
    {
        "question": "50×5203718=？",
        "answer": 8.415283757567167
    },
    {
        "question": "46473191÷335288=？",
        "answer": 2.141784483317736
    },
    {
        "question": "11167166÷189384=？",
        "answer": 1.770599686882846
    },
    {
        "question": "964÷890=？",
        "answer": 0.03468702725791797
    },
    {
        "question": "1×846=？",
        "answer": 2.9273703630390235
    },
    {
        "question": "36843432÷18692072=？",
        "answer": 0.29470263312995204
    },
    {
        "question": "144667÷632=？",
        "answer": 2.35965239718784
    },
    {
        "question": "86567455÷4612797=？",
        "answer": 1.2733903072700286
    },
    {
        "question": "14077888÷995717=？",
        "answer": 1.1504015837923176
    },
    {
        "question": "194950÷102079=？",
        "answer": 0.2809868326199694
    },
    {
        "question": "5×43464125=？",
        "answer": 8.337100945366197
    },
    {
        "question": "92819÷48080=？",
        "answer": 0.28567242617407074
    },
    {
        "question": "1313×6724=？",
        "answer": 6.9458924308569125
    },
    {
        "question": "388283÷40491=？",
        "answer": 0.9817898738597415
    },
    {
        "question": "800036824÷476697508=？",
        "answer": 0.22486709550640846
    },
    {
        "question": "17×49218=？",
        "answer": 5.922572883312888
    },
    {
        "question": "636888267÷111574193=？",
        "answer": 0.7564994938850367
    },
    {
        "question": "570001386÷4043232=？",
        "answer": 2.1491472498965583
    },
    {
        "question": "588140÷106384=？",
        "answer": 0.7426044016089146
    },
    {
        "question": "20780199÷276938=？",
        "answer": 1.8752671507522918
    },
    {
        "question": "38×36337=？",
        "answer": 6.140132665509916
    },
    {
        "question": "10324691÷13091=？",
        "answer": 2.8969042399858504
    },
    {
        "question": "95825850÷45584764=？",
        "answer": 0.32266296952174733
    },
    {
        "question": "477329516÷664112=？",
        "answer": 2.8565769624139983
    },
    {
        "question": "16090÷7325=？",
        "answer": 0.34174841507288245
    },
    {
        "question": "9×198512=？",
        "answer": 6.252029274323153
    },
    {
        "question": "33×89953=？",
        "answer": 6.472529591847611
    },
    {
        "question": "1×9189497=？",
        "answer": 6.963291740319422
    },
    {
        "question": "14×239=？",
        "answer": 3.5245259366263757
    },
    {
        "question": "13810819÷2714=？",
        "answer": 3.7066095902610035
    },
    {
        "question": "4832448÷3456=？",
        "answer": 3.1455934556532665
    },
    {
        "question": "108×2020632=？",
        "answer": 8.338910981955348
    },
    {
        "question": "2478529÷17742=？",
        "answer": 2.1451914298187167
    },
    {
        "question": "25×40615=？",
        "answer": 6.006626466242401
    },
    {
        "question": "566×342=？",
        "answer": 5.286842537244406
    },
    {
        "question": "585×294310=？",
        "answer": 8.235960884794215
    },
    {
        "question": "168×194015=？",
        "answer": 7.51314458982823
    },
    {
        "question": "7084317÷334714=？",
        "answer": 1.325624108343571
    },
    {
        "question": "18×252=？",
        "answer": 3.65667304588485
    },
    {
        "question": "491×1263=？",
        "answer": 5.7924848426782996
    },
    {
        "question": "6×167994=？",
        "answer": 6.003445021315316
    },
    {
        "question": "411171931÷24295=？",
        "answer": 4.228506556119589
    },
    {
        "question": "650÷601=？",
        "answer": 0.03403888464011602
    },
    {
        "question": "2318×52654=？",
        "answer": 8.086544800728214
    },
    {
        "question": "721×1109=？",
        "answer": 5.902866810868589
    },
    {
        "question": "32×30432=？",
        "answer": 5.9884804735772255
    },
    {
        "question": "30511×656=？",
        "answer": 7.30136028128109
    },
    {
        "question": "22×22991005=？",
        "answer": 8.70398063671152
    },
    {
        "question": "12409411÷405=？",
        "answer": 4.486296145429881
    },
    {
        "question": "1×7802699=？",
        "answer": 6.892244853723119
    },
    {
        "question": "43×251=？",
        "answer": 4.033142177060625
    },
    {
        "question": "564690667÷614=？",
        "answer": 5.963642238795296
    },
    {
        "question": "940696÷44778=？",
        "answer": 1.3223846053305366
    },
    {
        "question": "641804÷44613=？",
        "answer": 1.1579409911344145
    },
    {
        "question": "70×1457=？",
        "answer": 5.008557591784247
    },
    {
        "question": "24226÷3274=？",
        "answer": 0.8692030378096619
    },
    {
        "question": "156369740÷16895=？",
        "answer": 3.966394517942147
    },
    {
        "question": "14869×450=？",
        "answer": 6.825494275230344
    },
    {
        "question": "102490005÷40458=？",
        "answer": 3.403677104258323
    },
    {
        "question": "453×857328=？",
        "answer": 8.589245209860547
    },
    {
        "question": "10316×855=？",
        "answer": 6.945477448194072
    },
    {
        "question": "6024065÷222662=？",
        "answer": 1.4322435435994576
    },
    {
        "question": "926378491÷1441=？",
        "answer": 5.808124482075789
    },
    {
        "question": "7369662÷2642579=？",
        "answer": 0.44541959053839525
    },
    {
        "question": "8732×4424=？",
        "answer": 7.586928845333744
    },
    {
        "question": "102439÷42042=？",
        "answer": 0.3867819623974855
    },
    {
        "question": "5613380÷46720=？",
        "answer": 2.0797216088488133
    },
    {
        "question": "3079676÷232=？",
        "answer": 4.123017043683015
    },
    {
        "question": "108130224÷8823947=？",
        "answer": 1.0882842117641773
    },
    {
        "question": "631902÷19101=？",
        "answer": 1.5195936253454296
    },
    {
        "question": "90360267÷110484=？",
        "answer": 2.912678116321187
    },
    {
        "question": "346720÷69284=？",
        "answer": 0.6993459409511514
    },
    {
        "question": "12×15578=？",
        "answer": 5.271692945551126
    },
    {
        "question": "4181×864=？",
        "answer": 6.557793910029308
    },
    {
        "question": "131394×509=？",
        "answer": 7.825293316309488
    },
    {
        "question": "78×8494=？",
        "answer": 5.821206859345141
    },
    {
        "question": "278151042÷86508510=？",
        "answer": 0.5072218593121254
    },
    {
        "question": "1×79244=？",
        "answer": 4.898966389305721
    },
    {
        "question": "460196411÷760=？",
        "answer": 5.782129635070143
    },
    {
        "question": "1×861412=？",
        "answer": 5.935210917458486
    },
    {
        "question": "69727151÷365908=？",
        "answer": 2.2800300158622515
    },
    {
        "question": "31×10970832=？",
        "answer": 8.531601258447024
    },
    {
        "question": "81174046÷292=？",
        "answer": 5.444034341822884
    },
    {
        "question": "4620÷451=？",
        "answer": 1.0104654336781649
    },
    {
        "question": "3×794555=？",
        "answer": 6.377245219661136
    },
    {
        "question": "2×121789=？",
        "answer": 5.3866380601920785
    },
    {
        "question": "885963÷67255=？",
        "answer": 1.1196910080303608
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1847=？",
        "answer": 3.2664668954402414
    },
    {
        "question": "729543186÷14469=？",
        "answer": 4.702612488822142
    },
    {
        "question": "14×5890=？",
        "answer": 4.916243330465339
    },
    {
        "question": "11502571÷37736=？",
        "answer": 2.484039059404518
    },
    {
        "question": "39040÷236=？",
        "answer": 2.2185978060245475
    },
    {
        "question": "102261764÷280=？",
        "answer": 5.562555248627201
    },
    {
        "question": "52626901÷2719549=？",
        "answer": 1.2867109085973023
    },
    {
        "question": "26×9470589=？",
        "answer": 8.391350337691648
    },
    {
        "question": "7587987÷6622300=？",
        "answer": 0.05911772712396259
    },
    {
        "question": "4555733÷38294=？",
        "answer": 2.0754275303008325
    },
    {
        "question": "2812×1987=？",
        "answer": 6.7472131834576015
    },
    {
        "question": "2382÷871=？",
        "answer": 0.4369236021390955
    },
    {
        "question": "988655857÷24383700=？",
        "answer": 1.6079455371163758
    },
    {
        "question": "27×49878=？",
        "answer": 6.129272795044525
    },
    {
        "question": "35920÷397=？",
        "answer": 1.9565458212321516
    },
    {
        "question": "650×10658=？",
        "answer": 6.840589072547749
    },
    {
        "question": "3×4521106=？",
        "answer": 7.132365944163914
    },
    {
        "question": "19467180÷439130=？",
        "answer": 1.6467099367574372
    },
    {
        "question": "34×6910=？",
        "answer": 5.370956964416454
    },
    {
        "question": "82388222÷43265=？",
        "answer": 3.279728422505137
    },
    {
        "question": "228×969717=？",
        "answer": 8.344579856245213
    },
    {
        "question": "1×202335=？",
        "answer": 5.306071013725391
    },
    {
        "question": "468475÷7377=？",
        "answer": 1.8028066364148474
    },
    {
        "question": "902781÷1509=？",
        "answer": 2.776893170530459
    },
    {
        "question": "179186÷26502=？",
        "answer": 0.8300254251022423
    },
    {
        "question": "1×4687=？",
        "answer": 3.67089495352021
    },
    {
        "question": "36×6523=？",
        "answer": 5.370749879289775
    },
    {
        "question": "31270÷324=？",
        "answer": 1.9845828710363211
    },
    {
        "question": "872×20346=？",
        "answer": 7.248995525094297
    },
    {
        "question": "126905÷100729=？",
        "answer": 0.10032421098093752
    },
    {
        "question": "52119313÷2238=？",
        "answer": 4.367138600322593
    },
    {
        "question": "4×30232=？",
        "answer": 5.08252687023692
    },
    {
        "question": "22029÷19104=？",
        "answer": 0.061870473478202084
    },
    {
        "question": "79×22053=？",
        "answer": 6.241094768759706
    },
    {
        "question": "3111740÷2827812=？",
        "answer": 0.04155276945505631
    },
    {
        "question": "23025986÷3707394=？",
        "answer": 0.7931494935292633
    },
    {
        "question": "2×472=？",
        "answer": 2.974971994298069
    },
    {
        "question": "477611×930=？",
        "answer": 8.647557269154913
    },
    {
        "question": "1×450=？",
        "answer": 2.6532125137753435
    },
    {
        "question": "27×4755359=？",
        "answer": 8.108547073199754
    },
    {
        "question": "256174×1337=？",
        "answer": 8.534666456833317
    },
    {
        "question": "4347640÷124833=？",
        "answer": 1.541924168131355
    },
    {
        "question": "11731×5485=？",
        "answer": 7.808511666700669
    },
    {
        "question": "795444×607=？",
        "answer": 8.683798301397193
    },
    {
        "question": "363÷290=？",
        "answer": 0.09750862713715641
    },
    {
        "question": "4×213870=？",
        "answer": 5.932209860760614
    },
    {
        "question": "22947112÷347=？",
        "answer": 4.82039856055576
    },
    {
        "question": "919403733÷11873=？",
        "answer": 4.888945794954891
    },
    {
        "question": "280336÷33222=？",
        "answer": 0.9262530983828279
    },
    {
        "question": "596863969÷101972=？",
        "answer": 3.7673944252433333
    },
    {
        "question": "27×159164=？",
        "answer": 6.633208609160221
    },
    {
        "question": "10×12589420=？",
        "answer": 8.100005722434966
    },
    {
        "question": "15760839÷1431=？",
        "answer": 4.041939698897045
    },
    {
        "question": "55593717÷266=？",
        "answer": 5.320144075339186
    },
    {
        "question": "315383260÷1130=？",
        "answer": 5.445760194518451
    },
    {
        "question": "5023÷1379=？",
        "answer": 0.5613989119836996
    },
    {
        "question": "19307302÷5406=？",
        "answer": 3.552845548399245
    },
    {
        "question": "18866066÷4639=？",
        "answer": 3.609256976898354
    },
    {
        "question": "114×519=？",
        "answer": 4.77207220918493
    },
    {
        "question": "1802223×279=？",
        "answer": 8.701412731136088
    },
    {
        "question": "16917329÷7648110=？",
        "answer": 0.34477766972492774
    },
    {
        "question": "4×6234=？",
        "answer": 4.396826789268784
    },
    {
        "question": "578908506÷305754114=？",
        "answer": 0.27723762148427145
    },
    {
        "question": "2225841÷1658016=？",
        "answer": 0.1279054206419562
    },
    {
        "question": "23772010÷234=？",
        "answer": 5.006850046867595
    },
    {
        "question": "3159×9225=？",
        "answer": 7.464516000736247
    },
    {
        "question": "2590001÷23540=？",
        "answer": 2.0414934732550707
    },
    {
        "question": "141×2359910=？",
        "answer": 8.522114553231976
    },
    {
        "question": "12488822÷1935=？",
        "answer": 3.8098405064069523
    },
    {
        "question": "45821×2217=？",
        "answer": 8.006830256137723
    },
    {
        "question": "3031058÷59455=？",
        "answer": 1.7074058633255282
    },
    {
        "question": "3×1000=？",
        "answer": 3.4771212547196626
    },
    {
        "question": "13457×3351=？",
        "answer": 7.654122680244602
    },
    {
        "question": "46267866÷718=？",
        "answer": 4.809155024875125
    },
    {
        "question": "1169963÷133250=？",
        "answer": 0.9435049097313838
    },
    {
        "question": "29581565÷5589=？",
        "answer": 3.723687036815929
    },
    {
        "question": "89842÷6932=？",
        "answer": 1.1126208572802638
    },
    {
        "question": "637164÷239888=？",
        "answer": 0.4242427063757185
    },
    {
        "question": "581728845÷36222105=？",
        "answer": 1.2057469136415282
    },
    {
        "question": "11174937÷7671079=？",
        "answer": 0.1633886281091164
    },
    {
        "question": "85941×1673=？",
        "answer": 8.157696343742385
    },
    {
        "question": "688346118÷12623=？",
        "answer": 4.736644285293205
    },
    {
        "question": "889382÷177987=？",
        "answer": 0.6987000526003526
    },
    {
        "question": "5576203÷44561=？",
        "answer": 2.0973836473964638
    },
    {
        "question": "48×3176=？",
        "answer": 5.183121731130646
    },
    {
        "question": "2018815÷190486=？",
        "answer": 1.0252334607416882
    },
    {
        "question": "551×25797=？",
        "answer": 7.152720802520418
    },
    {
        "question": "12×328321=？",
        "answer": 6.595479907919341
    },
    {
        "question": "6×1963097=？",
        "answer": 7.071093009751329
    },
    {
        "question": "124×7231=？",
        "answer": 5.952620046696112
    },
    {
        "question": "6029525÷2759743=？",
        "answer": 0.3394144597566238
    },
    {
        "question": "158583×1674=？",
        "answer": 8.424012083032867
    },
    {
        "question": "4027597÷671564=？",
        "answer": 0.7779586014865226
    },
    {
        "question": "90×20653=？",
        "answer": 6.269225654478449
    },
    {
        "question": "2187×210342=？",
        "answer": 8.662774782053239
    },
    {
        "question": "252×65439=？",
        "answer": 7.217237194864734
    },
    {
        "question": "340×720=？",
        "answer": 5.388811413473523
    },
    {
        "question": "7085÷1702=？",
        "answer": 0.6193802988349102
    },
    {
        "question": "628122÷16934=？",
        "answer": 1.569284449417692
    },
    {
        "question": "1715736÷33538=？",
        "answer": 1.708913303445844
    },
    {
        "question": "4700708÷31601=？",
        "answer": 2.172462448493048
    },
    {
        "question": "47×2661=？",
        "answer": 5.097142732487106
    },
    {
        "question": "6×67953393=？",
        "answer": 8.610362396873615
    },
    {
        "question": "2×8685284=？",
        "answer": 7.2398140196694705
    },
    {
        "question": "502×1162865=？",
        "answer": 8.766233016432226
    },
    {
        "question": "7×117851=？",
        "answer": 5.916431312005184
    },
    {
        "question": "518382÷614=？",
        "answer": 2.9264815417900527
    },
    {
        "question": "1812×435=？",
        "answer": 5.896647450295432
    },
    {
        "question": "3×14975=？",
        "answer": 4.652488085781012
    },
    {
        "question": "327635893÷2064=？",
        "answer": 5.200681780346748
    },
    {
        "question": "310÷299=？",
        "answer": 0.015690505509843022
    },
    {
        "question": "191×9680=？",
        "answer": 6.266908724556121
    },
    {
        "question": "9318×4109=？",
        "answer": 7.583058847374073
    },
    {
        "question": "706925484÷88330565=？",
        "answer": 0.9032626294731437
    },
    {
        "question": "1×14014940=？",
        "answer": 7.146591242822335
    },
    {
        "question": "5926617÷73786=？",
        "answer": 1.9048328949030557
    },
    {
        "question": "84×122249=？",
        "answer": 7.01152460133191
    },
    {
        "question": "124949×987=？",
        "answer": 8.091049937372043
    },
    {
        "question": "306×1480=？",
        "answer": 5.655983141876537
    },
    {
        "question": "2×351878=？",
        "answer": 5.847422110531919
    },
    {
        "question": "2×2986=？",
        "answer": 3.776119799052988
    },
    {
        "question": "3×942=？",
        "answer": 3.45117215751254
    },
    {
        "question": "12166÷5493=？",
        "answer": 0.3453382131055456
    },
    {
        "question": "655839×633=？",
        "answer": 8.618200948793495
    },
    {
        "question": "221×1946820=？",
        "answer": 8.633718072857679
    },
    {
        "question": "6755197÷38714=？",
        "answer": 2.241769973033338
    },
    {
        "question": "9×9283=？",
        "answer": 4.921930859892638
    },
    {
        "question": "201×463956=？",
        "answer": 7.969672852925178
    },
    {
        "question": "313×1102=？",
        "answer": 5.537725932062215
    },
    {
        "question": "3386779÷63071=？",
        "answer": 1.7299571413786123
    },
    {
        "question": "1×15305426=？",
        "answer": 7.184845421935611
    },
    {
        "question": "60×6890=？",
        "answer": 5.616370472291269
    },
    {
        "question": "234×1119=？",
        "answer": 5.418045943938493
    },
    {
        "question": "66×3797=？",
        "answer": 5.3989845326816654
    },
    {
        "question": "306475934÷1357=？",
        "answer": 5.353816529591593
    },
    {
        "question": "409599954÷2651201=？",
        "answer": 2.188917244308703
    },
    {
        "question": "2887937÷4015=？",
        "answer": 2.856902165304096
    },
    {
        "question": "6×1203=？",
        "answer": 3.858416877723488
    },
    {
        "question": "160931×1744=？",
        "answer": 8.448186190526283
    },
    {
        "question": "9543503÷1294227=？",
        "answer": 0.8676973585839298
    },
    {
        "question": "546401799÷2671191=？",
        "answer": 2.310807177780709
    },
    {
        "question": "1101038÷376820=？",
        "answer": 0.4656683627535809
    },
    {
        "question": "87941143÷29722=？",
        "answer": 3.471114076144555
    },
    {
        "question": "1×4847=？",
        "answer": 3.6854730197227594
    },
    {
        "question": "18×1504=？",
        "answer": 4.43252034135893
    },
    {
        "question": "189069÷9170=？",
        "answer": 1.3142509915219527
    },
    {
        "question": "2325×148540=？",
        "answer": 8.538266376805552
    },
    {
        "question": "479×2997=？",
        "answer": 6.157022256360208
    },
    {
        "question": "16×9044=？",
        "answer": 5.1604805363292465
    },
    {
        "question": "2735382×247=？",
        "answer": 8.829714938008614
    },
    {
        "question": "25545174÷6010692=？",
        "answer": 0.628384390796804
    },
    {
        "question": "22×3160864=？",
        "answer": 7.842228491017948
    },
    {
        "question": "15×9436=？",
        "answer": 5.150879191269239
    },
    {
        "question": "966×88658=？",
        "answer": 7.93269505641557
    },
    {
        "question": "46×7296=？",
        "answer": 5.525842657001934
    },
    {
        "question": "2463×8364=？",
        "answer": 7.313878435984737
    },
    {
        "question": "257×395=？",
        "answer": 5.006530218957755
    },
    {
        "question": "234196665÷69834605=？",
        "answer": 0.5255100253301983
    },
    {
        "question": "28134÷1663=？",
        "answer": 1.2283392339029737
    },
    {
        "question": "120036×7920=？",
        "answer": 8.978036696442345
    },
    {
        "question": "207398811÷363=？",
        "answer": 5.756899637250183
    },
    {
        "question": "87×51896=？",
        "answer": 6.654653137540789
    },
    {
        "question": "3156327÷367=？",
        "answer": 3.934515926146791
    },
    {
        "question": "3045×2644=？",
        "answer": 6.905848747782497
    },
    {
        "question": "1162240÷71634=？",
        "answer": 1.2101766155873914
    },
    {
        "question": "4282981÷3019=？",
        "answer": 3.15188303477682
    },
    {
        "question": "1×24069793=？",
        "answer": 7.3814723553625115
    },
    {
        "question": "24232549÷2029985=？",
        "answer": 1.0769062707568513
    },
    {
        "question": "61×23413=？",
        "answer": 6.154786900137137
    },
    {
        "question": "209426484÷1828709=？",
        "answer": 2.058886999265712
    },
    {
        "question": "3503×398=？",
        "answer": 6.144323209391381
    },
    {
        "question": "1109×9295=？",
        "answer": 7.013180940257078
    },
    {
        "question": "34×3212511=？",
        "answer": 8.038323540457442
    },
    {
        "question": "17×39996=？",
        "answer": 5.8324654810864285
    },
    {
        "question": "103857÷6141=？",
        "answer": 1.2281966760832723
    },
    {
        "question": "3×2671747=？",
        "answer": 6.9039165851301645
    },
    {
        "question": "356926126÷230=？",
        "answer": 6.190850502250094
    },
    {
        "question": "4×49551129=？",
        "answer": 8.29711354546478
    },
    {
        "question": "749485947÷4548=？",
        "answer": 5.216943038143156
    },
    {
        "question": "805511041÷4504683=？",
        "answer": 2.2524072630335614
    },
    {
        "question": "44×14954502=？",
        "answer": 8.818224631650041
    },
    {
        "question": "230×3956059=？",
        "answer": 8.958990595986052
    },
    {
        "question": "9×27418=？",
        "answer": 5.392278281532405
    },
    {
        "question": "60476÷8926=？",
        "answer": 0.830926175858737
    },
    {
        "question": "11638375÷310977=？",
        "answer": 1.573164076884621
    },
    {
        "question": "313603316÷11355124=？",
        "answer": 1.4411887650534696
    },
    {
        "question": "81023421÷2315453=？",
        "answer": 1.5439746062377737
    },
    {
        "question": "196966÷616=？",
        "answer": 2.5048105531506915
    },
    {
        "question": "19273365÷206=？",
        "answer": 4.97109032580414
    },
    {
        "question": "18019×11545=？",
        "answer": 8.318124622534825
    },
    {
        "question": "162031÷49613=？",
        "answer": 0.5140026235676705
    },
    {
        "question": "45478824÷2489=？",
        "answer": 4.2617843294837545
    },
    {
        "question": "3×10767=？",
        "answer": 4.5092159677725645
    },
    {
        "question": "176215÷6657=？",
        "answer": 1.4227643172716704
    },
    {
        "question": "19×137064=？",
        "answer": 6.415677002829207
    },
    {
        "question": "1885738÷270=？",
        "answer": 3.844117588580385
    },
    {
        "question": "2×10501=？",
        "answer": 4.322260654143684
    },
    {
        "question": "3971123÷8003=？",
        "answer": 2.6956605220445122
    },
    {
        "question": "7×3047=？",
        "answer": 4.3289704942369305
    },
    {
        "question": "23344×925=？",
        "answer": 7.334317007288409
    },
    {
        "question": "42927301÷8948944=？",
        "answer": 0.6809617932228096
    },
    {
        "question": "366×29018=？",
        "answer": 7.026148561762982
    },
    {
        "question": "43923÷666=？",
        "answer": 1.8192177661822615
    },
    {
        "question": "15879817÷19150=？",
        "answer": 2.918676714978619
    },
    {
        "question": "793×2249=？",
        "answer": 6.251262642753236
    },
    {
        "question": "1×6884859=？",
        "answer": 6.837895050453656
    },
    {
        "question": "1520÷223=？",
        "answer": 0.8335387248966118
    },
    {
        "question": "845713162÷324208=？",
        "answer": 3.416399362568593
    },
    {
        "question": "55455÷721=？",
        "answer": 1.886005444909359
    },
    {
        "question": "315×1100=？",
        "answer": 5.539703238947825
    },
    {
        "question": "710102÷17909=？",
        "answer": 1.5982493993822244
    },
    {
        "question": "371195÷1403=？",
        "answer": 2.4225444466072728
    },
    {
        "question": "4×6668259=？",
        "answer": 7.426072451123153
    },
    {
        "question": "4127105÷10063=？",
        "answer": 2.612918045458368
    },
    {
        "question": "33350585÷1334=？",
        "answer": 4.397947626664351
    },
    {
        "question": "4×7284=？",
        "answer": 4.464429928450845
    },
    {
        "question": "6×5011=？",
        "answer": 4.478075653126121
    },
    {
        "question": "26826838÷232349=？",
        "answer": 2.0624286790114663
    },
    {
        "question": "2539927÷7229=？",
        "answer": 2.5457430100017997
    },
    {
        "question": "28×2353309=？",
        "answer": 7.818836987070807
    },
    {
        "question": "843653÷249=？",
        "answer": 3.529964508092764
    },
    {
        "question": "2×2929=？",
        "answer": 3.76774936734558
    },
    {
        "question": "16813293÷424215=？",
        "answer": 1.5980667604987753
    },
    {
        "question": "7484654÷1879835=？",
        "answer": 0.6000519972918381
    },
    {
        "question": "1679987÷434=？",
        "answer": 3.5878161915882876
    },
    {
        "question": "8×113999=？",
        "answer": 5.959991028710989
    },
    {
        "question": "186910968÷6439309=？",
        "answer": 1.462795520805434
    },
    {
        "question": "8×6120636=？",
        "answer": 7.689886539356349
    },
    {
        "question": "18563×1519=？",
        "answer": 7.450205938534388
    },
    {
        "question": "52×337156=？",
        "answer": 7.243834236384535
    },
    {
        "question": "10×1022483=？",
        "answer": 7.0096560960754015
    },
    {
        "question": "83586881÷31239=？",
        "answer": 3.427440996955097
    },
    {
        "question": "12567÷8389=？",
        "answer": 0.17552142068431914
    },
    {
        "question": "119448124÷6344253=？",
        "answer": 1.2747988395844831
    },
    {
        "question": "8755917÷8540695=？",
        "answer": 0.010808423217440572
    },
    {
        "question": "59031297÷242628=？",
        "answer": 2.386141407071598
    },
    {
        "question": "1196396÷81584=？",
        "answer": 1.166269957729169
    },
    {
        "question": "200575×1769=？",
        "answer": 8.550004633784257
    },
    {
        "question": "1×14319=？",
        "answer": 4.155912689085906
    },
    {
        "question": "6×299426=？",
        "answer": 6.254440759036877
    },
    {
        "question": "2×5805=？",
        "answer": 4.064832219738574
    },
    {
        "question": "16×48409929=？",
        "answer": 8.88905442834307
    },
    {
        "question": "51320514÷1572=？",
        "answer": 4.513838455692523
    },
    {
        "question": "3247÷1278=？",
        "answer": 0.4049514348036201
    },
    {
        "question": "41×662=？",
        "answer": 4.433641846159436
    },
    {
        "question": "580039×551=？",
        "answer": 8.504608793992945
    },
    {
        "question": "8022530÷286128=？",
        "answer": 1.4477509905961443
    },
    {
        "question": "36562666÷1838=？",
        "answer": 4.298692348142874
    },
    {
        "question": "1193600÷405=？",
        "answer": 3.469403786913925
    },
    {
        "question": "443509698÷358896560=？",
        "answer": 0.09193382509810086
    },
    {
        "question": "3683×12764=？",
        "answer": 7.672188514376386
    },
    {
        "question": "63657×14117=？",
        "answer": 8.953588582235176
    },
    {
        "question": "12275×1553=？",
        "answer": 7.280192956523565
    },
    {
        "question": "27430866÷4266651=？",
        "answer": 0.8081523983672254
    },
    {
        "question": "96842×4266=？",
        "answer": 8.616084601110641
    },
    {
        "question": "1840×3510=？",
        "answer": 6.810124939475361
    },
    {
        "question": "4712686÷467970=？",
        "answer": 1.0030504914679705
    },
    {
        "question": "715637499÷170520=？",
        "answer": 3.6229177653015867
    },
    {
        "question": "2638105÷105121=？",
        "answer": 1.3996025934255463
    },
    {
        "question": "42×155293=？",
        "answer": 6.814401170273984
    },
    {
        "question": "217667780÷63900167=？",
        "answer": 0.5322921547352885
    },
    {
        "question": "103713261÷289325=？",
        "answer": 2.554448327968303
    },
    {
        "question": "772140160÷95555391=？",
        "answer": 0.9074409473467786
    },
    {
        "question": "1×5327=？",
        "answer": 3.7264826967848297
    },
    {
        "question": "297493÷92169=？",
        "answer": 0.5088918756717622
    },
    {
        "question": "5×339=？",
        "answer": 3.229169702539101
    },
    {
        "question": "1206×101221=？",
        "answer": 8.086617931355212
    },
    {
        "question": "2483×128134=？",
        "answer": 8.502641103422212
    },
    {
        "question": "122×578=？",
        "answer": 4.848287669095277
    },
    {
        "question": "35×65641=？",
        "answer": 6.3612432329893105
    },
    {
        "question": "121356×853=？",
        "answer": 8.015010284455782
    },
    {
        "question": "187441096÷726=？",
        "answer": 5.41192819429001
    },
    {
        "question": "225×1169=？",
        "answer": 5.419997029273203
    },
    {
        "question": "12×67481=？",
        "answer": 5.908362755816283
    },
    {
        "question": "1×5750=？",
        "answer": 3.7596678446896306
    },
    {
        "question": "2×490688=？",
        "answer": 5.991835432904103
    },
    {
        "question": "962×7496=？",
        "answer": 6.858004649917535
    },
    {
        "question": "69159417÷9446=？",
        "answer": 3.8646033823613464
    },
    {
        "question": "40777÷309=？",
        "answer": 2.120456791762954
    },
    {
        "question": "8×64688428=？",
        "answer": 8.713916584426746
    },
    {
        "question": "1709045÷795101=？",
        "answer": 0.33233119838870545
    },
    {
        "question": "54×2096065=？",
        "answer": 8.053798506027606
    },
    {
        "question": "72490506÷4465=？",
        "answer": 4.210459668011197
    },
    {
        "question": "938874926÷20751252=？",
        "answer": 1.6555634363226621
    },
    {
        "question": "2×209748176=？",
        "answer": 8.622728188494495
    },
    {
        "question": "244541091÷35056412=？",
        "answer": 0.8435843811573286
    },
    {
        "question": "2412531÷1267505=？",
        "answer": 0.27952322135634
    },
    {
        "question": "128×1848685=？",
        "answer": 8.374072887071971
    },
    {
        "question": "151×160429=？",
        "answer": 7.384259823719983
    },
    {
        "question": "1721501÷71911=？",
        "answer": 1.3791119511890026
    },
    {
        "question": "5×403747=？",
        "answer": 6.305079312707287
    },
    {
        "question": "304×3086=？",
        "answer": 5.972269505335883
    },
    {
        "question": "19928050÷103718=？",
        "answer": 2.28361067053281
    },
    {
        "question": "17×794261=？",
        "answer": 7.130412159616168
    },
    {
        "question": "19445×291=？",
        "answer": 6.7527009364693855
    },
    {
        "question": "266178÷118469=？",
        "answer": 0.3515674349691551
    },
    {
        "question": "147425×1209=？",
        "answer": 8.250997437310616
    },
    {
        "question": "82×2081=？",
        "answer": 5.232085932595344
    },
    {
        "question": "441×2762=？",
        "answer": 6.085662263710451
    },
    {
        "question": "2×88925=？",
        "answer": 5.250053869521799
    },
    {
        "question": "26329×1466=？",
        "answer": 7.586568334814547
    },
    {
        "question": "158×331=？",
        "answer": 4.718485080730141
    },
    {
        "question": "39227358÷276=？",
        "answer": 5.152679976901439
    },
    {
        "question": "139302÷29607=？",
        "answer": 0.6725629480701721
    },
    {
        "question": "541131455÷3752257=？",
        "answer": 2.159010202953614
    },
    {
        "question": "1×278=？",
        "answer": 2.444044795918076
    },
    {
        "question": "26096÷5573=？",
        "answer": 0.6704849006400003
    },
    {
        "question": "41051796÷2053=？",
        "answer": 4.300943212714029
    },
    {
        "question": "3×4131636=？",
        "answer": 7.093243307607219
    },
    {
        "question": "211715÷9842=？",
        "answer": 1.3326682681595645
    },
    {
        "question": "1×198229323=？",
        "answer": 8.297167897753443
    },
    {
        "question": "42995×214=？",
        "answer": 6.963831726634179
    },
    {
        "question": "32671202÷2337=？",
        "answer": 4.145506400423104
    },
    {
        "question": "109709÷522=？",
        "answer": 2.3225717534695254
    },
    {
        "question": "1718468×366=？",
        "answer": 8.798622534842451
    },
    {
        "question": "135×39366=？",
        "answer": 6.7254550566359494
    },
    {
        "question": "177556÷4688=？",
        "answer": 1.5783477496223266
    },
    {
        "question": "30×13488532=？",
        "answer": 8.607085941308457
    },
    {
        "question": "7311848÷17236=？",
        "answer": 2.6275906692121547
    },
    {
        "question": "206×84441=？",
        "answer": 7.240420588205984
    },
    {
        "question": "170×361128=？",
        "answer": 7.788110084061705
    },
    {
        "question": "447671355÷4375764=？",
        "answer": 2.0099054152519367
    },
    {
        "question": "682365÷538=？",
        "answer": 3.10323446714623
    },
    {
        "question": "274581÷63168=？",
        "answer": 0.6381733556986339
    },
    {
        "question": "1×222024=？",
        "answer": 5.346399922667743
    },
    {
        "question": "13173×1430=？",
        "answer": 7.275020729289112
    },
    {
        "question": "1449×10041=？",
        "answer": 7.162845352548614
    },
    {
        "question": "1274464÷45054=？",
        "answer": 1.4515942176773875
    },
    {
        "question": "58×766=？",
        "answer": 4.647656763195541
    },
    {
        "question": "476062×1103=？",
        "answer": 8.720239029245619
    },
    {
        "question": "478526500÷6702=？",
        "answer": 4.853701569784133
    },
    {
        "question": "78351÷16456=？",
        "answer": 0.6777202650880808
    },
    {
        "question": "37×300129=？",
        "answer": 7.045509685274857
    },
    {
        "question": "1415396÷614032=？",
        "answer": 0.36268695913540483
    },
    {
        "question": "9781×3331=？",
        "answer": 7.51295789159741
    },
    {
        "question": "42032663÷35499=？",
        "answer": 3.0733707865817914
    },
    {
        "question": "15×51044084=？",
        "answer": 8.88403667374425
    },
    {
        "question": "175261633÷7248=？",
        "answer": 4.383468669245466
    },
    {
        "question": "30×474909=？",
        "answer": 7.153731654693975
    },
    {
        "question": "519479÷796=？",
        "answer": 2.814654928104594
    },
    {
        "question": "204338÷49026=？",
        "answer": 0.6199226774372056
    },
    {
        "question": "32193×1140=？",
        "answer": 7.564666300924767
    },
    {
        "question": "168144×1512=？",
        "answer": 8.405233165858467
    },
    {
        "question": "201×345112=？",
        "answer": 7.841156117967194
    },
    {
        "question": "30743629÷2968=？",
        "answer": 4.015291234014507
    },
    {
        "question": "13×13640=？",
        "answer": 5.248757722627297
    },
    {
        "question": "3×3064738=？",
        "answer": 6.963514607956548
    },
    {
        "question": "241×135827=？",
        "answer": 7.51500315114585
    },
    {
        "question": "131894÷1370=？",
        "answer": 1.9835044723159625
    },
    {
        "question": "455222634÷131898220=？",
        "answer": 0.5379849126894247
    },
    {
        "question": "7×1319=？",
        "answer": 3.965342835560622
    },
    {
        "question": "471185636÷33582637=？",
        "answer": 1.1470772474753408
    },
    {
        "question": "102223834÷997622=？",
        "answer": 2.010586147713884
    },
    {
        "question": "2972840÷118232=？",
        "answer": 1.400436499722173
    },
    {
        "question": "400086576÷385287398=？",
        "answer": 0.016369175535467524
    },
    {
        "question": "46×10569948=？",
        "answer": 8.686830682435678
    },
    {
        "question": "174×1303=？",
        "answer": 5.355493663995184
    },
    {
        "question": "15×896582=？",
        "answer": 7.1286812746705035
    },
    {
        "question": "202×43533=？",
        "answer": 6.944169966274404
    },
    {
        "question": "1141×507947=？",
        "answer": 8.76310404408728
    },
    {
        "question": "1389497÷1088=？",
        "answer": 3.1062287180867085
    },
    {
        "question": "39479×17568=？",
        "answer": 8.841088466261462
    },
    {
        "question": "195075427÷19733207=？",
        "answer": 0.9950048945851175
    },
    {
        "question": "12×3652654=？",
        "answer": 7.641789781383678
    },
    {
        "question": "3673÷216=？",
        "answer": 1.230567177194363
    },
    {
        "question": "990222535÷2113900=？",
        "answer": 2.6706483668151857
    },
    {
        "question": "69428964÷3039291=？",
        "answer": 1.358768400845035
    },
    {
        "question": "58×230054=？",
        "answer": 7.125257782404027
    },
    {
        "question": "69436685÷1428998=？",
        "answer": 1.6865573579046305
    },
    {
        "question": "3350÷2169=？",
        "answer": 0.188785255022652
    },
    {
        "question": "234210÷127632=？",
        "answer": 0.26364585937719587
    },
    {
        "question": "10×515802=？",
        "answer": 6.7124830217632985
    },
    {
        "question": "226162325÷12712=？",
        "answer": 4.250206375950872
    },
    {
        "question": "1285×259792=？",
        "answer": 8.52352890100421
    },
    {
        "question": "1417×163553=？",
        "answer": 8.36502836490532
    },
    {
        "question": "5×100451=？",
        "answer": 5.700924268887884
    },
    {
        "question": "126118×1572=？",
        "answer": 8.297229616720495
    },
    {
        "question": "1×360=？",
        "answer": 2.5563025007672873
    },
    {
        "question": "8130119÷56609=？",
        "answer": 2.1572114192545726
    },
    {
        "question": "7×410=？",
        "answer": 3.4578818967339924
    },
    {
        "question": "9×646=？",
        "answer": 3.764475027434409
    },
    {
        "question": "87056181÷206646=？",
        "answer": 2.6245726083530947
    },
    {
        "question": "4201×2067=？",
        "answer": 6.938693158165281
    },
    {
        "question": "787244÷210962=？",
        "answer": 0.5719051252530801
    },
    {
        "question": "1×30053012=？",
        "answer": 7.477888004772262
    },
    {
        "question": "1×25085=？",
        "answer": 4.39941410536377
    },
    {
        "question": "14449×236=？",
        "answer": 6.532749794041214
    },
    {
        "question": "1517631÷23730=？",
        "answer": 1.8058684509016931
    },
    {
        "question": "324497948÷323=？",
        "answer": 6.002009432502991
    },
    {
        "question": "1×371040=？",
        "answer": 5.569420731293912
    },
    {
        "question": "22744×518=？",
        "answer": 7.071196606427619
    },
    {
        "question": "6×1439632=？",
        "answer": 6.936402741927288
    },
    {
        "question": "5932206÷137999=？",
        "answer": 1.6333402844692904
    },
    {
        "question": "100×233639=？",
        "answer": 7.3685453387446325
    },
    {
        "question": "3355×118416=？",
        "answer": 8.599102911370334
    },
    {
        "question": "31×18284=？",
        "answer": 5.7534329064515655
    },
    {
        "question": "3564÷559=？",
        "answer": 0.8045258874784138
    },
    {
        "question": "581×130477=？",
        "answer": 7.8797100949962475
    },
    {
        "question": "6971×54678=？",
        "answer": 8.581107703393647
    },
    {
        "question": "246548×524=？",
        "answer": 8.111232770863714
    },
    {
        "question": "359×4939=？",
        "answer": 6.2487334747398675
    },
    {
        "question": "6162192÷4218=？",
        "answer": 3.1646286504244965
    },
    {
        "question": "8×1570975=？",
        "answer": 7.099259260861683
    },
    {
        "question": "20×434431=？",
        "answer": 6.938950803608903
    },
    {
        "question": "33×255=？",
        "answer": 3.9250541203118425
    },
    {
        "question": "2×13778=？",
        "answer": 4.44021617608011
    },
    {
        "question": "5730748÷932907=？",
        "answer": 0.7883729597234193
    },
    {
        "question": "3975×3171=？",
        "answer": 7.100533375019578
    },
    {
        "question": "5429005÷40199=？",
        "answer": 2.130504992027217
    },
    {
        "question": "15371005÷79750=？",
        "answer": 2.2849715721065906
    },
    {
        "question": "41596÷697=？",
        "answer": 1.7758187914361578
    },
    {
        "question": "766924÷245186=？",
        "answer": 0.49525666017301956
    },
    {
        "question": "34×134706=？",
        "answer": 6.660865857300195
    },
    {
        "question": "770609÷19312=？",
        "answer": 1.6010068241109807
    },
    {
        "question": "303027÷775=？",
        "answer": 2.59217962378015
    },
    {
        "question": "375150×217=？",
        "answer": 7.910664684634713
    },
    {
        "question": "1778×23484=？",
        "answer": 7.6207038283398205
    },
    {
        "question": "343508×516=？",
        "answer": 8.248586557478086
    },
    {
        "question": "222195÷208269=？",
        "answer": 0.028109650114258946
    },
    {
        "question": "4705×7417=？",
        "answer": 7.54278790677507
    },
    {
        "question": "10×1872=？",
        "answer": 4.272305844402086
    },
    {
        "question": "11476×1380=？",
        "answer": 7.199669625975197
    },
    {
        "question": "818×961509=？",
        "answer": 8.895706657385754
    },
    {
        "question": "102×3437=？",
        "answer": 5.544779703899143
    },
    {
        "question": "10827217÷9759=？",
        "answer": 3.0451115230316637
    },
    {
        "question": "411678518÷148717=？",
        "answer": 3.442197589425639
    },
    {
        "question": "15×53707=？",
        "answer": 5.906122153009403
    },
    {
        "question": "18×4141989=？",
        "answer": 7.872481446293853
    },
    {
        "question": "804147881÷3564915=？",
        "answer": 2.353286742661508
    },
    {
        "question": "2×2434=？",
        "answer": 3.6873505695580273
    },
    {
        "question": "101209811÷103728=？",
        "answer": 2.9893266095951208
    },
    {
        "question": "16×585894=？",
        "answer": 6.971939033180536
    },
    {
        "question": "845391×201=？",
        "answer": 8.230253677455785
    },
    {
        "question": "7309×31688=？",
        "answer": 8.364752791280209
    },
    {
        "question": "2664×2262=？",
        "answer": 6.7800268210877
    },
    {
        "question": "9×14709=？",
        "answer": 5.121825657405165
    },
    {
        "question": "72×314=？",
        "answer": 4.354262144504483
    },
    {
        "question": "271444414÷31339788=？",
        "answer": 0.9375848544951498
    },
    {
        "question": "1823×27534=？",
        "answer": 7.700655976733279
    },
    {
        "question": "57×31106=？",
        "answer": 6.248719023334814
    },
    {
        "question": "18035×1025=？",
        "answer": 7.266840012046155
    },
    {
        "question": "161642428÷1663=？",
        "answer": 4.987663116054447
    },
    {
        "question": "176×568=？",
        "answer": 4.999861003525169
    },
    {
        "question": "154859÷7950=？",
        "answer": 1.289569321829068
    },
    {
        "question": "124×123370=？",
        "answer": 7.1846312498963645
    },
    {
        "question": "7472×9896=？",
        "answer": 7.868896549843101
    },
    {
        "question": "938×1040495=？",
        "answer": 8.989442835970797
    },
    {
        "question": "1×330120=？",
        "answer": 5.518671836437308
    },
    {
        "question": "1333×209=？",
        "answer": 5.4449764355249135
    },
    {
        "question": "266262949÷1760=？",
        "answer": 5.17979806991902
    },
    {
        "question": "4983224÷67582=？",
        "answer": 1.8676793695020226
    },
    {
        "question": "255×255=？",
        "answer": 4.81308036086791
    },
    {
        "question": "2×4427782=？",
        "answer": 6.9472162260893455
    },
    {
        "question": "6082626÷6666=？",
        "answer": 2.96022580466765
    },
    {
        "question": "16511883÷24781=？",
        "answer": 2.823677774936995
    },
    {
        "question": "10×234270=？",
        "answer": 6.369716677548561
    },
    {
        "question": "25×3226=？",
        "answer": 4.90660437172498
    },
    {
        "question": "137280845÷1160763=？",
        "answer": 2.0728663874510316
    },
    {
        "question": "23×15256=？",
        "answer": 5.545168516055542
    },
    {
        "question": "4122080÷301=？",
        "answer": 4.136549920578464
    },
    {
        "question": "1725521÷1496133=？",
        "answer": 0.061950046909180385
    },
    {
        "question": "102623×963=？",
        "answer": 7.994870993452493
    },
    {
        "question": "87093097÷1628=？",
        "answer": 4.7283293336322805
    },
    {
        "question": "3199×12559=？",
        "answer": 7.603969300522576
    },
    {
        "question": "11455691÷1555=？",
        "answer": 3.8672908973197813
    },
    {
        "question": "19238×2055=？",
        "answer": 7.59697174661077
    },
    {
        "question": "40×14539011=？",
        "answer": 8.764594856458205
    },
    {
        "question": "960814÷22732=？",
        "answer": 1.6260016751637574
    },
    {
        "question": "40×296=？",
        "answer": 4.073351702386901
    },
    {
        "question": "520697113÷302=？",
        "answer": 6.2365782267837515
    },
    {
        "question": "79172÷311=？",
        "answer": 2.405811226962424
    },
    {
        "question": "14891×439=？",
        "answer": 6.815388383870666
    },
    {
        "question": "47805×4407=？",
        "answer": 8.323616373039332
    },
    {
        "question": "1×457942814=？",
        "answer": 8.660811248495444
    },
    {
        "question": "1×694659=？",
        "answer": 5.841771666804079
    },
    {
        "question": "334196795÷449=？",
        "answer": 5.871755939621408
    },
    {
        "question": "90974÷18430=？",
        "answer": 0.6933919552346506
    },
    {
        "question": "14×18888745=？",
        "answer": 8.422331139302504
    },
    {
        "question": "12×114199=？",
        "answer": 6.136843547011891
    },
    {
        "question": "86223954÷26418916=？",
        "answer": 0.5137129405408453
    },
    {
        "question": "3×11721512=？",
        "answer": 7.546104891222791
    },
    {
        "question": "166×2253588=？",
        "answer": 8.572982609474439
    },
    {
        "question": "1704×375994=？",
        "answer": 8.806650505071953
    },
    {
        "question": "49165÷3275=？",
        "answer": 1.1764447391703448
    },
    {
        "question": "57736823÷5463=？",
        "answer": 4.024021682398163
    },
    {
        "question": "1×238=？",
        "answer": 2.376576957056512
    },
    {
        "question": "10722×4189=？",
        "answer": 7.652386163250507
    },
    {
        "question": "316×7572=？",
        "answer": 6.378897687910163
    },
    {
        "question": "18179÷3511=？",
        "answer": 0.7141391601782083
    },
    {
        "question": "4882÷4014=？",
        "answer": 0.08502040692970306
    },
    {
        "question": "11×1880322=？",
        "answer": 7.315624912532883
    },
    {
        "question": "11×208=？",
        "answer": 3.3594560201209864
    },
    {
        "question": "6×10348233=？",
        "answer": 7.79301744907862
    },
    {
        "question": "835×31596=？",
        "answer": 7.421318580637295
    },
    {
        "question": "78875×1895=？",
        "answer": 8.174548586556282
    },
    {
        "question": "7266902÷386048=？",
        "answer": 1.2747079965778454
    },
    {
        "question": "266×871=？",
        "answer": 5.36489979163873
    },
    {
        "question": "19×2528161=？",
        "answer": 7.681558328468694
    },
    {
        "question": "5611×212=？",
        "answer": 6.075376129632208
    },
    {
        "question": "111060÷33409=？",
        "answer": 0.5216941926298592
    },
    {
        "question": "9932÷412=？",
        "answer": 1.3821394948493921
    },
    {
        "question": "310×1672129=？",
        "answer": 8.714631472814702
    },
    {
        "question": "140632872÷1554=？",
        "answer": 4.9566358315361505
    },
    {
        "question": "77×202230=？",
        "answer": 7.192336307030936
    },
    {
        "question": "80357773÷56691=？",
        "answer": 3.15151377460741
    },
    {
        "question": "41173×1225=？",
        "answer": 7.702748600973198
    },
    {
        "question": "834499600÷530=？",
        "answer": 6.197150263244513
    },
    {
        "question": "280349÷35174=？",
        "answer": 0.901477252065514
    },
    {
        "question": "22298655÷73383=？",
        "answer": 2.48268320591305
    },
    {
        "question": "2683422÷390660=？",
        "answer": 0.8368900302808457
    },
    {
        "question": "521×16212=？",
        "answer": 6.92667431836918
    },
    {
        "question": "109895156÷11998616=？",
        "answer": 0.9618473953212207
    },
    {
        "question": "595170304÷661=？",
        "answer": 5.9544397944858645
    },
    {
        "question": "71×254=？",
        "answer": 4.256092065339013
    },
    {
        "question": "4×4607363=？",
        "answer": 7.265512421658878
    },
    {
        "question": "1034998÷348181=？",
        "answer": 0.473134442301873
    },
    {
        "question": "43×20978953=？",
        "answer": 8.955252265573021
    },
    {
        "question": "123424×5329=？",
        "answer": 8.81804533742686
    },
    {
        "question": "669916604÷270726277=？",
        "answer": 0.3934903310569201
    },
    {
        "question": "104348389÷42790912=？",
        "answer": 0.387134205852082
    },
    {
        "question": "30797389÷42628=？",
        "answer": 2.858818941506669
    },
    {
        "question": "1814×6366=？",
        "answer": 7.062503917009061
    },
    {
        "question": "459×758=？",
        "answer": 5.5414818911693144
    },
    {
        "question": "3456×69824=？",
        "answer": 8.382578458379085
    },
    {
        "question": "236303580÷5697410=？",
        "answer": 1.6177928277369766
    },
    {
        "question": "81477×1171=？",
        "answer": 7.9795919248821825
    },
    {
        "question": "3266×3821=？",
        "answer": 7.096193218089058
    },
    {
        "question": "727174÷354=？",
        "answer": 3.3126350803300473
    },
    {
        "question": "106×661=？",
        "answer": 4.84550732475041
    },
    {
        "question": "137×6132=？",
        "answer": 5.924322713338745
    },
    {
        "question": "7089021÷378725=？",
        "answer": 1.2722622886145087
    },
    {
        "question": "62×95783=？",
        "answer": 6.773680124867631
    },
    {
        "question": "23048024÷2848=？",
        "answer": 3.9080937125403623
    },
    {
        "question": "563×139942=？",
        "answer": 7.896456471250085
    },
    {
        "question": "95811145÷11234=？",
        "answer": 3.9308816107333784
    },
    {
        "question": "15×260=？",
        "answer": 3.591064607026499
    },
    {
        "question": "3743651÷1307879=？",
        "answer": 0.45672778849636403
    },
    {
        "question": "51539×215=？",
        "answer": 7.044574447690927
    },
    {
        "question": "58243308÷889=？",
        "answer": 4.816344272322187
    },
    {
        "question": "7986×96092=？",
        "answer": 8.88501653847507
    },
    {
        "question": "5704×4684=？",
        "answer": 7.4267964032441345
    },
    {
        "question": "3×20372975=？",
        "answer": 7.786175706976766
    },
    {
        "question": "21×9535=？",
        "answer": 5.301539992115944
    },
    {
        "question": "131×6098=？",
        "answer": 5.9024587156851265
    },
    {
        "question": "468911÷203=？",
        "answer": 3.3635943828897585
    },
    {
        "question": "65648÷12210=？",
        "answer": 0.730505835677955
    },
    {
        "question": "354285÷2202=？",
        "answer": 2.2065354505816304
    },
    {
        "question": "42×294=？",
        "answer": 4.091596620810058
    },
    {
        "question": "2437333÷341=？",
        "answer": 3.854160489618851
    },
    {
        "question": "2×1025997=？",
        "answer": 6.312176086571016
    },
    {
        "question": "7811943÷7594876=？",
        "answer": 0.012238378170142788
    },
    {
        "question": "3275÷3169=？",
        "answer": 0.014289065137501328
    },
    {
        "question": "162×31334=？",
        "answer": 6.705530853632493
    },
    {
        "question": "83640÷16986=？",
        "answer": 0.6923229043968876
    },
    {
        "question": "391429355÷10516=？",
        "answer": 4.570802814752408
    },
    {
        "question": "1×7306=？",
        "answer": 3.863679667875898
    },
    {
        "question": "33×14275767=？",
        "answer": 8.673113390940715
    },
    {
        "question": "195042×4741=？",
        "answer": 8.965998096959293
    },
    {
        "question": "1619×5043=？",
        "answer": 6.911935816912507
    },
    {
        "question": "3390696÷17315=？",
        "answer": 2.291866358050426
    },
    {
        "question": "997032743÷303457288=？",
        "answer": 0.5166118487593689
    },
    {
        "question": "378×847712=？",
        "answer": 8.505740130802598
    },
    {
        "question": "12×345=？",
        "answer": 3.617000341120899
    },
    {
        "question": "69618347÷6022999=？",
        "answer": 1.0629109162304247
    },
    {
        "question": "65×6804=？",
        "answer": 5.645677661583387
    },
    {
        "question": "2×2072456=？",
        "answer": 6.617515314543686
    },
    {
        "question": "8249×22573=？",
        "answer": 8.26999058518336
    },
    {
        "question": "185890÷7400=？",
        "answer": 1.4000243076867973
    },
    {
        "question": "171519152÷6494=？",
        "answer": 4.421800336552503
    },
    {
        "question": "4747÷2747=？",
        "answer": 0.2375605722977981
    },
    {
        "question": "55643×3103=？",
        "answer": 8.237192312582149
    },
    {
        "question": "2×1761=？",
        "answer": 3.5467893516312583
    },
    {
        "question": "8456×25163=？",
        "answer": 8.327927391906305
    },
    {
        "question": "267683×891=？",
        "answer": 8.377498494945035
    },
    {
        "question": "97×1936=？",
        "answer": 5.27367708723862
    },
    {
        "question": "224×34932=？",
        "answer": 6.893471469820598
    },
    {
        "question": "4120340÷419376=？",
        "answer": 0.9923294813029246
    },
    {
        "question": "7272462÷14782=？",
        "answer": 2.691948262711068
    },
    {
        "question": "356340426÷162029=？",
        "answer": 3.3422723431951527
    },
    {
        "question": "79781÷211=？",
        "answer": 2.577617020293076
    },
    {
        "question": "4×78810056=？",
        "answer": 8.498641627430096
    },
    {
        "question": "52252×2696=？",
        "answer": 8.148822806040451
    },
    {
        "question": "156720685÷997=？",
        "answer": 5.196431162907987
    },
    {
        "question": "917×2300=？",
        "answer": 6.3240971716876135
    },
    {
        "question": "7692×438=？",
        "answer": 6.527513386070542
    },
    {
        "question": "5832×135701=？",
        "answer": 8.89840056335935
    },
    {
        "question": "11146405÷4732=？",
        "answer": 3.372090082960745
    },
    {
        "question": "89×4682389=？",
        "answer": 8.619857497495417
    },
    {
        "question": "238×335123=？",
        "answer": 7.90178119220394
    },
    {
        "question": "54×297550=？",
        "answer": 7.2059537144237815
    },
    {
        "question": "137693158÷27054=？",
        "answer": 3.706680874924954
    },
    {
        "question": "1×63515=？",
        "answer": 4.802876302424737
    },
    {
        "question": "30×10019=？",
        "answer": 5.477945631325268
    },
    {
        "question": "102893÷1729=？",
        "answer": 1.774590836641266
    },
    {
        "question": "26157÷7848=？",
        "answer": 0.5228289380112993
    },
    {
        "question": "26040562÷1308=？",
        "answer": 4.299042608828991
    },
    {
        "question": "48×6427=？",
        "answer": 5.489249537285987
    },
    {
        "question": "1×237806=？",
        "answer": 5.376222807953062
    },
    {
        "question": "22401×17020=？",
        "answer": 8.581226961796487
    },
    {
        "question": "49×109699=？",
        "answer": 6.730398748656448
    },
    {
        "question": "3227×3930=？",
        "answer": 7.103191515779332
    },
    {
        "question": "1608503÷13170=？",
        "answer": 2.0868361002744833
    },
    {
        "question": "7×97832561=？",
        "answer": 8.835581462379807
    },
    {
        "question": "537548808÷1007=？",
        "answer": 5.7273884326065385
    },
    {
        "question": "275396883÷12692471=？",
        "answer": 1.3364128407187328
    },
    {
        "question": "216874833÷2786=？",
        "answer": 4.891228045627609
    },
    {
        "question": "142×5558=？",
        "answer": 5.897206886824409
    },
    {
        "question": "143388128÷1447968=？",
        "answer": 1.9957542307766858
    },
    {
        "question": "2031111÷444573=？",
        "answer": 0.6597905747972987
    },
    {
        "question": "91497142÷114427=？",
        "answer": 2.902879016743294
    },
    {
        "question": "19×1093=？",
        "answer": 4.317373762902532
    },
    {
        "question": "794712÷107386=？",
        "answer": 0.869262105100666
    },
    {
        "question": "22285÷492=？",
        "answer": 1.6560475356548348
    },
    {
        "question": "821190099÷1336=？",
        "answer": 5.788637246349106
    },
    {
        "question": "3865875÷1007156=？",
        "answer": 0.5841510630230122
    },
    {
        "question": "68585×229=？",
        "answer": 7.196064625312674
    },
    {
        "question": "400284981÷365850732=？",
        "answer": 0.039065367034566575
    },
    {
        "question": "24×15961=？",
        "answer": 5.583271339307567
    },
    {
        "question": "107690755÷3406=？",
        "answer": 4.499933778103881
    },
    {
        "question": "321×6766=？",
        "answer": 6.336837025856834
    },
    {
        "question": "571414809÷219097=？",
        "answer": 3.4163150605350476
    },
    {
        "question": "38902÷3416=？",
        "answer": 1.0564540674998921
    },
    {
        "question": "149650÷539=？",
        "answer": 2.4434879559894713
    },
    {
        "question": "3654×5145=？",
        "answer": 7.274153922114971
    },
    {
        "question": "3962×321=？",
        "answer": 6.1044195036074
    },
    {
        "question": "275725×2880=？",
        "answer": 8.899868633153412
    },
    {
        "question": "675÷252=？",
        "answer": 0.4279032320494808
    },
    {
        "question": "942×22397=？",
        "answer": 7.324240752792211
    },
    {
        "question": "1045615÷550546=？",
        "answer": 0.27857819323054234
    },
    {
        "question": "54438938÷4090156=？",
        "answer": 1.1241697718869688
    },
    {
        "question": "9873145÷12697=？",
        "answer": 2.890754395651753
    },
    {
        "question": "338÷286=？",
        "answer": 0.07255066714861175
    },
    {
        "question": "3110309÷32853=？",
        "answer": 1.9762285033610818
    },
    {
        "question": "233947871÷2785299=？",
        "answer": 1.924247274091486
    },
    {
        "question": "67309×899=？",
        "answer": 7.781832830088103
    },
    {
        "question": "809226÷414=？",
        "answer": 3.2910694868522254
    },
    {
        "question": "18745879÷35368=？",
        "answer": 2.7242953075383003
    },
    {
        "question": "675561862÷466016719=？",
        "answer": 0.1612636261492068
    },
    {
        "question": "6592×1508=？",
        "answer": 6.997418540222815
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1453=？",
        "answer": 3.1622656142980214
    },
    {
        "question": "4×185736531=？",
        "answer": 8.870957321300466
    },
    {
        "question": "50756×2999=？",
        "answer": 8.182463854470257
    },
    {
        "question": "2995×11855=？",
        "answer": 7.550298385039537
    },
    {
        "question": "2209×319=？",
        "answer": 5.847986398928616
    },
    {
        "question": "163696÷6018=？",
        "answer": 1.4345858839177643
    },
    {
        "question": "54714349÷293=？",
        "answer": 5.271233615930137
    },
    {
        "question": "23739244÷2758586=？",
        "answer": 0.9347803564905303
    },
    {
        "question": "246×1507546=？",
        "answer": 8.569205679816978
    },
    {
        "question": "35814507÷202685=？",
        "answer": 2.2472373680271795
    },
    {
        "question": "39843911÷258=？",
        "answer": 5.188742255373622
    },
    {
        "question": "947943÷1047=？",
        "answer": 2.956835542231261
    },
    {
        "question": "4825980÷1456799=？",
        "answer": 0.5201858830862908
    },
    {
        "question": "3×80393692=？",
        "answer": 8.382343228380227
    },
    {
        "question": "243307÷123671=？",
        "answer": 0.2938867313709246
    },
    {
        "question": "41×115525=？",
        "answer": 6.6754598339104785
    },
    {
        "question": "5×136400895=？",
        "answer": 8.83378722430667
    },
    {
        "question": "7460÷4701=？",
        "answer": 0.20054857628441625
    },
    {
        "question": "907180÷2961=？",
        "answer": 2.4862550596606527
    },
    {
        "question": "1605690÷360=？",
        "answer": 3.6493592018909773
    },
    {
        "question": "2567575÷1006253=？",
        "answer": 0.4068159502232735
    },
    {
        "question": "7571935÷366=？",
        "answer": 4.315725791785557
    },
    {
        "question": "2×5435608=？",
        "answer": 7.036278124817984
    },
    {
        "question": "126407611÷21233=？",
        "answer": 3.7747618638441964
    },
    {
        "question": "27225516÷337842=？",
        "answer": 1.906262480189986
    },
    {
        "question": "21×517=？",
        "answer": 4.035709837827862
    },
    {
        "question": "60247÷17008=？",
        "answer": 0.5492821789077887
    },
    {
        "question": "3732501÷4128=？",
        "answer": 2.9562602441327437
    },
    {
        "question": "87×12581=？",
        "answer": 6.039234414969642
    },
    {
        "question": "1757720÷1629848=？",
        "answer": 0.03280259043240682
    },
    {
        "question": "195830919÷879=？",
        "answer": 5.347892386913195
    },
    {
        "question": "43×411778=？",
        "answer": 7.248131595496786
    },
    {
        "question": "183099683÷3505=？",
        "answer": 4.717999570106775
    },
    {
        "question": "291956÷1338=？",
        "answer": 2.338861291451325
    },
    {
        "question": "243163÷163879=？",
        "answer": 0.17137418761477838
    },
    {
        "question": "6×28181372=？",
        "answer": 8.228113383142947
    },
    {
        "question": "83008466÷3078674=？",
        "answer": 1.430758684147629
    },
    {
        "question": "15×1364=？",
        "answer": 4.310905629376141
    },
    {
        "question": "144×78646=？",
        "answer": 7.054039131043061
    },
    {
        "question": "152978970÷8540=？",
        "answer": 4.253173861823388
    },
    {
        "question": "42310833÷607194=？",
        "answer": 1.8431241042255044
    },
    {
        "question": "220906372÷33422111=？",
        "answer": 0.8201743659534151
    },
    {
        "question": "129×223355=？",
        "answer": 7.4595853892835295
    },
    {
        "question": "32×213106=？",
        "answer": 6.833745655768544
    },
    {
        "question": "441789×1540=？",
        "answer": 8.832735619110734
    },
    {
        "question": "233×273339=？",
        "answer": 7.804057522262832
    },
    {
        "question": "19361×1679=？",
        "answer": 7.511978481097304
    },
    {
        "question": "11×252=？",
        "answer": 3.442793225939769
    },
    {
        "question": "215×2438=？",
        "answer": 5.719472161197968
    },
    {
        "question": "3×221=？",
        "answer": 2.821513528404773
    },
    {
        "question": "530303÷245=？",
        "answer": 3.335357999627046
    },
    {
        "question": "1519×1945=？",
        "answer": 6.470477379524513
    },
    {
        "question": "4×1011281=？",
        "answer": 6.6069318390979435
    },
    {
        "question": "9991597÷2661=？",
        "answer": 3.574590034380964
    },
    {
        "question": "5×7410=？",
        "answer": 4.568788212315347
    },
    {
        "question": "2×1844=？",
        "answer": 3.5667909123815917
    },
    {
        "question": "25422×2893=？",
        "answer": 7.866558148032616
    },
    {
        "question": "252243874÷48591995=？",
        "answer": 0.715255897865821
    },
    {
        "question": "545019581÷2225=？",
        "answer": 5.3890820902027885
    },
    {
        "question": "138110938÷1262205=？",
        "answer": 2.0390981786266593
    },
    {
        "question": "93760÷8094=？",
        "answer": 1.0638543986184676
    },
    {
        "question": "50×1037=？",
        "answer": 4.71474876072506
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1817=？",
        "answer": 3.2593549273080344
    },
    {
        "question": "679310091÷70882=？",
        "answer": 3.9815321029213
    },
    {
        "question": "326×324004=？",
        "answer": 8.023767971901725
    },
    {
        "question": "4×3852=？",
        "answer": 4.187746269780459
    },
    {
        "question": "750498÷53209=？",
        "answer": 1.1493644422785871
    },
    {
        "question": "254999÷1336=？",
        "answer": 2.2807320191754736
    },
    {
        "question": "381883877÷10353=？",
        "answer": 4.5668651089923245
    },
    {
        "question": "16×1157=？",
        "answer": 4.267453341607674
    },
    {
        "question": "6×85561=？",
        "answer": 5.710427102159057
    },
    {
        "question": "26601÷1741=？",
        "answer": 1.1840991920670696
    },
    {
        "question": "89606×7728=？",
        "answer": 8.840404204315641
    },
    {
        "question": "47715×514=？",
        "answer": 7.38961804715832
    },
    {
        "question": "4509×1665=？",
        "answer": 6.875494473148909
    },
    {
        "question": "256177980÷55354=？",
        "answer": 3.665392787445722
    },
    {
        "question": "625779885÷133274=？",
        "answer": 3.6716761665698217
    },
    {
        "question": "23×2572=？",
        "answer": 4.7719988002697775
    },
    {
        "question": "6×1341246=？",
        "answer": 6.905659690162484
    },
    {
        "question": "55032÷337=？",
        "answer": 2.212985395570206
    },
    {
        "question": "2×99086=？",
        "answer": 5.2970422924069664
    },
    {
        "question": "7×19734616=？",
        "answer": 8.140326720241431
    },
    {
        "question": "9841512÷17567=？",
        "answer": 2.748364225062643
    },
    {
        "question": "31727792÷12497623=？",
        "answer": 0.40461243002112984
    },
    {
        "question": "2155994÷304=？",
        "answer": 3.850773964292535
    },
    {
        "question": "295436772÷6260=？",
        "answer": 4.673890216271897
    },
    {
        "question": "939595536÷2523=？",
        "answer": 5.5710236942683125
    },
    {
        "question": "29×816=？",
        "answer": 4.374088156652817
    },
    {
        "question": "10×6903=？",
        "answer": 4.839037873388306
    },
    {
        "question": "422÷339=？",
        "answer": 0.0951127527585917
    },
    {
        "question": "9739×502=？",
        "answer": 6.689218082978686
    },
    {
        "question": "102421÷404=？",
        "answer": 2.4040076466959324
    },
    {
        "question": "4855×20308=？",
        "answer": 7.9938563889765915
    },
    {
        "question": "110711226÷9982=？",
        "answer": 4.04497409457776
    },
    {
        "question": "1×109660=？",
        "answer": 5.040048241547462
    },
    {
        "question": "27×234268=？",
        "answer": 6.80107673405112
    },
    {
        "question": "3×458635=？",
        "answer": 6.13858844887036
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1093825=？",
        "answer": 6.038947845202426
    },
    {
        "question": "1×10106345=？",
        "answer": 7.0045941196531345
    },
    {
        "question": "35848720÷568747=？",
        "answer": 1.7995545346612398
    },
    {
        "question": "202225÷3964=？",
        "answer": 1.7077011982750827
    },
    {
        "question": "7563×117177=？",
        "answer": 8.947536475274946
    },
    {
        "question": "267635153÷10919=？",
        "answer": 4.389360290008187
    },
    {
        "question": "1×128147=？",
        "answer": 5.10770844353863
    },
    {
        "question": "11745980÷6001=？",
        "answer": 3.2916656302638256
    },
    {
        "question": "179774432÷631330=？",
        "answer": 2.4544714983275764
    },
    {
        "question": "345311×369=？",
        "answer": 8.10523677932812
    },
    {
        "question": "331076390÷2761=？",
        "answer": 5.078861804441047
    },
    {
        "question": "2×2253=？",
        "answer": 3.653791187387812
    },
    {
        "question": "518274474÷1457423=？",
        "answer": 2.550974200574471
    },
    {
        "question": "37343990÷2069237=？",
        "answer": 1.2564104826491278
    },
    {
        "question": "10×213=？",
        "answer": 3.3283796034387376
    },
    {
        "question": "52818×1302=？",
        "answer": 7.837392936472095
    },
    {
        "question": "1661×30962=？",
        "answer": 7.711198638755202
    },
    {
        "question": "1925×47017=？",
        "answer": 7.9566856486161885
    },
    {
        "question": "165237÷41874=？",
        "answer": 0.5961628527289003
    },
    {
        "question": "307704260÷878502=？",
        "answer": 2.5443907543142057
    },
    {
        "question": "2520061÷987936=？",
        "answer": 0.4066822420978546
    },
    {
        "question": "4481×1179=？",
        "answer": 6.722888749008132
    },
    {
        "question": "33×288932=？",
        "answer": 6.979309583673638
    },
    {
        "question": "4259×1432=？",
        "answer": 6.785250658045586
    },
    {
        "question": "7516901÷248=？",
        "answer": 4.481587149659757
    },
    {
        "question": "2425116÷971830=？",
        "answer": 0.3971422155110001
    },
    {
        "question": "1×22116651=？",
        "answer": 7.344719364841788
    },
    {
        "question": "3750120÷912=？",
        "answer": 3.6140503266003696
    },
    {
        "question": "48315130÷290462=？",
        "answer": 2.2209938290142244
    },
    {
        "question": "21805×336=？",
        "answer": 6.8648953683992895
    },
    {
        "question": "11102020÷2306475=？",
        "answer": 0.6824532537369615
    },
    {
        "question": "846÷247=？",
        "answer": 0.5346734097793578
    },
    {
        "question": "4×1439=？",
        "answer": 3.7601207852645677
    },
    {
        "question": "267087÷192128=？",
        "answer": 0.1430620881082835
    },
    {
        "question": "113216÷14278=？",
        "answer": 0.8992404292710349
    },
    {
        "question": "842030÷1837=？",
        "answer": 2.6612184085933155
    },
    {
        "question": "25219208÷39389=？",
        "answer": 2.8063564884236665
    },
    {
        "question": "7679909÷618679=？",
        "answer": 1.093890699176667
    },
    {
        "question": "37083587÷1321=？",
        "answer": 4.4482789180780635
    },
    {
        "question": "15398×290=？",
        "answer": 6.649862313191876
    },
    {
        "question": "31052663÷574=？",
        "answer": 4.733186957738248
    },
    {
        "question": "11432×2345=？",
        "answer": 7.428265062834016
    },
    {
        "question": "45495÷14531=？",
        "answer": 0.4956681665935925
    },
    {
        "question": "2847029÷61698=？",
        "answer": 1.6641208047297256
    },
    {
        "question": "974329÷303=？",
        "answer": 3.50726300061278
    },
    {
        "question": "3970095÷20926=？",
        "answer": 2.2781146780926687
    },
    {
        "question": "5042×29214=？",
        "answer": 8.168193866269965
    },
    {
        "question": "94×853751=？",
        "answer": 7.9044590789794515
    },
    {
        "question": "198792009÷3288=？",
        "answer": 4.781467113864529
    },
    {
        "question": "81042÷2305=？",
        "answer": 1.5460392205219908
    },
    {
        "question": "850913÷13830=？",
        "answer": 1.7890629786222605
    },
    {
        "question": "656÷342=？",
        "answer": 0.2828777333195252
    },
    {
        "question": "13066×22587=？",
        "answer": 8.470001205714121
    },
    {
        "question": "1145×597=？",
        "answer": 5.834779817805276
    },
    {
        "question": "63766÷318=？",
        "answer": 2.302162054844872
    },
    {
        "question": "209336085÷27322145=？",
        "answer": 0.8843293059109811
    },
    {
        "question": "2787462÷617843=？",
        "answer": 0.6543308249920483
    },
    {
        "question": "201514÷406=？",
        "answer": 2.695779190158179
    },
    {
        "question": "10×767932=？",
        "answer": 6.885322765171806
    },
    {
        "question": "1322×3977=？",
        "answer": 6.720787046135602
    },
    {
        "question": "92551÷34938=？",
        "answer": 0.42308307511087534
    },
    {
        "question": "2×25179176=？",
        "answer": 7.702071509183698
    },
    {
        "question": "3058480÷24715=？",
        "answer": 2.0925450301095982
    },
    {
        "question": "701069792÷2332=？",
        "answer": 5.478032708358606
    },
    {
        "question": "765×225=？",
        "answer": 5.23584395326498
    },
    {
        "question": "161350612÷12384=？",
        "answer": 4.114909673675472
    },
    {
        "question": "1941×320260=？",
        "answer": 8.793528234701308
    },
    {
        "question": "6615659÷21061=？",
        "answer": 2.4970941235541475
    },
    {
        "question": "81831÷3982=？",
        "answer": 1.3128166027293389
    },
    {
        "question": "20330707÷267811=？",
        "answer": 1.8803240703421007
    },
    {
        "question": "10635540÷2357563=？",
        "answer": 0.6542962382999156
    },
    {
        "question": "977×1386=？",
        "answer": 6.131657793994561
    },
    {
        "question": "1311×3060=？",
        "answer": 6.603324118171664
    },
    {
        "question": "450701523÷1087=？",
        "answer": 5.617659481544875
    },
    {
        "question": "11×24924=？",
        "answer": 5.438010427740949
    },
    {
        "question": "825155271÷229749473=？",
        "answer": 0.5552811543657414
    },
    {
        "question": "99970720÷146696=？",
        "answer": 2.8334545479774573
    },
    {
        "question": "369638÷193148=？",
        "answer": 0.2818863962501153
    },
    {
        "question": "6089231÷545658=？",
        "answer": 1.0476419228231821
    },
    {
        "question": "943410303÷7636=？",
        "answer": 5.091834695151393
    },
    {
        "question": "3326090÷2237208=？",
        "answer": 0.17222763288309026
    },
    {
        "question": "42×328=？",
        "answer": 4.139123134109579
    },
    {
        "question": "8626×625=？",
        "answer": 6.7316894711540085
    },
    {
        "question": "16790476÷42794=？",
        "answer": 2.5936801259613076
    },
    {
        "question": "3855×75834=？",
        "answer": 8.46588834661713
    },
    {
        "question": "1×48922903=？",
        "answer": 7.689512219408292
    },
    {
        "question": "131873÷4269=？",
        "answer": 1.4898297313312783
    },
    {
        "question": "48019÷9941=？",
        "answer": 0.6839830377960074
    },
    {
        "question": "16296×11816=？",
        "answer": 8.284551498296
    },
    {
        "question": "363645÷65779=？",
        "answer": 0.7425903536715942
    },
    {
        "question": "22568301÷2630901=？",
        "answer": 0.9333943594732198
    },
    {
        "question": "1792895÷834=？",
        "answer": 3.3323888054298143
    },
    {
        "question": "3947161÷16738=？",
        "answer": 2.3725812775893624
    },
    {
        "question": "1×34397872=？",
        "answer": 7.536531576081887
    },
    {
        "question": "119690015÷208=？",
        "answer": 5.759994586443836
    },
    {
        "question": "189149÷94493=？",
        "answer": 0.3014044122344381
    },
    {
        "question": "731181×352=？",
        "answer": 8.410567561052968
    },
    {
        "question": "5163932÷2004=？",
        "answer": 3.4110827975341067
    },
    {
        "question": "356225341÷298801050=？",
        "answer": 0.07634269159810578
    },
    {
        "question": "1039×507718=？",
        "answer": 8.722238108168991
    },
    {
        "question": "49611869÷2429=？",
        "answer": 4.310158073470668
    },
    {
        "question": "1453694÷372015=？",
        "answer": 0.5919125465246712
    },
    {
        "question": "34×3186843=？",
        "answer": 8.034839585500869
    },
    {
        "question": "4852×520=？",
        "answer": 6.401924135829335
    },
    {
        "question": "61052216÷236014=？",
        "answer": 2.4127636666284666
    },
    {
        "question": "3109÷335=？",
        "answer": 0.9675759150063465
    },
    {
        "question": "127×353765=？",
        "answer": 7.652518584411604
    },
    {
        "question": "10957÷1959=？",
        "answer": 0.7476572256542896
    },
    {
        "question": "370×99309=？",
        "answer": 7.56519033281634
    },
    {
        "question": "202404÷11601=？",
        "answer": 1.2417236641851228
    },
    {
        "question": "1663×11115=？",
        "answer": 7.266801716254529
    },
    {
        "question": "4×83330=？",
        "answer": 5.522861373153616
    },
    {
        "question": "4×102435=？",
        "answer": 5.612508363102049
    },
    {
        "question": "191457054÷249433=？",
        "answer": 2.885117461897093
    },
    {
        "question": "156537451÷3629=？",
        "answer": 4.634831289444497
    },
    {
        "question": "104×12764=？",
        "answer": 6.123020134820253
    },
    {
        "question": "5×3317=？",
        "answer": 4.2197154758555016
    },
    {
        "question": "22931192÷59061=？",
        "answer": 2.5891258346256536
    },
    {
        "question": "150×308=？",
        "answer": 4.664641975556125
    },
    {
        "question": "422995826÷372583419=？",
        "answer": 0.05511255822825869
    },
    {
        "question": "6×91424463=？",
        "answer": 8.739213668485093
    },
    {
        "question": "12×660=？",
        "answer": 3.8987251815894934
    },
    {
        "question": "3×24880248=？",
        "answer": 7.872975959697235
    },
    {
        "question": "264660544÷243254383=？",
        "answer": 0.036628526634490746
    },
    {
        "question": "75667734÷147783=？",
        "answer": 2.709286249964396
    },
    {
        "question": "45215÷7548=？",
        "answer": 0.7774506436843196
    },
    {
        "question": "174×8293=？",
        "answer": 6.159260913664921
    },
    {
        "question": "600×201=？",
        "answer": 5.0813473078041325
    },
    {
        "question": "18052815÷1570=？",
        "answer": 4.060645279242167
    },
    {
        "question": "26051÷20201=？",
        "answer": 0.11045153024746453
    },
    {
        "question": "15550÷1540=？",
        "answer": 1.0042096725263931
    },
    {
        "question": "10665244÷13640=？",
        "answer": 2.8931564253901074
    },
    {
        "question": "8847698÷6281=？",
        "answer": 3.1488014969611715
    },
    {
        "question": "79089983÷801467=？",
        "answer": 1.994235836989903
    },
    {
        "question": "3×2062731=？",
        "answer": 6.791563850199907
    },
    {
        "question": "100880760÷6644767=？",
        "answer": 1.1813285884701674
    },
    {
        "question": "22×37319275=？",
        "answer": 8.91435587895782
    },
    {
        "question": "111987842÷6315274=？",
        "answer": 1.2487786779138237
    },
    {
        "question": "2×1579579=？",
        "answer": 6.499571346959974
    },
    {
        "question": "28×11978=？",
        "answer": 5.525542340090409
    },
    {
        "question": "797÷260=？",
        "answer": 0.4864849734252944
    },
    {
        "question": "33196038÷28445=？",
        "answer": 3.06708031495519
    },
    {
        "question": "161471613÷4840295=？",
        "answer": 1.5232243523605886
    },
    {
        "question": "3×3696=？",
        "answer": 4.044853217267732
    },
    {
        "question": "3283863÷2878=？",
        "answer": 3.057294240824553
    },
    {
        "question": "5084158÷3238=？",
        "answer": 3.1959421942116464
    },
    {
        "question": "3577825÷2503=？",
        "answer": 3.1551582447581192
    },
    {
        "question": "61829×265=？",
        "answer": 7.214438096369793
    },
    {
        "question": "102×7081777=？",
        "answer": 8.85874241878239
    },
    {
        "question": "238×3451780=？",
        "answer": 8.914620065122065
    },
    {
        "question": "231071÷140149=？",
        "answer": 0.21715544053171784
    },
    {
        "question": "5816330÷283369=？",
        "answer": 1.3122967014675926
    },
    {
        "question": "1×519=？",
        "answer": 2.7151673578484576
    },
    {
        "question": "4×199522741=？",
        "answer": 8.902052393746501
    },
    {
        "question": "48083444÷9106667=？",
        "answer": 0.7226361104752647
    },
    {
        "question": "6444÷2601=？",
        "answer": 0.3940151795513077
    },
    {
        "question": "26780×339=？",
        "answer": 6.958010270879073
    },
    {
        "question": "242675961÷42058=？",
        "answer": 3.761178141440054
    },
    {
        "question": "992592876÷154879=？",
        "answer": 3.806778617986092
    },
    {
        "question": "106×56456=？",
        "answer": 6.777015969690848
    },
    {
        "question": "30828÷242=？",
        "answer": 2.10512998433354
    },
    {
        "question": "829981311÷33205=？",
        "answer": 4.397864828739822
    },
    {
        "question": "81494155÷864721=？",
        "answer": 1.9742504549109714
    },
    {
        "question": "987707÷8211=？",
        "answer": 2.0802320795476983
    },
    {
        "question": "7406059÷2498632=？",
        "answer": 0.47188486982467354
    },
    {
        "question": "321740÷780=？",
        "answer": 2.6154104547901866
    },
    {
        "question": "863740÷44871=？",
        "answer": 1.284417283966663
    },
    {
        "question": "16167÷851=？",
        "answer": 1.2786998782310999
    },
    {
        "question": "3×641949=？",
        "answer": 6.284621781389179
    },
    {
        "question": "146941÷246=？",
        "answer": 2.7762078839855158
    },
    {
        "question": "15360×38924=？",
        "answer": 8.776608679580209
    },
    {
        "question": "422×1869555=？",
        "answer": 8.897050697047339
    },
    {
        "question": "92×99558=？",
        "answer": 6.961863990918027
    },
    {
        "question": "13×3721183=？",
        "answer": 7.684624380548184
    },
    {
        "question": "713975809÷715=？",
        "answer": 5.99937745541516
    },
    {
        "question": "3×2461=？",
        "answer": 3.868232868422465
    },
    {
        "question": "2114260×241=？",
        "answer": 8.707175435963533
    },
    {
        "question": "648×514509=？",
        "answer": 8.522967981890622
    },
    {
        "question": "1450×119250=？",
        "answer": 8.237826389947127
    },
    {
        "question": "355251681÷25294115=？",
        "answer": 1.1475166528716783
    },
    {
        "question": "80552222÷2022=？",
        "answer": 4.6002963735006155
    },
    {
        "question": "9408028÷1119973=？",
        "answer": 0.9242910483283745
    },
    {
        "question": "69×47561=？",
        "answer": 6.5161000680951
    },
    {
        "question": "52×1347=？",
        "answer": 4.845370939357784
    },
    {
        "question": "3×1713=？",
        "answer": 3.710878617685173
    },
    {
        "question": "81461×256=？",
        "answer": 7.319189702412384
    },
    {
        "question": "23756216÷496224=？",
        "answer": 1.680099500176207
    },
    {
        "question": "28006833÷1979410=？",
        "answer": 1.1507282417817717
    },
    {
        "question": "2×354633=？",
        "answer": 5.850809141624511
    },
    {
        "question": "3×738=？",
        "answer": 3.345177616542704
    },
    {
        "question": "1180294×423=？",
        "answer": 8.698330566777864
    },
    {
        "question": "12976741÷3587=？",
        "answer": 3.5584342600541556
    },
    {
        "question": "4×17478=？",
        "answer": 4.844551726339273
    },
    {
        "question": "34×991=？",
        "answer": 4.52755257152753
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1222366=？",
        "answer": 6.087201261537783
    },
    {
        "question": "238077165÷2816859=？",
        "answer": 1.9269526337673604
    },
    {
        "question": "5×160587=？",
        "answer": 5.904680389258868
    },
    {
        "question": "21211912÷10468=？",
        "answer": 3.30671610276297
    },
    {
        "question": "18182×298=？",
        "answer": 6.733857917505116
    },
    {
        "question": "137957283÷918=？",
        "answer": 5.176901951364749
    },
    {
        "question": "1939÷551=？",
        "answer": 0.5464262102269203
    },
    {
        "question": "83807562÷84495=？",
        "answer": 2.996452196724723
    },
    {
        "question": "793402÷445450=？",
        "answer": 0.25069432763346056
    },
    {
        "question": "3056630÷4165=？",
        "answer": 2.865627865536937
    },
    {
        "question": "1161×119386=？",
        "answer": 8.141785621245235
    },
    {
        "question": "19260257÷2371=？",
        "answer": 3.9097305238745634
    },
    {
        "question": "20095147÷1385235=？",
        "answer": 1.1615677313852524
    },
    {
        "question": "2092498÷3193=？",
        "answer": 2.816466133029375
    },
    {
        "question": "681812843÷585=？",
        "answer": 6.066509311496375
    },
    {
        "question": "1091×183122=？",
        "answer": 8.300565273506361
    },
    {
        "question": "59×7022=？",
        "answer": 5.617312836771476
    },
    {
        "question": "3×679=？",
        "answer": 3.3089910290001643
    },
    {
        "question": "12118703÷129540=？",
        "answer": 1.9710522493826592
    },
    {
        "question": "8503809÷157470=？",
        "answer": 1.7324156696556605
    },
    {
        "question": "1985542×341=？",
        "answer": 8.83063345708357
    },
    {
        "question": "190952179÷274188=？",
        "answer": 2.8428761748590476
    },
    {
        "question": "10685640÷2791=？",
        "answer": 3.583040702191579
    },
    {
        "question": "7389÷344=？",
        "answer": 1.3320272239872355
    },
    {
        "question": "173131÷1085=？",
        "answer": 2.2029450993242694
    },
    {
        "question": "4×292=？",
        "answer": 3.0674428427763805
    },
    {
        "question": "137193126÷3588409=？",
        "answer": 1.5824304145374746
    },
    {
        "question": "5797071÷2694496=？",
        "answer": 0.3327310762339201
    },
    {
        "question": "433969717÷678363=？",
        "answer": 2.805997272766619
    },
    {
        "question": "1507÷363=？",
        "answer": 0.6182066272785193
    },
    {
        "question": "142868×704=？",
        "answer": 8.002507624254301
    },
    {
        "question": "27026008÷194530=？",
        "answer": 2.142795314193528
    },
    {
        "question": "662×932210=？",
        "answer": 8.79037174682357
    },
    {
        "question": "456701÷4222=？",
        "answer": 2.0341137335747246
    },
    {
        "question": "203546808÷602287=？",
        "answer": 2.528860806919182
    },
    {
        "question": "26142×949=？",
        "answer": 7.39460502274669
    },
    {
        "question": "3190×62634=？",
        "answer": 8.300600831026342
    },
    {
        "question": "5737630÷31794=？",
        "answer": 2.2563873687594214
    },
    {
        "question": "405×44152=？",
        "answer": 7.252405404271876
    },
    {
        "question": "63×457505=？",
        "answer": 7.4597363942178925
    },
    {
        "question": "136825×2901=？",
        "answer": 8.598713185617207
    },
    {
        "question": "49042÷652=？",
        "answer": 1.8763205772640101
    },
    {
        "question": "4500847÷206=？",
        "answer": 4.3394270295866315
    },
    {
        "question": "35×23642650=？",
        "answer": 8.917764197434117
    },
    {
        "question": "267422÷1742=？",
        "answer": 2.1861489818189512
    },
    {
        "question": "37822276÷43568=？",
        "answer": 2.9385800354813894
    },
    {
        "question": "130186630÷643245=？",
        "answer": 2.3061899659494816
    },
    {
        "question": "12×40325=？",
        "answer": 5.684755622108624
    },
    {
        "question": "3737÷2291=？",
        "answer": 0.21249800866024007
    },
    {
        "question": "3057002÷10071=？",
        "answer": 2.4822231268894837
    },
    {
        "question": "23×5061227=？",
        "answer": 8.065983652211296
    },
    {
        "question": "2885254÷152719=？",
        "answer": 1.2762909801412579
    },
    {
        "question": "277313÷434=？",
        "answer": 2.8054804995890756
    },
    {
        "question": "1720×265383=？",
        "answer": 8.659401546134312
    },
    {
        "question": "1×18067=？",
        "answer": 4.256886044558126
    },
    {
        "question": "1234039÷500=？",
        "answer": 3.3923588808208063
    },
    {
        "question": "4542547÷4974=？",
        "answer": 2.960593648548643
    },
    {
        "question": "4983×1489=？",
        "answer": 6.870385584923233
    },
    {
        "question": "345410538÷10122999=？",
        "answer": 1.5330263892135667
    },
    {
        "question": "1116133÷865245=？",
        "answer": 0.11057685052346944
    },
    {
        "question": "131855401÷37738465=？",
        "answer": 0.5433136924647282
    },
    {
        "question": "13206×400=？",
        "answer": 6.722831284264954
    },
    {
        "question": "254215÷2075=？",
        "answer": 2.0881830715468745
    },
    {
        "question": "1239216×256=？",
        "answer": 8.501386977444254
    },
    {
        "question": "44879×2304=？",
        "answer": 8.014525646098202
    },
    {
        "question": "2×16465=？",
        "answer": 4.517591730711907
    },
    {
        "question": "539117885÷49128=？",
        "answer": 4.040354655222968
    },
    {
        "question": "162817574÷123551451=？",
        "answer": 0.11985342925493012
    },
    {
        "question": "10×126726=？",
        "answer": 6.102865726944312
    },
    {
        "question": "11×5843128=？",
        "answer": 7.808038085260176
    },
    {
        "question": "3×2387=？",
        "answer": 3.854973673726417
    },
    {
        "question": "1×12618015=？",
        "answer": 7.100991039349355
    },
    {
        "question": "304×5635=？",
        "answer": 6.233767503990879
    },
    {
        "question": "2×34764=？",
        "answer": 4.8421597369153675
    },
    {
        "question": "1052×382147=？",
        "answer": 8.604246194374433
    },
    {
        "question": "1×985954=？",
        "answer": 5.993856653265563
    },
    {
        "question": "19421974÷6634074=？",
        "answer": 0.46651305683819394
    },
    {
        "question": "5×63089428=？",
        "answer": 8.49892659423099
    },
    {
        "question": "49287581÷1219=？",
        "answer": 4.606733798189992
    },
    {
        "question": "752890435÷282=？",
        "answer": 6.426482671417788
    },
    {
        "question": "11981743÷437=？",
        "answer": 4.4380385630712
    },
    {
        "question": "13229567÷127462=？",
        "answer": 2.016164901393339
    },
    {
        "question": "282549÷50770=？",
        "answer": 0.7454866111730373
    },
    {
        "question": "56×12575=？",
        "answer": 5.8476960207341655
    },
    {
        "question": "60×22573=？",
        "answer": 6.131740531963128
    },
    {
        "question": "31330799÷4576102=？",
        "answer": 0.8354757742358393
    },
    {
        "question": "19453×16193=？",
        "answer": 8.498313902669693
    },
    {
        "question": "5182×416=？",
        "answer": 6.3335907392765485
    },
    {
        "question": "1×50796690=？",
        "answer": 7.705835413827826
    },
    {
        "question": "1793÷524=？",
        "answer": 0.5342490025784562
    },
    {
        "question": "9163÷823=？",
        "answer": 1.0466378513527428
    },
    {
        "question": "212532010÷531441=？",
        "answer": 2.6019692929006046
    },
    {
        "question": "47766071÷452832=？",
        "answer": 2.023182410557951
    },
    {
        "question": "757×160555=？",
        "answer": 8.084719714401642
    },
    {
        "question": "4532183÷292=？",
        "answer": 4.190924585993081
    },
    {
        "question": "5545522÷2130576=？",
        "answer": 0.4154454019732068
    },
    {
        "question": "10025÷1638=？",
        "answer": 0.7867704838678202
    },
    {
        "question": "214×54699=？",
        "answer": 7.068393160039994
    },
    {
        "question": "13386975÷26331=？",
        "answer": 2.7062150992735527
    },
    {
        "question": "895628307÷5052=？",
        "answer": 5.248664469441323
    },
    {
        "question": "20×176822=？",
        "answer": 6.548566294147587
    },
    {
        "question": "1×31445=？",
        "answer": 4.4975515990645665
    },
    {
        "question": "222534÷17937=？",
        "answer": 1.0936465662077444
    },
    {
        "question": "3226619÷1581644=？",
        "answer": 0.30963894864811425
    },
    {
        "question": "34×215861=？",
        "answer": 6.865653101688829
    },
    {
        "question": "1×37275682=？",
        "answer": 7.57142559809759
    },
    {
        "question": "532821107÷1379902=？",
        "answer": 2.586733176397945
    },
    {
        "question": "5×316778=？",
        "answer": 6.199725016867206
    },
    {
        "question": "4128×9426=？",
        "answer": 7.590067124042772
    },
    {
        "question": "26885627÷228418=？",
        "answer": 2.070789844532154
    },
    {
        "question": "43×967=？",
        "answer": 4.618894929662588
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1264=？",
        "answer": 3.1017470739463664
    },
    {
        "question": "63070×6839=？",
        "answer": 8.634815434726349
    },
    {
        "question": "66381199÷3596=？",
        "answer": 4.266225409458231
    },
    {
        "question": "11656×14858=？",
        "answer": 8.23850989277461
    },
    {
        "question": "85×1614742=？",
        "answer": 8.137522067287144
    },
    {
        "question": "3120×155995=？",
        "answer": 8.687265272454894
    },
    {
        "question": "24×1128=？",
        "answer": 4.43252034135893
    },
    {
        "question": "2×21302=？",
        "answer": 4.629450376012932
    },
    {
        "question": "2×2945=？",
        "answer": 3.7701152947871015
    },
    {
        "question": "264593800÷1340=？",
        "answer": 5.2954748651551
    },
    {
        "question": "256219633÷6650398=？",
        "answer": 1.5857647679007991
    },
    {
        "question": "43391÷13632=？",
        "answer": 0.5028400816827897
    },
    {
        "question": "1124×106450=？",
        "answer": 8.077911977007384
    },
    {
        "question": "16442×423=？",
        "answer": 6.842295011244172
    },
    {
        "question": "22×19954=？",
        "answer": 5.6424526487045075
    },
    {
        "question": "23734×7999=？",
        "answer": 8.278406634817555
    },
    {
        "question": "410553790÷96422329=？",
        "answer": 0.6291924483544776
    },
    {
        "question": "2×10191253=？",
        "answer": 7.30925757883939
    },
    {
        "question": "3845851÷3343029=？",
        "answer": 0.06085231032264154
    },
    {
        "question": "119602572÷11619=？",
        "answer": 4.012571767356321
    },
    {
        "question": "100589473÷1993256=？",
        "answer": 1.702989452775922
    },
    {
        "question": "375×96114=？",
        "answer": 7.55681791949521
    },
    {
        "question": "564815217÷3698=？",
        "answer": 5.183939481946703
    },
    {
        "question": "47×2284380=？",
        "answer": 8.030866207148788
    },
    {
        "question": "1677474÷99174=？",
        "answer": 1.2282579674960663
    },
    {
        "question": "247×592042=？",
        "answer": 8.165049470322503
    },
    {
        "question": "102170÷498=？",
        "answer": 2.3120940506212957
    },
    {
        "question": "114×2014755=？",
        "answer": 8.361127093566848
    },
    {
        "question": "11285657÷1416434=？",
        "answer": 0.9013305038229134
    },
    {
        "question": "605×554736=？",
        "answer": 8.525841725305106
    },
    {
        "question": "426×2184=？",
        "answer": 5.968662233135419
    },
    {
        "question": "83×6891384=？",
        "answer": 8.757384542615045
    },
    {
        "question": "21327÷21258=？",
        "answer": 0.0014073662310789877
    },
    {
        "question": "2×337646=？",
        "answer": 5.829491604782473
    },
    {
        "question": "597467789÷2539841=？",
        "answer": 2.371507966718733
    },
    {
        "question": "22716×3144=？",
        "answer": 7.853814397378792
    },
    {
        "question": "11×391862=？",
        "answer": 6.634525835876778
    },
    {
        "question": "100909538÷649=？",
        "answer": 5.191687521022235
    },
    {
        "question": "75531279÷53408=？",
        "answer": 3.150520523834641
    },
    {
        "question": "769×5476=？",
        "answer": 6.6243897792633835
    },
    {
        "question": "479÷356=？",
        "answer": 0.12888551544168803
    },
    {
        "question": "5136×38119=？",
        "answer": 8.291766514052835
    },
    {
        "question": "5727×4224=？",
        "answer": 7.383651092639085
    },
    {
        "question": "57243×3111=？",
        "answer": 8.25062239736528
    },
    {
        "question": "3124×256=？",
        "answer": 5.9029509905171125
    },
    {
        "question": "2×323704004=？",
        "answer": 8.811178067029331
    },
    {
        "question": "1×54455373=？",
        "answer": 7.7360407371520035
    },
    {
        "question": "178319865÷1954=？",
        "answer": 4.960275167299739
    },
    {
        "question": "1926×330=？",
        "answer": 5.803170222666403
    },
    {
        "question": "216205÷40654=？",
        "answer": 0.725762450482322
    },
    {
        "question": "210×736=？",
        "answer": 5.189097109071418
    },
    {
        "question": "189090÷10878=？",
        "answer": 1.240119507366125
    },
    {
        "question": "457205÷580=？",
        "answer": 2.8966829776365444
    },
    {
        "question": "16932÷1284=？",
        "answer": 1.1201432360691381
    },
    {
        "question": "6987034÷3495389=？",
        "answer": 0.3007973414289504
    },
    {
        "question": "41573×12729=？",
        "answer": 8.723605651777557
    },
    {
        "question": "130×23984=？",
        "answer": 6.493864967811041
    },
    {
        "question": "237120168÷53162=？",
        "answer": 3.649367182889007
    },
    {
        "question": "4935÷701=？",
        "answer": 0.8475691390389969
    },
    {
        "question": "4603÷2304=？",
        "answer": 0.30055850014279983
    },
    {
        "question": "119×114638=？",
        "answer": 7.134875562049958
    },
    {
        "question": "35588÷1087=？",
        "answer": 1.5150740378099328
    },
    {
        "question": "15×206523=？",
        "answer": 6.491059684136961
    },
    {
        "question": "398947821÷342722732=？",
        "answer": 0.06597318623085961
    },
    {
        "question": "2×1833159=？",
        "answer": 6.564230131017834
    },
    {
        "question": "47676944÷15791=？",
        "answer": 3.4798987766492973
    },
    {
        "question": "9×3954346=？",
        "answer": 7.5513171762673865
    },
    {
        "question": "1×4495=？",
        "answer": 3.6527296960692475
    },
    {
        "question": "3381533÷207020=？",
        "answer": 1.2131013257635535
    },
    {
        "question": "5×243733=？",
        "answer": 6.08588433839413
    },
    {
        "question": "11693×15191=？",
        "answer": 8.249512313418379
    },
    {
        "question": "10792×86711=？",
        "answer": 8.971176131444235
    },
    {
        "question": "24×709206=？",
        "answer": 7.230983642859139
    },
    {
        "question": "2402×6494=？",
        "answer": 7.19308528735687
    },
    {
        "question": "67819674÷1877=？",
        "answer": 4.557891425230904
    },
    {
        "question": "71×37559=？",
        "answer": 6.425972369473336
    },
    {
        "question": "674356389÷56386=？",
        "answer": 4.077718189454441
    },
    {
        "question": "88116÷3101=？",
        "answer": 1.4535530080181132
    },
    {
        "question": "18932÷17705=？",
        "answer": 0.029100564701826554
    },
    {
        "question": "14×1534374=？",
        "answer": 7.332059266437962
    },
    {
        "question": "1851512÷3107=？",
        "answer": 2.7751852778844133
    },
    {
        "question": "1018535×715=？",
        "answer": 8.86228199908984
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1243=？",
        "answer": 3.094471128641645
    },
    {
        "question": "2×68837048=？",
        "answer": 8.138852233484531
    },
    {
        "question": "7308653÷83523=？",
        "answer": 1.9420312579173848
    },
    {
        "question": "1749×3238=？",
        "answer": 6.753066653896031
    },
    {
        "question": "159799715÷61378735=？",
        "answer": 0.4155580669319874
    },
    {
        "question": "551618×377=？",
        "answer": 8.31797977952456
    },
    {
        "question": "47×16438=？",
        "answer": 5.887946834047172
    },
    {
        "question": "233×1215=？",
        "answer": 5.45193219896035
    },
    {
        "question": "8×4614712=？",
        "answer": 7.567234589273989
    },
    {
        "question": "2238526÷2155=？",
        "answer": 3.0165148684893897
    },
    {
        "question": "853965276÷68122=？",
        "answer": 4.0981528217643115
    },
    {
        "question": "76×53308=？",
        "answer": 6.607605981328783
    },
    {
        "question": "39151131÷156156=？",
        "answer": 2.399185636663994
    },
    {
        "question": "29006435÷1025=？",
        "answer": 4.451770490264819
    },
    {
        "question": "7556÷6418=？",
        "answer": 0.07089223649031072
    },
    {
        "question": "81524129÷280=？",
        "answer": 5.464128136178529
    },
    {
        "question": "127×212619=？",
        "answer": 7.431405792180191
    },
    {
        "question": "630178÷7121=？",
        "answer": 1.946922251777517
    },
    {
        "question": "60600÷30125=？",
        "answer": 0.3035455685833614
    },
    {
        "question": "45327×417=？",
        "answer": 7.276493030891901
    },
    {
        "question": "87×2487=？",
        "answer": 5.335195037888554
    },
    {
        "question": "3666035×230=？",
        "answer": 8.925924442916106
    },
    {
        "question": "12157724÷626=？",
        "answer": 4.288277946762687
    },
    {
        "question": "99018212÷8089960=？",
        "answer": 1.0877687055955114
    },
    {
        "question": "886263818÷36428=？",
        "answer": 4.3861276915531775
    },
    {
        "question": "238×791789=？",
        "answer": 8.2751864210394
    },
    {
        "question": "3542757÷340855=？",
        "answer": 1.0167716957701833
    },
    {
        "question": "84×106976=？",
        "answer": 6.9535656409743565
    },
    {
        "question": "15267051÷327749=？",
        "answer": 1.668213781086345
    },
    {
        "question": "1×112752671=？",
        "answer": 8.052126838681453
    },
    {
        "question": "432×780312=？",
        "answer": 8.527752032563857
    },
    {
        "question": "19881012÷15513683=？",
        "answer": 0.10772357443697551
    },
    {
        "question": "40632×23607=？",
        "answer": 8.98190899985022
    },
    {
        "question": "7792821÷5139611=？",
        "answer": 0.1807644507311915
    },
    {
        "question": "615×6763=？",
        "answer": 6.619014503200759
    },
    {
        "question": "4100648÷5506=？",
        "answer": 2.8720162839520214
    },
    {
        "question": "24926299÷31703=？",
        "answer": 2.895557439539511
    },
    {
        "question": "410×1839=？",
        "answer": 5.877365585957813
    },
    {
        "question": "758662÷413=？",
        "answer": 3.264098279931572
    },
    {
        "question": "20×29776=？",
        "answer": 5.774896351450673
    },
    {
        "question": "175213174÷374=？",
        "answer": 5.670695154770896
    },
    {
        "question": "42310533÷914839=？",
        "answer": 1.665103825819877
    },
    {
        "question": "143720÷4367=？",
        "answer": 1.5173340166112719
    },
    {
        "question": "11×60985880=？",
        "answer": 8.826621980039072
    },
    {
        "question": "218×197161=？",
        "answer": 7.633277505833186
    },
    {
        "question": "93×14332=？",
        "answer": 6.124789748048008
    },
    {
        "question": "190103633÷998871=？",
        "answer": 2.2794810120488145
    },
    {
        "question": "687×251776=？",
        "answer": 8.237971066626756
    },
    {
        "question": "419×795792=？",
        "answer": 8.523013591889107
    },
    {
        "question": "3831446÷959431=？",
        "answer": 0.6013489622683883
    },
    {
        "question": "1481×28596=？",
        "answer": 7.626860346915289
    },
    {
        "question": "1170583÷6537=？",
        "answer": 2.2530237277391167
    },
    {
        "question": "1×16258401=？",
        "answer": 7.211077830862965
    },
    {
        "question": "2102684÷1297=？",
        "answer": 3.2098340339450657
    },
    {
        "question": "573×156364=？",
        "answer": 7.952291393702707
    },
    {
        "question": "69×562499=？",
        "answer": 7.58897084544089
    },
    {
        "question": "49666861÷640678=？",
        "answer": 1.8894269018021252
    },
    {
        "question": "184885130÷293547=？",
        "answer": 2.7992243366678995
    },
    {
        "question": "11×289534=？",
        "answer": 6.503092255450916
    },
    {
        "question": "71941435÷10138568=？",
        "answer": 0.8510024779967356
    },
    {
        "question": "5254516÷527398=？",
        "answer": 0.9983942402740538
    },
    {
        "question": "43880430÷65329=？",
        "answer": 2.8271648642949616
    },
    {
        "question": "488964×338=？",
        "answer": 8.218193585624418
    },
    {
        "question": "248643737÷4419=？",
        "answer": 4.750253522852135
    },
    {
        "question": "563423915÷511745=？",
        "answer": 3.041781668949166
    },
    {
        "question": "121852123÷83911422=？",
        "answer": 0.16201201929457607
    },
    {
        "question": "691266936÷202086741=？",
        "answer": 0.5341079644348521
    },
    {
        "question": "2696×1742=？",
        "answer": 6.6717680385349265
    },
    {
        "question": "5595÷4942=？",
        "answer": 0.053897349798308215
    },
    {
        "question": "106793840÷12746915=？",
        "answer": 0.9231411129537123
    },
    {
        "question": "587620159÷28738694=？",
        "answer": 1.3106296581697925
    },
    {
        "question": "50600659÷1370=？",
        "answer": 4.5674356057743
    },
    {
        "question": "2×37298=？",
        "answer": 4.872715540280947
    },
    {
        "question": "369926÷103868=？",
        "answer": 0.5516330872130433
    },
    {
        "question": "9149÷4026=？",
        "answer": 0.35649985704216547
    },
    {
        "question": "527389146÷86777498=？",
        "answer": 0.7837240632569027
    },
    {
        "question": "217×2862315=？",
        "answer": 8.79317716034912
    },
    {
        "question": "29785043÷283=？",
        "answer": 5.02221179589225
    },
    {
        "question": "7×12592543=？",
        "answer": 7.9452114825403
    },
    {
        "question": "141456290÷1737775=？",
        "answer": 1.9106287184957391
    },
    {
        "question": "118107730÷840=？",
        "answer": 5.147999036500693
    },
    {
        "question": "1646946÷745=？",
        "answer": 3.3445230870246863
    },
    {
        "question": "313832÷266=？",
        "answer": 3.0718155878807454
    },
    {
        "question": "69×102823=？",
        "answer": 6.850939361581622
    },
    {
        "question": "169063×241=？",
        "answer": 7.610065613779542
    },
    {
        "question": "76510081÷1008449=？",
        "answer": 1.8800647220900824
    },
    {
        "question": "1×7850248=？",
        "answer": 6.8948833769147075
    },
    {
        "question": "6630×351=？",
        "answer": 6.3668206448705975
    },
    {
        "question": "35×3176092=？",
        "answer": 8.045961118241875
    },
    {
        "question": "19846342÷6165520=？",
        "answer": 0.5077107601417905
    },
    {
        "question": "24261×1410=？",
        "answer": 7.534127810485659
    },
    {
        "question": "1×264=？",
        "answer": 2.4216039268698313
    },
    {
        "question": "6804254÷6506740=？",
        "answer": 0.019417063981484753
    },
    {
        "question": "323333881÷10071=？",
        "answer": 4.506578619192546
    },
    {
        "question": "8966×34271=？",
        "answer": 8.487525511505472
    },
    {
        "question": "65757178÷874065=？",
        "answer": 1.8763994367593002
    },
    {
        "question": "715627÷488=？",
        "answer": 3.1662668957643456
    },
    {
        "question": "70732669÷26849=？",
        "answer": 3.4206919310033896
    },
    {
        "question": "202×1114=？",
        "answer": 5.352236560284334
    },
    {
        "question": "3995222÷1838279=？",
        "answer": 0.337129490525455
    },
    {
        "question": "1×509392=？",
        "answer": 5.707052120087476
    },
    {
        "question": "3×2765=？",
        "answer": 3.9188163903603797
    },
    {
        "question": "49689÷403=？",
        "answer": 2.0909552104383535
    },
    {
        "question": "7839÷2580=？",
        "answer": 0.4826409584837579
    },
    {
        "question": "133×92548=？",
        "answer": 7.090218678876657
    },
    {
        "question": "353405627÷3608=？",
        "answer": 4.991006931285545
    },
    {
        "question": "41897÷453=？",
        "answer": 1.9660847247699182
    },
    {
        "question": "501÷434=？",
        "answer": 0.06234799635473503
    },
    {
        "question": "1301×194281=？",
        "answer": 8.402707626761824
    },
    {
        "question": "127134821÷2213422=？",
        "answer": 1.7592002936705382
    },
    {
        "question": "2×993=？",
        "answer": 3.2979792441593623
    },
    {
        "question": "239×49610=？",
        "answer": 7.073967127984323
    },
    {
        "question": "910035÷115601=？",
        "answer": 0.8960965046928557
    },
    {
        "question": "118×235=？",
        "answer": 4.442949869577862
    },
    {
        "question": "220601548÷2010=？",
        "answer": 5.040412498215411
    },
    {
        "question": "802410÷1183=？",
        "answer": 2.8314115877943977
    },
    {
        "question": "1492÷756=？",
        "answer": 0.29524702763544347
    },
    {
        "question": "15×1273=？",
        "answer": 4.280919662709336
    },
    {
        "question": "941442÷34710=？",
        "answer": 1.4333389556564664
    },
    {
        "question": "13122469÷1198=？",
        "answer": 4.039558737428049
    },
    {
        "question": "168533÷99682=？",
        "answer": 0.22806820858390825
    },
    {
        "question": "3756035÷173432=？",
        "answer": 1.335600398152291
    },
    {
        "question": "1991×5420=？",
        "answer": 7.0330705465657966
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1427=？",
        "answer": 3.154423973114647
    },
    {
        "question": "11586×17646=？",
        "answer": 8.310579799053752
    },
    {
        "question": "1230×106157=？",
        "answer": 8.115853748294127
    },
    {
        "question": "81976×6909=？",
        "answer": 8.753101915882363
    },
    {
        "question": "432×1389=？",
        "answer": 5.778185992552528
    },
    {
        "question": "77965÷23231=？",
        "answer": 0.5258317784137378
    },
    {
        "question": "567543391÷148083266=？",
        "answer": 0.5834930864291838
    },
    {
        "question": "4529892÷1555171=？",
        "answer": 0.4643096986831165
    },
    {
        "question": "2×349=？",
        "answer": 2.843855422623161
    },
    {
        "question": "16637÷1663=？",
        "answer": 1.000182767392202
    },
    {
        "question": "248×4161=？",
        "answer": 6.013649396619163
    },
    {
        "question": "22×297=？",
        "answer": 3.8151791301394185
    },
    {
        "question": "60×4819=？",
        "answer": 5.461108176684852
    },
    {
        "question": "29×76785=？",
        "answer": 6.347674386504883
    },
    {
        "question": "16×10988=？",
        "answer": 5.245038633404449
    },
    {
        "question": "12142106÷338=？",
        "answer": 4.555377319645714
    },
    {
        "question": "28163605÷11830012=？",
        "answer": 0.37670305946183036
    },
    {
        "question": "200888016÷8616=？",
        "answer": 4.367648339338821
    },
    {
        "question": "3×85074341=？",
        "answer": 8.406919848383225
    },
    {
        "question": "16012379÷2724957=？",
        "answer": 0.7690962074808676
    },
    {
        "question": "3177074÷1081790=？",
        "answer": 0.4678843679430965
    },
    {
        "question": "695×83593=？",
        "answer": 7.764154716136119
    },
    {
        "question": "23580995÷10737137=？",
        "answer": 0.341673631694555
    },
    {
        "question": "959685÷62945=？",
        "answer": 1.183167468897497
    },
    {
        "question": "41624÷1116=？",
        "answer": 1.5716796182864203
    },
    {
        "question": "101×780=？",
        "answer": 4.896415976473123
    },
    {
        "question": "55×1263703=？",
        "answer": 7.8420077059902535
    },
    {
        "question": "50×9329=？",
        "answer": 5.668805097411816
    },
    {
        "question": "97359319÷27436=？",
        "answer": 3.55005673328313
    },
    {
        "question": "108×44367=？",
        "answer": 6.680483819148427
    },
    {
        "question": "5279542÷58798=？",
        "answer": 1.953233695239896
    },
    {
        "question": "64814530÷1335531=？",
        "answer": 1.686018402903548
    },
    {
        "question": "11×537=？",
        "answer": 3.771366970857781
    },
    {
        "question": "32758383÷76266=？",
        "answer": 2.6329914871248334
    },
    {
        "question": "13688×820=？",
        "answer": 7.050153848916761
    },
    {
        "question": "5058115÷1073753=？",
        "answer": 0.6730843088949995
    },
    {
        "question": "2×117237=？",
        "answer": 5.370094692328064
    },
    {
        "question": "1×361717=？",
        "answer": 5.55836892024267
    },
    {
        "question": "2×118657=？",
        "answer": 5.375323359554883
    },
    {
        "question": "396×2126=？",
        "answer": 5.925258446112791
    },
    {
        "question": "231871292÷797285=？",
        "answer": 2.4636333885186206
    },
    {
        "question": "693917÷99310=？",
        "answer": 0.8443145453398196
    },
    {
        "question": "1×868858=？",
        "answer": 5.938948804232792
    },
    {
        "question": "51592642÷250363=？",
        "answer": 2.314017621274832
    },
    {
        "question": "182386÷13520=？",
        "answer": 1.1300148071011629
    },
    {
        "question": "625601×1266=？",
        "answer": 8.898731139937308
    },
    {
        "question": "1993×268410=？",
        "answer": 8.72830599076345
    },
    {
        "question": "1×87370=？",
        "answer": 4.941362335711761
    },
    {
        "question": "26538÷20387=？",
        "answer": 0.11451486683446738
    },
    {
        "question": "8834×4519=？",
        "answer": 7.601199736253574
    },
    {
        "question": "1126×1486=？",
        "answer": 6.223557199939884
    },
    {
        "question": "172×18657=？",
        "answer": 6.506370258440735
    },
    {
        "question": "50×48941=？",
        "answer": 6.388642843279966
    },
    {
        "question": "9307×57695=？",
        "answer": 8.72994789160066
    },
    {
        "question": "68271÷305=？",
        "answer": 2.34993642488326
    },
    {
        "question": "434796724÷3241=？",
        "answer": 5.127607232178545
    },
    {
        "question": "93×3420715=？",
        "answer": 8.502599840604134
    },
    {
        "question": "1036×21276=？",
        "answer": 7.343249737057757
    },
    {
        "question": "6778×46423=？",
        "answer": 8.497834767000978
    },
    {
        "question": "2705366÷26639=？",
        "answer": 2.0067081098315325
    },
    {
        "question": "19×3222171=？",
        "answer": 7.786902185572892
    },
    {
        "question": "7908831÷828=？",
        "answer": 3.980081958625792
    },
    {
        "question": "283417560÷7184417=？",
        "answer": 1.5960352229490935
    },
    {
        "question": "14857536÷3394544=？",
        "answer": 0.6411653488707945
    },
    {
        "question": "10856116÷2077=？",
        "answer": 3.718237978673946
    },
    {
        "question": "424934781÷60420=？",
        "answer": 3.847141558700562
    },
    {
        "question": "12821141÷37397=？",
        "answer": 2.535089912001779
    },
    {
        "question": "21043861÷201440=？",
        "answer": 2.018979711746415
    },
    {
        "question": "4785÷1010=？",
        "answer": 0.6755605683302198
    },
    {
        "question": "126×35961=？",
        "answer": 6.656202305165501
    },
    {
        "question": "14101376÷468498=？",
        "answer": 1.4785537515595106
    },
    {
        "question": "93356735÷6031643=？",
        "answer": 1.1897100258952171
    },
    {
        "question": "1842÷1533=？",
        "answer": 0.07974747100645496
    },
    {
        "question": "5027526÷220=？",
        "answer": 4.35893164441919
    },
    {
        "question": "1971×15419=？",
        "answer": 7.482742832717812
    },
    {
        "question": "2440160÷216399=？",
        "answer": 1.0521630542079508
    },
    {
        "question": "424×39601=？",
        "answer": 7.225072009412146
    },
    {
        "question": "214395÷1183=？",
        "answer": 2.258229908138463
    },
    {
        "question": "3×1780=？",
        "answer": 3.727541257028556
    },
    {
        "question": "222035÷527=？",
        "answer": 2.6246108236920116
    },
    {
        "question": "1×3433=？",
        "answer": 3.53567380342575
    },
    {
        "question": "91×543489=？",
        "answer": 7.694232150885734
    },
    {
        "question": "422199÷377471=？",
        "answer": 0.048633608660240024
    },
    {
        "question": "18477÷659=？",
        "answer": 1.447746044215907
    },
    {
        "question": "320360061÷4702046=？",
        "answer": 1.8333514941834597
    },
    {
        "question": "76×26852=？",
        "answer": 6.309790230793674
    },
    {
        "question": "334347÷1856=？",
        "answer": 2.2556194588703904
    },
    {
        "question": "982340606÷336=？",
        "answer": 6.4659228190108395
    },
    {
        "question": "2×59608=？",
        "answer": 5.07633454605351
    },
    {
        "question": "9×6123372=？",
        "answer": 7.7412331534316134
    },
    {
        "question": "1×270749=？",
        "answer": 5.432566861251988
    },
    {
        "question": "1317680÷202085=？",
        "answer": 0.8142758754961743
    },
    {
        "question": "1×4607386=？",
        "answer": 6.663454598327696
    },
    {
        "question": "1233×15727=？",
        "answer": 7.287608963382819
    },
    {
        "question": "150283÷3748=？",
        "answer": 1.6031102737952585
    },
    {
        "question": "95472808÷84482=？",
        "answer": 3.053115509350876
    },
    {
        "question": "19830286÷12000380=？",
        "answer": 0.21813397932379583
    },
    {
        "question": "85236492÷218523=？",
        "answer": 2.5911284134417625
    },
    {
        "question": "120×4020934=？",
        "answer": 8.683508190657363
    },
    {
        "question": "3×10923873=？",
        "answer": 7.51549789714673
    },
    {
        "question": "147×2073546=？",
        "answer": 8.484031009039278
    },
    {
        "question": "26×221865=？",
        "answer": 6.76106214409307
    },
    {
        "question": "78824246÷433023=？",
        "answer": 2.260148860658453
    },
    {
        "question": "78×472726=？",
        "answer": 7.566704091911106
    },
    {
        "question": "20×20821=？",
        "answer": 5.619531579822768
    },
    {
        "question": "4558238÷1886893=？",
        "answer": 0.3830497239871705
    },
    {
        "question": "4353×3931=？",
        "answer": 7.233291710977488
    },
    {
        "question": "35×1477910=？",
        "answer": 7.7137160320670874
    },
    {
        "question": "32105821÷337=？",
        "answer": 4.978953879165655
    },
    {
        "question": "934686937÷1785=？",
        "answer": 5.71902795267003
    },
    {
        "question": "447717600÷117152=？",
        "answer": 3.582254459848175
    },
    {
        "question": "416×169890=？",
        "answer": 7.8492611469729345
    },
    {
        "question": "4×39249948=？",
        "answer": 8.195899077037819
    },
    {
        "question": "224×2970204=？",
        "answer": 8.823034296954996
    },
    {
        "question": "104×2415=？",
        "answer": 5.399950474386311
    },
    {
        "question": "638323247÷33527022=？",
        "answer": 1.2796456818010644
    },
    {
        "question": "2284×76126=？",
        "answer": 8.240229110195095
    },
    {
        "question": "15126447÷114342=？",
        "answer": 2.1215311456821113
    },
    {
        "question": "262128÷3170=？",
        "answer": 1.9174541516933792
    },
    {
        "question": "714646822÷50031482=？",
        "answer": 1.1548480993019268
    },
    {
        "question": "27768571÷1084=？",
        "answer": 4.408524248870075
    },
    {
        "question": "4×473=？",
        "answer": 3.276921132065774
    },
    {
        "question": "3634305÷106983=？",
        "answer": 1.5311065994392976
    },
    {
        "question": "175956374÷1762476=？",
        "answer": 1.9992817918993073
    },
    {
        "question": "111×401016=？",
        "answer": 7.6484846795192745
    },
    {
        "question": "8327×574=？",
        "answer": 6.679400457056271
    },
    {
        "question": "1229×185148=？",
        "answer": 8.357070907974832
    },
    {
        "question": "1456÷431=？",
        "answer": 0.5286841048162868
    },
    {
        "question": "1×3770038=？",
        "answer": 6.576345727687793
    },
    {
        "question": "151015432÷2508380=？",
        "answer": 1.7796279999777451
    },
    {
        "question": "848698992÷2867126=？",
        "answer": 2.471306907300116
    },
    {
        "question": "4160424÷1050511=？",
        "answer": 0.5977369886966285
    },
    {
        "question": "150×937112=？",
        "answer": 8.147882758241396
    },
    {
        "question": "1294565÷565=？",
        "answer": 3.3600754133883934
    },
    {
        "question": "419226088÷277186791=？",
        "answer": 0.17967576985035258
    },
    {
        "question": "38076÷12969=？",
        "answer": 0.46774482789472294
    },
    {
        "question": "73538803÷162683=？",
        "answer": 2.6551743839948925
    },
    {
        "question": "8×61990=？",
        "answer": 5.695411623343517
    },
    {
        "question": "804730÷341320=？",
        "answer": 0.3724884549859625
    },
    {
        "question": "34×51148=？",
        "answer": 6.240307573547024
    },
    {
        "question": "1571×9256=？",
        "answer": 7.162599530983666
    },
    {
        "question": "126850092÷186631=？",
        "answer": 2.8323070034459086
    },
    {
        "question": "163268÷35962=？",
        "answer": 0.6570572360644086
    },
    {
        "question": "16×60142=？",
        "answer": 5.983297848963179
    },
    {
        "question": "10×38055=？",
        "answer": 5.580411726277412
    },
    {
        "question": "68290÷487=？",
        "answer": 2.1468281515037706
    },
    {
        "question": "81×353=？",
        "answer": 4.456259724266472
    },
    {
        "question": "252161899÷300=？",
        "answer": 5.924558211720017
    },
    {
        "question": "5×1551798=？",
        "answer": 6.889805192137757
    },
    {
        "question": "1×2390=？",
        "answer": 3.3783979009481375
    },
    {
        "question": "19×1068=？",
        "answer": 4.307324853645366
    },
    {
        "question": "61665649÷519=？",
        "answer": 5.074875948743035
    },
    {
        "question": "151770×2120=？",
        "answer": 8.50752179505698
    },
    {
        "question": "1160186÷8157=？",
        "answer": 2.152997158211219
    },
    {
        "question": "176955÷31569=？",
        "answer": 0.7486020133543825
    },
    {
        "question": "5×15309028=？",
        "answer": 7.883917621707226
    },
    {
        "question": "348×58712=？",
        "answer": 7.310306118638153
    },
    {
        "question": "922×653=？",
        "answer": 5.779644102328703
    },
    {
        "question": "478×472986=？",
        "answer": 8.354276182777564
    },
    {
        "question": "106649÷1698=？",
        "answer": 1.7980191017113816
    },
    {
        "question": "950888966÷5185734=？",
        "answer": 2.2633195718715493
    },
    {
        "question": "17×32751=？",
        "answer": 5.745673486403835
    },
    {
        "question": "4251×14702=？",
        "answer": 7.795867523380706
    },
    {
        "question": "47×7000522=？",
        "answer": 8.517228282702437
    },
    {
        "question": "62321÷7775=？",
        "answer": 0.9039340156915242
    },
    {
        "question": "316287129÷217176=？",
        "answer": 3.1632696891549905
    },
    {
        "question": "1100÷999=？",
        "answer": 0.04182719693224275
    },
    {
        "question": "36×80537=？",
        "answer": 6.462297948888072
    },
    {
        "question": "17×2882=？",
        "answer": 4.690142897856244
    },
    {
        "question": "126345509÷483831=？",
        "answer": 2.4168661183493225
    },
    {
        "question": "4149110÷484668=？",
        "answer": 0.9325106023112755
    },
    {
        "question": "273543÷10299=？",
        "answer": 1.4242305474595003
    },
    {
        "question": "2204238×235=？",
        "answer": 8.71432634741804
    },
    {
        "question": "900978÷307=？",
        "answer": 3.4675758110676353
    },
    {
        "question": "18×1111493=？",
        "answer": 7.301179237031751
    },
    {
        "question": "3931÷364=？",
        "answer": 1.0334016601710332
    },
    {
        "question": "92675543÷58384301=？",
        "answer": 0.20066905427641793
    },
    {
        "question": "585483190÷34761407=？",
        "answer": 1.2264170838140078
    },
    {
        "question": "120×29832=？",
        "answer": 6.553863616400876
    },
    {
        "question": "16×3336=？",
        "answer": 4.7273460246216255
    },
    {
        "question": "259137×2556=？",
        "answer": 8.821090276168075
    },
    {
        "question": "12486573÷11474=？",
        "answer": 3.036728414972623
    },
    {
        "question": "2×91446784=？",
        "answer": 8.262198432479009
    },
    {
        "question": "20630÷10642=？",
        "answer": 0.2874759733844479
    },
    {
        "question": "336934241÷914264=？",
        "answer": 2.5664735291218714
    },
    {
        "question": "2301743÷141317=？",
        "answer": 1.211862421780376
    },
    {
        "question": "5×47819=？",
        "answer": 5.378570494162139
    },
    {
        "question": "49901×12800=？",
        "answer": 8.805319218480282
    },
    {
        "question": "33677069÷51766=？",
        "answer": 2.813289678733261
    },
    {
        "question": "13×1739668=？",
        "answer": 7.354409727298979
    },
    {
        "question": "12932671÷1203=？",
        "answer": 4.031422602162728
    },
    {
        "question": "94123÷35088=？",
        "answer": 0.42853714674046767
    },
    {
        "question": "26915×6890=？",
        "answer": 8.268213606059332
    },
    {
        "question": "419793÷270=？",
        "answer": 3.1916714283372287
    },
    {
        "question": "4×71126520=？",
        "answer": 8.454091551863728
    },
    {
        "question": "5×358=？",
        "answer": 3.2528530309798933
    },
    {
        "question": "603879501÷11430=？",
        "answer": 4.7229040571138725
    },
    {
        "question": "167246÷495=？",
        "answer": 2.5287505406680175
    },
    {
        "question": "22×14005812=？",
        "answer": 8.488730973338921
    },
    {
        "question": "3×1080=？",
        "answer": 3.510545010206612
    },
    {
        "question": "4×713957=？",
        "answer": 6.455732047326719
    },
    {
        "question": "409702851÷764=？",
        "answer": 5.729375627513796
    },
    {
        "question": "2×9127691=？",
        "answer": 7.261390925138735
    },
    {
        "question": "160017294÷528=？",
        "answer": 5.481532999390197
    },
    {
        "question": "88×198924=？",
        "answer": 7.243169855670651
    },
    {
        "question": "12181×420=？",
        "answer": 6.708932233592516
    },
    {
        "question": "438153÷18047=？",
        "answer": 1.3852207712862674
    },
    {
        "question": "1×880=？",
        "answer": 2.9444826721501687
    },
    {
        "question": "25315×5594=？",
        "answer": 8.151100393758368
    },
    {
        "question": "1×107139130=？",
        "answer": 8.029948115457287
    },
    {
        "question": "3802×325=？",
        "answer": 6.091895473508298
    },
    {
        "question": "1169×204927=？",
        "answer": 8.379413693469846
    },
    {
        "question": "731×1673=？",
        "answer": 6.087413317920255
    },
    {
        "question": "8×120976=？",
        "answer": 5.985789207710088
    },
    {
        "question": "391156250÷1217812=？",
        "answer": 2.5067700247482887
    },
    {
        "question": "261525867÷398=？",
        "answer": 5.817631578451915
    },
    {
        "question": "429385415÷2914=？",
        "answer": 5.168357741169765
    },
    {
        "question": "31×60628=？",
        "answer": 6.274034935773837
    },
    {
        "question": "6998898÷134176=？",
        "answer": 1.7173548235486285
    },
    {
        "question": "121042÷307=？",
        "answer": 2.5957977155275986
    },
    {
        "question": "53×1458=？",
        "answer": 4.888033393582745
    },
    {
        "question": "785463÷2309=？",
        "answer": 2.5317017990758814
    },
    {
        "question": "781021÷2705=？",
        "answer": 2.460495441850215
    },
    {
        "question": "25×13742=？",
        "answer": 5.535989952876927
    },
    {
        "question": "3×202941=？",
        "answer": 5.784491050767123
    },
    {
        "question": "3842293÷6081=？",
        "answer": 2.8006154761737316
    },
    {
        "question": "2786915÷173364=？",
        "answer": 1.2061648042401445
    },
    {
        "question": "9×213=？",
        "answer": 3.2826221128780624
    },
    {
        "question": "740070176÷14947=？",
        "answer": 4.694718868459534
    },
    {
        "question": "75626×273=？",
        "answer": 7.314833777400264
    },
    {
        "question": "72×39186=？",
        "answer": 6.4504634305756685
    },
    {
        "question": "1179÷265=？",
        "answer": 0.6482679311582813
    },
    {
        "question": "184458204÷3497135=？",
        "answer": 1.7221855780458317
    },
    {
        "question": "2519÷1220=？",
        "answer": 0.31486833682336485
    },
    {
        "question": "30649×762=？",
        "answer": 7.368371280485493
    },
    {
        "question": "515×299649=？",
        "answer": 8.188420061732108
    },
    {
        "question": "299793×228=？",
        "answer": 7.834756335096221
    },
    {
        "question": "163194447÷3324645=？",
        "answer": 1.6909600980967359
    },
    {
        "question": "23×68368=？",
        "answer": 6.196580711490714
    },
    {
        "question": "710365÷1468=？",
        "answer": 2.6847554998350263
    },
    {
        "question": "636504×644=？",
        "answer": 8.612687004607096
    },
    {
        "question": "110×1293553=？",
        "answer": 8.153176912672318
    },
    {
        "question": "447583384÷286564=？",
        "answer": 3.1936523248488897
    },
    {
        "question": "2×169873=？",
        "answer": 5.53115435226795
    },
    {
        "question": "159658311÷632=？",
        "answer": 5.402474452344368
    },
    {
        "question": "1×6712753=？",
        "answer": 6.826900667338272
    },
    {
        "question": "92×429=？",
        "answer": 4.59624511953028
    },
    {
        "question": "1×488309025=？",
        "answer": 8.688694751053484
    },
    {
        "question": "327084÷4171=？",
        "answer": 1.8944191103731183
    },
    {
        "question": "1×6654=？",
        "answer": 3.8230827965328036
    },
    {
        "question": "121×656044=？",
        "answer": 7.899718338223182
    },
    {
        "question": "75631×6302=？",
        "answer": 8.678178241553416
    },
    {
        "question": "781×21487=？",
        "answer": 7.224826817707724
    },
    {
        "question": "14768×2022=？",
        "answer": 7.475102834936819
    },
    {
        "question": "6666×514=？",
        "answer": 6.534828428319787
    },
    {
        "question": "332×840=？",
        "answer": 5.445417369765918
    },
    {
        "question": "6233×637=？",
        "answer": 6.598836559227349
    },
    {
        "question": "90802÷60852=？",
        "answer": 0.17382055777798783
    },
    {
        "question": "738961÷679235=？",
        "answer": 0.036601461943988826
    },
    {
        "question": "6700773÷2337904=？",
        "answer": 0.45729823171742967
    },
    {
        "question": "130797÷8517=？",
        "answer": 1.1863111357458844
    },
    {
        "question": "263669×2090=？",
        "answer": 8.741205358186061
    },
    {
        "question": "599×29344=？",
        "answer": 7.244946136379238
    },
    {
        "question": "1209×803564=？",
        "answer": 8.987446772800148
    },
    {
        "question": "243×1009=？",
        "answer": 5.389497439835223
    },
    {
        "question": "340×427=？",
        "answer": 5.161906792067279
    },
    {
        "question": "251750989÷10402279=？",
        "answer": 1.3838426875212393
    },
    {
        "question": "612484÷11967=？",
        "answer": 1.7091094570234424
    },
    {
        "question": "188×5769=？",
        "answer": 6.0352583882218225
    },
    {
        "question": "243898÷261=？",
        "answer": 2.970567731710484
    },
    {
        "question": "6×1343911=？",
        "answer": 6.906521759065196
    },
    {
        "question": "863337×649=？",
        "answer": 8.74842505065198
    },
    {
        "question": "1×14805=？",
        "answer": 4.170408411725318
    },
    {
        "question": "207198777÷169091498=？",
        "answer": 0.0882654160222476
    },
    {
        "question": "53217720÷892=？",
        "answer": 4.775691409814637
    },
    {
        "question": "81255782÷72727849=？",
        "answer": 0.04815353122192783
    },
    {
        "question": "20122633÷8045=？",
        "answer": 3.39815875809574
    },
    {
        "question": "39361×4014=？",
        "answer": 8.198643491675126
    },
    {
        "question": "746579633÷9222=？",
        "answer": 4.908251020136092
    },
    {
        "question": "241254×227=？",
        "answer": 7.738500379886782
    },
    {
        "question": "447923504÷4104592=？",
        "answer": 2.037933857530407
    },
    {
        "question": "666351972÷40237956=？",
        "answer": 1.2190677759076411
    },
    {
        "question": "1312÷846=？",
        "answer": 0.19056347200061793
    },
    {
        "question": "4×24194160=？",
        "answer": 7.985770539711121
    },
    {
        "question": "52193302÷555520=？",
        "answer": 1.972915074127657
    },
    {
        "question": "1×37359=？",
        "answer": 4.572395242817844
    },
    {
        "question": "36875×1731=？",
        "answer": 7.805029096861613
    },
    {
        "question": "573699899÷480629=？",
        "answer": 3.076874801879924
    },
    {
        "question": "30463×8773=？",
        "answer": 8.426920799838873
    },
    {
        "question": "219275÷204=？",
        "answer": 3.031358952254546
    },
    {
        "question": "409×1545=？",
        "answer": 5.800651791768195
    },
    {
        "question": "4470976÷465=？",
        "answer": 3.9829493857109024
    },
    {
        "question": "673676300÷201969028=？",
        "answer": 0.5231664937106222
    },
    {
        "question": "26035694÷5489=？",
        "answer": 3.6760759278136717
    },
    {
        "question": "102863609÷891=？",
        "answer": 5.06238405356524
    },
    {
        "question": "2704×1291=？",
        "answer": 6.542932929536018
    },
    {
        "question": "9×713025=？",
        "answer": 6.807347266740988
    },
    {
        "question": "5×43019720=？",
        "answer": 8.332637583728916
    },
    {
        "question": "347565÷103629=？",
        "answer": 0.5255547289525153
    },
    {
        "question": "46357365÷7625271=？",
        "answer": 0.7838634592533491
    },
    {
        "question": "15×31993457=？",
        "answer": 8.681152428646126
    },
    {
        "question": "1082×2616=？",
        "answer": 6.451865000422781
    },
    {
        "question": "3689074÷10957=？",
        "answer": 2.527225705279954
    },
    {
        "question": "2029758÷680=？",
        "answer": 3.474935349083993
    },
    {
        "question": "66807÷51037=？",
        "answer": 0.11693683174240851
    },
    {
        "question": "28452851÷102264=？",
        "answer": 2.444403013677829
    },
    {
        "question": "177011÷5501=？",
        "answer": 1.507558610625949
    },
    {
        "question": "58019600÷1298650=？",
        "answer": 1.6500826104977453
    },
    {
        "question": "223949345÷92788=？",
        "answer": 3.382657982753342
    },
    {
        "question": "134×1371317=？",
        "answer": 8.26424265828719
    },
    {
        "question": "51273244÷47383=？",
        "answer": 3.034268241517496
    },
    {
        "question": "2×3710=？",
        "answer": 3.870403905279027
    },
    {
        "question": "554634035÷712307=？",
        "answer": 2.891339304173981
    },
    {
        "question": "7×21989353=？",
        "answer": 8.187310491172976
    },
    {
        "question": "105069245÷71379234=？",
        "answer": 0.167903728491211
    },
    {
        "question": "168927÷1832=？",
        "answer": 1.9647736000963012
    },
    {
        "question": "234739276÷11373499=？",
        "answer": 1.3146916669999982
    },
    {
        "question": "9891667÷497462=？",
        "answer": 1.2985095759690286
    },
    {
        "question": "15×67639=？",
        "answer": 6.006288437258554
    },
    {
        "question": "638355×467=？",
        "answer": 8.474379144966887
    },
    {
        "question": "70910646÷331=？",
        "answer": 5.33088344806416
    },
    {
        "question": "349189293÷153284=？",
        "answer": 3.357564093754001
    },
    {
        "question": "5×160603516=？",
        "answer": 8.90472505314097
    },
    {
        "question": "36562381÷312=？",
        "answer": 5.068879875906891
    },
    {
        "question": "2924×331=？",
        "answer": 5.985805362061542
    },
    {
        "question": "512090037÷1798=？",
        "answer": 5.454556639075706
    },
    {
        "question": "1628644÷5742=？",
        "answer": 2.4527629755021976
    },
    {
        "question": "120×16204=？",
        "answer": 6.288803480559175
    },
    {
        "question": "1×216039=？",
        "answer": 5.334532158354171
    },
    {
        "question": "61×3217=？",
        "answer": 5.2927808959127365
    },
    {
        "question": "32149511÷2046043=？",
        "answer": 1.196259614929834
    },
    {
        "question": "1601×119934=？",
        "answer": 8.283333650290743
    },
    {
        "question": "1156567÷791769=？",
        "answer": 0.16457230265297937
    },
    {
        "question": "22×1266343=？",
        "answer": 7.444974034869664
    },
    {
        "question": "6×238930=？",
        "answer": 6.156421933480002
    },
    {
        "question": "854020729÷193342414=？",
        "answer": 0.645141275392027
    },
    {
        "question": "2×172312=？",
        "answer": 5.53734551891764
    },
    {
        "question": "913×12047=？",
        "answer": 7.041349687876116
    },
    {
        "question": "40200960÷382843=？",
        "answer": 2.021215713421738
    },
    {
        "question": "315×978919=？",
        "answer": 8.489057311672026
    },
    {
        "question": "1×38196=？",
        "answer": 4.582017884668628
    },
    {
        "question": "29094÷2613=？",
        "answer": 1.0466640247718424
    },
    {
        "question": "788×938=？",
        "answer": 5.86872905586862
    },
    {
        "question": "23745×2401=？",
        "answer": 7.755964333975064
    },
    {
        "question": "311×604584=？",
        "answer": 8.27421703864393
    },
    {
        "question": "73×5358314=？",
        "answer": 8.592351020021912
    },
    {
        "question": "661×48894=？",
        "answer": 7.50945702767332
    },
    {
        "question": "1152537÷19721=？",
        "answer": 1.766725943387118
    },
    {
        "question": "5×1018608=？",
        "answer": 6.70697708707566
    },
    {
        "question": "8×1192=？",
        "answer": 3.979366242396161
    },
    {
        "question": "633705÷2015=？",
        "answer": 2.4976120832913855
    },
    {
        "question": "7932896÷2703=？",
        "answer": 3.4675857150387084
    },
    {
        "question": "35961420÷28910731=？",
        "answer": 0.09477775945443719
    },
    {
        "question": "226×10431=？",
        "answer": 6.3724343845503215
    },
    {
        "question": "10795052÷49171=？",
        "answer": 2.3415156979716034
    },
    {
        "question": "491049072÷234404666=？",
        "answer": 0.3211586422478035
    },
    {
        "question": "3910387÷668285=？",
        "answer": 0.7672580271554696
    },
    {
        "question": "1×4153640=？",
        "answer": 6.6184288531069715
    },
    {
        "question": "5×7422=？",
        "answer": 4.569490954348783
    },
    {
        "question": "2×450=？",
        "answer": 2.9542425094393248
    },
    {
        "question": "7×1084=？",
        "answer": 3.880127322216625
    },
    {
        "question": "29505557÷9951=？",
        "answer": 3.472037091337572
    },
    {
        "question": "5×49749=？",
        "answer": 5.395754359792703
    },
    {
        "question": "589×4314=？",
        "answer": 6.404995435553628
    },
    {
        "question": "2121×44638=？",
        "answer": 7.976245396372114
    },
    {
        "question": "222×607960=？",
        "answer": 8.130227980778075
    },
    {
        "question": "73×42807=？",
        "answer": 6.4948376527971154
    },
    {
        "question": "102×180573=？",
        "answer": 7.265252985139054
    },
    {
        "question": "17×1995159=？",
        "answer": 7.530426432965472
    },
    {
        "question": "82798669÷548384=？",
        "answer": 2.1789385804468324
    },
    {
        "question": "103252÷400=？",
        "answer": 2.4118384814029112
    },
    {
        "question": "10×92028944=？",
        "answer": 8.963924438677607
    },
    {
        "question": "54825794÷1433=？",
        "answer": 4.582738739552246
    },
    {
        "question": "7677×3056=？",
        "answer": 7.3703448905105
    },
    {
        "question": "1×93312371=？",
        "answer": 7.9699392246776535
    },
    {
        "question": "3288×1580=？",
        "answer": 6.715588895822435
    },
    {
        "question": "754217÷124168=？",
        "answer": 0.7834866312435594
    },
    {
        "question": "1288333÷226736=？",
        "answer": 0.7545076504771522
    },
    {
        "question": "995244÷18939=？",
        "answer": 1.7205725239978698
    },
    {
        "question": "354114÷1283=？",
        "answer": 2.4409164406812773
    },
    {
        "question": "6×348092=？",
        "answer": 6.319845292640125
    },
    {
        "question": "9874×6080=？",
        "answer": 7.778396702156248
    },
    {
        "question": "376×54501=？",
        "answer": 7.311592315837287
    },
    {
        "question": "8697×52956=？",
        "answer": 8.663284643569478
    },
    {
        "question": "99583333÷378=？",
        "answer": 5.420694857945601
    },
    {
        "question": "723363×846=？",
        "answer": 8.786726653880459
    },
    {
        "question": "49143078÷315=？",
        "answer": 5.193151800563488
    },
    {
        "question": "12928÷2830=？",
        "answer": 0.6597449079062208
    },
    {
        "question": "644583114÷178902=？",
        "answer": 3.556663728504776
    },
    {
        "question": "398195674÷733029=？",
        "answer": 2.734975381055351
    },
    {
        "question": "55×66762=？",
        "answer": 6.5648920279261604
    },
    {
        "question": "473906968÷35708588=？",
        "answer": 1.122920416785818
    },
    {
        "question": "2303×214947=？",
        "answer": 8.694625326042342
    },
    {
        "question": "882796810÷8319938=？",
        "answer": 2.0257406652129957
    },
    {
        "question": "1343÷593=？",
        "answer": 0.35502131930445274
    },
    {
        "question": "6628515÷8143=？",
        "answer": 2.910631808613077
    },
    {
        "question": "629728÷36087=？",
        "answer": 1.2418022244409745
    },
    {
        "question": "9887÷4384=？",
        "answer": 0.35319398867982876
    },
    {
        "question": "30×5483609=？",
        "answer": 8.216187735265244
    },
    {
        "question": "173×810823=？",
        "answer": 8.1469721626261
    },
    {
        "question": "2411402÷990=？",
        "answer": 3.386634422179092
    },
    {
        "question": "26×14027=？",
        "answer": 5.561938144960566
    },
    {
        "question": "15×31538=？",
        "answer": 5.674925407893072
    },
    {
        "question": "546691÷213=？",
        "answer": 3.409362320859788
    },
    {
        "question": "41×354006=？",
        "answer": 7.161794479606566
    },
    {
        "question": "11×39905=？",
        "answer": 5.64242000030271
    },
    {
        "question": "936236854÷189214=？",
        "answer": 3.694432465850935
    },
    {
        "question": "1×5994256=？",
        "answer": 6.7777352866598815
    },
    {
        "question": "96169863÷690=？",
        "answer": 5.144189906629566
    },
    {
        "question": "164939742÷215005=？",
        "answer": 2.88487675123107
    },
    {
        "question": "346÷262=？",
        "answer": 0.12077480747303118
    },
    {
        "question": "14198774÷75930=？",
        "answer": 2.2718374467571634
    },
    {
        "question": "2×36949=？",
        "answer": 4.86863268466387
    },
    {
        "question": "540÷330=？",
        "answer": 0.21387981994508107
    },
    {
        "question": "2×216171=？",
        "answer": 5.63582742725752
    },
    {
        "question": "657632972÷109297493=？",
        "answer": 0.7793733789902038
    },
    {
        "question": "118192×777=？",
        "answer": 7.963009100477826
    },
    {
        "question": "124×7167274=？",
        "answer": 8.94877569273118
    },
    {
        "question": "505017÷337=？",
        "answer": 3.1756760968154945
    },
    {
        "question": "2381×1231=？",
        "answer": 6.467017448336196
    },
    {
        "question": "1057088÷30015=？",
        "answer": 1.546772795077775
    },
    {
        "question": "17×27842827=？",
        "answer": 8.67516225031137
    },
    {
        "question": "144959÷31770=？",
        "answer": 0.6592279695344266
    },
    {
        "question": "2730×4185=？",
        "answer": 7.057858109370035
    },
    {
        "question": "1×44240=？",
        "answer": 4.645815118296642
    },
    {
        "question": "217345÷3291=？",
        "answer": 1.8198217714462546
    },
    {
        "question": "627908660÷534532=？",
        "answer": 3.069922763250063
    },
    {
        "question": "5324×511=？",
        "answer": 6.4346589469373505
    },
    {
        "question": "7×633=？",
        "answer": 3.646501750031612
    },
    {
        "question": "249×2517832=？",
        "answer": 8.79722609593865
    },
    {
        "question": "7×7162=？",
        "answer": 4.700132356690141
    },
    {
        "question": "268514÷60485=？",
        "answer": 0.6473192492385522
    },
    {
        "question": "107037×4740=？",
        "answer": 8.705312269996712
    },
    {
        "question": "60828073÷202=？",
        "answer": 5.478752689023162
    },
    {
        "question": "874899129÷5423=？",
        "answer": 5.207718379736595
    },
    {
        "question": "65×42891=？",
        "answer": 6.445279528538704
    },
    {
        "question": "904243÷2346=？",
        "answer": 2.585957147671133
    },
    {
        "question": "215022÷16685=？",
        "answer": 1.110156686086661
    },
    {
        "question": "1×5521=？",
        "answer": 3.7420177471401384
    },
    {
        "question": "5×3254=？",
        "answer": 4.211387552936859
    },
    {
        "question": "902161377÷131525=？",
        "answer": 3.836275919835362
    },
    {
        "question": "3666367÷385=？",
        "answer": 3.9787752057760146
    },
    {
        "question": "4×7798=？",
        "answer": 4.494043222179929
    },
    {
        "question": "29×257005=？",
        "answer": 6.872339570457046
    },
    {
        "question": "21×7344=？",
        "answer": 5.188151962927106
    },
    {
        "question": "132×20793=？",
        "answer": 6.438491084772606
    },
    {
        "question": "420986÷1973=？",
        "answer": 2.3291405682465567
    },
    {
        "question": "6614821÷4825=？",
        "answer": 3.1370207788007645
    },
    {
        "question": "116430587÷47554967=？",
        "answer": 0.38887120237848855
    },
    {
        "question": "833312÷19618=？",
        "answer": 1.62815290567334
    },
    {
        "question": "429298675÷394=？",
        "answer": 6.037263326236729
    },
    {
        "question": "442×36302=？",
        "answer": 7.205352821796682
    },
    {
        "question": "5727×8986=？",
        "answer": 7.711493597370336
    },
    {
        "question": "1031947÷76411=？",
        "answer": 1.1305015094502833
    },
    {
        "question": "283×3953=？",
        "answer": 6.0487132498672604
    },
    {
        "question": "57987÷1148=？",
        "answer": 1.7033887527237164
    },
    {
        "question": "2711÷1149=？",
        "answer": 0.3728094888922004
    },
    {
        "question": "112×9544=？",
        "answer": 6.028948453332467
    },
    {
        "question": "59281693÷15042221=？",
        "answer": 0.5956086329406785
    },
    {
        "question": "356963526÷42475673=？",
        "answer": 0.9244835741023596
    },
    {
        "question": "139348÷60374=？",
        "answer": 0.36325078944144734
    },
    {
        "question": "23×1853928=？",
        "answer": 7.629820699693449
    },
    {
        "question": "32959433÷976=？",
        "answer": 4.528529914269512
    },
    {
        "question": "1986×206=？",
        "answer": 5.611846464528516
    },
    {
        "question": "15×40978=？",
        "answer": 5.788642017167711
    },
    {
        "question": "42×455709=？",
        "answer": 7.281936896140191
    },
    {
        "question": "39659232÷2642=？",
        "answer": 4.176411486570816
    },
    {
        "question": "10182784÷5986301=？",
        "answer": 0.23070798147480254
    },
    {
        "question": "61×369=？",
        "answer": 4.352356201169828
    },
    {
        "question": "4×23482208=？",
        "answer": 7.97279892194151
    },
    {
        "question": "65626461÷1849369=？",
        "answer": 1.5500554114386322
    },
    {
        "question": "301×117592=？",
        "answer": 7.548944272486718
    },
    {
        "question": "694×5630=？",
        "answer": 6.5918678653062015
    },
    {
        "question": "21488080÷2315=？",
        "answer": 3.9676466168495717
    },
    {
        "question": "11×107979=？",
        "answer": 6.074731986284809
    },
    {
        "question": "89×1995=？",
        "answer": 5.2493329066676795
    },
    {
        "question": "45258120÷3543606=？",
        "answer": 1.1062510812580362
    },
    {
        "question": "13887034÷13638=？",
        "answer": 3.007858812690057
    },
    {
        "question": "648387÷1748=？",
        "answer": 2.569292870467755
    },
    {
        "question": "3985×6624=？",
        "answer": 7.421548649508955
    },
    {
        "question": "32×75924=？",
        "answer": 6.3855290588266795
    },
    {
        "question": "267×274=？",
        "answer": 4.864261824184963
    },
    {
        "question": "97709×412=？",
        "answer": 7.6048317845658095
    },
    {
        "question": "80×791617=？",
        "answer": 7.80160509911412
    },
    {
        "question": "156208×1180=？",
        "answer": 8.265585279273056
    },
    {
        "question": "1×462773906=？",
        "answer": 8.665368862812768
    },
    {
        "question": "2×631=？",
        "answer": 3.1010593549081156
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1225=？",
        "answer": 3.0881360887005513
    },
    {
        "question": "703415294÷1189=？",
        "answer": 5.772029952108319
    },
    {
        "question": "72×46555=？",
        "answer": 6.525298827415599
    },
    {
        "question": "60184×10198=？",
        "answer": 8.787996056442585
    },
    {
        "question": "5×47560850=？",
        "answer": 8.376219611994424
    },
    {
        "question": "690517÷4710=？",
        "answer": 2.1661534679150947
    },
    {
        "question": "205837700÷2281609=？",
        "answer": 1.9552836992006
    },
    {
        "question": "18413÷17849=？",
        "answer": 0.013510663615589018
    },
    {
        "question": "25678674÷12158=？",
        "answer": 3.3247104547506012
    },
    {
        "question": "2×1681=？",
        "answer": 3.526597709103452
    },
    {
        "question": "14247×5606=？",
        "answer": 7.902376517725948
    },
    {
        "question": "125592520÷60144073=？",
        "answer": 0.31977093910062643
    },
    {
        "question": "92377÷1351=？",
        "answer": 1.8349085051365872
    },
    {
        "question": "13959386÷3517=？",
        "answer": 3.598693948059296
    },
    {
        "question": "225685303÷15682179=？",
        "answer": 1.158096871338366
    },
    {
        "question": "3180377÷5848=？",
        "answer": 2.7354712400959884
    },
    {
        "question": "3×1487=？",
        "answer": 3.6494322232416168
    },
    {
        "question": "24501×1101=？",
        "answer": 7.430971129279917
    },
    {
        "question": "474424270÷2479=？",
        "answer": 5.281890371247463
    },
    {
        "question": "300663841÷989=？",
        "answer": 5.482884909704454
    },
    {
        "question": "7952748÷894550=？",
        "answer": 0.9489126010635426
    },
    {
        "question": "26290÷353=？",
        "answer": 1.87201588071854
    },
    {
        "question": "4860906÷3268=？",
        "answer": 3.172435174926565
    },
    {
        "question": "64×61925=？",
        "answer": 6.598045989241761
    },
    {
        "question": "17371×6595=？",
        "answer": 8.059039620170651
    },
    {
        "question": "415870865÷1234=？",
        "answer": 5.527643336015278
    },
    {
        "question": "19065×491=？",
        "answer": 6.971318301732658
    },
    {
        "question": "13139×490=？",
        "answer": 6.808758392664116
    },
    {
        "question": "6278×1308=？",
        "answer": 6.914429055352272
    },
    {
        "question": "837×298=？",
        "answer": 5.396941722069515
    },
    {
        "question": "2817805÷12174=？",
        "answer": 2.364477638001413
    },
    {
        "question": "8771794÷839=？",
        "answer": 4.0193264631670065
    },
    {
        "question": "3×183567700=？",
        "answer": 8.740917521204553
    },
    {
        "question": "30×132998=？",
        "answer": 6.600966364893556
    },
    {
        "question": "425508÷815=？",
        "answer": 2.717750120952532
    },
    {
        "question": "1×63596328=？",
        "answer": 7.803432040563888
    },
    {
        "question": "161×3519=？",
        "answer": 5.7532451428670415
    },
    {
        "question": "424847494÷309340693=？",
        "answer": 0.13779600675092915
    },
    {
        "question": "321734÷3722=？",
        "answer": 1.9367205896270867
    },
    {
        "question": "14752928÷1923=？",
        "answer": 3.8848989386551334
    },
    {
        "question": "158×20573=？",
        "answer": 6.511954713041292
    },
    {
        "question": "108216÷2043=？",
        "answer": 1.724023110385729
    },
    {
        "question": "124×1232300=？",
        "answer": 8.184138133643334
    },
    {
        "question": "194715×3960=？",
        "answer": 8.88709459489958
    },
    {
        "question": "18282681÷572031=？",
        "answer": 1.5046203165736252
    },
    {
        "question": "173799×616=？",
        "answer": 8.029627985452382
    },
    {
        "question": "7900×4588=？",
        "answer": 7.5592505005196715
    },
    {
        "question": "49913002÷7201529=？",
        "answer": 0.8407889772423183
    },
    {
        "question": "44118÷503=？",
        "answer": 1.9430478312994566
    },
    {
        "question": "628966115÷2572=？",
        "answer": 5.388356284587489
    },
    {
        "question": "181800÷4105=？",
        "answer": 1.646280717430489
    },
    {
        "question": "595813727÷393=？",
        "answer": 6.180717954364085
    },
    {
        "question": "3×407204=？",
        "answer": 6.086933290181458
    },
    {
        "question": "1×81051=？",
        "answer": 4.908758377504124
    },
    {
        "question": "118193×265=？",
        "answer": 7.495837630081066
    },
    {
        "question": "862×14140=？",
        "answer": 7.085956675285593
    },
    {
        "question": "231561÷191739=？",
        "answer": 0.08195495839498083
    },
    {
        "question": "187281710÷2244=？",
        "answer": 4.921472513504773
    },
    {
        "question": "652609÷470175=？",
        "answer": 0.14239352553070578
    },
    {
        "question": "1893÷567=？",
        "answer": 0.5235675550708901
    },
    {
        "question": "29×3146=？",
        "answer": 4.960156716186225
    },
    {
        "question": "3×19235461=？",
        "answer": 7.761223853855193
    },
    {
        "question": "8380×34981=？",
        "answer": 8.467076239103816
    },
    {
        "question": "1×40804834=？",
        "answer": 7.610711615422422
    },
    {
        "question": "12662×50706=？",
        "answer": 8.807561661274532
    },
    {
        "question": "8×894=？",
        "answer": 3.854427505787861
    },
    {
        "question": "333×2077=？",
        "answer": 5.839880730041419
    },
    {
        "question": "35803004÷31138999=？",
        "answer": 0.06061481948584273
    },
    {
        "question": "42×5545898=？",
        "answer": 8.367221168181302
    },
    {
        "question": "3668177÷39090=？",
        "answer": 1.9723846130184806
    },
    {
        "question": "968×33629=？",
        "answer": 7.512589310530285
    },
    {
        "question": "1855×415614=？",
        "answer": 8.887034082336543
    },
    {
        "question": "226446÷19085=？",
        "answer": 1.0742724893129245
    },
    {
        "question": "213×366303=？",
        "answer": 7.892220078964081
    },
    {
        "question": "1389934÷3966=？",
        "answer": 2.54464146871839
    },
    {
        "question": "32011÷279=？",
        "answer": 2.0596950381213412
    },
    {
        "question": "2×11798=？",
        "answer": 4.37283838749711
    },
    {
        "question": "6801×3069=？",
        "answer": 7.319569663278003
    },
    {
        "question": "162458812÷102376448=？",
        "answer": 0.20054321565811772
    },
    {
        "question": "2359×10881=？",
        "answer": 7.409396751185692
    },
    {
        "question": "369066÷18510=？",
        "answer": 1.2996976191479301
    },
    {
        "question": "91×114516=？",
        "answer": 7.017907562195744
    },
    {
        "question": "1×5123=？",
        "answer": 3.709524355876341
    },
    {
        "question": "34824578÷4741=？",
        "answer": 3.8660159070812283
    },
    {
        "question": "11262581÷3099=？",
        "answer": 3.5604163511863742
    },
    {
        "question": "51165×4949=？",
        "answer": 8.403490432274234
    },
    {
        "question": "523047432÷309=？",
        "answer": 6.228582594761402
    },
    {
        "question": "3457÷316=？",
        "answer": 1.039012296924003
    },
    {
        "question": "12×1980112=？",
        "answer": 7.375871001766893
    },
    {
        "question": "5596×3010=？",
        "answer": 7.226444201413633
    },
    {
        "question": "2702896÷22133=？",
        "answer": 2.086789051544115
    },
    {
        "question": "1×2775=？",
        "answer": 3.443262987458695
    },
    {
        "question": "1760094÷469480=？",
        "answer": 0.5739187665575606
    },
    {
        "question": "29007×549=？",
        "answer": 7.202075159401751
    },
    {
        "question": "193×364=？",
        "answer": 4.846658692656829
    },
    {
        "question": "608460÷78369=？",
        "answer": 0.8900877279581102
    },
    {
        "question": "4895718÷1192967=？",
        "answer": 0.6131879635774026
    },
    {
        "question": "1005333÷12475=？",
        "answer": 1.9062693841857785
    },
    {
        "question": "7209928÷10595=？",
        "answer": 2.8328299667296437
    },
    {
        "question": "18×21908=？",
        "answer": 5.595875237360054
    },
    {
        "question": "103×9759=？",
        "answer": 6.002242542706688
    },
    {
        "question": "84×14144=？",
        "answer": 6.07485153373088
    },
    {
        "question": "122141843÷367505=？",
        "answer": 2.5216012166363995
    },
    {
        "question": "138×8814=？",
        "answer": 6.085052132575137
    },
    {
        "question": "3×922=？",
        "answer": 3.441852175773292
    },
    {
        "question": "700×559=？",
        "answer": 5.59250984790068
    },
    {
        "question": "82326÷403=？",
        "answer": 2.3102319685765043
    },
    {
        "question": "29×344984=？",
        "answer": 7.00019695131181
    },
    {
        "question": "2×96912=？",
        "answer": 5.2874075519832076
    },
    {
        "question": "1036934÷899164=？",
        "answer": 0.06191220413823939
    },
    {
        "question": "4132237÷3168=？",
        "answer": 3.115400049136443
    },
    {
        "question": "110686÷10166=？",
        "answer": 1.036942587713941
    },
    {
        "question": "7029008÷121839=？",
        "answer": 1.7611077117573126
    },
    {
        "question": "74397462÷264=？",
        "answer": 5.449954193377717
    },
    {
        "question": "609928910÷2158677=？",
        "answer": 2.4510915546718506
    },
    {
        "question": "36493÷5324=？",
        "answer": 0.8359715203134719
    },
    {
        "question": "67147690÷67649=？",
        "answer": 2.9967696955989505
    },
    {
        "question": "42×1072=？",
        "answer": 4.653444075754652
    },
    {
        "question": "25989÷3191=？",
        "answer": 0.9108627649251572
    },
    {
        "question": "9395÷2608=？",
        "answer": 0.5565891973766618
    },
    {
        "question": "1466676÷250318=？",
        "answer": 0.767842105239979
    },
    {
        "question": "685816×200=？",
        "answer": 8.13723760859609
    },
    {
        "question": "14×112400=？",
        "answer": 6.1968943469112805
    },
    {
        "question": "32834517÷1448592=？",
        "answer": 1.355384549707624
    },
    {
        "question": "8720÷7299=？",
        "answer": 0.07725312128208633
    },
    {
        "question": "99921÷15407=？",
        "answer": 0.8119386891986815
    },
    {
        "question": "136×3609=？",
        "answer": 5.690925790429724
    },
    {
        "question": "763×24409=？",
        "answer": 7.270074525345114
    },
    {
        "question": "161376×2328=？",
        "answer": 8.57482192245689
    },
    {
        "question": "42×1584754=？",
        "answer": 7.823211147024741
    },
    {
        "question": "30×803=？",
        "answer": 4.381836799998343
    },
    {
        "question": "157971321÷4185164=？",
        "answer": 1.5768657689101155
    },
    {
        "question": "777×48731=？",
        "answer": 7.578226342351834
    },
    {
        "question": "461202048÷18095981=？",
        "answer": 1.406309095550877
    },
    {
        "question": "4054×1175=？",
        "answer": 6.677921610964745
    },
    {
        "question": "7393483÷1773=？",
        "answer": 3.6201403430276686
    },
    {
        "question": "5×747365=？",
        "answer": 6.572502759793998
    },
    {
        "question": "1570544÷6189=？",
        "answer": 2.4044296253066095
    },
    {
        "question": "42585×869=？",
        "answer": 7.568276428030205
    },
    {
        "question": "18×2839070=？",
        "answer": 7.708448605709104
    },
    {
        "question": "6×15070221=？",
        "answer": 7.956270871535485
    },
    {
        "question": "383175÷244590=？",
        "answer": 0.19495846903027053
    },
    {
        "question": "975081÷353=？",
        "answer": 3.4412659886613617
    },
    {
        "question": "580227÷3069=？",
        "answer": 2.276601045752476
    },
    {
        "question": "2×5199=？",
        "answer": 4.01694981309756
    },
    {
        "question": "4558÷385=？",
        "answer": 1.073313591335856
    },
    {
        "question": "5×14481197=？",
        "answer": 7.8597744659905935
    },
    {
        "question": "163×5538=？",
        "answer": 5.9555405558135135
    },
    {
        "question": "107×508369=？",
        "answer": 7.735562837388941
    },
    {
        "question": "3×16171095=？",
        "answer": 7.685860683182445
    },
    {
        "question": "1×6375715=？",
        "answer": 6.804528895481265
    },
    {
        "question": "15×697009=？",
        "answer": 7.019329644937194
    },
    {
        "question": "22066271÷489=？",
        "answer": 4.654420088403491
    },
    {
        "question": "699188÷6824=？",
        "answer": 2.0105549478362956
    },
    {
        "question": "30×5396=？",
        "answer": 5.209193195719529
    },
    {
        "question": "526188509÷8838304=？",
        "answer": 1.7747724242887082
    },
    {
        "question": "133667×2330=？",
        "answer": 8.493380121953821
    },
    {
        "question": "11×9477=？",
        "answer": 5.018063565783036
    },
    {
        "question": "265533÷8693=？",
        "answer": 1.4849488225429879
    },
    {
        "question": "2035977÷35535=？",
        "answer": 1.7581165477814102
    },
    {
        "question": "8742÷509=？",
        "answer": 1.234893019816875
    },
    {
        "question": "2×31330=？",
        "answer": 4.7969903905456865
    },
    {
        "question": "1×403=？",
        "answer": 2.6053050461411096
    },
    {
        "question": "33×11986=？",
        "answer": 5.597188213238353
    },
    {
        "question": "6534458÷1337=？",
        "answer": 3.689078163633764
    },
    {
        "question": "5×8935=？",
        "answer": 4.650064561177682
    },
    {
        "question": "358×623=？",
        "answer": 5.348371073303044
    },
    {
        "question": "412643÷16067=？",
        "answer": 1.409639688531412
    },
    {
        "question": "38×1109=？",
        "answer": 4.62471514276597
    },
    {
        "question": "2734÷255=？",
        "answer": 1.0302583297978483
    },
    {
        "question": "25873283÷281964=？",
        "answer": 1.9626578758864612
    },
    {
        "question": "166370×345=？",
        "answer": 7.758894111684995
    },
    {
        "question": "160154721÷2740742=？",
        "answer": 1.766671590097802
    },
    {
        "question": "25×2763=？",
        "answer": 4.839320893588549
    },
    {
        "question": "231687855÷1104=？",
        "answer": 5.321934195421723
    },
    {
        "question": "730669÷1689=？",
        "answer": 2.6360910324087587
    },
    {
        "question": "6×804594=？",
        "answer": 6.68372804002007
    },
    {
        "question": "74386569÷876=？",
        "answer": 4.92899042163923
    },
    {
        "question": "4814÷4086=？",
        "answer": 0.07120772364258239
    },
    {
        "question": "32458979÷6474=？",
        "answer": 3.700162159867905
    },
    {
        "question": "99234247÷41512=？",
        "answer": 3.3784879208820953
    },
    {
        "question": "1513743÷713=？",
        "answer": 3.3269626179964176
    },
    {
        "question": "144×663=？",
        "answer": 4.979876020500023
    },
    {
        "question": "29751÷2351=？",
        "answer": 1.1022489388281331
    },
    {
        "question": "3299×214=？",
        "answer": 5.8487960888945345
    },
    {
        "question": "379×10531=？",
        "answer": 6.601108822735842
    },
    {
        "question": "798440÷1522=？",
        "answer": 2.719827633540309
    },
    {
        "question": "190065÷1766=？",
        "answer": 2.0319114507310467
    },
    {
        "question": "596333÷970=？",
        "answer": 2.788717108823163
    },
    {
        "question": "457342÷320=？",
        "answer": 3.1550911083235404
    },
    {
        "question": "430405÷39417=？",
        "answer": 1.038193740516349
    },
    {
        "question": "1478×2348=？",
        "answer": 6.540372526634384
    },
    {
        "question": "1×43315995=？",
        "answer": 7.636648294910629
    },
    {
        "question": "2×1020613=？",
        "answer": 6.30989109149667
    },
    {
        "question": "219542÷50297=？",
        "answer": 0.6399755342282832
    },
    {
        "question": "90841×403=？",
        "answer": 7.563586952535257
    },
    {
        "question": "84706÷1178=？",
        "answer": 1.8567688834522544
    },
    {
        "question": "3579229÷1350=？",
        "answer": 3.4234557170575464
    },
    {
        "question": "694562÷176444=？",
        "answer": 0.5951041243432246
    },
    {
        "question": "103151421÷636021=？",
        "answer": 2.2100037598085076
    },
    {
        "question": "4396×102842=？",
        "answer": 8.655228197662746
    },
    {
        "question": "140591÷10588=？",
        "answer": 1.1231435873756785
    },
    {
        "question": "398×135661=？",
        "answer": 7.732338086136034
    },
    {
        "question": "4×131228506=？",
        "answer": 8.720088175862928
    },
    {
        "question": "201778171÷1157193=？",
        "answer": 2.2414683832088294
    },
    {
        "question": "100×4621852=？",
        "answer": 8.66481603447662
    },
    {
        "question": "17770869÷141086=？",
        "answer": 2.100224744695406
    },
    {
        "question": "184658378÷34512=？",
        "answer": 3.7283988887323343
    },
    {
        "question": "5152×3720=？",
        "answer": 7.282518794233654
    },
    {
        "question": "23777÷13822=？",
        "answer": 0.23558616915030361
    },
    {
        "question": "210×18017=？",
        "answer": 6.577901773279801
    },
    {
        "question": "54717×12778=？",
        "answer": 8.844585161850981
    },
    {
        "question": "32681×6920=？",
        "answer": 8.354401431418648
    },
    {
        "question": "25861228÷405=？",
        "answer": 4.805194119950031
    },
    {
        "question": "1332155÷964068=？",
        "answer": 0.14044709146201867
    },
    {
        "question": "303277×1346=？",
        "answer": 8.610884535309602
    },
    {
        "question": "1359091÷220179=？",
        "answer": 0.7904726416212549
    },
    {
        "question": "4178×119918=？",
        "answer": 8.699852812354035
    },
    {
        "question": "4897582÷776491=？",
        "answer": 0.7998452897428374
    },
    {
        "question": "2537×275426=？",
        "answer": 8.844325402138827
    },
    {
        "question": "13×2007260=？",
        "answer": 7.416546982518263
    },
    {
        "question": "1012×364736=？",
        "answer": 8.567159143461499
    },
    {
        "question": "370743665÷6009=？",
        "answer": 4.790271534840119
    },
    {
        "question": "85×59340=？",
        "answer": 6.702766467695116
    },
    {
        "question": "8561×396=？",
        "answer": 6.530219682976055
    },
    {
        "question": "2760570÷7376=？",
        "answer": 2.5731778560110206
    },
    {
        "question": "1869×293241=？",
        "answer": 8.73883399323096
    },
    {
        "question": "22847×4933=？",
        "answer": 8.051940297155465
    },
    {
        "question": "5843671÷5369045=？",
        "answer": 0.03678871310783529
    },
    {
        "question": "124×75374=？",
        "answer": 6.9706432484880505
    },
    {
        "question": "2×35512=？",
        "answer": 4.851405127681291
    },
    {
        "question": "192017÷7138=？",
        "answer": 1.429763136538907
    },
    {
        "question": "58375998÷261=？",
        "answer": 5.349593811027116
    },
    {
        "question": "72×1076347=？",
        "answer": 7.889284801117344
    },
    {
        "question": "199×2450=？",
        "answer": 5.688019160774239
    },
    {
        "question": "1221×584=？",
        "answer": 5.853128511057282
    },
    {
        "question": "34×3526=？",
        "answer": 5.078761225005558
    },
    {
        "question": "16×4899=？",
        "answer": 4.894227422112255
    },
    {
        "question": "3×149359=？",
        "answer": 5.651352651948206
    },
    {
        "question": "5×11541=？",
        "answer": 4.761213445362497
    },
    {
        "question": "933×274=？",
        "answer": 5.407632206566888
    },
    {
        "question": "905×443=？",
        "answer": 5.603052305428273
    },
    {
        "question": "4433×210884=？",
        "answer": 8.97074136189085
    },
    {
        "question": "317898829÷13716570=？",
        "answer": 1.3650434039908401
    },
    {
        "question": "31124151÷5751=？",
        "answer": 3.7333541460468234
    },
    {
        "question": "328168×360=？",
        "answer": 8.07239873104629
    },
    {
        "question": "53364÷21872=？",
        "answer": 0.3873598782728124
    },
    {
        "question": "344778112÷1331656=？",
        "answer": 2.4131476369307814
    },
    {
        "question": "425×833=？",
        "answer": 5.5490339314570996
    },
    {
        "question": "11×3125=？",
        "answer": 4.536242706838319
    },
    {
        "question": "653×2223=？",
        "answer": 6.161852643974065
    },
    {
        "question": "98073657÷82626347=？",
        "answer": 0.07443381715215516
    },
    {
        "question": "1×774=？",
        "answer": 2.8887409606828927
    },
    {
        "question": "1×2338=？",
        "answer": 3.3688445068258215
    },
    {
        "question": "46857682÷36690=？",
        "answer": 3.1062330889474055
    },
    {
        "question": "5350×1675=？",
        "answer": 6.952368593394093
    },
    {
        "question": "162761488÷20777635=？",
        "answer": 0.893955538847668
    },
    {
        "question": "5×10459588=？",
        "answer": 7.718484582476215
    },
    {
        "question": "35068225÷795=？",
        "answer": 4.644546655696257
    },
    {
        "question": "10×379=？",
        "answer": 3.578639209968072
    },
    {
        "question": "417369661÷232614=？",
        "answer": 3.2538850271669184
    },
    {
        "question": "17×547=？",
        "answer": 3.9684362477117046
    },
    {
        "question": "2×709=？",
        "answer": 3.151676230847048
    },
    {
        "question": "18×2731498=？",
        "answer": 7.691673391964055
    },
    {
        "question": "4740423÷187111=？",
        "answer": 1.4037177767746731
    },
    {
        "question": "2121560÷304901=？",
        "answer": 0.8424964698452578
    },
    {
        "question": "52325675÷12152777=？",
        "answer": 0.6340393106394572
    },
    {
        "question": "576863÷128061=？",
        "answer": 0.6536557953871015
    },
    {
        "question": "9×1379=？",
        "answer": 4.093806775615175
    },
    {
        "question": "226×10498=？",
        "answer": 6.375215007579523
    },
    {
        "question": "10×201=？",
        "answer": 3.303196057420489
    },
    {
        "question": "209542÷216=？",
        "answer": 2.9868173336219996
    },
    {
        "question": "13172660÷51888=？",
        "answer": 2.4046065510493575
    },
    {
        "question": "1815298÷264190=？",
        "answer": 0.8370315542975478
    },
    {
        "question": "2387×215286=？",
        "answer": 8.71086820767633
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1765695=？",
        "answer": 6.246915687204944
    },
    {
        "question": "145727458÷100564753=？",
        "answer": 0.16109559808492138
    },
    {
        "question": "3519465÷7873=？",
        "answer": 2.6503363991932987
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1042560=？",
        "answer": 6.018101058292396
    },
    {
        "question": "12×39250=？",
        "answer": 5.673020907128897
    },
    {
        "question": "18541348÷444185=？",
        "answer": 1.6205774167357108
    },
    {
        "question": "8560196÷256=？",
        "answer": 4.524243743377447
    },
    {
        "question": "63956897÷20082674=？",
        "answer": 0.503065846438607
    },
    {
        "question": "84786÷6297=？",
        "answer": 1.1291904534747121
    },
    {
        "question": "1332396×611=？",
        "answer": 8.910674530463634
    },
    {
        "question": "1×7222=？",
        "answer": 3.858657484090808
    },
    {
        "question": "299×331=？",
        "answer": 4.995499182100148
    },
    {
        "question": "59680÷307=？",
        "answer": 2.288690438987426
    },
    {
        "question": "556140315÷9953=？",
        "answer": 4.747230374459067
    },
    {
        "question": "6053589÷430=？",
        "answer": 4.148544476222457
    },
    {
        "question": "575×449674=？",
        "answer": 8.412565622222075
    },
    {
        "question": "28604602÷3728740=？",
        "answer": 0.8848738077877307
    },
    {
        "question": "13161÷6927=？",
        "answer": 0.2787437014877688
    },
    {
        "question": "468×293326=？",
        "answer": 8.137596413006863
    },
    {
        "question": "2880×1266=？",
        "answer": 6.5618261934405675
    },
    {
        "question": "107×813840=？",
        "answer": 7.939922809174902
    },
    {
        "question": "184×931134=？",
        "answer": 8.233830008043407
    },
    {
        "question": "4864×1628=？",
        "answer": 6.898647966817861
    },
    {
        "question": "529552÷14473=？",
        "answer": 1.5633500505025648
    },
    {
        "question": "21652÷268=？",
        "answer": 1.907363224390235
    },
    {
        "question": "45312687÷8622=？",
        "answer": 3.7206117976819013
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1920482=？",
        "answer": 6.283410241031365
    },
    {
        "question": "1697411÷1422=？",
        "answer": 3.0768874158829784
    },
    {
        "question": "14679861÷10191298=？",
        "answer": 0.15849244255096695
    },
    {
        "question": "586494086÷490243503=？",
        "answer": 0.07785179035304578
    },
    {
        "question": "6×416=？",
        "answer": 3.397244581010386
    },
    {
        "question": "268789939÷45351243=？",
        "answer": 0.7728238139042392
    },
    {
        "question": "555303÷7790=？",
        "answer": 1.8529925620631504
    },
    {
        "question": "5×1029=？",
        "answer": 3.7113853790984517
    },
    {
        "question": "2×9758296=？",
        "answer": 7.2904039831660885
    },
    {
        "question": "42352504÷7832=？",
        "answer": 3.733006413350624
    },
    {
        "question": "212×1325=？",
        "answer": 5.448551739201578
    },
    {
        "question": "161812609÷17570=？",
        "answer": 3.964240598832637
    },
    {
        "question": "242455÷115776=？",
        "answer": 0.32101260388756553
    },
    {
        "question": "376101×532=？",
        "answer": 8.301216120447318
    },
    {
        "question": "51379÷18350=？",
        "answer": 0.44714957866202737
    },
    {
        "question": "80×32074=？",
        "answer": 6.409243111859579
    },
    {
        "question": "1×408823271=？",
        "answer": 8.611535608700148
    },
    {
        "question": "15717718÷295350=？",
        "answer": 1.7260525174034527
    },
    {
        "question": "1125323÷292=？",
        "answer": 3.585894343873584
    },
    {
        "question": "82×2504841=？",
        "answer": 8.31259401571504
    },
    {
        "question": "687445×1181=？",
        "answer": 8.909487855167447
    },
    {
        "question": "5170558÷11759=？",
        "answer": 2.643167023760618
    },
    {
        "question": "8429612÷1075=？",
        "answer": 3.89439912103303
    },
    {
        "question": "2318×29572=？",
        "answer": 7.835994129153057
    },
    {
        "question": "68640889÷2280607=？",
        "answer": 1.4785324466322425
    },
    {
        "question": "137502×2036=？",
        "answer": 8.447086788795707
    },
    {
        "question": "1×15885635=？",
        "answer": 7.2010045796594895
    },
    {
        "question": "6×71574=？",
        "answer": 5.632906539350898
    },
    {
        "question": "614×13917=？",
        "answer": 6.93171399837959
    },
    {
        "question": "7735129÷18606=？",
        "answer": 2.6188145442742745
    },
    {
        "question": "314062÷107297=？",
        "answer": 0.4664278126623343
    },
    {
        "question": "577812133÷11532457=？",
        "answer": 1.6998648130253684
    },
    {
        "question": "958×7792=？",
        "answer": 6.8730144529491035
    },
    {
        "question": "19467455÷201319=？",
        "answer": 1.985424414990755
    },
    {
        "question": "8373÷334=？",
        "answer": 1.399134624396729
    },
    {
        "question": "275×5136=？",
        "answer": 6.149957708891059
    },
    {
        "question": "7×57470=？",
        "answer": 5.6045392371479545
    },
    {
        "question": "76216÷447=？",
        "answer": 2.2317386290775985
    },
    {
        "question": "14269205÷749=？",
        "answer": 4.279917959638655
    },
    {
        "question": "2003×10245=？",
        "answer": 7.31219291203079
    },
    {
        "question": "129421÷1077=？",
        "answer": 2.079789047873604
    },
    {
        "question": "947855557÷515=？",
        "answer": 6.264934931527512
    },
    {
        "question": "2×848=？",
        "answer": 3.229425847920695
    },
    {
        "question": "20066×1257=？",
        "answer": 7.401796085596337
    },
    {
        "question": "6×445069=？",
        "answer": 6.426578596187631
    },
    {
        "question": "161932÷53700=？",
        "answer": 0.479358394123423
    },
    {
        "question": "1×83239378=？",
        "answer": 7.920328826318818
    },
    {
        "question": "14858508÷2101615=？",
        "answer": 0.8494220429240562
    },
    {
        "question": "9577302÷4639=？",
        "answer": 3.314818809676811
    },
    {
        "question": "14×245=？",
        "answer": 3.5352941200427703
    },
    {
        "question": "43902583÷639619=？",
        "answer": 1.8365687165626126
    },
    {
        "question": "15×2571=？",
        "answer": 4.586193335698542
    },
    {
        "question": "4914÷216=？",
        "answer": 1.3569814009931311
    },
    {
        "question": "77×1316462=？",
        "answer": 8.005899052778265
    },
    {
        "question": "274720÷8174=？",
        "answer": 1.5264556444412667
    },
    {
        "question": "547241012÷654=？",
        "answer": 5.922600889031538
    },
    {
        "question": "19×510311=？",
        "answer": 6.986588530813206
    },
    {
        "question": "2444×285488=？",
        "answer": 8.843689059709966
    },
    {
        "question": "41319×12744=？",
        "answer": 8.72145556499842
    },
    {
        "question": "361288532÷2258=？",
        "answer": 5.204130238847153
    },
    {
        "question": "30671060÷6400=？",
        "answer": 3.680548811590896
    },
    {
        "question": "264062÷1845=？",
        "answer": 2.1557095378011817
    },
    {
        "question": "12637555÷1513=？",
        "answer": 3.921824130676328
    },
    {
        "question": "28×253=？",
        "answer": 3.850278552518037
    },
    {
        "question": "29179÷4103=？",
        "answer": 0.8519688870427573
    },
    {
        "question": "4×3695=？",
        "answer": 4.169674434058807
    },
    {
        "question": "46×2941=？",
        "answer": 5.1312528561886435
    },
    {
        "question": "279828÷3847=？",
        "answer": 1.861768982165959
    },
    {
        "question": "4223×229=？",
        "answer": 5.985456563764796
    },
    {
        "question": "1×321788=？",
        "answer": 5.507569844514549
    },
    {
        "question": "373865143÷2775454=？",
        "answer": 2.12938094217404
    },
    {
        "question": "136056÷19332=？",
        "answer": 0.8474409122357333
    },
    {
        "question": "629×112014=？",
        "answer": 7.847922951533046
    },
    {
        "question": "1169806÷5102=？",
        "answer": 2.3603733902797837
    },
    {
        "question": "784×402253=？",
        "answer": 8.498815354432727
    },
    {
        "question": "50×420060=？",
        "answer": 7.322281332371608
    },
    {
        "question": "2682×325=？",
        "answer": 5.940342134494455
    },
    {
        "question": "6×4267294=？",
        "answer": 7.408303815478522
    },
    {
        "question": "10×7896=？",
        "answer": 4.89740713966158
    },
    {
        "question": "316558×1242=？",
        "answer": 8.594574889253108
    },
    {
        "question": "12254×1372=？",
        "answer": 7.225631987366668
    },
    {
        "question": "9×997059=？",
        "answer": 6.952963367466425
    },
    {
        "question": "179306198÷2789027=？",
        "answer": 1.8081425832892017
    },
    {
        "question": "4×151303=？",
        "answer": 5.7819075305245065
    },
    {
        "question": "1×8866=？",
        "answer": 3.9477277269633158
    },
    {
        "question": "1304887×316=？",
        "answer": 8.615259987088647
    },
    {
        "question": "6797580÷2053=？",
        "answer": 3.519965378084842
    },
    {
        "question": "66704571÷2544=？",
        "answer": 4.418638488440287
    },
    {
        "question": "31×16193837=？",
        "answer": 8.700711457380287
    },
    {
        "question": "4888÷2528=？",
        "answer": 0.2863541276241504
    },
    {
        "question": "677468997÷494091=？",
        "answer": 3.137082482220534
    },
    {
        "question": "6×485340=？",
        "answer": 6.46419733618357
    },
    {
        "question": "1×5642917=？",
        "answer": 6.751503662407718
    },
    {
        "question": "366776322÷81120=？",
        "answer": 3.6552733491399585
    },
    {
        "question": "171×378622=？",
        "answer": 7.811201955627467
    },
    {
        "question": "4502×644=？",
        "answer": 6.462291358024313
    },
    {
        "question": "25×358=？",
        "answer": 3.951823035315912
    },
    {
        "question": "861174÷4629=？",
        "answer": 2.269603728632709
    },
    {
        "question": "1814×519466=？",
        "answer": 8.974194410179148
    },
    {
        "question": "867754÷189837=？",
        "answer": 0.6600157621781473
    },
    {
        "question": "484980÷45225=？",
        "answer": 1.0303452536503432
    },
    {
        "question": "30208÷382=？",
        "answer": 1.8980586097062662
    },
    {
        "question": "65093392÷12359570=？",
        "answer": 0.7215335415663174
    },
    {
        "question": "233415×1396=？",
        "answer": 8.513014180056071
    },
    {
        "question": "17265973÷10825=？",
        "answer": 3.2027631524138513
    },
    {
        "question": "20061÷366=？",
        "answer": 1.7388714925251518
    },
    {
        "question": "513907458÷3467=？",
        "answer": 5.1709310787038945
    },
    {
        "question": "14587÷2538=？",
        "answer": 0.7594743651961975
    },
    {
        "question": "1475019×393=？",
        "answer": 8.763190164955379
    },
    {
        "question": "42891×779=？",
        "answer": 7.523903629568413
    },
    {
        "question": "255×21932=？",
        "answer": 6.747618417645398
    },
    {
        "question": "22×2475824=？",
        "answer": 7.736142449382902
    },
    {
        "question": "1533×5829=？",
        "answer": 6.9511362101738206
    },
    {
        "question": "9092330÷4809251=？",
        "answer": 0.2765977458019761
    },
    {
        "question": "139934564÷40227=？",
        "answer": 3.5414073534877546
    },
    {
        "question": "91979157÷2946=？",
        "answer": 4.494456682388659
    },
    {
        "question": "7550222÷50312=？",
        "answer": 2.176288139704398
    },
    {
        "question": "134543÷529=？",
        "answer": 2.405405435189403
    },
    {
        "question": "171×326=？",
        "answer": 4.7462137104600925
    },
    {
        "question": "2252826÷17989=？",
        "answer": 2.0977206279178526
    },
    {
        "question": "33133÷286=？",
        "answer": 2.0638947273668524
    },
    {
        "question": "3×571=？",
        "answer": 3.2337573629655103
    },
    {
        "question": "2397248÷385=？",
        "answer": 3.7942522354638983
    },
    {
        "question": "676251564÷7544764=？",
        "answer": 1.9524626229246145
    },
    {
        "question": "122218444÷3154=？",
        "answer": 4.588275061291632
    },
    {
        "question": "3168689×300=？",
        "answer": 8.978000870933677
    },
    {
        "question": "103×1659=？",
        "answer": 5.2326836107295325
    },
    {
        "question": "441×12352=？",
        "answer": 6.7361758724595
    },
    {
        "question": "1×97498018=？",
        "answer": 7.988995787181488
    },
    {
        "question": "210144320÷2155=？",
        "answer": 4.9890703814388315
    },
    {
        "question": "325×646=？",
        "answer": 5.322115878973959
    },
    {
        "question": "1332242÷464376=？",
        "answer": 0.4577133546920284
    },
    {
        "question": "7438421÷23497=？",
        "answer": 2.500468338048316
    },
    {
        "question": "200×13071=？",
        "answer": 6.417338810319397
    },
    {
        "question": "14×737502=？",
        "answer": 7.0138912380745895
    },
    {
        "question": "16×3669090=？",
        "answer": 7.768678347457385
    },
    {
        "question": "207277÷186179=？",
        "answer": 0.046620421009256625
    },
    {
        "question": "3906662÷65508=？",
        "answer": 1.7755114978267093
    },
    {
        "question": "39346988÷320=？",
        "answer": 5.089761514536668
    },
    {
        "question": "7723043÷564575=？",
        "answer": 1.1360668096888875
    },
    {
        "question": "57×219=？",
        "answer": 4.09631897051261
    },
    {
        "question": "115034×1259=？",
        "answer": 8.160851951592022
    },
    {
        "question": "199342×1194=？",
        "answer": 8.376603138020403
    },
    {
        "question": "136344110÷46929386=？",
        "answer": 0.4631915092064955
    },
    {
        "question": "1×310911263=？",
        "answer": 8.49263645498031
    },
    {
        "question": "58947867÷4088=？",
        "answer": 4.1589572078534
    },
    {
        "question": "12×291=？",
        "answer": 3.543074235033532
    },
    {
        "question": "7×3998=？",
        "answer": 4.446940829796355
    },
    {
        "question": "71×579=？",
        "answer": 4.613936912446511
    },
    {
        "question": "20×51380=？",
        "answer": 6.011824095594308
    },
    {
        "question": "8202893÷1631=？",
        "answer": 3.701513085532926
    },
    {
        "question": "236130×3888=？",
        "answer": 8.962877423370127
    },
    {
        "question": "56310×380=？",
        "answer": 7.330369123957819
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1680421=？",
        "answer": 6.22541810022083
    },
    {
        "question": "33758187÷157743=？",
        "answer": 2.3304290184805083
    },
    {
        "question": "52×1980=？",
        "answer": 5.01266853389633
    },
    {
        "question": "1695×6798=？",
        "answer": 7.061550862786142
    },
    {
        "question": "189791680÷311=？",
        "answer": 5.785516781080832
    },
    {
        "question": "70×15410=？",
        "answer": 6.032900678732676
    },
    {
        "question": "163254626÷1780=？",
        "answer": 4.96244549402602
    },
    {
        "question": "6476÷401=？",
        "answer": 1.2081624674611537
    },
    {
        "question": "11×631=？",
        "answer": 3.8414220444023592
    },
    {
        "question": "1279×6725=？",
        "answer": 6.934562833153099
    },
    {
        "question": "9151586÷593227=？",
        "answer": 1.1882754560659659
    },
    {
        "question": "11×151953=？",
        "answer": 6.223101963911694
    },
    {
        "question": "1243140×420=？",
        "answer": 8.717769331190535
    },
    {
        "question": "4×3543068=？",
        "answer": 7.151439478897203
    },
    {
        "question": "105×6889=？",
        "answer": 5.859345483822086
    },
    {
        "question": "7189496÷348603=？",
        "answer": 1.3143673261883977
    },
    {
        "question": "24×17824401=？",
        "answer": 8.631226185746549
    },
    {
        "question": "3369831÷807=？",
        "answer": 3.620734586443677
    },
    {
        "question": "1333×28745=？",
        "answer": 7.583392462395853
    },
    {
        "question": "62035310÷6515=？",
        "answer": 3.9787245367571655
    },
    {
        "question": "87141422÷1100=？",
        "answer": 4.898831957447643
    },
    {
        "question": "7×2423=？",
        "answer": 4.229451454151763
    },
    {
        "question": "18×803692=？",
        "answer": 7.160362150458492
    },
    {
        "question": "8428934÷305=？",
        "answer": 4.441472813902936
    },
    {
        "question": "162093423÷7976887=？",
        "answer": 1.3079319536375382
    },
    {
        "question": "4×162622=？",
        "answer": 5.813239289242182
    },
    {
        "question": "8×119017=？",
        "answer": 5.978698986022163
    },
    {
        "question": "22266÷10828=？",
        "answer": 0.3130939576339579
    },
    {
        "question": "26684×1375=？",
        "answer": 7.564553630146827
    },
    {
        "question": "5724740÷250=？",
        "answer": 4.359815758474488
    },
    {
        "question": "2991÷1987=？",
        "answer": 0.177618545921503
    },
    {
        "question": "127059×224=？",
        "answer": 7.454253451293181
    },
    {
        "question": "9642262÷242=？",
        "answer": 4.600363561997127
    },
    {
        "question": "22557642÷3779682=？",
        "answer": 0.7758384375098777
    },
    {
        "question": "237192142÷171380998=？",
        "answer": 0.14113762955432665
    },
    {
        "question": "817679÷2293=？",
        "answer": 2.5521787894190933
    },
    {
        "question": "2×15851202=？",
        "answer": 7.50109219610887
    },
    {
        "question": "109153207÷25799804=？",
        "answer": 0.6264200934586425
    },
    {
        "question": "174897×949=？",
        "answer": 8.220048572537074
    },
    {
        "question": "388145936÷2355=？",
        "answer": 5.217004131869728
    },
    {
        "question": "45×1100=？",
        "answer": 4.694605198933568
    },
    {
        "question": "910916148÷215=？",
        "answer": 6.627039941056343
    },
    {
        "question": "64685×9646=？",
        "answer": 8.795150840070729
    },
    {
        "question": "14260959÷4120591=？",
        "answer": 0.5391892216615277
    },
    {
        "question": "704797148÷298=？",
        "answer": 6.373847873935046
    },
    {
        "question": "438787÷85190=？",
        "answer": 0.7118651339493756
    },
    {
        "question": "168×1071=？",
        "answer": 5.255098752557719
    },
    {
        "question": "1×4192=？",
        "answer": 3.6224212739756703
    },
    {
        "question": "17885827÷1636868=？",
        "answer": 1.0384953672088413
    },
    {
        "question": "1×320593802=？",
        "answer": 8.505955121938218
    },
    {
        "question": "4×59966576=？",
        "answer": 8.379969243321343
    },
    {
        "question": "14623608÷1851=？",
        "answer": 3.8976481181079508
    },
    {
        "question": "3060966÷11030=？",
        "answer": 2.4432829932125535
    },
    {
        "question": "6×8653500=？",
        "answer": 7.715343048397467
    },
    {
        "question": "256464÷9302=？",
        "answer": 1.4404500763829955
    },
    {
        "question": "51149×3463=？",
        "answer": 8.248289638908934
    },
    {
        "question": "1511327÷3148=？",
        "answer": 2.6813237174428197
    },
    {
        "question": "162855÷49970=？",
        "answer": 0.5130917474409562
    },
    {
        "question": "1×219121500=？",
        "answer": 8.340684992226432
    },
    {
        "question": "26859919÷239=？",
        "answer": 5.0507067977082345
    },
    {
        "question": "189760×213=？",
        "answer": 7.6065842751229065
    },
    {
        "question": "9100773÷4570159=？",
        "answer": 0.29914697208911534
    },
    {
        "question": "9253167÷37756=？",
        "answer": 2.389304422912928
    },
    {
        "question": "373×1037188=？",
        "answer": 8.587566315258941
    },
    {
        "question": "264074×214=？",
        "answer": 7.7521394172203175
    },
    {
        "question": "2717329÷21642=？",
        "answer": 2.09884483100644
    },
    {
        "question": "61485157÷3611=？",
        "answer": 4.2311427979011444
    },
    {
        "question": "12036265÷394590=？",
        "answer": 1.4843456661121923
    },
    {
        "question": "228629÷46834=？",
        "answer": 0.6885700651852765
    },
    {
        "question": "535×191288=？",
        "answer": 8.010041508466475
    },
    {
        "question": "449÷346=？",
        "answer": 0.11317024221054654
    },
    {
        "question": "468÷220=？",
        "answer": 0.3278231722519178
    },
    {
        "question": "52×1379439=？",
        "answer": 7.855705843992492
    },
    {
        "question": "2039×81105=？",
        "answer": 8.218464854409445
    },
    {
        "question": "739083749÷81879717=？",
        "answer": 0.9555173201552276
    },
    {
        "question": "75×4701=？",
        "answer": 5.547251514579953
    },
    {
        "question": "275925×842=？",
        "answer": 8.366103142722476
    },
    {
        "question": "386325009÷6022747=？",
        "answer": 1.8071582034222227
    },
    {
        "question": "360531÷5376=？",
        "answer": 1.8264833531154034
    },
    {
        "question": "53135×17747=？",
        "answer": 8.974505634217966
    },
    {
        "question": "121×543=？",
        "answer": 4.817585199905297
    },
    {
        "question": "3500723÷8397=？",
        "answer": 2.62003359473122
    },
    {
        "question": "71425530÷6293=？",
        "answer": 4.054995739921526
    },
    {
        "question": "929×310530=？",
        "answer": 8.460119277298785
    },
    {
        "question": "20147×10251=？",
        "answer": 8.314976619953658
    },
    {
        "question": "70783940÷237=？",
        "answer": 5.4751863868129425
    },
    {
        "question": "9699÷493=？",
        "answer": 1.2938800400539885
    },
    {
        "question": "291178×2506=？",
        "answer": 8.863139625350168
    },
    {
        "question": "1361989÷3629=？",
        "answer": 2.5743866318442037
    },
    {
        "question": "1×43561=？",
        "answer": 4.639097840998727
    },
    {
        "question": "29124737÷895269=？",
        "answer": 1.512308465647636
    },
    {
        "question": "1236201÷881042=？",
        "answer": 0.14709247848748686
    },
    {
        "question": "3×24281=？",
        "answer": 4.862387823677194
    },
    {
        "question": "3×5380594=？",
        "answer": 7.207951477724742
    },
    {
        "question": "78221007÷963615=？",
        "answer": 1.9094198508904248
    },
    {
        "question": "19497315÷9086=？",
        "answer": 3.3316020757571696
    },
    {
        "question": "183×2183213=？",
        "answer": 8.601547198418038
    },
    {
        "question": "654216÷142411=？",
        "answer": 0.6621776253183472
    },
    {
        "question": "847224055÷159525=？",
        "answer": 3.7251695247840506
    },
    {
        "question": "360×7217=？",
        "answer": 6.4146592060650605
    },
    {
        "question": "2×4924=？",
        "answer": 3.99334803992326
    },
    {
        "question": "582×1514935=？",
        "answer": 8.945316983991898
    },
    {
        "question": "1×2700337=？",
        "answer": 6.431417967161723
    },
    {
        "question": "4×174161859=？",
        "answer": 8.843013043035857
    },
    {
        "question": "226461÷2594=？",
        "answer": 1.941023448979793
    },
    {
        "question": "97160923÷2323=？",
        "answer": 4.621442422021441
    },
    {
        "question": "197762814÷25370=？",
        "answer": 3.8918241658794326
    },
    {
        "question": "61515186÷111111=？",
        "answer": 2.743225285230917
    },
    {
        "question": "125×5342=？",
        "answer": 5.8246138966934105
    },
    {
        "question": "1×5465=？",
        "answer": 3.7375901662857216
    },
    {
        "question": "102×586558=？",
        "answer": 7.776911134222906
    },
    {
        "question": "659847÷3681=？",
        "answer": 2.253477429066809
    },
    {
        "question": "980×689604=？",
        "answer": 8.82982584761137
    },
    {
        "question": "23270154÷28659=？",
        "answer": 2.9095382249566333
    },
    {
        "question": "33634÷4110=？",
        "answer": 0.9129366979697765
    },
    {
        "question": "10070195÷8615=？",
        "answer": 3.0677825985614295
    },
    {
        "question": "1×475837096=？",
        "answer": 8.677458296381571
    },
    {
        "question": "511510072÷2317321=？",
        "answer": 2.3438679923934442
    },
    {
        "question": "774817783÷131651=？",
        "answer": 3.7697754174559104
    },
    {
        "question": "6655÷944=？",
        "answer": 0.8481760655126249
    },
    {
        "question": "54068312÷680947=？",
        "answer": 1.89982950033549
    },
    {
        "question": "488358053÷28199=？",
        "answer": 4.2385046460754925
    },
    {
        "question": "125715827÷50034=？",
        "answer": 3.400124732431999
    },
    {
        "question": "2×4785=？",
        "answer": 3.9809119377768436
    },
    {
        "question": "7152854÷733=？",
        "answer": 3.9893753859210617
    },
    {
        "question": "956127097÷414873086=？",
        "answer": 0.3626003646146
    },
    {
        "question": "137×5259=？",
        "answer": 5.857623737969864
    },
    {
        "question": "140458844÷1030221=？",
        "answer": 2.1346186914950427
    },
    {
        "question": "446×944361=？",
        "answer": 8.624472902097093
    },
    {
        "question": "24×842360=？",
        "answer": 7.305708977629154
    },
    {
        "question": "1352125÷7230=？",
        "answer": 2.271878545421169
    },
    {
        "question": "3×112597443=？",
        "answer": 8.52864978285844
    },
    {
        "question": "1416×5525=？",
        "answer": 6.893395535710899
    },
    {
        "question": "6×451=？",
        "answer": 3.4323277922616042
    },
    {
        "question": "57857067÷933337=？",
        "answer": 1.7923179310156192
    },
    {
        "question": "367669752÷207058876=？",
        "answer": 0.2493640500024699
    },
    {
        "question": "596901630÷406117=？",
        "answer": 3.167251595474924
    },
    {
        "question": "42718227÷710767=？",
        "answer": 1.7788859633398508
    },
    {
        "question": "95768215÷13236=？",
        "answer": 3.8594646343005192
    },
    {
        "question": "54×13451396=？",
        "answer": 8.861161118037657
    },
    {
        "question": "26×15757312=？",
        "answer": 8.612455482245407
    },
    {
        "question": "1801649÷434=？",
        "answer": 3.618180455459488
    },
    {
        "question": "219591397÷212=？",
        "answer": 6.015279460693498
    },
    {
        "question": "35×1691=？",
        "answer": 4.772211651948018
    },
    {
        "question": "2457×314=？",
        "answer": 5.887334804553296
    },
    {
        "question": "10×490=？",
        "answer": 3.690196080028514
    },
    {
        "question": "283355442÷101390=？",
        "answer": 3.446336434871738
    },
    {
        "question": "650201804÷3327=？",
        "answer": 5.290995369253079
    },
    {
        "question": "4724÷2491=？",
        "answer": 0.2779361614049707
    },
    {
        "question": "946909652÷11787013=？",
        "answer": 1.9049047808880522
    },
    {
        "question": "198707843÷19694=？",
        "answer": 4.003881075470999
    },
    {
        "question": "27400÷1990=？",
        "answer": 1.1388974864106813
    },
    {
        "question": "1×73843=？",
        "answer": 4.868309332343146
    },
    {
        "question": "479×46167=？",
        "answer": 7.344667167784278
    },
    {
        "question": "292×14495=？",
        "answer": 6.626601071139435
    },
    {
        "question": "16×18782481=？",
        "answer": 8.477872940843916
    },
    {
        "question": "462×1077736=？",
        "answer": 8.697154365549007
    },
    {
        "question": "19755061÷1588=？",
        "answer": 4.094827876950053
    },
    {
        "question": "1057÷256=？",
        "answer": 0.6158350219955767
    },
    {
        "question": "335×101526=？",
        "answer": 7.531622082887598
    },
    {
        "question": "72990÷54686=？",
        "answer": 0.125387205524679
    },
    {
        "question": "205×89597=？",
        "answer": 7.264047329364555
    },
    {
        "question": "6611025÷2272=？",
        "answer": 3.463860472436538
    },
    {
        "question": "24×22865731=？",
        "answer": 8.739396331713966
    },
    {
        "question": "3323525÷1253=？",
        "answer": 3.423647878949532
    },
    {
        "question": "238326÷983=？",
        "answer": 2.3846179061365596
    },
    {
        "question": "47×210065=？",
        "answer": 6.994451556352633
    },
    {
        "question": "5×18194816=？",
        "answer": 7.95891767236002
    },
    {
        "question": "1×12537=？",
        "answer": 4.0981936258632885
    },
    {
        "question": "932971108÷215115447=？",
        "answer": 0.6371965975341186
    },
    {
        "question": "944840953÷172946196=？",
        "answer": 0.737447694961112
    },
    {
        "question": "81179986÷661=？",
        "answer": 5.0892475125988135
    },
    {
        "question": "6×2156182=？",
        "answer": 7.111836666573541
    },
    {
        "question": "28750÷1166=？",
        "answer": 1.391939298602654
    },
    {
        "question": "63×8714=？",
        "answer": 5.739558105053317
    },
    {
        "question": "1×156242=？",
        "answer": 5.193797789569381
    },
    {
        "question": "1×317569=？",
        "answer": 5.501838101481665
    },
    {
        "question": "6878489÷2058127=？",
        "answer": 0.5240208770119885
    },
    {
        "question": "4×26008=？",
        "answer": 5.017166947816032
    },
    {
        "question": "30724×2636=？",
        "answer": 7.9084231623608705
    },
    {
        "question": "47255125÷2572141=？",
        "answer": 1.264154144183097
    },
    {
        "question": "129374094÷1577=？",
        "answer": 4.914015628141243
    },
    {
        "question": "5×4009801=？",
        "answer": 7.302092824151607
    },
    {
        "question": "924756615÷52446243=？",
        "answer": 1.2463130637605724
    },
    {
        "question": "12895÷5949=？",
        "answer": 0.3359773775489912
    },
    {
        "question": "10810008÷867616=？",
        "answer": 1.0954984629678313
    },
    {
        "question": "166×10603=？",
        "answer": 6.245536849447296
    },
    {
        "question": "9210623÷5549397=？",
        "answer": 0.22004321151016146
    },
    {
        "question": "900893455÷143643926=？",
        "answer": 0.7973861652524327
    },
    {
        "question": "1×31350998=？",
        "answer": 7.496251370334015
    },
    {
        "question": "84×4158=？",
        "answer": 5.543163771057332
    },
    {
        "question": "63×2666861=？",
        "answer": 8.22534092978307
    },
    {
        "question": "102992751÷81770659=？",
        "answer": 0.10020916077429852
    },
    {
        "question": "6461514÷1101=？",
        "answer": 3.7685469706653567
    },
    {
        "question": "209660871÷26241=？",
        "answer": 3.902537004420915
    },
    {
        "question": "647923986÷483831=？",
        "answer": 3.126830366711232
    },
    {
        "question": "10×511=？",
        "answer": 3.708420900134713
    },
    {
        "question": "29×580909=？",
        "answer": 7.226506102934418
    },
    {
        "question": "348743148÷1328556=？",
        "answer": 2.4191258183881152
    },
    {
        "question": "14×10530=？",
        "answer": 5.168556406863725
    },
    {
        "question": "50×15609560=？",
        "answer": 8.892360665741473
    },
    {
        "question": "236882513÷847=？",
        "answer": 5.446649591346398
    },
    {
        "question": "61×306856=？",
        "answer": 7.272264454536912
    },
    {
        "question": "3253×3022=？",
        "answer": 6.99257852328486
    },
    {
        "question": "6×19451620=？",
        "answer": 8.067107027138558
    },
    {
        "question": "1×224079=？",
        "answer": 5.350401157688722
    },
    {
        "question": "3370×23447=？",
        "answer": 7.897717184306538
    },
    {
        "question": "536055886÷24220315=？",
        "answer": 1.3450302819050934
    },
    {
        "question": "219×489733=？",
        "answer": 8.030403484194318
    },
    {
        "question": "2611÷1849=？",
        "answer": 0.1498699606637714
    },
    {
        "question": "12059865÷580473=？",
        "answer": 1.3175604224100557
    },
    {
        "question": "72816613÷26082647=？",
        "answer": 0.4458788105313445
    },
    {
        "question": "7886300÷2342758=？",
        "answer": 0.5271458643238249
    },
    {
        "question": "8×563=？",
        "answer": 3.65359838184329
    },
    {
        "question": "498326399÷423=？",
        "answer": 6.071173527294194
    },
    {
        "question": "3656×366=？",
        "answer": 6.126487272456204
    },
    {
        "question": "4031÷331=？",
        "answer": 1.0855848043773324
    },
    {
        "question": "60930600÷155733=？",
        "answer": 2.592454804945036
    },
    {
        "question": "25733044÷109210=？",
        "answer": 2.3722287554837047
    },
    {
        "question": "2×692500=？",
        "answer": 6.141449773400467
    },
    {
        "question": "2896÷944=？",
        "answer": 0.4868265632270403
    },
    {
        "question": "10104÷1682=？",
        "answer": 0.778667346085381
    },
    {
        "question": "15×123725=？",
        "answer": 6.268548721538875
    },
    {
        "question": "9×24591033=？",
        "answer": 8.345019282048595
    },
    {
        "question": "238038×2130=？",
        "answer": 8.705025896095968
    },
    {
        "question": "8×137617=？",
        "answer": 6.041762073145488
    },
    {
        "question": "6761779÷397=？",
        "answer": 4.231270465545228
    },
    {
        "question": "31×2977=？",
        "answer": 4.9651405284809975
    },
    {
        "question": "119564×499=？",
        "answer": 7.775700981506096
    },
    {
        "question": "109968×8385=？",
        "answer": 8.964769393507089
    },
    {
        "question": "93443290÷476109=？",
        "answer": 2.2928417297812524
    },
    {
        "question": "102×81066=？",
        "answer": 6.917438916127593
    },
    {
        "question": "33883217÷907=？",
        "answer": 4.572377350106898
    },
    {
        "question": "637×420=？",
        "answer": 5.427388722733251
    },
    {
        "question": "5×94828=？",
        "answer": 5.675906595366384
    },
    {
        "question": "3×162544=？",
        "answer": 5.688092197699859
    },
    {
        "question": "26832×8621=？",
        "answer": 8.364210690355025
    },
    {
        "question": "265322998÷20978555=？",
        "answer": 1.1019993251931817
    },
    {
        "question": "974479868÷118008=？",
        "answer": 3.9168614213566206
    },
    {
        "question": "269810866÷9203718=？",
        "answer": 1.467096132371938
    },
    {
        "question": "27×251=？",
        "answer": 3.8310374856400253
    },
    {
        "question": "45×1249804=？",
        "answer": 7.750054424069245
    },
    {
        "question": "71456598÷4497=？",
        "answer": 4.201119448325942
    },
    {
        "question": "5061805÷49980=？",
        "answer": 2.0055091586771634
    },
    {
        "question": "1×272=？",
        "answer": 2.4345689040341987
    },
    {
        "question": "45156÷498=？",
        "answer": 1.9574861216077717
    },
    {
        "question": "100097×3920=？",
        "answer": 8.593707128486091
    },
    {
        "question": "672063682÷9788=？",
        "answer": 4.836716466289007
    },
    {
        "question": "8559×1573=？",
        "answer": 7.129151749000026
    },
    {
        "question": "6×76935794=？",
        "answer": 8.664279690574867
    },
    {
        "question": "6132384÷1276108=？",
        "answer": 0.6817419105574046
    },
    {
        "question": "10968888÷1258811=？",
        "answer": 0.9402020727570777
    },
    {
        "question": "841121258÷7750=？",
        "answer": 5.0355569067091865
    },
    {
        "question": "90×561999=？",
        "answer": 7.703978052241716
    },
    {
        "question": "28498754÷53829=？",
        "answer": 2.723809560692035
    },
    {
        "question": "5166×378=？",
        "answer": 6.290646201674524
    },
    {
        "question": "277533990÷19783364=？",
        "answer": 1.1470160376245488
    },
    {
        "question": "33×5303=？",
        "answer": 5.243035566996451
    },
    {
        "question": "174668×4261=？",
        "answer": 8.871724881676917
    },
    {
        "question": "26240179÷17222935=？",
        "answer": 0.1828596307501032
    },
    {
        "question": "400567÷12638=？",
        "answer": 1.5009968168246626
    },
    {
        "question": "11422×1772=？",
        "answer": 7.306205873379785
    },
    {
        "question": "3658582÷28827=？",
        "answer": 2.103513345241508
    },
    {
        "question": "5088÷1653=？",
        "answer": 0.48827424906891
    },
    {
        "question": "194×286556=？",
        "answer": 7.745011236214174
    },
    {
        "question": "11616080÷5631042=？",
        "answer": 0.3144708277487162
    },
    {
        "question": "109728746÷24076=？",
        "answer": 3.658736081379267
    },
    {
        "question": "257×23960=？",
        "answer": 6.789419937048568
    },
    {
        "question": "256251×2916=？",
        "answer": 8.873453088514175
    },
    {
        "question": "708×355162=？",
        "answer": 8.400459750626435
    },
    {
        "question": "1455×2595=？",
        "answer": 6.577000355506403
    },
    {
        "question": "11952÷10262=？",
        "answer": 0.06620857415195762
    },
    {
        "question": "7489×77283=？",
        "answer": 8.762507802924548
    },
    {
        "question": "124789867÷4399460=？",
        "answer": 1.4527799484096795
    },
    {
        "question": "4×4658977=？",
        "answer": 7.270350557797274
    },
    {
        "question": "1025920÷124561=？",
        "answer": 0.9157314101631753
    },
    {
        "question": "1×27444684=？",
        "answer": 7.438458234649557
    },
    {
        "question": "43×347910=？",
        "answer": 7.17493536746142
    },
    {
        "question": "720044735÷682147423=？",
        "answer": 0.023481236349825556
    },
    {
        "question": "6171×1658=？",
        "answer": 7.009940072628641
    },
    {
        "question": "123×533=？",
        "answer": 4.8166323204659705
    },
    {
        "question": "619170553÷260827870=？",
        "answer": 0.3754562988402115
    },
    {
        "question": "1×247=？",
        "answer": 2.392696953259666
    },
    {
        "question": "2×2263928=？",
        "answer": 6.655892606475303
    },
    {
        "question": "19841645÷10743179=？",
        "answer": 0.26644486322555105
    },
    {
        "question": "2182478÷1096398=？",
        "answer": 0.29898163993987886
    },
    {
        "question": "2508146÷27071=？",
        "answer": 1.9668485144574803
    },
    {
        "question": "148792716÷288748=？",
        "answer": 2.712062686484662
    },
    {
        "question": "77218067÷55702318=？",
        "answer": 0.1418456574201141
    },
    {
        "question": "44×2947830=？",
        "answer": 8.112955110832376
    },
    {
        "question": "100×586=？",
        "answer": 4.76789761601809
    },
    {
        "question": "293×247668=？",
        "answer": 7.860737517447851
    },
    {
        "question": "409795913÷1819198=？",
        "answer": 2.3526876528694056
    },
    {
        "question": "75514÷3230=？",
        "answer": 1.3688249532596262
    },
    {
        "question": "2×1554551=？",
        "answer": 6.492634970132772
    },
    {
        "question": "10×2424=？",
        "answer": 4.3845326154942486
    },
    {
        "question": "3×373989=？",
        "answer": 6.04998008336518
    },
    {
        "question": "89769047÷326789=？",
        "answer": 2.4388591853015904
    },
    {
        "question": "4×8808=？",
        "answer": 4.546937297291658
    },
    {
        "question": "2×31884161=？",
        "answer": 7.804604989110061
    },
    {
        "question": "6×235=？",
        "answer": 3.1492191126553797
    },
    {
        "question": "447×194319=？",
        "answer": 7.938822789978417
    },
    {
        "question": "4747×193641=？",
        "answer": 8.963416548474655
    },
    {
        "question": "40854÷7472=？",
        "answer": 0.7377977213399497
    },
    {
        "question": "7857298÷19954=？",
        "answer": 2.5952432568549764
    },
    {
        "question": "27332950÷34012=？",
        "answer": 2.905054336501537
    },
    {
        "question": "1425÷245=？",
        "answer": 0.7646487799799966
    },
    {
        "question": "12558×257=？",
        "answer": 6.508853602053625
    },
    {
        "question": "525×331862=？",
        "answer": 8.241116829586394
    },
    {
        "question": "2×13607370=？",
        "answer": 7.434804189577044
    },
    {
        "question": "727×1448=？",
        "answer": 6.022302972720166
    },
    {
        "question": "17×9911698=？",
        "answer": 8.226596982408546
    },
    {
        "question": "1×141460=？",
        "answer": 5.150633653746429
    },
    {
        "question": "8×2154=？",
        "answer": 4.2363356859539065
    },
    {
        "question": "155779423÷10057=？",
        "answer": 4.190041640770854
    },
    {
        "question": "467380420÷45702=？",
        "answer": 4.009735308531743
    },
    {
        "question": "234×292016=？",
        "answer": 7.834622505164526
    },
    {
        "question": "31288086÷525=？",
        "answer": 4.7752196932633195
    },
    {
        "question": "289×4142=？",
        "answer": 6.078107937313981
    },
    {
        "question": "9×85720007=？",
        "answer": 8.887324707274132
    },
    {
        "question": "83×2386=？",
        "answer": 5.296748531710397
    },
    {
        "question": "214855÷739=？",
        "answer": 2.4635010264305075
    },
    {
        "question": "62835621÷229=？",
        "answer": 5.438370429199884
    },
    {
        "question": "65×9906=？",
        "answer": 5.808811680289293
    },
    {
        "question": "664326920÷4498=？",
        "answer": 5.169362400274005
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1441=？",
        "answer": 3.1586639808139894
    },
    {
        "question": "558215537÷4226463=？",
        "answer": 2.120824848828733
    },
    {
        "question": "1107131×205=？",
        "answer": 8.355952872369095
    },
    {
        "question": "13×1460188=？",
        "answer": 7.278352127342165
    },
    {
        "question": "43461797÷14393585=？",
        "answer": 0.4799387021525413
    },
    {
        "question": "2×200=？",
        "answer": 2.6020599913279625
    },
    {
        "question": "9077÷651=？",
        "answer": 1.1443613468772127
    },
    {
        "question": "109754357÷10942=？",
        "answer": 4.001325059324633
    },
    {
        "question": "416671895÷3365007=？",
        "answer": 2.0928082357865345
    },
    {
        "question": "19×37943636=？",
        "answer": 8.857892546352979
    },
    {
        "question": "12×15942=？",
        "answer": 5.281724050841546
    },
    {
        "question": "1078×125132=？",
        "answer": 8.129987146853297
    },
    {
        "question": "1364375÷1200=？",
        "answer": 3.0557525070055895
    },
    {
        "question": "842073026÷605084=？",
        "answer": 3.143534086681555
    },
    {
        "question": "85607÷387=？",
        "answer": 2.3447983129418692
    },
    {
        "question": "4×3820=？",
        "answer": 4.184123354239671
    },
    {
        "question": "9488×233=？",
        "answer": 6.344530597046206
    },
    {
        "question": "51052847÷32623740=？",
        "answer": 0.1944862185831359
    },
    {
        "question": "40404÷999=？",
        "answer": 1.6068588742097312
    },
    {
        "question": "676351660÷1428147=？",
        "answer": 2.675399648347717
    },
    {
        "question": "95504×1138=？",
        "answer": 8.036163823606651
    },
    {
        "question": "92551780÷8907=？",
        "answer": 4.016653323412265
    },
    {
        "question": "11575196÷1383368=？",
        "answer": 0.9225906281754629
    },
    {
        "question": "132406÷54974=？",
        "answer": 0.38175032756974
    },
    {
        "question": "75×5664=？",
        "answer": 5.628184508073413
    },
    {
        "question": "783241762÷40492494=？",
        "answer": 1.2865213092331889
    },
    {
        "question": "126688547÷75465=？",
        "answer": 3.2249917788372517
    },
    {
        "question": "17×3505=？",
        "answer": 4.775136943680951
    },
    {
        "question": "528×227666=？",
        "answer": 8.079932099767666
    },
    {
        "question": "59089364÷1833092=？",
        "answer": 1.5083250534725303
    },
    {
        "question": "19×12170018=？",
        "answer": 8.364044821524299
    },
    {
        "question": "27516469÷466=？",
        "answer": 4.771206786412617
    },
    {
        "question": "2×18013=？",
        "answer": 4.556616044682539
    },
    {
        "question": "18×271061=？",
        "answer": 6.688339541299762
    },
    {
        "question": "59×203=？",
        "answer": 4.078348049555357
    },
    {
        "question": "31×3939=？",
        "answer": 5.086747674643415
    },
    {
        "question": "41354×2221=？",
        "answer": 7.963066081963277
    },
    {
        "question": "66×290=？",
        "answer": 4.281941933440825
    },
    {
        "question": "797569181÷202025=？",
        "answer": 3.5963632485464587
    },
    {
        "question": "38873933÷8500524=？",
        "answer": 0.6602127839478394
    },
    {
        "question": "45127÷20065=？",
        "answer": 0.3519972989262029
    },
    {
        "question": "49616921÷87319=？",
        "answer": 2.754521057024294
    },
    {
        "question": "394619015÷156838=？",
        "answer": 3.400726712675981
    },
    {
        "question": "3511×15162=？",
        "answer": 7.72618732176891
    },
    {
        "question": "526481÷7538=？",
        "answer": 1.8441265695797162
    },
    {
        "question": "9×8963=？",
        "answer": 4.9066959058623585
    },
    {
        "question": "325728÷393=？",
        "answer": 2.9184625423092596
    },
    {
        "question": "3×8883333=？",
        "answer": 7.425697197066363
    },
    {
        "question": "30298600÷14433=？",
        "answer": 3.3220659500047787
    },
    {
        "question": "6032835÷76132=？",
        "answer": 1.8989542084537416
    },
    {
        "question": "161×4446632=？",
        "answer": 8.854857065075462
    },
    {
        "question": "55001891÷746340=？",
        "answer": 1.8674409028682701
    },
    {
        "question": "420208405÷50807758=？",
        "answer": 0.9175347037375489
    },
    {
        "question": "1224×16275=？",
        "answer": 7.299302415049772
    },
    {
        "question": "165800÷66590=？",
        "answer": 0.39617551132171014
    },
    {
        "question": "6522527÷62097=？",
        "answer": 2.021345266277916
    },
    {
        "question": "27814539÷371=？",
        "answer": 4.874897956696125
    },
    {
        "question": "66×1017790=？",
        "answer": 7.827202115065828
    },
    {
        "question": "30×40868=？",
        "answer": 6.088504639428638
    },
    {
        "question": "1275÷626=？",
        "answer": 0.3089358515595443
    },
    {
        "question": "755×13249=？",
        "answer": 7.0001300517230565
    },
    {
        "question": "31446684÷868=？",
        "answer": 4.559055131395624
    },
    {
        "question": "911×7606=？",
        "answer": 6.840674698048562
    },
    {
        "question": "10412804÷11162=？",
        "answer": 2.969825675571081
    },
    {
        "question": "6145÷1306=？",
        "answer": 0.6725787102834178
    },
    {
        "question": "20224×947=？",
        "answer": 7.282217035605564
    },
    {
        "question": "45244÷14514=？",
        "answer": 0.49377387496885417
    },
    {
        "question": "189167982÷23123572=？",
        "answer": 0.9127927086046802
    },
    {
        "question": "1×32647=？",
        "answer": 4.513843279231117
    },
    {
        "question": "475492÷326=？",
        "answer": 3.1639256144019554
    },
    {
        "question": "194×495648=？",
        "answer": 7.982975088017017
    },
    {
        "question": "2082×620=？",
        "answer": 6.110872414672771
    },
    {
        "question": "17×18614=？",
        "answer": 5.500288630955113
    },
    {
        "question": "5374172÷1479=？",
        "answer": 3.5603433878872894
    },
    {
        "question": "28×529258=？",
        "answer": 7.1708254626620995
    },
    {
        "question": "9×229375=？",
        "answer": 6.314788591035489
    },
    {
        "question": "408600÷99953=？",
        "answer": 0.6115025286857841
    },
    {
        "question": "826×30354=？",
        "answer": 7.399195977112593
    },
    {
        "question": "17649×5073=？",
        "answer": 7.951984965424513
    },
    {
        "question": "1060×140430=？",
        "answer": 8.172765761111874
    },
    {
        "question": "5094×18419=？",
        "answer": 7.972324988514973
    },
    {
        "question": "208277676÷11405=？",
        "answer": 4.261547433481601
    },
    {
        "question": "2060662÷2421=？",
        "answer": 2.9300119730444365
    },
    {
        "question": "365×291=？",
        "answer": 5.026185853442382
    },
    {
        "question": "447294349÷32671=？",
        "answer": 4.136430983799678
    },
    {
        "question": "441422156÷324394966=？",
        "answer": 0.13378002146070456
    },
    {
        "question": "1156×681706=？",
        "answer": 8.896554950520144
    },
    {
        "question": "86463÷73734=？",
        "answer": 0.06916250553252302
    },
    {
        "question": "12×3913835=？",
        "answer": 7.6717837587083935
    },
    {
        "question": "186×1419124=？",
        "answer": 8.421533289050252
    },
    {
        "question": "34037556÷74937=？",
        "answer": 2.6572620661459663
    },
    {
        "question": "922478428÷22225=？",
        "answer": 4.618114449405536
    },
    {
        "question": "1356×227553=？",
        "answer": 8.489342255037519
    },
    {
        "question": "57551890÷23030=？",
        "answer": 3.3977656524358606
    },
    {
        "question": "1×275637301=？",
        "answer": 8.440337988715639
    },
    {
        "question": "447×488=？",
        "answer": 5.3387273451346475
    },
    {
        "question": "3396×232717=？",
        "answer": 8.897795791272573
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1021=？",
        "answer": 3.0090257420869104
    },
    {
        "question": "16744889÷2448753=？",
        "answer": 0.8349372919326981
    },
    {
        "question": "62299÷367=？",
        "answer": 2.2298150113321613
    },
    {
        "question": "840×734343=？",
        "answer": 8.790178245450354
    },
    {
        "question": "69697×390=？",
        "answer": 7.434278691989851
    },
    {
        "question": "6×5697=？",
        "answer": 4.533797469840324
    },
    {
        "question": "139921640÷1729=？",
        "answer": 4.908089893525287
    },
    {
        "question": "1029×3163=？",
        "answer": 6.512514566678155
    },
    {
        "question": "39055978÷898481=？",
        "answer": 1.6381786198350996
    },
    {
        "question": "5050×53160=？",
        "answer": 8.428876350389356
    },
    {
        "question": "5×2123679=？",
        "answer": 7.026058876884737
    },
    {
        "question": "135999666÷441=？",
        "answer": 5.489099252324915
    },
    {
        "question": "3753520÷398=？",
        "answer": 3.9745556621999825
    },
    {
        "question": "2381×18746=？",
        "answer": 7.6496680080951265
    },
    {
        "question": "5×1571=？",
        "answer": 3.895146189375992
    },
    {
        "question": "22×12313117=？",
        "answer": 8.432790687006584
    },
    {
        "question": "8509026÷7900=？",
        "answer": 3.032252759389409
    },
    {
        "question": "82082×786=？",
        "answer": 7.809670475902443
    },
    {
        "question": "75810220÷90903=？",
        "answer": 2.9211495408201134
    },
    {
        "question": "6×579=？",
        "answer": 3.54082981411108
    },
    {
        "question": "572885666÷566=？",
        "answer": 6.005251524845628
    },
    {
        "question": "12233×1055=？",
        "answer": 7.110785435367805
    },
    {
        "question": "2608611÷17176=？",
        "answer": 2.1814872898532593
    },
    {
        "question": "457325×260=？",
        "answer": 8.0751982910206
    },
    {
        "question": "5×398=？",
        "answer": 3.298853076409707
    },
    {
        "question": "207×306229=？",
        "answer": 7.80201666161538
    },
    {
        "question": "592×4396=？",
        "answer": 6.415379390474373
    },
    {
        "question": "1×217=？",
        "answer": 2.3364597338485296
    },
    {
        "question": "84×110831=？",
        "answer": 6.968940537843374
    },
    {
        "question": "46283÷8982=？",
        "answer": 0.7120484508326022
    },
    {
        "question": "854872×711=？",
        "answer": 8.783770693405074
    },
    {
        "question": "60×74764=？",
        "answer": 6.651843779198729
    },
    {
        "question": "41002÷6935=？",
        "answer": 0.7717585758904172
    },
    {
        "question": "1470×84104=？",
        "answer": 8.092133986153897
    },
    {
        "question": "102×105623=？",
        "answer": 7.032358670314343
    },
    {
        "question": "6146315÷1992=？",
        "answer": 3.489325480091084
    },
    {
        "question": "1762×26850=？",
        "answer": 7.674950194111603
    },
    {
        "question": "3501603÷11117=？",
        "answer": 2.4982793000262493
    },
    {
        "question": "152477×656=？",
        "answer": 8.000108177967244
    },
    {
        "question": "1×567194=？",
        "answer": 5.753731628062398
    },
    {
        "question": "37×81784=？",
        "answer": 6.480870071853481
    },
    {
        "question": "2×6449=？",
        "answer": 4.110522372601323
    },
    {
        "question": "49×1367=？",
        "answer": 4.825964594596336
    },
    {
        "question": "1043956÷14906=？",
        "answer": 1.8453210777874385
    },
    {
        "question": "1341990÷258844=？",
        "answer": 0.7147111771523941
    },
    {
        "question": "9339939÷2995=？",
        "answer": 3.4939472130968503
    },
    {
        "question": "71790÷2655=？",
        "answer": 1.4319994279156119
    },
    {
        "question": "1521×19386=？",
        "answer": 7.469617422454286
    },
    {
        "question": "24337×1949=？",
        "answer": 7.676078881222636
    },
    {
        "question": "31849×1312=？",
        "answer": 7.62102963587742
    },
    {
        "question": "1293394÷1704=？",
        "answer": 2.8802612515113775
    },
    {
        "question": "488328÷927=？",
        "answer": 2.7216318926521423
    },
    {
        "question": "53384×9574=？",
        "answer": 8.708504534988645
    },
    {
        "question": "27420252÷16494=？",
        "answer": 3.2207454515358833
    },
    {
        "question": "5728355÷11373=？",
        "answer": 2.7021548852660784
    },
    {
        "question": "139886860÷318468=？",
        "answer": 2.6427111213038232
    },
    {
        "question": "1650528÷613=？",
        "answer": 3.430162421698565
    },
    {
        "question": "142036007÷1566359=？",
        "answer": 1.9575071478621737
    },
    {
        "question": "150×166488=？",
        "answer": 7.3974741952668195
    },
    {
        "question": "1×43415=？",
        "answer": 4.637639805358698
    },
    {
        "question": "70785125÷4978=？",
        "answer": 4.1528871110507195
    },
    {
        "question": "117588331÷2033663=？",
        "answer": 1.7620852389685975
    },
    {
        "question": "1×18715457=？",
        "answer": 7.272200436321134
    },
    {
        "question": "351×279=？",
        "answer": 4.990911319739421
    },
    {
        "question": "763217349÷60224825=？",
        "answer": 1.1028726872218277
    },
    {
        "question": "27670÷256=？",
        "answer": 2.0337691938291025
    },
    {
        "question": "398181÷11695=？",
        "answer": 1.532080306813864
    },
    {
        "question": "151×226=？",
        "answer": 4.53308538644057
    },
    {
        "question": "432456565÷287213341=？",
        "answer": 0.17773788546760666
    },
    {
        "question": "397592330÷74717764=？",
        "answer": 0.7260141310386377
    },
    {
        "question": "26×1586=？",
        "answer": 4.615276530952403
    },
    {
        "question": "47386368÷3583068=？",
        "answer": 1.1213983724662673
    },
    {
        "question": "187×62459=？",
        "answer": 7.067436633213283
    },
    {
        "question": "193×835702=？",
        "answer": 8.207608750528692
    },
    {
        "question": "81648085÷896778=？",
        "answer": 1.9592610576239269
    },
    {
        "question": "8×4717675=？",
        "answer": 7.5768180060832195
    },
    {
        "question": "28×240725=？",
        "answer": 6.828679226720047
    },
    {
        "question": "1442399÷66342=？",
        "answer": 1.3372968526464561
    },
    {
        "question": "1323447÷13089=？",
        "answer": 2.0048000861149213
    },
    {
        "question": "879÷205=？",
        "answer": 0.6322350140180176
    },
    {
        "question": "121×719=？",
        "answer": 4.939514260699332
    },
    {
        "question": "66812÷1518=？",
        "answer": 1.6435827008822077
    },
    {
        "question": "24141×4506=？",
        "answer": 8.03654644343443
    },
    {
        "question": "252244÷89914=？",
        "answer": 0.4479935261555956
    },
    {
        "question": "722778÷410041=？",
        "answer": 0.24617764098802025
    },
    {
        "question": "1136×620=？",
        "answer": 5.847770020873254
    },
    {
        "question": "1×7413=？",
        "answer": 3.869994000121742
    },
    {
        "question": "47747439÷414=？",
        "answer": 5.061949741437703
    },
    {
        "question": "3×73299=？",
        "answer": 5.342219304429762
    },
    {
        "question": "1774189÷6129=？",
        "answer": 2.4616102609333077
    },
    {
        "question": "1656÷301=？",
        "answer": 0.7404938368550179
    },
    {
        "question": "1×13395887=？",
        "answer": 7.126971475424754
    },
    {
        "question": "325×25614=？",
        "answer": 6.920360766166465
    },
    {
        "question": "477÷374=？",
        "answer": 0.10564677683963375
    },
    {
        "question": "12523×1588=？",
        "answer": 7.298558878672707
    },
    {
        "question": "11×15383614=？",
        "answer": 8.228451059367513
    },
    {
        "question": "133518082÷559509=？",
        "answer": 2.377733008255888
    },
    {
        "question": "123×64551=？",
        "answer": 6.8998080860219755
    },
    {
        "question": "14209933÷10385=？",
        "answer": 3.1361855293576264
    },
    {
        "question": "125180531÷53105237=？",
        "answer": 0.3723994380785747
    },
    {
        "question": "552742612÷15450521=？",
        "answer": 1.5535798178215943
    },
    {
        "question": "27581×8283=？",
        "answer": 8.35879766963127
    },
    {
        "question": "800153÷26636=？",
        "answer": 1.4777040316496135
    },
    {
        "question": "2×3961=？",
        "answer": 3.8988348380682742
    },
    {
        "question": "173343×258=？",
        "answer": 7.650526014472202
    },
    {
        "question": "1176×255684=？",
        "answer": 8.47811087366508
    },
    {
        "question": "3×2041568=？",
        "answer": 6.787085104583842
    },
    {
        "question": "26×426=？",
        "answer": 4.044382947073537
    },
    {
        "question": "4×9226457=？",
        "answer": 7.567094953378102
    },
    {
        "question": "217044003÷6398=？",
        "answer": 4.530503554887406
    },
    {
        "question": "23191895÷674=？",
        "answer": 4.536676339572236
    },
    {
        "question": "99×265511=？",
        "answer": 7.4197177130106695
    },
    {
        "question": "1×831=？",
        "answer": 2.919601023784111
    },
    {
        "question": "1×78964=？",
        "answer": 4.897429139837969
    },
    {
        "question": "1×27647024=？",
        "answer": 7.441648389530858
    },
    {
        "question": "3737×923=？",
        "answer": 6.53772479887555
    },
    {
        "question": "9975560÷38434=？",
        "answer": 2.414221699313881
    },
    {
        "question": "770467582÷2412=？",
        "answer": 5.504377066705466
    },
    {
        "question": "12553×9661=？",
        "answer": 8.083769610934354
    },
    {
        "question": "80528106÷37760=？",
        "answer": 3.3289154990938417
    },
    {
        "question": "3132192÷1281=？",
        "answer": 3.3882992462417247
    },
    {
        "question": "967279651÷5901=？",
        "answer": 5.214626436825682
    },
    {
        "question": "3071×1989=？",
        "answer": 6.785914599567504
    },
    {
        "question": "4146÷2471=？",
        "answer": 0.22475655235576264
    },
    {
        "question": "25×1106486=？",
        "answer": 7.441885931986185
    },
    {
        "question": "444484163÷123700=？",
        "answer": 3.5554865920117824
    },
    {
        "question": "198213679÷1024366=？",
        "answer": 2.2866784671922535
    },
    {
        "question": "3×21645676=？",
        "answer": 7.812492408208426
    },
    {
        "question": "44061840÷23811691=？",
        "answer": 0.26727239095435873
    },
    {
        "question": "25010206÷265=？",
        "answer": 4.974871394934631
    },
    {
        "question": "6×491=？",
        "answer": 3.469232742506612
    },
    {
        "question": "25627×252=？",
        "answer": 6.810098309677332
    },
    {
        "question": "22818×423=？",
        "answer": 6.984617943170268
    },
    {
        "question": "648633082÷104233374=？",
        "answer": 0.79399229910387
    },
    {
        "question": "70264909÷48021151=？",
        "answer": 0.16530592286361256
    },
    {
        "question": "1654619÷9592=？",
        "answer": 2.2367888369353635
    },
    {
        "question": "898093552÷98385644=？",
        "answer": 0.9603898456011648
    },
    {
        "question": "2672593÷485258=？",
        "answer": 0.7409601226473048
    },
    {
        "question": "28344309÷8872313=？",
        "answer": 0.504429019304885
    },
    {
        "question": "2717×248=？",
        "answer": 5.828541319244107
    },
    {
        "question": "223226÷18717=？",
        "answer": 1.0765085368282052
    },
    {
        "question": "446136388÷178449133=？",
        "answer": 0.39795320456559546
    },
    {
        "question": "462742÷210378=？",
        "answer": 0.3423385972102707
    },
    {
        "question": "7×36649=？",
        "answer": 5.409160169048514
    },
    {
        "question": "247521÷6199=？",
        "answer": 1.6012904145835694
    },
    {
        "question": "3×11413=？",
        "answer": 4.534521071985725
    },
    {
        "question": "19214÷1736=？",
        "answer": 1.0440680655251706
    },
    {
        "question": "3×1581709=？",
        "answer": 6.67624784050643
    },
    {
        "question": "13760×33597=？",
        "answer": 8.664918933265122
    },
    {
        "question": "5×18440938=？",
        "answer": 7.964753012044055
    },
    {
        "question": "145818449÷1158=？",
        "answer": 5.100103915153062
    },
    {
        "question": "60×1803387=？",
        "answer": 8.03424018505358
    },
    {
        "question": "303329590÷28041=？",
        "answer": 4.0341212806787246
    },
    {
        "question": "71591968÷24530=？",
        "answer": 3.4651667527474577
    },
    {
        "question": "100393441÷898=？",
        "answer": 5.048429003327389
    },
    {
        "question": "49×27473=？",
        "answer": 6.1291021661803065
    },
    {
        "question": "15583×3463=？",
        "answer": 7.73210356221744
    },
    {
        "question": "408×746600=？",
        "answer": 8.483748148680165
    },
    {
        "question": "162834÷9473=？",
        "answer": 1.2352575540999204
    },
    {
        "question": "426639÷393868=？",
        "answer": 0.034709854959366994
    },
    {
        "question": "70455÷10366=？",
        "answer": 0.8323006147354178
    },
    {
        "question": "78×34693=？",
        "answer": 6.43233645880559
    },
    {
        "question": "1511÷312=？",
        "answer": 0.6851098703205826
    },
    {
        "question": "5×352=？",
        "answer": 3.24551266781415
    },
    {
        "question": "20727820÷88012=？",
        "answer": 2.372011738501532
    },
    {
        "question": "121636÷8363=？",
        "answer": 1.1627000331475903
    },
    {
        "question": "38×33960=？",
        "answer": 6.110751278188725
    },
    {
        "question": "761837343÷741=？",
        "answer": 6.012044048690776
    },
    {
        "question": "162180418÷717981=？",
        "answer": 2.353885463806332
    },
    {
        "question": "3192×475=？",
        "answer": 6.1807564923035585
    },
    {
        "question": "1051511÷3037=？",
        "answer": 2.539369028341653
    },
    {
        "question": "4×5723554=？",
        "answer": 7.359725775939556
    },
    {
        "question": "14×30091=？",
        "answer": 5.624564656361671
    },
    {
        "question": "15×2955=？",
        "answer": 4.646648744272955
    },
    {
        "question": "1346×29343=？",
        "answer": 7.596549573513854
    },
    {
        "question": "12211588÷1469447=？",
        "answer": 0.9196182168909572
    },
    {
        "question": "761173959÷289427625=？",
        "answer": 0.41994394107904975
    },
    {
        "question": "21430972÷37720=？",
        "answer": 2.7544701848143043
    },
    {
        "question": "57975113÷6617=？",
        "answer": 3.942580469155927
    },
    {
        "question": "117206×3478=？",
        "answer": 8.610279422285567
    },
    {
        "question": "112×369=？",
        "answer": 4.616244388829242
    },
    {
        "question": "1×2143=？",
        "answer": 3.3310221710418286
    },
    {
        "question": "354433099÷170231=？",
        "answer": 3.318495621662967
    },
    {
        "question": "631888288÷3927638=？",
        "answer": 2.206508852637944
    },
    {
        "question": "53×334=？",
        "answer": 4.248022336412354
    },
    {
        "question": "11×1033798=？",
        "answer": 7.05582837279856
    },
    {
        "question": "16495891÷3887=？",
        "answer": 3.6277612376273476
    },
    {
        "question": "9×412537=？",
        "answer": 6.569705415477288
    },
    {
        "question": "1336×112984=？",
        "answer": 8.17882340424506
    },
    {
        "question": "42777852÷7437=？",
        "answer": 3.759821192110165
    },
    {
        "question": "95388×6193=？",
        "answer": 8.771394823040923
    },
    {
        "question": "6219×23806=？",
        "answer": 8.170406986075438
    },
    {
        "question": "5488×14548=？",
        "answer": 7.90221739508137
    },
    {
        "question": "335×174135=？",
        "answer": 7.76593087728791
    },
    {
        "question": "590015488÷12855876=？",
        "answer": 1.6617617372569689
    },
    {
        "question": "1878580×429=？",
        "answer": 8.906286986563504
    },
    {
        "question": "13×15899=？",
        "answer": 5.315313161649959
    },
    {
        "question": "12330491÷266854=？",
        "answer": 1.664706653508526
    },
    {
        "question": "8×748=？",
        "answer": 3.776991584856405
    },
    {
        "question": "39863796÷1079=？",
        "answer": 4.567557207016187
    },
    {
        "question": "38019÷201=？",
        "answer": 2.2768046321685516
    },
    {
        "question": "10×95594=？",
        "answer": 5.980430634444868
    },
    {
        "question": "365×1729432=？",
        "answer": 8.800196355001507
    },
    {
        "question": "62×97176=？",
        "answer": 6.779950707978274
    },
    {
        "question": "39×19671469=？",
        "answer": 8.884901399826989
    },
    {
        "question": "57560÷24171=？",
        "answer": 0.3768261669008565
    },
    {
        "question": "1×14925855=？",
        "answer": 7.173939218270189
    },
    {
        "question": "17492921÷200033=？",
        "answer": 1.9417606864800652
    },
    {
        "question": "91×206109=？",
        "answer": 7.273138348510777
    },
    {
        "question": "10431902÷76327=？",
        "answer": 2.1356853055730194
    },
    {
        "question": "65×4379291=？",
        "answer": 8.454317161276688
    },
    {
        "question": "1734864÷233=？",
        "answer": 3.871909514086717
    },
    {
        "question": "1399×18326=？",
        "answer": 7.408885396720821
    },
    {
        "question": "1265158×244=？",
        "answer": 8.489534592359048
    },
    {
        "question": "223972÷3287=？",
        "answer": 1.8333940240490922
    },
    {
        "question": "11535383÷371774=？",
        "answer": 1.4917530044947827
    },
    {
        "question": "6×58753884=？",
        "answer": 8.5471878318638
    },
    {
        "question": "19306742÷46913=？",
        "answer": 2.614415786886469
    },
    {
        "question": "31785041÷163531=？",
        "answer": 2.2886226834824788
    },
    {
        "question": "35144093÷804=？",
        "answer": 4.640596290761413
    },
    {
        "question": "598027686÷331662=？",
        "answer": 3.2560255750337994
    },
    {
        "question": "22262÷4234=？",
        "answer": 0.7208133247315576
    },
    {
        "question": "19×201665=？",
        "answer": 6.5833841316602095
    },
    {
        "question": "18283558÷333=？",
        "answer": 4.73961648028789
    },
    {
        "question": "67520115÷5144607=？",
        "answer": 1.1180809689898694
    },
    {
        "question": "2611316÷1097631=？",
        "answer": 0.3764030655921144
    },
    {
        "question": "661030308÷379497259=？",
        "answer": 0.2410127287285214
    },
    {
        "question": "3463×2687=？",
        "answer": 6.968720157982629
    },
    {
        "question": "5×4481=？",
        "answer": 4.350344948249062
    },
    {
        "question": "5602648÷4875=？",
        "answer": 3.060418717682023
    },
    {
        "question": "268857224÷1001=？",
        "answer": 5.429087632670579
    },
    {
        "question": "12×17251=？",
        "answer": 5.315995521218897
    },
    {
        "question": "6×35887229=？",
        "answer": 8.333091176354971
    },
    {
        "question": "723084392÷967=？",
        "answer": 5.873762513171481
    },
    {
        "question": "470899247÷317058=？",
        "answer": 3.1717892802074084
    },
    {
        "question": "8×368=？",
        "answer": 3.4689378056654614
    },
    {
        "question": "1×300=？",
        "answer": 2.4771212547196626
    },
    {
        "question": "1391×547=？",
        "answer": 5.881314456325478
    },
    {
        "question": "3241×1069=？",
        "answer": 6.539656736240988
    },
    {
        "question": "41239×294=？",
        "answer": 7.083655455991933
    },
    {
        "question": "54×1002=？",
        "answer": 4.733261481354195
    },
    {
        "question": "9611×943=？",
        "answer": 6.95728026998834
    },
    {
        "question": "46822211÷3571=？",
        "answer": 4.117662067549448
    },
    {
        "question": "2700752÷11127=？",
        "answer": 2.385106618324874
    },
    {
        "question": "18550÷640=？",
        "answer": 1.4621639399671775
    },
    {
        "question": "5516301÷161442=？",
        "answer": 1.5336314265495874
    },
    {
        "question": "4118252÷75401=？",
        "answer": 1.737335812307832
    },
    {
        "question": "3883×1211=？",
        "answer": 6.6723115336891
    },
    {
        "question": "1×9354=？",
        "answer": 3.9709973655724853
    },
    {
        "question": "2024888÷2344=？",
        "answer": 2.936443399302335
    },
    {
        "question": "2297252÷8348=？",
        "answer": 2.4396261979041425
    },
    {
        "question": "24446×3289=？",
        "answer": 7.905271680907792
    },
    {
        "question": "568977÷19110=？",
        "answer": 1.4738340240237644
    },
    {
        "question": "10699645÷12481=？",
        "answer": 2.9331199854209533
    },
    {
        "question": "159×48462=？",
        "answer": 6.8867984575854235
    },
    {
        "question": "689×75398=？",
        "answer": 7.7155790478770845
    },
    {
        "question": "7×35096088=？",
        "answer": 8.390356750363347
    },
    {
        "question": "42559237÷982=？",
        "answer": 4.6368823455587815
    },
    {
        "question": "11×659=？",
        "answer": 3.860278099752235
    },
    {
        "question": "146338÷3893=？",
        "answer": 1.5750727115213794
    },
    {
        "question": "16340468÷557775=？",
        "answer": 1.4668054459284068
    },
    {
        "question": "168×6943=？",
        "answer": 6.066856446982416
    },
    {
        "question": "1909×593=？",
        "answer": 6.05386062175793
    },
    {
        "question": "16925769÷8701=？",
        "answer": 3.2889792407467557
    },
    {
        "question": "136418322÷2452757=？",
        "answer": 1.745218179398393
    },
    {
        "question": "47284÷1762=？",
        "answer": 1.4287083045849676
    },
    {
        "question": "10860185÷228=？",
        "answer": 4.677902376391861
    },
    {
        "question": "470384×669=？",
        "answer": 8.497878658663524
    },
    {
        "question": "5431449÷5203709=？",
        "answer": 0.018602703867060436
    },
    {
        "question": "3109701÷1701=？",
        "answer": 3.262014319693153
    },
    {
        "question": "2269740÷2286=？",
        "answer": 2.9968998853046194
    },
    {
        "question": "242235×2943=？",
        "answer": 8.853027155690642
    },
    {
        "question": "8×3729=？",
        "answer": 4.474682370353251
    },
    {
        "question": "38126÷2298=？",
        "answer": 1.219871219183857
    },
    {
        "question": "18144436÷1088=？",
        "answer": 4.222114577814005
    },
    {
        "question": "475605÷54902=？",
        "answer": 0.9376582462217323
    },
    {
        "question": "36472385÷23416476=？",
        "answer": 0.19244262593500663
    },
    {
        "question": "656841072÷4646559=？",
        "answer": 2.15032884520959
    },
    {
        "question": "7876×46705=？",
        "answer": 8.5656690838817
    },
    {
        "question": "26×57855=？",
        "answer": 6.177314245892541
    },
    {
        "question": "9370×99216=？",
        "answer": 8.968321304890654
    },
    {
        "question": "10×19818=？",
        "answer": 5.297059824075058
    },
    {
        "question": "11×403586=？",
        "answer": 6.647328777737464
    },
    {
        "question": "71981÷711=？",
        "answer": 2.0053482750890037
    },
    {
        "question": "63117828÷39108809=？",
        "answer": 0.20787745522260723
    },
    {
        "question": "35743376÷25085=？",
        "answer": 3.15378146432034
    },
    {
        "question": "354034÷10888=？",
        "answer": 1.5120968597269158
    },
    {
        "question": "3×68036=？",
        "answer": 5.3098600271941
    },
    {
        "question": "346÷291=？",
        "answer": 0.07518310980686932
    },
    {
        "question": "6926649÷799=？",
        "answer": 3.937976401505267
    },
    {
        "question": "21×21126101=？",
        "answer": 8.647038646474684
    },
    {
        "question": "1×13456=？",
        "answer": 4.128915978453837
    },
    {
        "question": "289571509÷331=？",
        "answer": 5.941927835528469
    },
    {
        "question": "28528344÷881=？",
        "answer": 4.510300654253256
    },
    {
        "question": "2272×22122=？",
        "answer": 7.701232715028741
    },
    {
        "question": "1070388÷78459=？",
        "answer": 1.134898463100279
    },
    {
        "question": "10489372÷298279=？",
        "answer": 1.5461268092872984
    },
    {
        "question": "16082×3839=？",
        "answer": 7.790558169897472
    },
    {
        "question": "411548114÷2635=？",
        "answer": 5.1936399962407975
    },
    {
        "question": "244108÷1453=？",
        "answer": 2.2253163982159436
    },
    {
        "question": "1606×1029=？",
        "answer": 6.218160915705095
    },
    {
        "question": "1217404×533=？",
        "answer": 8.812161933398608
    },
    {
        "question": "78×218=？",
        "answer": 4.230551096295085
    },
    {
        "question": "285781610÷52934369=？",
        "answer": 0.7322965381018626
    },
    {
        "question": "17424÷3956=？",
        "answer": 0.643891579486558
    },
    {
        "question": "1×2514219=？",
        "answer": 6.400403104037742
    },
    {
        "question": "3381×69848=？",
        "answer": 8.373199145977615
    },
    {
        "question": "1196565÷177592=？",
        "answer": 0.8285128972188035
    },
    {
        "question": "42164×663=？",
        "answer": 7.446455333064766
    },
    {
        "question": "688118490÷2551823=？",
        "answer": 2.4308126801747543
    },
    {
        "question": "945988111÷661=？",
        "answer": 6.155684218819386
    },
    {
        "question": "13000554÷82945=？",
        "answer": 2.1951716480556196
    },
    {
        "question": "2378×133971=？",
        "answer": 8.503222649371258
    },
    {
        "question": "1166×21693=？",
        "answer": 7.403018166676535
    },
    {
        "question": "7376×13778=？",
        "answer": 8.007007088461702
    },
    {
        "question": "15387568÷3128550=？",
        "answer": 0.6918268849609526
    },
    {
        "question": "19953332÷423=？",
        "answer": 4.673675061388787
    },
    {
        "question": "148155÷13330=？",
        "answer": 1.0458861634104266
    },
    {
        "question": "169206021÷1615819=？",
        "answer": 2.0200231022610957
    },
    {
        "question": "8×93935=？",
        "answer": 5.87591742669908
    },
    {
        "question": "13776836÷67283=？",
        "answer": 2.311244141128048
    },
    {
        "question": "933949139÷7268=？",
        "answer": 5.108908307430194
    },
    {
        "question": "106670÷574=？",
        "answer": 2.269130402692776
    },
    {
        "question": "300480823÷464=？",
        "answer": 5.8112987795408175
    },
    {
        "question": "1×26789=？",
        "answer": 4.427956502238756
    },
    {
        "question": "214323541÷74394837=？",
        "answer": 0.45952707939986
    },
    {
        "question": "172×23085=？",
        "answer": 6.598858325794708
    },
    {
        "question": "85×28587=？",
        "answer": 6.38558750738192
    },
    {
        "question": "8698÷317=？",
        "answer": 1.4383601411115656
    },
    {
        "question": "2045137÷5280=？",
        "answer": 2.5880884833797846
    },
    {
        "question": "398004981÷18156389=？",
        "answer": 1.340859028353262
    },
    {
        "question": "3×13004=？",
        "answer": 4.591198215543751
    },
    {
        "question": "1816150÷51832=？",
        "answer": 1.5445537481079326
    },
    {
        "question": "15751378÷8006=？",
        "answer": 3.293902968014783
    },
    {
        "question": "2×572477=？",
        "answer": 6.0587880386868465
    },
    {
        "question": "716×5662=？",
        "answer": 6.60788288733694
    },
    {
        "question": "12804÷2236=？",
        "answer": 0.757873866257709
    },
    {
        "question": "1×69809441=？",
        "answer": 7.843914160401646
    },
    {
        "question": "137922032÷1100=？",
        "answer": 5.098240961813468
    },
    {
        "question": "36×15295881=？",
        "answer": 8.740876996956871
    },
    {
        "question": "3×17422548=？",
        "answer": 7.718232924416486
    },
    {
        "question": "12×16688884=？",
        "answer": 8.301608542053014
    },
    {
        "question": "317×1306591=？",
        "answer": 8.617198924594582
    },
    {
        "question": "76797239÷61365328=？",
        "answer": 0.09742254675733938
    },
    {
        "question": "891×37470=？",
        "answer": 7.523561397130673
    },
    {
        "question": "326770856÷16715049=？",
        "answer": 1.2911356617228782
    },
    {
        "question": "112012348÷1645=？",
        "answer": 4.833099998711574
    },
    {
        "question": "46761×597=？",
        "answer": 7.445858121254717
    },
    {
        "question": "4×2073083=？",
        "answer": 6.91867668161304
    },
    {
        "question": "11854×1108=？",
        "answer": 7.11840468329541
    },
    {
        "question": "9391851÷62666=？",
        "answer": 2.1757192195902144
    },
    {
        "question": "34876967÷2656=？",
        "answer": 4.118310639726352
    },
    {
        "question": "25×7837789=？",
        "answer": 8.292133576391675
    },
    {
        "question": "955988÷239=？",
        "answer": 3.602054539898578
    },
    {
        "question": "332×4247=？",
        "answer": 6.149220344694716
    },
    {
        "question": "3579871÷869=？",
        "answer": 3.6148476007545485
    },
    {
        "question": "9×4574=？",
        "answer": 4.614538669710055
    },
    {
        "question": "145×354=？",
        "answer": 4.710371264260763
    },
    {
        "question": "13468×1691=？",
        "answer": 7.357446715313793
    },
    {
        "question": "23624345÷26024=？",
        "answer": 2.9579857259835216
    },
    {
        "question": "890060÷1204=？",
        "answer": 2.868792797015922
    },
    {
        "question": "451144367÷11225795=？",
        "answer": 1.6040984320438323
    },
    {
        "question": "25×3498=？",
        "answer": 4.941759813814695
    },
    {
        "question": "413409÷37206=？",
        "answer": 1.045766945344881
    },
    {
        "question": "980×601=？",
        "answer": 5.770100547695234
    },
    {
        "question": "24009167÷14817740=？",
        "answer": 0.2095951222863428
    },
    {
        "question": "186×224=？",
        "answer": 4.619760962552079
    },
    {
        "question": "3294583÷1744125=？",
        "answer": 0.27622284590640445
    },
    {
        "question": "7112097÷259=？",
        "answer": 4.438697907148266
    },
    {
        "question": "83314÷24985=？",
        "answer": 0.5230386321644268
    },
    {
        "question": "127155÷327=？",
        "answer": 2.5897856895527043
    },
    {
        "question": "37×22462=？",
        "answer": 5.919650146976111
    },
    {
        "question": "2286÷2155=？",
        "answer": 0.025628951562512537
    },
    {
        "question": "12832832÷937=？",
        "answer": 4.136582917883935
    },
    {
        "question": "17588×13484=？",
        "answer": 8.375035200796603
    },
    {
        "question": "93353÷3340=？",
        "answer": 1.446381812222442
    },
    {
        "question": "474234476÷4245=？",
        "answer": 5.048115428643596
    },
    {
        "question": "23×3925811=？",
        "answer": 7.955657223580899
    },
    {
        "question": "113×7847401=？",
        "answer": 8.947804288986445
    },
    {
        "question": "692537×954=？",
        "answer": 8.819991356002413
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1551=？",
        "answer": 3.190611797813605
    },
    {
        "question": "18939×7564=？",
        "answer": 8.156108564220018
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1322=？",
        "answer": 3.1212314551496214
    },
    {
        "question": "7952008÷26533=？",
        "answer": 2.4766904512821077
    },
    {
        "question": "64×11274489=？",
        "answer": 8.858276841207111
    },
    {
        "question": "42739572÷2083=？",
        "answer": 4.3121408988169225
    },
    {
        "question": "854×1404=？",
        "answer": 6.078824978482792
    },
    {
        "question": "8×2009739=？",
        "answer": 7.206229647288174
    },
    {
        "question": "450×1019335=？",
        "answer": 8.661529450227023
    },
    {
        "question": "12×542=？",
        "answer": 3.8131805325860118
    },
    {
        "question": "32×749=？",
        "answer": 4.379631796019372
    },
    {
        "question": "175×80624=？",
        "answer": 7.149502389697988
    },
    {
        "question": "126×466224=？",
        "answer": 7.768965171228944
    },
    {
        "question": "64343÷36433=？",
        "answer": 0.24700637227487868
    },
    {
        "question": "469×650882=？",
        "answer": 8.484675104103692
    },
    {
        "question": "11475653÷5791312=？",
        "answer": 0.2970004449471912
    },
    {
        "question": "189779÷767=？",
        "answer": 2.3934527899341873
    },
    {
        "question": "154316274÷970428=？",
        "answer": 2.2014484097818947
    },
    {
        "question": "934697673÷47065=？",
        "answer": 4.297973098458315
    },
    {
        "question": "93×37741=？",
        "answer": 6.545296351768333
    },
    {
        "question": "153×1137699=？",
        "answer": 8.240718807173563
    },
    {
        "question": "540698208÷1044503=？",
        "answer": 2.7140452385349976
    },
    {
        "question": "1×144084=？",
        "answer": 5.158615756681368
    },
    {
        "question": "736498÷32763=？",
        "answer": 1.35178791000574
    },
    {
        "question": "3×308389=？",
        "answer": 5.966220133422511
    },
    {
        "question": "66984822÷79014=？",
        "answer": 2.9282723595994007
    },
    {
        "question": "1×630333=？",
        "answer": 5.799570044461392
    },
    {
        "question": "978044÷422=？",
        "answer": 3.3650459421974643
    },
    {
        "question": "116895688÷19761=？",
        "answer": 3.7719895732201265
    },
    {
        "question": "40×479=？",
        "answer": 4.282395504742525
    },
    {
        "question": "3317219÷385933=？",
        "answer": 0.9342622288135315
    },
    {
        "question": "2515450÷8031=？",
        "answer": 2.4958460633004282
    },
    {
        "question": "94962÷4955=？",
        "answer": 1.282506193921966
    },
    {
        "question": "147×550914=？",
        "answer": 7.908401143689824
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1816037=？",
        "answer": 6.2591246926058455
    },
    {
        "question": "20455÷2119=？",
        "answer": 0.984668527123598
    },
    {
        "question": "513×44459=？",
        "answer": 7.358077055157962
    },
    {
        "question": "253×10044=？",
        "answer": 6.405027225216703
    },
    {
        "question": "373487÷37666=？",
        "answer": 0.99632598781455
    },
    {
        "question": "293244×2372=？",
        "answer": 8.842343819568285
    },
    {
        "question": "169×245091=？",
        "answer": 7.617214068407159
    },
    {
        "question": "219580÷3172=？",
        "answer": 1.8402596020997268
    },
    {
        "question": "218225÷5695=？",
        "answer": 1.5834107737497178
    },
    {
        "question": "63382417÷12490=？",
        "answer": 3.7054063580097814
    },
    {
        "question": "1425808÷44024=？",
        "answer": 1.5103715473434796
    },
    {
        "question": "195849÷7616=？",
        "answer": 1.4101944230165775
    },
    {
        "question": "742×1061=？",
        "answer": 5.896119289180367
    },
    {
        "question": "930223648÷2792=？",
        "answer": 5.5226719619310645
    },
    {
        "question": "245×76328=？",
        "answer": 7.271849967205406
    },
    {
        "question": "15137276÷164090=？",
        "answer": 1.964965614536201
    },
    {
        "question": "58744÷7492=？",
        "answer": 0.8943657464965585
    },
    {
        "question": "669186561÷85207=？",
        "answer": 3.8950719358469743
    },
    {
        "question": "145768×6413=？",
        "answer": 8.970723435032676
    },
    {
        "question": "326×27581=？",
        "answer": 6.9538276083402835
    },
    {
        "question": "470873788÷3059998=？",
        "answer": 2.1871833727367487
    },
    {
        "question": "114579029÷43917=？",
        "answer": 3.416472471995315
    },
    {
        "question": "62736×4979=？",
        "answer": 8.49465895123159
    },
    {
        "question": "17366285÷3441=？",
        "answer": 3.703022251378393
    },
    {
        "question": "242158938÷941645=？",
        "answer": 2.410213298628326
    },
    {
        "question": "2×44960=？",
        "answer": 4.953856298224986
    },
    {
        "question": "166615368÷82556=？",
        "answer": 3.3049664142992388
    },
    {
        "question": "19909×29111=？",
        "answer": 8.76310657086227
    },
    {
        "question": "261108482÷300310=？",
        "answer": 2.9392511859480757
    },
    {
        "question": "2503641÷1190811=？",
        "answer": 0.3227292172650119
    },
    {
        "question": "545999÷6645=？",
        "answer": 1.914696862014119
    },
    {
        "question": "69×12046=？",
        "answer": 5.919691949571817
    },
    {
        "question": "341238÷11509=？",
        "answer": 1.4720197978230019
    },
    {
        "question": "260240669÷3034=？",
        "answer": 4.933359590264197
    },
    {
        "question": "133×4668=？",
        "answer": 5.792982488340418
    },
    {
        "question": "5977×11621=？",
        "answer": 7.841726757020146
    },
    {
        "question": "5802×560=？",
        "answer": 6.511765751472845
    },
    {
        "question": "583×209=？",
        "answer": 5.085814840870068
    },
    {
        "question": "1×892=？",
        "answer": 2.950364854376123
    },
    {
        "question": "142518÷344=？",
        "answer": 2.6173112765589046
    },
    {
        "question": "684353780÷288=？",
        "answer": 6.375888182646962
    },
    {
        "question": "2546×5217=？",
        "answer": 7.123279236040012
    },
    {
        "question": "210312÷118876=？",
        "answer": 0.2477698701036782
    },
    {
        "question": "6×224176=？",
        "answer": 6.128740366111439
    },
    {
        "question": "15580317÷666487=？",
        "answer": 1.368784606854823
    },
    {
        "question": "18×39134632=？",
        "answer": 8.847833759418126
    },
    {
        "question": "1558679×520=？",
        "answer": 8.90876002785324
    },
    {
        "question": "356503÷20179=？",
        "answer": 1.2471635484916637
    },
    {
        "question": "4223×1111=？",
        "answer": 6.671335140365775
    },
    {
        "question": "1×70567584=？",
        "answer": 7.848605248886173
    },
    {
        "question": "38×3773=？",
        "answer": 5.156470401817805
    },
    {
        "question": "7×10691877=？",
        "answer": 7.874151993977494
    },
    {
        "question": "817798÷378138=？",
        "answer": 0.3349957212566813
    },
    {
        "question": "25767529÷524745=？",
        "answer": 1.691124464367664
    },
    {
        "question": "2×31721=？",
        "answer": 4.802376865596947
    },
    {
        "question": "33027×2552=？",
        "answer": 7.925749796492053
    },
    {
        "question": "3×542=？",
        "answer": 3.2111205412580492
    },
    {
        "question": "51557×5817=？",
        "answer": 8.476986702476802
    },
    {
        "question": "2138×1222=？",
        "answer": 6.417078906779294
    },
    {
        "question": "559435×280=？",
        "answer": 8.194907665046243
    },
    {
        "question": "453839397÷1596=？",
        "answer": 5.45386930651094
    },
    {
        "question": "12557×2353=？",
        "answer": 7.470507821428343
    },
    {
        "question": "4240×638=？",
        "answer": 6.432186535313895
    },
    {
        "question": "2×983541=？",
        "answer": 6.29382246434498
    },
    {
        "question": "17516949÷226750=？",
        "answer": 1.8879111698070752
    },
    {
        "question": "159094855÷8631583=？",
        "answer": 1.2655656841371026
    },
    {
        "question": "57×2972=？",
        "answer": 5.228923660761029
    },
    {
        "question": "1862÷339=？",
        "answer": 0.7397799784422416
    },
    {
        "question": "50086897÷376302=？",
        "answer": 2.1241876004185203
    },
    {
        "question": "14×30371336=？",
        "answer": 8.628591932129467
    },
    {
        "question": "2158×335174=？",
        "answer": 8.859321762672451
    },
    {
        "question": "34256×6875=？",
        "answer": 8.372009352452663
    },
    {
        "question": "6394089÷6827=？",
        "answer": 2.971548774116817
    },
    {
        "question": "248888÷22012=？",
        "answer": 1.0533444537012282
    },
    {
        "question": "1575÷620=？",
        "answer": 0.40488886862736545
    },
    {
        "question": "51265352÷251=？",
        "answer": 5.3101502222075005
    },
    {
        "question": "780654÷5502=？",
        "answer": 2.151938003283171
    },
    {
        "question": "47×270=？",
        "answer": 4.103461622094705
    },
    {
        "question": "19×100936=？",
        "answer": 6.282799691004265
    },
    {
        "question": "1220084÷20815=？",
        "answer": 1.768013316665594
    },
    {
        "question": "164544×3167=？",
        "answer": 8.716930113998659
    },
    {
        "question": "1972÷900=？",
        "answer": 0.34066440116586755
    },
    {
        "question": "1039×490765=？",
        "answer": 8.707489130037418
    },
    {
        "question": "5×79806=？",
        "answer": 5.60100554817967
    },
    {
        "question": "57724×2159=？",
        "answer": 8.09560906035058
    },
    {
        "question": "4890÷320=？",
        "answer": 1.1841588808037142
    },
    {
        "question": "13900×18306=？",
        "answer": 8.405608258280147
    },
    {
        "question": "99×73091=？",
        "answer": 6.859499098354706
    },
    {
        "question": "202083837÷1571=？",
        "answer": 5.109355394272366
    },
    {
        "question": "3×220862=？",
        "answer": 5.8212422552903105
    },
    {
        "question": "20×2109401=？",
        "answer": 7.625189143223723
    },
    {
        "question": "763789÷42659=？",
        "answer": 1.2529627287974305
    },
    {
        "question": "1450×5028=？",
        "answer": 6.862763271248895
    },
    {
        "question": "742÷381=？",
        "answer": 0.28947892960340776
    },
    {
        "question": "442654831÷146686505=？",
        "answer": 0.47967504728132326
    },
    {
        "question": "2×30624=？",
        "answer": 4.787091911760731
    },
    {
        "question": "120788÷57768=？",
        "answer": 0.32033645831957797
    },
    {
        "question": "20×2641=？",
        "answer": 4.722798396870905
    },
    {
        "question": "211939994÷108737397=？",
        "answer": 0.2898339852322757
    },
    {
        "question": "3632300÷959845=？",
        "answer": 0.5779806037942156
    },
    {
        "question": "392066×838=？",
        "answer": 8.516603200505537
    },
    {
        "question": "1214×9299=？",
        "answer": 7.052654934450944
    },
    {
        "question": "18×29051286=？",
        "answer": 8.718437866970518
    },
    {
        "question": "286376434÷1783=？",
        "answer": 5.205785933711677
    },
    {
        "question": "14×3935=？",
        "answer": 4.741072772373322
    },
    {
        "question": "410619÷504=？",
        "answer": 2.9110085045565244
    },
    {
        "question": "16×59548591=？",
        "answer": 8.978991472602942
    },
    {
        "question": "28176÷7674=？",
        "answer": 0.5648575437609041
    },
    {
        "question": "13923÷1102=？",
        "answer": 1.101551228622926
    },
    {
        "question": "1345010÷8807=？",
        "answer": 2.1838975169384627
    },
    {
        "question": "56×4485=？",
        "answer": 5.399950474386311
    },
    {
        "question": "28×120851=？",
        "answer": 6.529408279736572
    },
    {
        "question": "1002×50330=？",
        "answer": 7.7026946519283666
    },
    {
        "question": "89750241÷3935280=？",
        "answer": 1.3580599850526578
    },
    {
        "question": "1×300950952=？",
        "answer": 8.478495721469391
    },
    {
        "question": "19173106÷10787616=？",
        "answer": 0.24976699455775872
    },
    {
        "question": "11×8121979=？",
        "answer": 7.951054547411983
    },
    {
        "question": "674172052÷899630=？",
        "answer": 2.8747068153113964
    },
    {
        "question": "21×574745=？",
        "answer": 7.081694496542387
    },
    {
        "question": "700672460÷5014200=？",
        "answer": 2.145313395290864
    },
    {
        "question": "1768×380083=？",
        "answer": 8.827360705993655
    },
    {
        "question": "21×12444=？",
        "answer": 5.417179297170585
    },
    {
        "question": "468182÷664=？",
        "answer": 2.848246633172967
    },
    {
        "question": "40150537÷19799=？",
        "answer": 3.3070481025540666
    },
    {
        "question": "2×202559754=？",
        "answer": 8.607583156569827
    },
    {
        "question": "17762892÷24217=？",
        "answer": 2.865393333485832
    },
    {
        "question": "160358368÷9626182=？",
        "answer": 1.221637559172524
    },
    {
        "question": "142440÷5127=？",
        "answer": 1.4437686475618168
    },
    {
        "question": "5×174327382=？",
        "answer": 8.940335612430031
    },
    {
        "question": "3×65956022=？",
        "answer": 8.296375708915507
    },
    {
        "question": "40528984÷2495957=？",
        "answer": 1.2105286176659722
    },
    {
        "question": "87213181÷261845=？",
        "answer": 2.522537841820462
    },
    {
        "question": "616148706÷430522=？",
        "answer": 3.1556901916044287
    },
    {
        "question": "16117883÷133622=？",
        "answer": 2.0814300310858775
    },
    {
        "question": "64476÷726=？",
        "answer": 1.948461465916225
    },
    {
        "question": "70×254866=？",
        "answer": 7.251409942971718
    },
    {
        "question": "61×6358=？",
        "answer": 5.588650358589521
    },
    {
        "question": "2326973÷123577=？",
        "answer": 1.2748536962559747
    },
    {
        "question": "1×232=？",
        "answer": 2.3654879848909
    },
    {
        "question": "9301974÷14418=？",
        "answer": 2.809670100090694
    },
    {
        "question": "361209903÷221=？",
        "answer": 6.2133673748204155
    },
    {
        "question": "16479840÷30560=？",
        "answer": 2.7317996409856957
    },
    {
        "question": "380947÷140308=？",
        "answer": 0.43378212372044683
    },
    {
        "question": "21135653÷23815=？",
        "answer": 2.94816508434041
    },
    {
        "question": "2402178÷1459=？",
        "answer": 3.2165498933356345
    },
    {
        "question": "1941×5651=？",
        "answer": 7.040150842686261
    },
    {
        "question": "34506÷23305=？",
        "answer": 0.17044551071276426
    },
    {
        "question": "1069280÷127921=？",
        "answer": 0.9221495980071653
    },
    {
        "question": "394×597=？",
        "answer": 5.371470552954944
    },
    {
        "question": "12×360399=？",
        "answer": 6.635964823318345
    },
    {
        "question": "204035×2082=？",
        "answer": 8.628185397517415
    },
    {
        "question": "502×238747=？",
        "answer": 8.07864164026308
    },
    {
        "question": "14754×1868=？",
        "answer": 7.440286651016435
    },
    {
        "question": "3493÷548=？",
        "answer": 0.8044180271532776
    },
    {
        "question": "71981357÷259805=？",
        "answer": 2.4425725248556764
    },
    {
        "question": "1325×428=？",
        "answer": 5.753659647285999
    },
    {
        "question": "819577÷19560=？",
        "answer": 1.6222209117309163
    },
    {
        "question": "136×3079=？",
        "answer": 5.621948597273415
    },
    {
        "question": "736×1584=？",
        "answer": 6.066632991590973
    },
    {
        "question": "511×614265=？",
        "answer": 8.496776670639195
    },
    {
        "question": "39609947÷3413752=？",
        "answer": 1.0645722937118536
    },
    {
        "question": "3×9963577=？",
        "answer": 7.475536536162876
    },
    {
        "question": "34966918÷2431898=？",
        "answer": 1.1577119995183598
    },
    {
        "question": "135472691÷376405=？",
        "answer": 2.5561963738490965
    },
    {
        "question": "4×1224174=？",
        "answer": 6.689903142690739
    },
    {
        "question": "6457784÷14315=？",
        "answer": 2.654292162281885
    },
    {
        "question": "1×4624344=？",
        "answer": 6.665050133315778
    },
    {
        "question": "1×142525=？",
        "answer": 5.15389104967617
    },
    {
        "question": "2×22489928=？",
        "answer": 7.653018060737108
    },
    {
        "question": "9442÷1183=？",
        "answer": 0.9020792514673057
    },
    {
        "question": "3697242÷1362669=？",
        "answer": 0.4334875018380122
    },
    {
        "question": "6076302÷244444=？",
        "answer": 1.3954599689639067
    },
    {
        "question": "579910÷17360=？",
        "answer": 1.5238108769702943
    },
    {
        "question": "58×228=？",
        "answer": 4.121362840563391
    },
    {
        "question": "625296×1316=？",
        "answer": 8.915341539798547
    },
    {
        "question": "2567418÷5222=？",
        "answer": 2.691659714201587
    },
    {
        "question": "940×31488=？",
        "answer": 7.471272930350946
    },
    {
        "question": "129334762÷5045=？",
        "answer": 4.408854097662102
    },
    {
        "question": "420×101001=？",
        "answer": 7.627574964104622
    },
    {
        "question": "1955588÷1563=？",
        "answer": 3.097318385636135
    },
    {
        "question": "53×14738816=？",
        "answer": 8.892738466738503
    },
    {
        "question": "550×321=？",
        "answer": 5.2468677218991155
    },
    {
        "question": "282×39704=？",
        "answer": 7.049083370508628
    },
    {
        "question": "941944767÷53463=？",
        "answer": 4.245972112809002
    },
    {
        "question": "54176383÷1567869=？",
        "answer": 1.5385002333836855
    },
    {
        "question": "258452÷2352=？",
        "answer": 2.0409425798487018
    },
    {
        "question": "8523÷362=？",
        "answer": 1.3718839179094326
    },
    {
        "question": "3313×480=？",
        "answer": 6.201462673257547
    },
    {
        "question": "19787×3116=？",
        "answer": 7.789977402771912
    },
    {
        "question": "17095÷257=？",
        "answer": 1.8229359818013189
    },
    {
        "question": "2092189÷295=？",
        "answer": 3.8507788984185574
    },
    {
        "question": "42×54139=？",
        "answer": 6.356759520064881
    },
    {
        "question": "5171×25530=？",
        "answer": 8.12062535257632
    },
    {
        "question": "714239780÷247=？",
        "answer": 6.461147081554499
    },
    {
        "question": "3144÷283=？",
        "answer": 1.0456961018430802
    },
    {
        "question": "872×1338=？",
        "answer": 6.066972598364371
    },
    {
        "question": "5572÷234=？",
        "answer": 1.376795250341783
    },
    {
        "question": "2989857÷1689228=？",
        "answer": 0.2479621457096023
    },
    {
        "question": "14895137÷401=？",
        "answer": 4.569900129430403
    },
    {
        "question": "83×93704=？",
        "answer": 6.890836222653917
    },
    {
        "question": "30930×234=？",
        "answer": 6.859595777413322
    },
    {
        "question": "3915×200286=？",
        "answer": 8.89438235954554
    },
    {
        "question": "242767÷40463=？",
        "answer": 0.7781315725399762
    },
    {
        "question": "43193462÷959992=？",
        "answer": 1.6531504006840978
    },
    {
        "question": "3×25909=？",
        "answer": 4.890571905726987
    },
    {
        "question": "2×117415787=？",
        "answer": 8.370756489049542
    },
    {
        "question": "955407347÷12252=？",
        "answer": 4.891981588512706
    },
    {
        "question": "984979851÷15635967=？",
        "answer": 1.7993026013747986
    },
    {
        "question": "141184630÷49264=？",
        "answer": 3.4572577484603815
    },
    {
        "question": "27055730÷14838=？",
        "answer": 3.260883889531227
    },
    {
        "question": "1563×162967=？",
        "answer": 8.406058648871884
    },
    {
        "question": "75260455÷580=？",
        "answer": 5.113138846030687
    },
    {
        "question": "381122052÷276920=？",
        "answer": 3.1387097551553653
    },
    {
        "question": "6047141÷634=？",
        "answer": 3.979460837201476
    },
    {
        "question": "3102×248137=？",
        "answer": 8.886333320739496
    },
    {
        "question": "27322147÷13876=？",
        "answer": 3.2942505324491385
    },
    {
        "question": "2094×11249=？",
        "answer": 7.372090594120425
    },
    {
        "question": "8×12404015=？",
        "answer": 7.996652269743728
    },
    {
        "question": "1×252800078=？",
        "answer": 8.402777203609416
    },
    {
        "question": "694×168157=？",
        "answer": 8.067074421190236
    },
    {
        "question": "505×225=？",
        "answer": 5.055473896230024
    },
    {
        "question": "488062089÷202004=？",
        "answer": 3.383115105198942
    },
    {
        "question": "992×22665=？",
        "answer": 7.351867395548886
    },
    {
        "question": "15965÷207=？",
        "answer": 1.887198577418546
    },
    {
        "question": "21×347797=？",
        "answer": 6.863545126313595
    },
    {
        "question": "7268×893=？",
        "answer": 6.812266377524543
    },
    {
        "question": "9×5176280=？",
        "answer": 7.668260269983655
    },
    {
        "question": "8×2883=？",
        "answer": 4.362934629380152
    },
    {
        "question": "51761726÷2990=？",
        "answer": 4.238337561171184
    },
    {
        "question": "306÷304=？",
        "answer": 0.0028478428728262407
    },
    {
        "question": "1031463÷10616=？",
        "answer": 1.9874927439903252
    },
    {
        "question": "13465×2163=？",
        "answer": 7.464262877186621
    },
    {
        "question": "10×105327=？",
        "answer": 6.022539714470779
    },
    {
        "question": "111758399÷4660330=？",
        "answer": 1.3798635012848999
    },
    {
        "question": "33487322÷494019=？",
        "answer": 1.8311367659178546
    },
    {
        "question": "1×26047=？",
        "answer": 4.415757710035791
    },
    {
        "question": "142428373÷114197615=？",
        "answer": 0.09593947941713253
    },
    {
        "question": "5275×19180=？",
        "answer": 8.005071066804375
    },
    {
        "question": "628×119261=？",
        "answer": 7.874458090308724
    },
    {
        "question": "38021760÷147337=？",
        "answer": 2.4117203934461444
    },
    {
        "question": "6×322=？",
        "answer": 3.2860071220794747
    },
    {
        "question": "241718÷41156=？",
        "answer": 0.7688758336428904
    },
    {
        "question": "18×33795370=？",
        "answer": 8.784129710671357
    },
    {
        "question": "2867500÷1400253=？",
        "answer": 0.31129691476864546
    },
    {
        "question": "5×10081=？",
        "answer": 4.702473619078555
    },
    {
        "question": "1015×948=？",
        "answer": 5.983274379587298
    },
    {
        "question": "21×25402776=？",
        "answer": 8.727100473385576
    },
    {
        "question": "3×153789946=？",
        "answer": 8.66404919916138
    },
    {
        "question": "10974544÷3119=？",
        "answer": 3.5463711092915933
    },
    {
        "question": "52548320÷2222812=？",
        "answer": 1.3736561032543233
    },
    {
        "question": "1128×28893=？",
        "answer": 7.513101737227182
    },
    {
        "question": "1092262÷519=？",
        "answer": 3.3231594668814246
    },
    {
        "question": "3795÷962=？",
        "answer": 0.5960367081936863
    },
    {
        "question": "948943÷437056=？",
        "answer": 0.33670303981464805
    },
    {
        "question": "8×203=？",
        "answer": 3.2105860249051563
    },
    {
        "question": "37233590÷2018768=？",
        "answer": 1.2658485001742834
    },
    {
        "question": "70333÷17733=？",
        "answer": 0.5983769282369162
    },
    {
        "question": "10481×313=？",
        "answer": 6.515947058530327
    },
    {
        "question": "313267868÷3573485=？",
        "answer": 1.9428238879680904
    },
    {
        "question": "12036259÷1774=？",
        "answer": 3.8315379089578947
    },
    {
        "question": "4276×1492=？",
        "answer": 6.804806519673391
    },
    {
        "question": "1872×180388=？",
        "answer": 8.528513487878945
    },
    {
        "question": "431891÷268876=？",
        "answer": 0.2058221154359019
    },
    {
        "question": "39×10584=？",
        "answer": 5.615714438205944
    },
    {
        "question": "224513068÷32034412=？",
        "answer": 0.8456248677925129
    },
    {
        "question": "2×3723047=？",
        "answer": 6.871928514480227
    },
    {
        "question": "164881515÷3080=？",
        "answer": 4.7286212527675415
    },
    {
        "question": "58294×1291=？",
        "answer": 7.876550098895279
    },
    {
        "question": "575132÷166381=？",
        "answer": 0.5386638019446371
    },
    {
        "question": "37128÷5630=？",
        "answer": 0.8191931605596273
    },
    {
        "question": "135917÷14573=？",
        "answer": 0.9697248151894293
    },
    {
        "question": "177591÷6006=？",
        "answer": 1.4708356248556491
    },
    {
        "question": "591×385=？",
        "answer": 5.357048210389756
    },
    {
        "question": "227823285÷37261054=？",
        "answer": 0.7863429741093692
    },
    {
        "question": "26×991611=？",
        "answer": 7.4113146837479285
    },
    {
        "question": "372336219÷54156=？",
        "answer": 3.8372887046945685
    },
    {
        "question": "636×2795=？",
        "answer": 6.249838927870856
    },
    {
        "question": "267707÷31558=？",
        "answer": 0.9285502554282264
    },
    {
        "question": "308599905÷147618=？",
        "answer": 3.32025647103354
    },
    {
        "question": "6×6254456=？",
        "answer": 7.574340791995432
    },
    {
        "question": "6×243=？",
        "answer": 3.163757523981956
    },
    {
        "question": "18228507÷2764535=？",
        "answer": 0.8191290067290768
    },
    {
        "question": "580×301543=？",
        "answer": 8.242777244802477
    },
    {
        "question": "3244÷1383=？",
        "answer": 0.3702586654298078
    },
    {
        "question": "946755÷533502=？",
        "answer": 0.2491015555408244
    },
    {
        "question": "139×3975=？",
        "answer": 5.742351933246584
    },
    {
        "question": "152483÷641=？",
        "answer": 2.376363398309989
    },
    {
        "question": "6×35125040=？",
        "answer": 8.323768077866728
    },
    {
        "question": "1×594=？",
        "answer": 2.7737864449811935
    },
    {
        "question": "502174÷2157=？",
        "answer": 2.367004078310526
    },
    {
        "question": "7002294÷445561=？",
        "answer": 1.1963331712156533
    },
    {
        "question": "514×16846=？",
        "answer": 6.937459915350795
    },
    {
        "question": "2687376÷22775=？",
        "answer": 2.071870048670939
    },
    {
        "question": "554861141÷43174770=？",
        "answer": 1.1089542779345474
    },
    {
        "question": "129603140÷1855=？",
        "answer": 4.8442716097143235
    },
    {
        "question": "124×143336=？",
        "answer": 7.249776965844336
    },
    {
        "question": "2×179188=？",
        "answer": 5.554338917796539
    },
    {
        "question": "13707×323=？",
        "answer": 6.64614493510647
    },
    {
        "question": "61868868÷14018=？",
        "answer": 3.644786114262066
    },
    {
        "question": "94464×232=？",
        "answer": 7.340754316361809
    },
    {
        "question": "68623653÷66613129=？",
        "answer": 0.012913998732007399
    },
    {
        "question": "3×13238511=？",
        "answer": 7.598960395348348
    },
    {
        "question": "684282÷346488=？",
        "answer": 0.2955469178685007
    },
    {
        "question": "312836920÷81292568=？",
        "answer": 0.5852671584802298
    },
    {
        "question": "175×1306=？",
        "answer": 5.3589812256253495
    },
    {
        "question": "75646853÷1164989=？",
        "answer": 1.8124690408545194
    },
    {
        "question": "144519319÷284879=？",
        "answer": 2.705265470248827
    },
    {
        "question": "270617×2110=？",
        "answer": 8.756637530538933
    },
    {
        "question": "1498×1753=？",
        "answer": 6.419293729457243
    },
    {
        "question": "47244093÷2035=？",
        "answer": 4.365783102186172
    },
    {
        "question": "27×31259=？",
        "answer": 5.926338844642266
    },
    {
        "question": "18407188÷135084=？",
        "answer": 2.1343835358263297
    },
    {
        "question": "28×51765=？",
        "answer": 6.1611942496893874
    },
    {
        "question": "242567431÷39070907=？",
        "answer": 0.7929789955294265
    },
    {
        "question": "27754×5076=？",
        "answer": 8.148847197376412
    },
    {
        "question": "804118127÷2971265=？",
        "answer": 2.4323784651856406
    },
    {
        "question": "664311×832=？",
        "answer": 8.742494770061114
    },
    {
        "question": "63861÷48356=？",
        "answer": 0.12078534596837343
    },
    {
        "question": "127966÷1077=？",
        "answer": 2.0748788915542375
    },
    {
        "question": "65×105258=？",
        "answer": 6.835168470403007
    },
    {
        "question": "16562÷1981=？",
        "answer": 0.9222283047676214
    },
    {
        "question": "93×9595346=？",
        "answer": 8.95054358819671
    },
    {
        "question": "635÷262=？",
        "answer": 0.38447243397223024
    },
    {
        "question": "17×11689110=？",
        "answer": 8.29823036694531
    },
    {
        "question": "2179×3276=？",
        "answer": 6.853601123334636
    },
    {
        "question": "3×18642=？",
        "answer": 4.7476137583582805
    },
    {
        "question": "31×98567=？",
        "answer": 6.485093232337879
    },
    {
        "question": "1×523183874=？",
        "answer": 8.718654349343835
    },
    {
        "question": "11×18742=？",
        "answer": 5.31420861870132
    },
    {
        "question": "95×677=？",
        "answer": 4.808312273973992
    },
    {
        "question": "9598×200=？",
        "answer": 6.283210741260384
    },
    {
        "question": "72976902÷249363=？",
        "answer": 2.466353408695608
    },
    {
        "question": "30×35807=？",
        "answer": 6.031089190978044
    },
    {
        "question": "2452×6581=？",
        "answer": 7.207812356646373
    },
    {
        "question": "6×74843625=？",
        "answer": 8.652306064478463
    },
    {
        "question": "703531÷219=？",
        "answer": 3.5068391238635797
    },
    {
        "question": "25346426÷6652672=？",
        "answer": 0.5809206180901149
    },
    {
        "question": "100×258=？",
        "answer": 4.41161970596323
    },
    {
        "question": "28×29612038=？",
        "answer": 8.918626329366301
    },
    {
        "question": "4×521=？",
        "answer": 3.3188977146274867
    },
    {
        "question": "44777÷506=？",
        "answer": 1.946904476219861
    },
    {
        "question": "35913896÷3476235=？",
        "answer": 1.0141533927896322
    },
    {
        "question": "4910104÷10141=？",
        "answer": 2.6850099082149765
    },
    {
        "question": "57×1488=？",
        "answer": 4.928477786882351
    },
    {
        "question": "170×5034724=？",
        "answer": 8.93242458920487
    },
    {
        "question": "3×268056=？",
        "answer": 5.905346787369323
    },
    {
        "question": "809×3545=？",
        "answer": 6.457564761131358
    },
    {
        "question": "4010×1110=？",
        "answer": 6.64846735140684
    },
    {
        "question": "2232×151426=？",
        "answer": 8.52889464064148
    },
    {
        "question": "217×270216=？",
        "answer": 7.76817079469288
    },
    {
        "question": "1×30636544=？",
        "answer": 7.4862397725015875
    },
    {
        "question": "126275×3715=？",
        "answer": 8.671276195280981
    },
    {
        "question": "306901536÷28503358=？",
        "answer": 1.0321030344704212
    },
    {
        "question": "45944×17449=？",
        "answer": 8.903999345919235
    },
    {
        "question": "3637÷521=？",
        "answer": 0.8439055777551875
    },
    {
        "question": "511555875÷853658=？",
        "answer": 2.77760916207122
    },
    {
        "question": "208×2929=？",
        "answer": 5.78478270664436
    },
    {
        "question": "52×2901985=？",
        "answer": 8.178698506928086
    },
    {
        "question": "28455×23616=？",
        "answer": 8.827364930087292
    },
    {
        "question": "229543604÷34044604=？",
        "answer": 0.8288169091773246
    },
    {
        "question": "1608371÷54809=？",
        "answer": 1.4675343555187528
    },
    {
        "question": "3986892÷6299=？",
        "answer": 2.801362862968573
    },
    {
        "question": "29×40695=？",
        "answer": 6.071939050716233
    },
    {
        "question": "1×1730=？",
        "answer": 3.2380461031287955
    },
    {
        "question": "140167093÷3829=？",
        "answer": 4.563560700022104
    },
    {
        "question": "5×19279134=？",
        "answer": 7.984057526254065
    },
    {
        "question": "1722×15516=？",
        "answer": 7.426812918045655
    },
    {
        "question": "37×28928=？",
        "answer": 6.029520132862264
    },
    {
        "question": "18×1021=？",
        "answer": 4.264298247190216
    },
    {
        "question": "17982872÷11216414=？",
        "answer": 0.20500502222242867
    },
    {
        "question": "460267÷1122=？",
        "answer": 2.6130169812550292
    },
    {
        "question": "234646671÷228=？",
        "answer": 6.012479550130689
    },
    {
        "question": "1×3029=？",
        "answer": 3.481299273332856
    },
    {
        "question": "125787×1598=？",
        "answer": 8.303212534370203
    },
    {
        "question": "897266904÷6280=？",
        "answer": 5.154962005207082
    },
    {
        "question": "1×10352623=？",
        "answer": 7.015050399078201
    },
    {
        "question": "3796×1370=？",
        "answer": 6.716046770911662
    },
    {
        "question": "747521640÷29491630=？",
        "answer": 1.4039249929311337
    },
    {
        "question": "15201424÷7139926=？",
        "answer": 0.32819056191314144
    },
    {
        "question": "38197015÷3983165=？",
        "answer": 0.9818011280774386
    },
    {
        "question": "1933×162132=？",
        "answer": 8.49610059405821
    },
    {
        "question": "101899×9674=？",
        "answer": 8.993776005070513
    },
    {
        "question": "1714×5141=？",
        "answer": 6.945058421454213
    },
    {
        "question": "112536731÷1632582=？",
        "answer": 1.8384192916028679
    },
    {
        "question": "1×74239=？",
        "answer": 4.870632113299614
    },
    {
        "question": "24×2726623=？",
        "answer": 7.8158363355247955
    },
    {
        "question": "356288551÷12711962=？",
        "answer": 1.4475892809672042
    },
    {
        "question": "1079246÷658186=？",
        "answer": 0.21477180734971524
    },
    {
        "question": "8224848÷2257=？",
        "answer": 3.56159632160246
    }
]